Hello racers,
and welcome to the starting line
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
[dramatic music]
Just plug it in and blow.
[imitates blow dryer]
♪ ♪
I'm a man in a dress.
Halleloo, ladies.
Drag is not a contact sport.
-We're Heathers.
-Who the fuck is Heather?
Get those nuts
away from my face.
Go back to Party City
where you belong.
Tootsie Lou.
Hi!
Hi, kids!
[clicks tongue]
C'mon season six,
let's get sickening!
-Party.
-Absolutely.
Not today, Satan.
Do you have a smoke?
Can't tease me.
I love my babies.
I'm first!
[RuPaul] Bring back my girls.
[upbeat dance music]
I am Naomi Smalls
and I am 21 years old.
Check your lipstick
before you come for me.
Naomi is a tall glass of water.
She has legs all the way up
to her asshole.
I got my drag name
from Naomi Campbell
and Biggie Smalls.
First one,
I don't blame them.
I'm obsessed
with '90s supermodels.
I'm gonna set myself
right in the center.
Yeah, spotlight on me.
[laughs]
Naomi is a fashion girl.
She's fucking fierce.
[upbeat percussive music]
How you doing mis amores?
Do you want to see my cuckoo?
[laughs]
My name
is Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
How are you?
I'm from Puerto Rico, but
I live in Austin, Texas, y'all.
I call myself between
pageant queen and performer
'cause I do comedy,
I do campy sometimes.
Sometimes?
You know.
[laughs]
I'm sexy as a goddess is
and funny as a clown.
Are you ready for me?
Oh, my God,
the room is huge.
Fantastic,
so my cuckoo have a space.
I need a space
for this junk in the trunk.
[thunder rumbling]
What's up, nerds.
Ah!
My name is
Dax ExclamationPoint
and I am the queen
of all nerds.
It's Storm.
I'm a cosplayer and my look
is very inspired by,
like, science fiction
and comics.
Superheroes.
Just strong, bad bitches
who don't take any crap
from anybody else.
You know what?
I'm gonna sit
'cause my cats are growling.
So I'm just gonna sit
right here.
Okay.
Can I get some brunch?
[laughs]
Hola.
The beauty is here.
My name is Naysha Lopez.
I think the most important
element of my drag
has to be appearance.
It sounds so shallow,
but my drag is flawless.
It's gorgeous, it's stunning,
it's gorgeous, it's everything.
Did I say it was stunning
and gorgeous?
Did I say that already?
Okay.
[both scream]
Naysha is here!
Yes, my sister!
How are you, Mama?
Welcome to season eight,
Mommy.
We made it!
Continental sisters.
She Puerto Rico also,
or from Austin?
I'm originally
from Puerto Rico,
but, um, I live in Chicago.
[whistling]
That's a little frog
in Puerto Rico.
They are so annoying.
I love me some Cynthia.
[whistles]
You don't even understand
what she's saying,
but you don't really care.
[whistles]
[dramatic music]
-Oh!
No need to adjust
your TV sets.
This acid trip is all real.
[cheers]
Watch out bitches.
Here's Acid Betty
from Brooklyn, New York.
My drag style is completely
over-the-top.
Basically, a drug trip
without the drugs.
I kind of want to run around.
[laughs]
The main bullet point
of Acid Betty is she's a bitch.
That's it.
Even Bianca
won't fuck with her.
That's the T.
Wait, I want to put my stink
all over this place.
I'm excited to be here.
Come on, like,
before we all hate each other.
[laughter]
[percussive music]
Good morning.
I didn't realize
this was happening today.
My name is Robbie Turner
and I'm the kindest queen
you'll ever meet.
I'm trying to give
old classic Hollywood.
Rita Hayworth hair,
Jean Harlow robe.
Gorgeous.
How long you been
doing drag for?
Going on 14.
14 years of drag?
I know, can you imagine?
I'm only 12.
You don't look old.
I know I don't.
[futuristic music]
-Yes!
-Oh!
-Yay!
-Oh, Kim Chi!
I came to chop
through the competition.
My name is Kim Chi and
I came here to destroy everyone.
With my makeup.
I'm known for crazy,
over-the-top,
pure anime fantasy.
-Oh, my God.
-[cheering]
Hi, I'm Naomi.
This is beautiful.
Seeing Kim Chi on Instagram
for so long,
double-tapping everything,
I'm fucking star-struck.
I want to go subtle
with everything, so.
I may come across as shy
because I'm soft-spoken,
but "donut" come for me
because I'll destroy you.
Get it, donut?
[laughing]
[upbeat music]
Whoo!
Thorgy with a TH and orgy
and I feel incredible.
My name is Thorgy
and I'm 29 years old.
I'm not 29 years old.
Where did that come from?
I'm colorful, I'm fun,
and I'm a fashion clown.
Whoo!
O-M-baby Jesus.
My drag style
is kind of incredibly eclectic.
I can be campy,
but also I can be,
like, fucking fierce.
[cheers and applause]
-Hi, guys!
-Fuck you, Thorgy.
I know Acid Betty very well.
Lord, it's gonna
be the shit show.
She's gonna be a lot.
She's gonna be extra.
Oh, really?
She's gonna be a diva.
[upbeat dance music]
-Ooh!
-Girl.
NY in the house.
My name is Bob the Drag Queen
and I am 29 years old.
My drag is funny
It's irreverent.
What you see is what you get.
My bodysuit says it all.
You're welcome.
[screaming and cheers]
Yes!
-Take it!
-Yeah!
-[screams]
I'm hilarious, beautiful,
talented, and humble.
How are you?
Now just one more.
[screaming]
The New York girls,
they get really excited.
And they just talk
over one another.
0Thorgy, you are--
0Whoo!
-Take it.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Too real.
New York, New York,
New York, yeah, girl.
Oh.
Maybe some of
the other queens are, like,
resentful that there's so much
New York City representation.
There's a reason New York City
has some of the best
drag queens in the world
and that is a fact.
This is a gag.
The children don't even know.
[laughter]
All right, ladies.
Let's turn up the juice
and see what shakes loose.
Uh-oh, this is trouble.
Don't say "Beetlejuice"
three times.
I'm Layla McQueen
and I'm 22 years old.
Layla is like a whorey,
quasi-rock star.
I don't want to say gothy,
but like, gothy.
-Hi.
[cheers and applause]
You had the smart idea.
[laughter]
I'm gonna tell you
a story about flats.
No.
14 hours from now,
we're all like, "Ugh, ow!"
She's like Sketchers,
it's the S.
[laughter]
[purposeful piano music]
Laissez les bon temps roulez.
What'd she say?
My name is Chi Chi DeVayne
and I don't get ready,
I stay ready.
-Oh!
-Hey!
My drag is that
real Southern
dragged out style of drag.
Creole fish.
It's like a whole 'nother level
of drag right here.
If you made it to
"RuPaul's Drag Race,"
you made it, honey.
Tell us about yourself.
Well, I'm a cheap queen.
She's on a budget.
Um, I don't mean cheap.
Resourceful.
Yeah, resourceful.
Chi Chi walked in
in a trash bag.
Chi Chi will take herself
out in a trash bag.
[upbeat music]
It's Derrick, bitch.
[cheers and applause]
Yeah!
My name is Derrick Berry.
I'm 32 years old.
I may look angelic,
but I am not that innocent.
I'm a Britney Spears
impersonator.
I impersonate her
six nights a week
on the Las Vegas Strip.
I would love to believe
that I'm the best
Britney in the world.
That's what people say.
Derrick,
I'm so fucking excited.
-Hey!
-How are you?
Derrick Berry
is huge competition.
She is a quasi-celebrity.
-Hey, Derrick, I'm Bob.
-Bob?
There's two boy names here
this season, girl.
Alright, Bob and Derrick.
So, where you from?
Vegas girl.
Yeah, so place your bets on me
if you like to gamble.
Is Beyoncé
scared of Britney?
Then Bob ain't scared
of Derrick.
Okay, I want to know
who else did this.
Who else has been
carb-free for two weeks?
[chuckles]
[siren blaring]
-Shut up!
-Ooh, girl!
This is it!
She done already
done had herses.
Let's go!
Welcome, ladies.
[cheers and applause]
Now whether you're
walking children in nature
or feeling the shade of it all,
the time has come for you
to echa, echa, echa pa' lante,
'cause, bitch,
you may be from Chicago
or Cameroon,
but this is not
RuPaul's Best Friend Race.
I have one thing to say.
May I call you Jiggly?
[laughter]
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and applause]
Beautiful.
Welcome, ladies.
-Whoo!
-Thank you.
Now, are you ready
to make "herstory"?
[all] Yes!
Well, guess what?
You already have.
This is the 100th episode
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
[cheers and applause]
Isn't that crazy?
And Derrick Berry,
you are the 100th queen
to prance into this workroom.
-Wow!
-Yes!
-Nice!
-Congratulations.
Oh, my God,
RuPaul just said my name.
Like, freaked out.
I feel like it's a new chapter.
Now there's 1 to 99
and I open a new door with 100.
It's crazy.
Now an occasion
such as this
demands to be acknowledged
on an epic scale.
So I've arranged a photo shoot
with some extra special
guest stars.
I hope you're ready
for your close-up
because if you get upstaged,
this 100th episode
could be your last.
[dramatic music]
The stakes are high.
Nobody wants to be the first
drag queen voted off the island.
Oh, snuff out your candle.
No!
Now, let's go.
The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
receives
a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra-special guest judge
Nicole Richie.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman,
best woman win ♪
[upbeat dance music]
[laughs]
Naysha Lopez,
welcome, darling.
In honor of our
100th episode,
I've gathered the champions
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
BeBe Zahara Benet.
Tyra Sanchez.
Raja.
Sharon Needles.
Boo.
Chad Michaels.
Jinkx Monsoon.
Violet Chachki.
And Bianca Del Rio...
could not be here
so we just hired a circus clown.
[party horn squeaks]
Oh, my God.
Not really a god,
but close enough.
[laughs]
Now, for your first
photo challenge,
we are going to take
some photographs
with the great Mathu Andersen.
We're gonna find out
if you have what it takes
-to stand amongst greatness.
-Got it.
Going to the challenge,
we're looking for
that spark of individuality
and we want to see
who knows how to get
their cream
to rise to the top.
Face is on lock and go.
Body.
Face.
Naysha Lopez was adorable,
incredible energy
and she seemed quite comfortable
quite quickly.
Why, she's covered
in black cock.
[laughter]
Queens of a feather,
stick together.
Acid Betty, we will see
if you have what it takes
to sit among
the goddesses, all right?
Yes, RuPaul,
very intimidating.
Sitting next to these
wannabe ass drag queens.
[dramatic music]
[camera shutter clicking]
Lovely.
Beautiful.
Acid Betty,
your pussy's on fire.
Chemical fire.
Is that--
Oh, that's your face.
Yes, yes.
I'm surprised
she didn't smack you.
Acid Betty, that one...
you got to watch that one.
Well, you passed
the acid test, Betty.
Naomi Smalls.
-Hi, girl.
-Hey, girl.
-Go big, Naomi Smalls.
-Okay.
[upbeat music]
Oh, all of that right there.
Yeah.
I think Naomi's done this
once or twice.
I have studied thousands
fashion magazines.
Just let me pose and I'm happy.
She has come to model.
Naomi Smalls
looks really hot.
She has a great ass,
great legs,
but she does have cliff hangers.
You see her toes, like,
literally
clinging onto the shoe.
Boner killer.
Show me the winner.
Robbie Turner.
What?
I am very excited
to see Jinkx.
She's my Seattle homegirl.
She's our hometown hero.
-You fucking bitch.
-[laughs] Hi.
Yes, mother.
In walks my sister,
Robbie Turner,
wearing the same wig.
Even though we're sisters,
it's like, who's Beyoncé here?
[clicks tongue]
Let's do this,
one, two, three.
[stammering]
This sleeve happens to be
in my light, darling.
Well, you should move.
[laughter]
Know your place, bitch.
Season eight winner.
Season four winner.
Difference.
Movie star glamour.
Gorgeous.
Welcome to my home.
Thank you, darling.
Sharon, did she try
to come for you?
Oh yeah,
she came for me.
-Hi.
-Come through, Kim Chi.
-Hi girl.
-Oh, my God.
[camera shutter clicking]
Well, you're blocking
Sharon a bit.
Oh, sorry.
-Is she blocking Raja now?
-She's blocking Raja now.
Sorry.
There you go.
What a considerate queen.
♪ ♪
Loving Kim Chi.
She's like JuJubee on steroids.
She was kind of giving me anime
and I was loving it.
Yes, give me anime-azing.
Next up, Thorgy Thor,
here we go.
Ah.
It's time for a queen orgy,
Thorgy.
-How 'bout this?
-Oh!
Best smile all day.
[all laugh]
Thorgy's like this fireball
that just came in.
I love her energy
and I think
gonna be
really, really fun.
-Give me something bigger.
-Bigger?
Give me something bigger,
bigger.
No, you just put
your arms up in the air.
-Bigger.
Oh, okay, yeah.
Grow in size.
Whoo!
[laughter]
Looking good,
feeling Thorgeous.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
-My goodness.
-Garbage.
You have no idea
how many of those dresses
Alaska left at my house.
Really?
Ready to run
with the big dogs?
-I'm ready.
-Get it, trash.
Prove to us
that you're a champion.
I'm gonna
tell you something.
When your skirt covers up
your whole legs
and just leaves two
little feet at the bottom,
it makes me want to laugh,
'cause it looks like you're this
tall with little feet.
[laughter]
Okay, that was my hot tip.
Carry on.
Oh, there she is.
There she is.
Nice.
Pose the house down.
Dax ExclamationPoint.
Get it.
Show me
your exclamation point.
Yay.
Oh.
You've got two left,
so make it happen.
Take it to the Dax.
Next up is Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
Or as I like to call her,
Santially.
Yes!
I'm ready to show my cuckoo
on everything else.
Go.
Model, model for me.
Escandelo.
Prove that you're
a winner, baby.
Gorgeous.
You own everything.
Next,
Bob the Drag Queen.
Little Kim up in the house.
She's trying to keep it
fresh and clean.
Yes.
Slappin' with Raja.
Hey.
[laughter]
Yeah, you got two more left.
I'll just looked shocked.
[laughter]
How about we do like that black
and white photo where no one--
Nice.
Just keeping it editorial,
real and art.
Yes.
Thank you.
I saw the tights
and they were ripped.
Next up, Layla McQueen.
Ready, boom.
Oh, okay.
You remind me of a dog trying
to get comfortable on the couch.
Everyone is so gorgeous
and here I am looking
like a Beetlejuice trash bag
and oh, my God.
It's intimidating for sure.
I can go anywhere?
Yeah, sure, yeah.
Anywhere you want, girl.
Ready, here we go.
Oh, a nice.
She's a shy girl.
Layla McQueen,
I could have used a little more
enthusiasm from her.
She's like the Hamburglar
scurrying around behind people.
[laughter]
Earn those stripes, girl.
From Las Vegas, Nevada,
Derrick Berry.
It's Britney, witch.
[laughs]
That's it,
make them your backup dancers.
Yes, you're gonna work
this whole set, aren't you?
You know it.
Atta girl.
[camera clicking]
-Can I take this?
-Sure, why not.
Yeah.
Yeah, you seem stronger
than yesterday.
Derrick completely used
every last bit of that set
and that's
exactly what you do.
This is the last shot.
Hit me baby, one more time.
Oh, she's toxic.
Yeah!
Whoo.
That was amazing.
Did you guys have fun?
-Whoo!
-Oh, come on, boy Bob.
The de-dragging process
is the most exciting for me
because I want to see what
everybody looks like as a boy
and fuck,
everybody's so cute.
Look at this butch
motherfucker right here.
This is my everyday look, hon.
Layla out of drag,
I want to sleep with.
I like little shorties.
Like, little husky shorties.
Whoo.
Oh, my God, that fucking
Layla's ass is amazing.
I can't help it.
I'm such a top.
[upbeat music]
Betty, I still can't get over
the gag of seeing you here.
I know, I mean, it is because
some people think I'm dead.
Is that based on
how you look or--
It's how I treat people,
so watch yourself.
-Oh.
A lot of the queens are
turning into hens in a henhouse.
They're like,
"Oh, cluck, cluck."
The competition has begun.
[upbeat music]
Ladies,
over the past 99 episodes,
I'm sure you've yelled
at your TV,
"Girl, I coulda slayed
that challenge."
Now it's your chance
to prove it.
For this week's maxi challenge,
each of you will be assigned
a legendary design challenge
from a past season.
It's your job
to take the materials
and make them your own.
To assign the looks,
I'll choose one of your names
at random.
In honor
of the drag classic,
"Priscilla,
Queen of the Desert,"
I've asked Morgan McMichaels
to assume the position.
[cheers and applause]
[laughter]
All right, Morgan,
let 'er rip.
[dramatic percussive music]
[cheers and applause]
All right, the winner is...
Robbie Turner.
[cheers and applause]
Now Robbie, you get to assign
all the queens' looks
and choose your own.
And now, it's time
to bring back my girls.
From season one,
Shannel,
presenting the Drag on a Dime
thrift store challenge.
-Ow!
-Yeah!
-Latrice Royale...
-Yes!
Presenting our Pride Float
challenge from season four.
Next, Violet Chachki,
presenting the Money Ball
from season three.
Ooh.
It's time to assign
these three looks.
All right, Robbie Turner,
who gets Drag on a Dime?
Um, Naysha.
Who gets Float Your Boat?
Naomi.
Who gets Money Ball?
-Acid Betty.
-Wow!
Yes, this is the competition
I came here for.
To show people that I can make
something out of nothing.
That is what I do.
-Next up, Jinkx Monsoon...
-Yes!
Presenting the Sugar Ball
challenge from season 5.
Isn't she sweet?
-Tyra Sanchez...
-Gorgeous.
Presenting the Glitter Ball
challenge from season six.
-Chad Michaels...
-[all] Ooh.
Presenting the Post
Apocalyptic Couture challenge
from season four.
[laughter]
All right, Robbie,
who gets Sugar Ball?
Cynthia.
Cuckoo sugar
for everybody here.
-Azúcar.
-Okay.
Who gets Glitter Ball?
-Chi Chi.
-That's a good one.
Who get Apocalyptic Couture?
Layla.
-Layla.
-Oh, wow.
Next up, it's Raja...
[all ooh]
Serving the Cake Couture
challenge from season three.
Mmm.
Next up is
BeBe Zahara Benet
presenting the Hair challenge
from season three.
Cameroon.
Well, Hello, Kitty.
Presenting the Hello Kitty
Couture challenge
from season seven.
-Hey, kitty girl.
-Aww.
All right, Robbie,
who gets Cake Couture?
-Thorgee.
-Yes, it's Thorgy.
-Thorgy, fuck my life.
-[laughs]
Who gets Hair Ball?
Kim Chi.
And who gets Hello Kitty?
-Dax.
-[gasps]
-Meow.
-Oh, my God.
-Next up, we've got Raven...
-Raven!
Presenting the Gone With
the Window challenge
from season two.
Next up, the Pit Crew...
Ohh.
Serving the Queen Who Mopped
Christmas challenge
from season three.
Christmas came early,
girls.
Clearly, holy shit.
Next, the bitch is back,
and she brought Sharon Needles,
presenting the Bitch Ball
challenge from season four.
Sit, Sharon.
[growls and barks]
[laughter]
Okay, Robbie,
who gets Gone With the Window?
-Bob the Drag Queen.
-Yes.
Who's gonna get a big
Christmas package?
-Derrick Berry.
-Yes.
And Robbie, does this mean
you're going to be doing it
doggie style?
Damn it.
Can you believe I forget
to pick a theme for myself?
Guess who gets stuck
with the poodle?
[sighs]
All right, ladies, well,
you've got some serious
designing to do.
Now if I've said this once,
I've said it 100 times.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
-Yeah!
-All right!
-Oh, my God.
-Let's do it.
All right,
this is kind of interesting.
I'm super excited
about this challenge
because I've watched
every episode
and I can kill
any one of these challenges.
Whoo,
this is fun.
Oh, these are shit bags.
[laughs]
So I'm looking through
my materials
and I realize
that a lot of these things
can't be made into clothing.
Dog chew toys, ropes.
Huh.
Fuck my life.
-You guys, I brought treats.
-[laughs] Dog treats.
It's just a couple of treats,
you know.
Have you ever tasted one of
those for real?
They're actually good.
You know, I'm from the South,
we eat everything, honey.
-Possums, rats, raccoons.
-Possums?
Speaking of,
here's a beaver.
[laughs]
I don't eat beaver.
Oh, too real.
Chi Chi's a fucking bumpkin.
she's just country as fucking
catfish sandwiches.
She's like country.
♪ ♪
So I get the pride float
challenge
and I got to drag
this big ass boat
for my very first
impression.
How heavy is that?
Bitch, I don't even know
if I can pick this up.
The skinniest,
scrawniest girl.
"Lift this down the runway."
I can hardly lift anything.
How am I going to carry
that on the runway
and still walk as fierce
as Naomi Campbell?
It's like the thing
that covers up
the only thing I love
about my body: my legs.
Shit.
Do brown and green--do they
go together, like those two?
In a challenge about wearing
curtains on your body?
-Yeah.
-Sure.
I got Gone With the Window
and I'm excited
because you get fabric.
It's ugly fabric, but hey, girl,
at least I got fabric.
This is nice.
Why don't you wear
something like that?
-Girl, I'm gonna look naked.
-You would disappear.
I'm gonna look butt naked,
that's why.
-Where did Bob go, girl?
-Where is she?
["12 Days of Christmas"
playing]
There's so much stuff to use.
My theme for the challenge is
The Queen Who Mopped Christmas.
Oh, my God.
[exhales]
My strategy
for this first challenge
is to basically still come out
with my Britney look.
Like, I just want to add to it.
So what kind of vibe
are you going for?
Like,
this Christmas skirt.
Like a tree skirt,
but then I don't know
how to finish a whole outfit.
Girl.
Derrick Berry
is not creative,
obviously because
he's impersonating someone else
his whole life.
He will definitely have
the hardest time
with this challenge.
And I'm like stuck on
what to do for the top.
[groans]
[upbeat music]
The maxi challenge this week
is to design a garment
based on past challenges
that other queens from other
seasons have already done.
My theme is the Hair Ball.
What are you doing?
So, do you remember
the Givenchy collection
with like, the big fur?
-Yes.
-It's inspired by that.
I want to find a way to, like,
celebrate this beige color.
Oh, God,
how can you celebrate that?
This material is going to be
challenging to work with,
especially because
everything I have
is a Florence Henderson
shade of poop brown.
There's so much stuff that I'm
trying not to get overwhelmed
and like, I got this and this
and this and this and this.
I don't do drag on a dime.
I don't sew.
I'm a pageant girl.
I brought so many
beautiful garments.
I spend money.
I don't want to get lost
with all the stuff that I got.
You know what I mean?
There's a fucking piggy bank.
A piggy bank.
Am I supposed to
mount this shit on my head?
Make it work, bitch.
Make it work.
Hello, hello, hello.
[all] Hi.
How's my dirty dozen?
[laughter]
Bob the Drag Queen.
RuPaul.
How did you get
Bob the Drag Queen?
How did that come about?
It's my dad's name.
My dad's name
is The Drag Queen.
[laughs]
It's a family name.
Yeah, Bob stands
for big old bottom, what!
[laughter]
Well, you know it does pay
to advertise.
Now which one did you get?
I got Gone With the Window.
Now do you know how to sew?
I'm not, like,
the world's best sewer,
but I know how
to slap a garment together.
So, you're not
the world's greatest sewer.
What are you
the world's greatest?
I'm a stand-up comedian.
Who's your competition?
You know, Ru, I don't want
to sound so, uh, stereotypical.
Do, do it, it's between us.
I don't--
I don't have competition
because no one here
does what I do.
I learned from listening
to your podcast
with you and Michelle,
that there really is no reason
to pretend to be modest.
I'm fucking funny.
I'm really funny.
Let the world know.
First name, Bob,
last name, The Drag Queen.
Can she turn it?
Yes, she can.
[laughing]
It's true, girl.
All right, I'm gonna let you
get back to work.
-Thank you, Ru. Thank you.
-All right.
-Acid Betty.
-RuPaul.
How you doing?
I'm gagging
that you just said my name.
I'm so honored to be here.
Yes, now tell me about
the Brooklyn drag scene.
Well, some of them are here.
Thorgy Thor is here.
Are you guys friends
or are you friendly rivals?
We're definitely friends.
We've never worked together.
I actually haven't worked with
a lot of queens in Brooklyn
because I mostly work
in Manhattan.
-Is that a read?
-It could be.
[laughter]
Describe for me
what Brooklyn drag is.
Technically, I guess,
Brooklyn drag right now
is unpolished,
um, hairy,
so I try and elevate myself
and shave my beard.
Uh-huh, all right.
Now, what challenge did you get?
The Money Ball.
Right, do you know how to sew?
I do, but this is, like,
paper and glue.
Now, I don't see
any paper or glue yet.
So I'm trying to build
a base first
and then attach the paper,
the money to it.
Right.
All right, I'm gonna let you
get back to work.
Thank you, RuPaul.
Layla McQueen.
What's going on, lady?
-Which challenge did you get?
-I got the Rupocalypse.
Rupocalypse!
So what do you have planned?
Um, I was given, like,
a few plastic hands
and then like, a shit-ton
of camouflage.
I think camouflage
is a disgusting component
of human culture.
Okay, yeah.
Um, I'd really like to play
with the whole, like,
deconstruction, like,
jagged shapes and like...
Um...
-Rough around the edges.
-Yeah.
Now tell me,
how are you feeling?
You seem a little shy.
I am and we started
this day kind of...
It was--it was all--
it was a lot.
But now, I'm, like,
getting into the groove.
Well, listen, you better
get your shit together
because there's some
very competitive girls here.
Oh, good.
All right, Layla,
I can't wait to see it.
Thanks.
All right, listen up, ladies.
Tomorrow on the main stage,
we'll decide
how you measured up.
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
All right.
Oh, my God.
Timing is not my friend
right now.
Now I get why girls
have emotional breakdowns.
Amen.
Everyone is freaking out
because in the back of
everyone's mind,
while they're working
on their outfits,
is, "Fuck, I do not want
to go home first."
[dramatic music]
[upbeat music]
Whoo, we're back.
Hello, couture.
This thing is too big.
And that's not normally
a complaint.
Today is our very first runway
and everyone is just trying
to get their shit done.
So I'm not the
only one stressing.
And I'm burning myself,
and I'm burning myself,
and I'm burning myself.
Well stop burning yourself
and shut up.
Did you have to change
anything?
Nothing major,
but I made this clutch,
which I'm very proud of.
Oh, my God.
It is a known fact that
a lady do carry a bag to dinner.
This purse is hideous,
but I'm using it.
I think it goes
with the look though.
That was shade!
No!
I think it's cute.
Kim, you are shady.
I'm not,
I think it's cute.
Get away from me,
Shade Chi.
♪ ♪
I actually
do a lot of pageants,
and I won this pageant.
It's an international pageant.
It's called Miss Continental
and it is one of
the most prestigious pageants.
I've heard of it.
Yeah, so I'm
a former Miss Continental.
-That's awesome.
-Yeah.
I hate pageants.
Girl, I've done,
like, two pageants.
And you didn't win them and
that's why you hate pageants.
Exactly.
I knew it.
That always happens to someone
who don't win.
Bitch, I was robbed.
Like, to me, pageants are all
about the who's who of drag.
You know how many people
who would tell me,
"You're not gonna
win the pageant.
Why are you wasting your money?
Why are you doing that?"
Yeah, but you're gambling,
you're gambling your money.
Anything you do is a gamble,
remember that.
Are you really living
if you're like,
"Well, I'm not going to do it
because I don't know
the outcome."
Really?
This is the thing,
you don't have to compromise
who you are when you do stuff.
You get what I'm saying?
Be you.
It just sucks that pageants
get such a bad rap.
I owe a whole lot
of my work ethic
and who I am
to pageant experiences.
You've given me
a different outlook on pageants,
but, girl,
I still hate them.
[laughs]
So, Derrick, how long have
you been doing Britney?
I started on Halloween 2003.
And how long
you been doing drag?
Halloween 2003.
I've been doing Britney
for 12 years
and I think a lot of other girls
are not going to think I can do
anything else,
and maybe the judges even.
I have to prove
that I can do more than Britney.
I've found
there's two breeds of queen.
There's Halloween queens
and there's pride queens.
-I was a pride queen.
-Really?
I, like, started drag
on Gay Pride wearing,
like, shitty potato sack
and a wig from, you know,
who knows where.
Was that this Pride?
-How dare you?
-[laughter]
Oh you little bitch,
how dare you.
Oh, Layla!
It's all fun and jokes until
someone gets sent home, girl.
Mm-mm.
No, ma'am.
♪ ♪
How long have you
been doing drag?
I've been doing drag
for two and a half years.
Does your family
support your drag?
My family doesn't know
that I do drag.
-They don't know?
-Really?
-No.
-At all?
Like, my mom thinks
I'm a makeup artist.
Has your mother ever seen you
in drag ever,
like pictures or anything?
Well, I've shown her pictures
of me in drag
and she thinks they're, like,
makeup jobs that I did.
She doesn't recognize
that it's me.
-Stop.
-Really?
Yeah.
I guess I'm worried about
my mom finding out
that I did drag
because growing up,
I always felt like I could
never be a model child
that all Asian mothers want.
I've already disappointed her
so many times in her life.
She could even stop
talking to me.
And...
And you know, I'm just scared
of letting her down again.
What foundation
do you like to use?
Girl, like,
somebody gave me this.
And they was just like,
"This look like your color."
So, I'm like, "Okay."
-How long you been in drag?
-Five years.
And you're not
brand loyal yet?
No ma'am, I use whatever
cost a dollar or free.
[laughing]
I want to be like
the Anna Wintour of drag.
Wait, if you're the Nomi,
then, uh,--who does that--
am I the older one
in "Showgirls"?
I'm Naomi, not Nomi.
Oh, then that's perfect.
Come on, Naomi Shambles.
Work the runway, girl.
Naomi Shambles
on the runway, girl.
Knees clackin',
clickity clackin, boom.
-God, Bob and his mouth.
-He is like madness.
-I love it.
-Do you really?
He's like a talking head.
When I'm trying
to concentrate,
I really don't need,
like, someone
trying to, like, crack
one-liners all the time.
Especially when
they're not always funny.
Well, he's a comedian,
which means I say 300 jokes,
four of them are funny.
I guess, like I'm just used
to, like, getting ready
with girls who's just like,
loud and like, you know.
And see, I get ready alone.
Y'all know we ain't got
no insurance, now sit down.
♪ ♪
[fabric rips]
[gasps]
What's the matter girl?
Speak it out.
I go to put on my outfit
and what happens?
Pop.
My outfit has just ripped apart.
Oh, God,
I'm having a meltdown.
[sewing machine buzzing]
Uh, that don't work.
This some bullshit.
My fucking panties
just ripped at the last second.
And it's all coming apart.
This fabric,
for some reason,
will not catch
the bottom thread.
This is some bullshit.
Shit.
I am going into panic mode
right now.
Girl, you cannot go home,
not on the first day.
I want this so freaking bad.
Like, I'm so distraught,
I don't even know
what I'm doing now.
I have no clue
how she's gonna fix this outfit.
I think she's done.
I hope you know
the lip synch song,
'cause your outfit
is crumbling before your hands.
Fuck.
["Cover Girl"
by RuPaul plays]
♪ ♪
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe
let your whole body talk ♪
And what.
[laughter]
Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Michelle Visage,
happy 100th.
Happy birthday,
gorgeous.
Style superstar,
Carson Kressley.
You look amazing for 100.
I know, I don't look
a day over 95.
-Thank you Doctor Zizmor.
-Yes.
[laughs]
And the straight-talking
Ross Mathews.
Now, on a scale from one to 100,
how excited are you?
Like, a dragzillion.
And the fabulous
Nicole Richie.
-Hey, kitty girl.
-Hi, gorge.
Your dress is very
"Wizard of Oz."
Are you a good witch
or a bad witch?
-Or a sandwich.
-[laughter]
This week, our queens posed
with Drag Race champions.
And tonight,
they're debuting
their own creations
based on a design challenge
from the "anals"
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Michele,
did I say that right?
-Eh.
-Eh, close enough.
Gentlemen, start your engines
and may the best woman win.
[upbeat music]
♪ The realness ♪
[RuPaul] First up, Acid Betty,
Money Ball.
Well,
bitch better have my money.
I do freaky drag
and I think I do it the best.
The drag scene should not
be homogenized
and not everyone
should look the same.
Therefore, Acid Betty
is here to represent.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
make it rain.
[Nicole] Don't you love
when you just find a dollar
in your dress pocket?
-[Carson] Yes.
-Didn't know this was here.
[RuPaul] Cash is queen,
I own everything.
Bob the Drag Queen,
Gone with The Window.
[Carson] Yes, honey,
lead with the bag.
I love it.
This outfit shows
that I have the ability
to make a finished garment.
The fabric is hideous, but
the construction is everything.
I'm living my dream with this
ugly purse that I made.
[Ross] No shade,
but that dress looks like
it was made out of curtains.
[Nicole] It's very
Butterfly McQueen.
[Michelle] Frankly my dear,
I don't give a dental damn.
[RuPaul] Dax ExclamationPoint,
Hello Kitty.
[Carson] Hello, Herve Leger.
-[Michelle] Hello, Angeline.
-[Ross] Meow.
This outfit
is totally me.
I love Hello Kitty.
Anything a 12-year-old Asian
girl wants, I want it more.
I feel like a neon '80s
nightmare and I love it.
[Carson] I do love a pink pussy.
[Nicole] It's better than
a purple one.
[Carson] Why it got
to be purple?
[RuPaul] Naysha Lopez,
Drag on a Dime.
[Nicole] Fashion sure
is changing.
I am serving Greek goddess,
giving you face for the gods.
Face, body, glamour.
And I am definitely serving
that all right now.
[Michelle] Peek-a-Ru, I see you.
[RuPaul] Uh-huh.
[Michelle] A dress that
makes cents. Not dollars.
[RuPaul] A dollar
make me holler.
Kim Chi, Hair Ball.
-[clears throat]
-[laughs]
You got a little--
[Michelle] Someone's in a furry.
I've made a lion outfit
inspired by Givenchy.
I turned these ratty,
dirty blonde wigs
into a golden treasure.
This outfit is big, grand,
and conceptual.
It's Kim Chi.
[Nicole] She stepped
that pussy up. Meow.
[RuPaul] Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
Sugar Ball.
[Michelle] Gumdrop it
like it's hot.
I feel like a goddess
of the snow.
My "corselet"
is just sickening.
It's sugar, azúcar.
Are you ready for my cuckoo?
-Yeah.
-[all] Yes.
[RuPaul] Now see, that's
the real sugar right there.
[Nicole] She's serving cake.
[Michelle] That's her
sugar walls.
[Nicole] Whoa!
[RuPaul] Naomi Smalls,
Float Your Boat.
[Carson] Washington's
cross-dressing the Delaware.
[Nicole] She has
my dream chest.
[Carson] Yeah.
I'm trying to give you
'90s supermodel walk
and this boat is covering
half of it.
When I can finally
step out of this boat,
that's when the judges
can really see
the true Naomi Smalls.
[Carson] Land ho.
I am giving you
Naomi Campbell
strutting down
a Versace runway.
[Michelle] Legzilla.
[Ross] Oh, oh that, yeah.
That boat looks heavy.
Are there any seamen
to help her?
[Michelle] Where are they?
[Ross] The seamen
are all below deck.
[RuPaul] Chi Chi DeVayne,
Glitter Ball.
[Carson] You know I always say,
when life hands you
disco balls...
-[Nicole] Oh.
-[Carson] What do you do?
[Michelle] You make an outfit.
[all laughing]
[Ross] Yeah.
After my little meltdown,
I'm just gonna roll
with the punches
and I'm really feeling this
disco queen kind of vibe.
It's a dream come true.
[Ross] That's a disco ball?
I thought that
was a fabulous globe.
-[Carson] Yes.
-[Ross] It's her ring.
[Carson] I thought it was
a Judith Leiber bag.
-[RuPaul] Cocktail bag.
-[Carson] Balls to the walls.
[RuPaul] Thorgy Thor,
Red Velvet Cake Couture.
[Michelle] I'm hungry
for that creamy middle.
[Nicole] This is feeling
a little menstrual.
[all laughing]
[RuPaul] I'm glad you said it
and I didn't.
I don't wear gowns,
but for this challenge
I just wanted to feel decadent
and I still kept
with my cartoon hair,
giving you cream cheese
realness.
[Michelle] Oh, happy birthday!
[RuPaul] Have her cake
and serve it too.
Robbie Turner,
Bitch Ball.
Who let the dogs out?
[Nicole] I love two bitches
on a runway.
I think I'm looking more like
a sheep than a poodle.
The dog is looking at me like,
"Get me the fuck
out of here."
I'm looking at the dog like,
"Get me the fuck
out of here."
This is not going well.
[RuPaul] Bow wow wow.
[Michelle] Yippee yo,
yippee yay.
[Ross] I give this look about
a canine out of 10.
[RuPaul] Uh-huh, she's fade
and she's throwing shade.
[Michelle] Those bitches
are over it.
[RuPaul] Derrick Berry,
The Queen Who Mopped Christmas.
[Ross] Well, hey, y'all.
I'm giving you
Christmas in Vegas.
I'm representing showgirls.
I'm serving body.
But I'm also giving comedy.
-[all] Whoa!
-[Ross] Ho, ho, ho.
[Nicole] She's trimming
her bush.
[RuPaul] Is that mistletoe
or camel toe.
[Nicole] I respect that.
[Carson] She's putting
the X back in Xmas.
[RuPaul] Yes, she is.
[Ross] Oops,
she's doing it again.
[RuPaul] Layla McQueen,
Apocalyptic Couture.
Now, her pussy's not on fire,
but her shoulder is.
This look
is classic Layla.
I'm loving this cute
little jacket I made.
I'm giving you, like,
a post-apocalyptic,
like, devil commander, like,
she's coming up,
the world is over
and I'm here to take over.
[Michelle] The thigh's
the limit.
[RuPaul] Layla McQueen,
Beyond Thunderdome.
Welcome, ladies.
I feel like I just saw my whole
life flash before my eyes.
[laughter]
Now, ladies, when I call
your name, please step forward.
Bob the Drag Queen.
Dax ExclamationPoint.
Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Thorgy Thor.
You are all...
Safe.
Thank you.
And for the 100th time,
safe is not a word I associate
with America's Next
Drag Superstar.
Now you may leave the stage.
Time for the judges critiques.
Ladies, you represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges critiques.
Acid Betty.
I love that you're different.
Every inch was kind of
covered with a thought.
To me,
that's what drag is about.
And then the photo,
you seem like you're a little
bit more of the avant-garde,
artsy, like, you're giving me
Tunnel 1993.
-I was there.
-I might've seen you there.
-You might've.
-Great job.
Thank you Acid Betty.
Next up, Naysha Lopez.
-You're gorgeous.
-Thank you.
You're giving me Eva Longoria,
Miss America.
Your makeup is stunning.
I think, Naysha,
you're beautiful,
but when you're part
of an ensemble photo,
you really want to stand out.
The dark hair and the dark top,
I don't think it works
in this picture.
I have a pet peeve
with seeing undergarments.
So when you turn around
I see illusion net.
Give me the full illusion.
That big gold piece
just makes you look thick
and I just don't think
it looks good.
This is actually the first
garment I've ever made.
I don't really sew.
I felt like it was wearable
and, you know,
I got the challenge down.
All right, well,
thank you very much.
-Next up, Kim Chi.
-Hi.
Your photo is pretty fabulous.
And I really like
your runway look.
You are giving me, like,
this Cowardly Lion
anime ferociousness.
I think it totally worked.
The artistry on your face
is just like geometric orgasm.
I'm gonna give you
the benefit of the doubt
and say the walk
was a character choice.
Every time I'm wearing
something different,
I'm living whatever fantasy
of the outfit I've got going on.
In my personal eyes,
I'm an anime character
who works
as a high fashion model.
You're just a total nerd.
-I am.
-I love that.
And by the way, I like that
you kept your areolas bald.
The breasts are the windows
to the soul, for sure.
[laughter]
Nicole,
would you wear this?
I would definitely
wear it.
Where would you wear this?
Um, probably school drop off.
Okay, yeah.
Thank you, Kim Chi.
Next up, Naomi Smalls.
I love that you
are rocking a boy chest.
You're giving me
like, '70s "Studio 54."
Michele,
how do you like her hair?
Very pretty, only
my hairline's not clockable.
Okay, all right.
The Pride Float
was beautifully decorated,
but it became really cumbersome.
And I almost saw you thinking,
"I have to get back in that boat
and strap it on."
And I'm saying that
about the boat.
Yeah, I know, how many times
have you said that in your life?
-Girl.
-Yeah.
But the picture.
Hello?
And it's a big butt.
That is a big butt.
I believe they call that
serving it.
Okay.
That needs to come through
with everything that you do,
whether you're dragging a
50-pound boat with you or not.
Next up,
Robbie Turner.
Your photo, I loved,
because you're giving me kind of
funny glamour there.
-You chose fur?
-It's like a fringe.
Fringy kind of
carpety-looking stuff.
You're literally a blob.
We lose all shape and
from the side, it's even worse.
And you got to choose
your challenge.
I actually forgot that I--
to choose one for myself.
I didn't have
my '40s dress pattern,
but I was trying to figure
it out, like,
at the last minute.
So, it was like a series
of misfortunate events.
Do you think that you deserve
to be in the bottom.
Um, no, I think
my personality is winning.
All right, well, thank you
very much, Robbie Turner.
Next up, Derrick Berry.
Your look tonight,
it's adorable.
I will say it's pretty simple.
I like the comedic moment
where you trimmed
your holiday bush.
I love a bush
on the front door,
but on the back door
not so much.
-No.
-Definitely not berries.
[laughter]
And then your photo,
like, everyone in this photo
looks like
they're your backup dancers
and you're the star.
-Wow.
-We've seen Britney now.
My personal challenge to you
is to show me everything else
but Britney.
-Okay.
-We love your Britney.
I do want to see more of it,
but we do want to see
other things.
I want more!
And I'll give you more.
[laughter]
You can't help yourself,
can you?
Up next,
Layla McQueen.
-Hi, Layla.
-Hey, bitch.
I love the shoulder detail.
Did you sew that?
I sewed the jacket, yes.
-That's pretty impressive.
-Thank you.
But I felt like the bottom
half was just a cop out.
This was a really fun category
I think to like,
do, like,
totally, like, singe.
To me, it's just like,
Wynonna Judd opened the oven
too quickly and got
a little, like, you know,
burnt on the outside.
In the picture we lose you
crumpling up into a ball.
You're with all these
kind of legendary people
and it's almost like your
body's saying "I'm not worthy."
[dramatic music]
Do you think
that your missteps
would warrant you
in the bottom?
I think I have
a lot more to show
and I don't think that I am...
the least put together.
Who do you think
is the least put together?
I think Naomi.
Her look is very plain.
Do you agree with that,
Naomi?
No. I tried to take something
that was from a past season
and make it new and fresh.
Well, thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges
and I will deliberate.
[tense music]
Alright now, just between
us squirrel friends,
what do you think?
Let's start with Acid Betty.
I love Acid Betty.
she's a little bit dangerous,
she's rock 'n' roll.
In the photo she looks great,
but she is this punk girl.
Like, give me
a little screaming...
Ahh!
Tongue out punkness.
I don't hate her photo,
and like her name implies,
she's kind of a trip
and she's a little East Village.
Well, you know, I did
a lot of antacid in the 60s
and I think that Acid Betty
really represents that.
[laughter]
[RuPaul]: Alright,
Naysha Lopez.
Her photo, unfortunately,
I think she got lost.
And also,
don't stand on that stage
and tell us
it's the first dress you made.
I mean, this is not the place
you make your first dress.
-Girl.
-You make your first dress
when you learn that
you're gonna come on the show.
Or you make them
when your mom's at work
-and you're in the sixth grade.
-[all laughs]
[RuPaul] All right, next up,
Kim Chi.
I love the photograph.
She was kind of
the queen of the castle
in this anime jungle.
Everything about her tonight
made me happy,
except for
that lumbering walk.
Right, because
she was serving a little bit
of Sasquatch on the runway.
Sasquatch that walk.
You can say Yeti that walk.
Yeti that walk.
[laughter]
Next up, Naomi Smalls.
I love that she looks like
she might faint at any moment.
All I saw
was a really tiny thing
lumbering with
a heavy ass boat.
I kind of like
the contrast of her like,
fumbling with the boat.
It's like a cartoon of an ant
carrying a giant piece
of cheese.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[Ross] Well, that's the picture
of the day.
It says,
"bow down bitches."
If she doesn't bring
the photo her
to this her,
to me, she's gone.
Moving on down
to Robbie Turner.
This look in her photo
is probably her go to look.
It's that Carole Lombard
meets Carol Burnett.
Superstar from the 20s.
But what we saw today
was basic.
Yes, she said
she forgot to choose
a category for herself.
The dog ate my category.
A dingo ate my category.
Quite honestly,
if she put any creativity
into that,
she could've turned it out
and that's a shame
because I like
what I saw in the picture.
Let's move on down
to Derrick Berry.
Her Britney is amazing.
You know he can nail
the Britney thing.
I mean,
the photo was phenomenal.
I'm glad she brought
it the first episode.
Now bring Derrick Berry
to the table.
But don't you want to see
a little bit more Britney?
Yes,
we'll get more Britney.
Layla McQueen.
She did the most
basic bottom half to that.
I expect so much more.
This is season eight and
the bar has been raised so high.
There was just
nothing standing out for me.
The worst picture
of the week, by far,
but I find her interesting
because she is an artist.
That warrants
a second chance to me.
Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
[dramatic music]
Acid Betty,
you put your money
where your mouth is
and where your ass is
-and where your chest is.
-[laughter]
-You're safe.
-Thank you.
Kim Chi, your photo
and main stage presentation
wigged us out.
Condragulations, you're the
winner of this week's challenge.
-[cheering]
-Oh, my God.
You've won $3,000
from selfieonastick.com.
The original and the best
selfie on a stick.
-Say hi, everybody.
-Cheese.
I can be the Asian tourist
that I've always wanted to be.
Bitch,
I just won $3,000.
This win means I have a place
in this competition
and I am a force
to be reckoned with.
[upbeat music]
Derrick Berry, you're safe.
[whispers] Thank you.
Naomi Smalls, you're safe.
[silent]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Naysha Lopez,
you are gorgeous,
-Thank you.
-but...
The judges felt short changed
by your Drag on a Dime.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
[dramatic music]
[Naysha] I am absolutely
gagging.
I don't deserve
to be in the bottom two.
You have some queen
rocking this five dollar dress.
I-I don't get it.
Robbie Turner,
your photo was iconic,
but on the main stage,
you screwed the pooch.
♪ ♪
Layla McQueen,
you are an edgy artist,
but your photo and your
Post Apocalyptic Couture
were not earth shattering.
Robbie Turner...
You're safe.
♪ ♪
-Oh.
-All right.
Wow.
Layla McQueen,
I'm sorry my dear,
but you are up for
elimination.
My heart drops,
but I'm not gonna be
the first one to go home.
I'm gonna do every kind of
quasi-gimmick I have.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
[dramatic music]
The time has come...
[thunder rumbles]
For you to lip synch
for your life.
[thunder rumbles]
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
♪ I stand here
waiting for you ♪
♪ To bang the gong ♪
♪ ♪
♪ To crash the critic saying ♪
♪ "Is it right
or is it wrong?" ♪
♪ ♪
♪ If only fame
had an IV, baby ♪
♪ I could bear ♪
♪ Being away from you ♪
♪ I found the vein,
put it here ♪
♪ I live for the applause,
applause, applause ♪
♪ I live for
the applause-plause ♪
♪ Live for
♪ Live for the way that
you cheer and scream for me ♪
♪ The applause,
applause, applause ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Give me the thing
that I love ♪
♪ I'll turn the lights out ♪
♪ Put your hands up,
make them touch ♪
♪ Make it real loud ♪
Naysha is always giving
like, beautiful, sexy,
J.Lo boom shell,
I feel it.
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Touch, touch ♪
♪ Ooh, touch, touch ♪
Layla is giving you
sex on a stick and it's awesome.
She is looking
so good right now
throwing her body
all over the floor.
♪ I live for the applause,
applause, applause ♪
♪ I live for
the applause-plause ♪
♪ Live for
Naysha's dancing
like a soccer mom.
"You can get the ball in
the goal, kids, you can do it."
♪ I live for the applause,
applause, applause ♪
♪ Give me the thing
that I love ♪
♪ I'll turn the lights out ♪
♪ Put your hands up,
make them touch ♪
♪ I'll turn the lights out ♪
♪ Give me the thing
that I love ♪
♪ I'll turn the lights out ♪
♪ Put your hands up,
make them touch ♪
♪ Make it real loud ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Put your hands up,
make them touch, touch ♪
♪ A-R-T-P-O-P ♪
[cheering]
Good job! Yes!
Ladies,
I've made my decision.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Layla McQueen,
shantay, you stay.
You may join the other girls.
Thank you.
Naysha Lopez,
out of 100 queens,
you are by far one
of the most beautiful
-to grace this stage.
-Thank you, Ru.
And I'm sorry
to see you go so soon.
I'm sorry that I wasn't
able to show you
everything that I had to offer.
Thank you, Ru,
for this opportunity.
Thank you.
Now, sashay away.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Now, good luck with
all these monsters, Mary.
[laughter]
[Naysha] I am first to go and I
feel like I didn't let Ru see
what I'm all about because
there's so much more to me.
Ru, I want to thank you
for the platform
that you have given me
because not everyone
appreciates it.
I thank you for that
from the bottom
of my heart.
♪ ♪
Well,
condragulations, ladies,
and remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here.
[all] Amen.
Alright,
now let the music play.
♪ Dance for life ♪
♪ Die tomorrow ♪
♪ Live tonight ♪
♪ Dance tonight ♪