Welcome to the grand finale
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race."
Ladies and gentlemen...
RuPaul.
[epic music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
Why don‘t you take a picture?
It‘ll last longer.
[laughter]
Wait, wait,
someone‘s missing.
Raja,
may I borrow your phone?
[phone dialing]
Hello?
It‘s RuPaul.
How soon can you get here?
Good.
[cheers and applause]
[laughter]
I just want to say
I love your makeup.
[laughs]
All right,
enough clowning around.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman...
-[all] win.
[cheers and applause]
[engine turns over]
The winner
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly
Hills cosmetics
and $100,000.
♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman,
best woman win ♪
From the Orpheum Theater
in downtown Los Angeles,
welcome the queens
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race"
season eight.
["The Realness" by RuPaul]
The queen of all nerds,
Dax ExclamationPoint.
♪ Place your bet
and spin the wheel ♪
♪ ♪
She‘s punky yet spunky.
It‘s Laila McQueen.
♪ ♪
♪ The realness ♪
Still spreading that cuckoo,
Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
♪ The realness ♪
♪ ♪
The beauty has arrived.
Give it up for Naysha Lopez.
♪ Th--the realness ♪
♪ Gonna move into the house ♪
She‘s bitch perfect.
Get ready to trip
with Acid Betty.
♪ The realness ♪
♪ Catch it, touch it,
touch it, catch it ♪
♪ Flavor of this fever ♪
She‘s hell on wheels.
It‘s Robbie Turner.
♪ The realness ♪
♪ Catch it, touch it,
touch it, catch it ♪
♪ Flavor of this fever ♪
♪ The realness,
ooh, ooh ♪
Looking good,
feeling thorgeous,
it‘s Thorgy Thor.
♪ The realness,
ooh, ooh ♪
♪ My love is real,
the realness, ooh, ooh ♪
She‘s not that innocent.
She‘s Derrick Barry.
♪ My love is real ♪
♪ The way I feel is real ♪
♪ ‘Cause I know what I feel ♪
Serving Louisiana glamour,
Miss Chi Chi DeVayne.
♪ ♪
♪ Is real ♪
And now our,
top three queens.
Is the train still running?
It‘s Bob The Drag Queen.
♪ Place your bet
and spin the wheel ♪
♪ The realness ♪
You‘ll nut come for her.
It‘s Kim Chi.
♪ Catch it, touch it,
touch it, catch it ♪
♪ Flavor of this fever ♪
♪ The realness ♪
♪ Th--the realness ♪
♪ Catch it, touch it,
touch it, catch it ♪
♪ Flavor of this fever ♪
And last,
but not least,
check your lipstick
before you come for her.
It‘s Naomi Smalls.
♪ ♪
♪ The realness ♪
♪ Only really matters
how we feel ♪
♪ Th--the realness ♪
♪ The realness ♪
One more time,
give it up for the queens
of season eight.
[cheers and applause]
[drum roll]
And now...
RuPaul.
["U Wear It Well" by RuPaul]
- ♪ You wear it well ♪
♪ French tip, lipstick,
painted on ♪
♪ Value sure suits you,
ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Work it for me,
work it for me, me ♪
♪ You wear it, you wear it,
you wear it well ♪
♪ Wig shop, nonstop,
hair salon ♪
♪ You wear it well ♪
♪ Value brand new,
ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Work it for me,
work it for me, me ♪
♪ You wear it, you wear it,
you wear it well ♪
[cheers and applause]
Well, well,
well, look at you.
Everyone is wearing it
well tonight.
Welcome to the grand finale
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race."
Yes, the tribe has gathered,
heeney. [laughs]
I know we‘re in the middle
of a presidential election,
but tonight this
is the race everybody‘s
talking about...
because together,
right here on Logo TV,
we can make America
gay again!
[cheers and applause]
And I got to tell you,
in this theater
you have my permission
to use any damn bathroom
you want.
[cheers and applause]
Well,
except mine, of course.
You hear that, Jiggly?
Tonight our legendary judges
are here.
Fresh from the drop-off
at Calabasas Junior High School,
it‘s Michelle Visage.
[cheers and applause]
[laughs]
Also here are Ross Mathews
and Carson Kressley.
-Hi.
Now, this season
we‘ve been to Oz and back,
but the competition
ain‘t over.
Bob The Drag Queen,
Kim Chi, and Naomi Smalls...
[cheers and applause]
Tonight one of you
will be crowned
America‘s next drag superstar,
but I have not made
my final decision,
and because we‘re still
keeping it 100,
I‘ve asked each of you
to prepare
a lip sync performance
to a song created just for you.
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me
and to show the world
that you deserve to be
America‘s next drag superstar,
so good luck,
and don‘t fuck it up.
[cheers and applause]
Now, our top three queens
have snatched your attention
all season long,
and tonight
I‘ve challenged each of them
to slay the stage one last time.
Purse first,
a New York City girl
who puts the taint
in entertaintment,
give it up
for a demure little lady
we call
Bob The Drag Queen.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
♪ I don‘t go out
looking for the spotlight ♪
♪ The spotlight finds me ♪
[deep voice]
Uh, over here.
♪ Try to tone it down,
tuck it in real tight ♪
♪ But it‘s not that easy ♪
♪ It‘s not that easy ♪
♪ Since I was a child ♪
♪ People keep saying
I‘ve been doing too much ♪
-[both] ♪ Doing too much ♪
♪ Mama always said,
"Hold your head up high ♪
♪ You‘ve got
that magic touch" ♪
-[both] ♪ The magic touch ♪
♪ So whether it‘s acting,
comedy ♪
♪ Body, singing, dancing ♪
♪ Or serving chocolate
chip cookies ♪
♪ I don‘t like to show off ♪
-[both] ♪ Don‘t show off ♪
♪ I keep it subtle,
keep it humble ♪
♪ ‘Cause it‘s not my gig ♪
♪ I like to keep my talents
tucked under my wig, whoo ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ I don‘t like to show off ♪
-[both] ♪ Don‘t show off ♪
-♪ Read my lips ♪
All the other bitches
call me ratchet.
You‘re way too big
I snatch it.
Go ahead
and hand me the Oscar.
I‘m the only one
on the roster.
If you come for B-O-B,
you must be an SOB.
Never was a hater,
but I‘m making mashed potater
out of err‘body right
in front of you.
Ha, ha, ha.
♪ I don‘t like to show off ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I keep it subtle,
keep it humble ♪
♪ ‘Cause it‘s not my gig ♪
♪ I like to keep my talents
tucked under my wig ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ I don‘t
like to show off ♪
♪ Off ♪
[cheers and applause]
[audience chanting] Bob! Bob!
Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob!
Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob!
[cheers and applause]
-Wow.
-[laughs]
Work it out for team humble.
[cheers and applause]
Now, while you catch
your breath,
let‘s talk to the judges.
Michelle Visage,
what‘d you think?
That was amazing.
Come on, choreography.
Phenomenal.
I‘m so proud of you.
And I love that you play safe.
Every one of your dancers
was wearing a hard hat.
I love that.
[laughter]
It‘s important.
I think you need to change
your name to Bob The Superstar.
Ooh.
Well, thank you, judges.
Now, Bob The Drag Queen,
from the moment
you entered the workroom
you had uniqueness, nerve,
and talent written all over you.
Let‘s take a look.
-[Bob] My name is
Bob The Drag Queen.
I‘m hilarious, beautiful,
talented, and humble.
That‘s the biggest
pearl necklace I‘ve ever seen.
-How you doing, RuPaul?
-[laughs]
I‘m sorry that I‘m late,
but "Uzo Abubu"
left the stage.
[laughing]
Well, then why did I waste
my time putting on this?
Oh, there‘s more.
This.
Sometimes you borderline
on showboating.
-[Bob] Insert shady
rattlesnake noise here.
[rolls tongue]
-Bob, how‘s your head?
-No complaints.
-[Bob] I‘m Bob The Drag Queen,
a queen for the people.
[upbeat music]
[cheers and applause]
Now, Bob, when did you first
become aware of drag?
I used to watch
"To Wong Foo."
Yas!
I saw, like, this, like,
glamazonian, like,
goddess coming down
from the ceiling
wearing a big confederate flag.
I was like,
"Oh, this bitch is--"
when I say bitch,
I mean it, like,
the way you‘d call
your grandmother a bitch.
[laughter]
I was like, "This bitch
is pushing buttons, girl,"
and I loved it.
You excelled at so many
of the challenges.
Did you study the show
before you came on?
No,
I‘m just really talented.
[laughter]
You know, listen,
this is my favorite show.
This is what I thought I was
supposed to be doing
my whole life.
When I was performing in,
like, bars in New York City,
dodging beer bottles
literally,
I was like,
"This doesn‘t feel right.
There‘s something bigger
coming."
Lo and behold,
I found something bigger.
Her name is RuPaul,
and she blessed me.
[cheers and applause]
Now, Bob, at one point
in the season
the other queens
were rooting for you to fail.
-Mm-hmm.
-What did that feel like?
It felt like
I was doing it right.
[laughs]
I mean, no one‘s rooting
for the person doing the worst.
No one‘s like, "Oh, you‘re doing
bad. You should get out."
They‘re like,
"Ooh, she‘s doing so well.
Get her the fuck
out of here."
All right,
so we‘ve got some
fan questions over there.
[cheers and applause]
Hallelu, I‘m back,
RuPaul!
[laughter]
Tucker from Florida
wants to know,
"Does your humor come
from overcoming
a dark place in your life?"
Um, see, I mean,
I have the struggles
that a lot of y‘all homosexuals
here had, especially--
What?
They‘re--wait, wait--
They‘re--this--
[laughter]
These are homosexuals?
A few.
I had the same hardships
that everyone else here has,
and we all deal with it
in different ways.
If you find something
to filter your pain
and your anger into,
it‘ll flourish.
It really will.
Thank you, Shangela.
Now, Bob,
you blew everyone away
with your Snatch Game
impersonations.
Now, did you ever hear
from Uzo or Carol Channing?
Well, Uzo
tweeted at me
and was like,
"This was amazing,"
and I was like, "Thank you,"
and I am obsessed
with Carol Channing,
but she‘s just--she‘s 95.
It‘s hard to get
out of the house when you‘re 95.
I‘m 18, and it‘s hard
for me to get out, so.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Well, we did hear from
the one and only Carol Channing.
Take a look.
Thank you, Bob,
for your colorful
impersonation of me.
I‘m so honored
to be a part of your history.
Oh, I‘m proud of that.
[cheers and applause]
Oh, my God.
Yes.
So Bob, I know your brother‘s
over there, right?
Yeah, he‘s the one who‘s just
a shade darker than me.
I‘m 11:00.
He‘s midnight.
[laughter]
Justin, what was it
like growing up with Bob?
Bob used to cry
on my birthdays
‘cause it wasn‘t about him.
That‘s true.
Now, Bob,
I know that your mother
couldn‘t be here
because of her health.
-Yes.
-Darn, you know,
it would have been
a great opportunity for us
to have a taped message
or something,
but we didn‘t--we don‘t have--
wait a minute.
Oh, actually,
we do have a taped message.
- Oh.
- Let‘s roll that.
- Hey.
- Bob, this is your mother.
I‘m very proud of you.
I‘ve always believed in you,
even when you didn‘t
believe in yourself.
Continue to work hard
on your craft.
Always respect your fans.
Reach for the stars,
Chris, do the best you can.
Like I always tell you
and your brother,
keep the first thing
the first thing,
and I love you.
[cheers and applause]
You got me.
Oh, my goodness.
Now, Bob, what would it mean
to you to win $100,000?
$100,000 isn‘t the thing
because money comes and goes,
but winning this title,
that means something.
You get to go forth
and carry a legacy
and do something and make
a change in somebody‘s life
and put first things first
and do something.
Right, well--right, well--
Now, I‘ve watched
all 109 episodes
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race,"
and I‘ve noticed
you have never once
walked into
the room purse first.
Oh, my God,
look at this.
Oh,
and it matches my outfit.
It‘s perfect.
I love it.
Purse first.
[cheers and applause]
Give it up for Bob
The Drag Queen.
Up next we‘ve got
an Instagram superstar
who‘s about to
lisp sync for her life.
Now serving Kim Chi.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
♪ I came here to debut ♪
♪ A brand-new dance for you ♪
♪ Really easy to do ♪
♪ It‘s the new sensation ♪
♪ Only three things you need
to do it just like me ♪
♪ Count it like one, two,
three, every generation ♪
♪ Beyoncé ♪
♪ Madonna ♪
♪ Got nothing
on this triple threat ♪
♪ Do the ♪
Fat, fem, and Asian.
♪ Yeah,
fat, fem, and Asian ♪
♪ Fat, fem, and Asian ♪
♪ ♪
[speaking foreign language]
♪ ...one, two, three ♪
[singing in foreign language]
♪ Britney ♪
♪ Rihanna ♪
♪ Got nothing
on this triple threat ♪
♪ Do the
fat, fem, and Asian ♪
♪ Fat, fem, and Asian ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
[speaks in foreign language]
♪ Fat, fem, and Asian,
fat, fem, and Asian ♪
♪ Fat, fem, and Asian ♪
[speaks in foreign language]
♪ Fat, fem, and Asian,
fat, fem, and Asian ♪
♪ Fat, fem, and Asian ♪
[speaks in foreign language]
[cheers and applause]
Wow.
Kim Chi,
I love that song.
It‘s got a good beat,
and you can‘t dance to it.
[laughter]
All right, Kim Chi,
let‘s hear from the judges.
Michelle Visage,
what‘s the tea on Kim Chi?
I love that your purity
and your beautiful energy
took something that was normally
considered negative
and turned it into something
fun and beautiful.
Yes.
Nailed it.
[laughter]
Today Kim Chi
is on the menu,
and you are the main course.
Who‘s hungry?
Now, Kim Chi, you came
to this competition hungry.
You won the first challenge,
and then you stayed hungry.
Let‘s take a look.
My name is Kim Chi.
-[Kim] I came to chop suey
the competition.
I‘m known for crazy,
over-the-top
pure anime fantasy.
Animazing.
I may across shy
because I am soft-spoken,
but donut come for me
because I‘ll destroy you.
I do get concerned
about your walk.
It‘s very stiff, darling.
Exqueeze me?
My mom doesn‘t know
that I do drag.
What?
Kim Chi,
you didn‘t just get better.
You got fierce.
I don‘t want to be
America‘s next drag superstar.
I am America‘s
next drag superstar.
Now, Kim Chi,
you were so honest
and vulnerable this season.
In fact,
watching the show back,
at one point
you made me ugly cry, girl,
so I hope you don‘t mind
if I ask you
some very personal questions.
First one, when was
the last time you fell down?
[laughter]
Actually, earlier today.
I‘m not even joking.
I tripped on my skirt,
and I fell over
the craft service table.
[laughter]
Now, everyone
is gagging on your looks,
just so many amazing looks.
What inspires you?
My inspiration comes
from a lot of random places.
I could be walking
down the street
and see a rock and be like,
"Oh, that rock is pretty.
Let me make a gown
inspired by the rock,"
so there‘s no one
set inspiration,
but everyday life and nature.
Now, is it true
you gave the $3,000
you won in
the first challenge
to your mother?
Why‘d you do that?
My mom works really hard to,
you know, pay the bills,
and she works as a server
at a Korean restaurant
currently,
and I want to do everything
that I can to help
my mom financially.
Yeah.
Have you told her
that you do drag yet?
I still have not,
but, you know, it‘s like--
She didn‘t watch the show?
I mean,
she‘s very Korean-American,
and she‘s really, like, not open
to American culture at all,
so I don‘t think--
yeah, I don‘t think
she‘ll ever find out
about "Drag Race."
Well, listen,
I am a firm believer in
things happen when
they‘re supposed to happen,
so right after this,
why don‘t we drive
over to your mother‘s house
and I tell her myself?
-Road trip?
-Road trip.
- Road trip.
- Yes.
Who‘s here
supporting you tonight?
I have my friend
Ryan, Diana, Amy, and Trixie.
So Diana, what do you think
of Kim Chi‘s journey?
I think Kim Chi
is the most creative, talented,
and hardworking person I know.
I‘m so happy
to be your friend,
and I want the best for you.
All right, now,
we‘ve got some fan questions
for you, Kim Chi.
Oh, look,
we have the Pit Crew coming d--
and they--
you forgot your pants, guys.
Kim Chi,
Tiara from Facebook asks,
"If you could
lose your virginity
to a member of the Pit Crew,
who would it be?"
Um, I‘m not trying
to catch anything,
so I‘m gonna say none of them,
but--
[audience groans, laughs]
Shade. Shade.
Shade!
[laughs]
Oh, thank you,
Pit Crew members.
I don‘t know what
to say after that.
All right, Kim Chi,
well, we have one more question.
Well, actually,
it‘s more of a statement.
Take a look.
Kim Chi,
I am supreme leader,
but you are supreme
drag queen.
You better work,
or else I put you
in a labor camp.
Kim Chi, it‘s Margaret Cho.
I‘m so proud of you.
You‘re so beautiful.
You are so funny, and I think
you are a good dancer.
[cheers and applause]
So Kim Chi,
what would it mean to you
to become America‘s
next drag superstar?
It would obviously
change my life.
I‘d be able to not be broke.
I‘d be able to afford
guacamole on my burrito bowl.
I‘d be able to start
my own makeup company,
which I would love to do,
and it would mean that
anybody who‘s ever felt
like they weren‘t
part of anything,
anybody that felt like
they couldn‘t be anything,
as long as you stay true
to who you are,
be creative, be original,
and your dreams
will eventually come true.
Well, Kim Chi,
read my lisp,
we love you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for Kim Chi.
[cheers and applause]
Now it‘s time for our
final performance
of the night.
Oh, and by the way,
kittens,
you can buy these
top three songs right now
wherever fine music is sold,
and you can watch them
again and again
at logotv.com.
Now, our next queen
strutted her stuff
all the way to the top.
Please give a big supermodel
welcome to Naomi Smalls.
♪ They tried to put me
on the cover of "Vogue," ♪
♪ But my legs were too long ♪
♪ Every day is leg day ♪
♪ Monday, Tuesday Wednesday ♪
♪ Thighs, calves,
all the way ♪
♪ Thursday, Friday,
Saturday ♪
♪ Sunday is the one day ♪
♪ I get on my runway ♪
♪ Ready for it, hunty? ♪
♪ I‘m legendary,
all legs, no dairy ♪
-♪ Legs, legs ♪
-♪ What‘s on the menu? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Legs. Legs, legs,
legs, legs ♪
♪ Legs ♪
♪ Every day is leg day ♪
♪ Never taking no break ♪
♪ Want this
chocolate milkshake? ♪
♪ Watch it
while your heart breaks ♪
♪ Sunday is the one day ♪
♪ I get on the runway ♪
♪ Ready for it, hunty? ♪
♪ I‘m legendary,
all legs, no dairy ♪
-♪ Legs, legs ♪
-♪ What‘s on the menu? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Legs ♪
♪ Linda, Naomi Smalls ♪
♪ Christie, Naomi Smalls. ♪
♪ Cindy, Naomi Smalls. ♪
♪ Claudia, Naomi Smalls. ♪
-♪ Legs, legs ♪
-♪ What‘s on the menu? ♪
♪ Legs ♪
[cheers and applause]
Wow.
Legs for days.
Okay, Naomi, let‘s talk
to the judges. Michelle Visage?
Honey, whatever‘s on the menu,
I‘m buying two.
Look how far
you‘ve come, honey,
and you have proven tonight
that you have legs up
on the competition.
Yes, you do.
You came, you saw,
you contoured,
and you conquered.
Yes.
Thank you, Naomi Smalls.
Now, as the youngest queen
to compete this season,
you‘ve come a long way,
baby.
Let‘s take a look.
I am Naomi Smalls.
Check your lipstick
before you come for me.
-[Naomi] Naomi has legs all
the way up to her asshole.
Naomi is a fashion girl.
She‘s fucking fierce.
Bitches better beware.
Oh, all of that right there.
I‘m giving you Naomi Campbell
strutting down
a Versace runway.
I just thought
it was perfection.
This is how you win
this competition.
I have eight brothers
and three sisters.
-Whoa.
-That is crazy.
This is my mom.
She‘s, like, the best mom ever.
Do you have a message
you want to say to your mother?
Thank you for everything
you‘ve ever done,
and I hope I can repay you
for the rest of my life.
I‘m Naomi Smalls,
and I promise
to represent you fiercely.
[cheers and applause]
Naomi, you have the fever
and the flavor for fashion.
Now, where does that come from?
I honestly don‘t know
because I grew up in, like,
a family
that was--sorry, guys,
not the most fashion-forward
or anything like that,
but I just remember,
like, looking at magazines
when I was a kid and just
being so obsessed with them,
and I wanted to look
like these amazing supermodels
-that were in the glossy pages.
-Sure, yeah.
Now, halfway through
the competition
you seemed to come to life.
What happened?
I was so scared
in the beginning
of standing out and--like,
for the wrong reasons,
but when it comes
to Snatch Game,
you can‘t hide anywhere,
and being in the bottom two
and having to lip
sync for my life
just put that fire
underneath my ass
to take chances and stand out
for all the right reasons.
-Yeah, you did really well.
-Thank you.
Now, Naomi,
we have a taped message
from one fierce queen.
Let‘s take a look.
Hi, Naomi.
Now, in Westeros
there‘s only room
for one queen,
but in Ru‘s queendom, girl,
I can‘t wait to see
you take that crown.
Now...Cersei that walk.
[cheers and applause]
-I love that.
-So good.
Now, we have some
fan questions.
G-G-G-Gia?
-Herminio from Mexico...
-Hi, Herminio.
Would like to know
how did it feel
when Naomi Campbell
checked you online?
[laughs] It was, like,
the biggest moment of my life.
What did she say?
Well, she followed me
on Instagram,
and then she had,
like, this interview saying,
"I really am loving that
Naomi Smalls," and I, like--
I love that.
Tell me this.
What would it mean to you
to become America‘s
next drag superstar?
It would mean
the world to me
to be America‘s
next drag superstar.
Just to get that
stamp of approval
from you and carry on
your legacy would be--
-[Crowd] Yeah, supermodel,
work!
The biggest goal
I ever met in my life.
I love it.
Now, before we go,
I want to say hello
to your mother.
Where is she?
She‘s right there.
- Would you--where--
Oh, there she is.
Hi.
So June,
what was it like
raising a leggy supermodel?
Well, I‘m a little shocked
that he didn‘t get
fashion tips from me.
I had no idea.
He has always been amazing.
-Really?
-Yes.
Did you buy the fashion
magazines, or did--
No, but I did start buying
the wigs and the shoes
and the--
[cheers and applause]
Now, besides Naomi,
how many kids did you raise?
-12 altogether.
-Wow.
Wow.
Naomi, where are
your other brothers
and sisters tonight?
Well, they‘re
all over the world.
They‘re actually
all over this theater too.
Well, let‘s bring them out,
the Von Trapp family singers.
[laughter]
Come on out.
Where are they?
Oh! Oh! How are you?
- Hi, sweetie.
- How are you?
-How are you?
-Ahh!
You know,
like I always say,
the family that drags together
slays together.
Let‘s hear it
for the legendary,
all legs, no dairy,
Naomi Smalls.
Now, we‘re just moments
away from crowning
America‘s next drag superstar,
but first it‘s time
to bring back my girls.
[cheers and applause]
Starting with a nerdy bird,
a glam rock rebel,
and one cuckoo queen.
My name is
Dax ExclamationPoint.
What‘s up, nerds?
-[Dax] My look is very
inspired by, like, science
fiction
and comics,
strong, bad bitches
who don‘t take any crap
from anybody else.
Show me your
exclamation point.
Yeah!
All right, ladies,
let‘s turn up the juice
and see what shakes loose.
Laila is,
like, a whory quasi--
I don‘t want to say gothy,
but, like, gothy.
-[Tyler] My biggest concern is
that I‘m gonna
fade into the background.
I‘m here too.
Dax ExclamationPoint,
Laila McQueen,
neither one of you
survived that lip sync.
Sashay away.
-[Dax] Both of us?
Really?
How you doing,
mis amores?
My name is Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
Do you want to see my cuckoo?
Cuckoo.
I need a space
for this junk in the trunk.
-[Cynthia] I‘m sexy as a
goddess is.
I‘m funny as a clown.
♪ I am sickening ♪
[record scratches]
Did my teeth look yellow?
No.
[cheers and applause]
Dax ExclamationPoint
and Laila McQueen, welcome back.
-Hello.
-Hey, Ru.
So Dax, I hear that the song
"I Will Survive"
is haunting you
everywhere you go.
-Is that true?
-Yes,
like, literally everywhere I go,
like, it could be a gas station,
grocery store, anywhere,
it just happens to come on.
Listen, if I were you two,
I would seize the moment.
I would record another song.
I would s--call it
"I Didn‘t Survive."
You know?
It‘d be a huge hit.
But seriously, there are
no losers on "Drag Race."
Dax, what‘s life been like
since you were on the show?
Honestly, life
has been absolutely amazing.
Like, the fans
have been phenomenal.
I mean, obviously, like,
I don‘t have as many fans as,
like, you know, Kim Chi
or Bob or Naomi.
That‘s fine.
It‘s fine,
but the ones
I do have are phenomenal.
Now, I‘ve got a confession
to make.
Laila McQueen
and I have a secret past.
I deny it, but there‘s proof.
Take a look.
[groans]
That little pixie to the right
of me is Laila McQueen
when I was not
running for president
in Manchester, New Hampshire.
You know, my grandmother
calls you Ron Paul.
[laughter]
Now, did you ever
imagine at that point
that you would be on this stage?
Oh, absolutely not.
I mean, I was performing in,
like, function halls
and Mexican restaurants.
Like, I never imagined being
here or anywhere else
around the world.
So now, what‘s happened
to you because of "Drag Race"?
I get to go everywhere
and meet the people
that love the work I do
and embrace so much love
that I never thought
I would see.
All that at the truck stop?
[laughter]
So Dax, Laila,
you aren‘t just surviving.
-You are thriving.
-Thank you.
Next up,
straight from Santee Alley,
Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
Now, since the show,
you‘ve been through it,
haven‘t you, girl?
Yes, actually the episode
that I been eliminated,
I was experience symptoms.
I‘m here to celebrate that.
-Wow.
-Yes.
And how do you feel right now?
I‘m in the discharge process
already right now,
so I feel amazing.
-I feel fantastic.
-Good. Yeah.
Did any of your drag sisters
reach out to you?
Yes, one special person,
and it‘s Acid Betty.
- That Acid Betty?
- That Acid Betty.
Yeah, Acid Betty.
She came to visit me as soon
as she knew
that I was diagnosed.
She was taking care of me.
She was like, "Bitch,
you‘re not alone.
I got your back."
I think the positive attitude
from all my entire
new sisterhood
helped me to recovery
and helped me
to be more positive every day.
Wow.
I love it.
Well, Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
we are cuckoo for your cuckoo.
Thank you.
Now a queen
who always picks up when I call
and a badass
in total control of herself.
Let‘s take a look.
The beauty is here.
My name is Naysha Lopez.
I spend money.
I don‘t do drag on a dime.
Naysha Lopez, sashay away.
How soon can you get here?
Bitches, I‘m back!
Face, body, glamour.
Your ass is real?
Yes. Realness, boo.
This acid trip is all real.
My drag style is completely over
the top, punk unicorn realness.
The main bullet point
of Acid Betty is she‘s a bitch.
I‘m not gonna be unprepared
because of you, boo.
Acid Betty,
you‘ve taken us
on one wild trip.
Now, Naysha Lopez, Michelle
and I have a running bet, okay?
That ass of yours, is it real?
So listen, Ru, I--
[laughter]
I eat well.
I work out.
I have 10 ccs
of medical grade silicon.
I--no.
[laughter]
So on the show
you said your ass was real.
My ass is real.
However, have I had
some enhancements
to the body-ody-ody?
-Yeah.
-Yes, I have.
Ah.
[laughing]
Now, you missed
the Madonna runway storyline.
- Yes.
- What would you have worn?
I‘m a very creative person,
and what I had going on
was another kimono.
What?
What is it with these queens
and kimonos?
Naysha, thanks for gracing us
with your gorgeous beauty
and that booty twice.
Yes.
Next, Acid Betty.
Now, are you really here,
or am I having a flashback?
Now, you turned out some killer
looks this season.
-[crowd whooping]
-Thank you.
How have fans been to you?
I love the fans.
They are the best, the best.
The best thing
of this show are the fans.
The love is so intense,
and it‘s wonderful.
I actually had a kid
that I met at DragCon,
and they decided that
they were gonna go into fashion
and got a full
scholarship to FIDM
because of seeing me
on the TV show.
-Wow. Wow.
-That‘s really great.
Now, Acid Betty,
you took a lot of heat
for your Nancy Grace
impersonation,
but some people really,
really liked it.
Take a look.
Acid Betty,
I loved watching you be me,
but frankly,
speaking professionally,
you got a raw deal.
You were robbed.
No tea, no shade,
but unleash the lawyers.
We got a case here.
-That‘s fierce.
-I love it.
Aci, I could go
on talking to you all night,
but I refuse
to say anything further
until I lawyer up.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Acid Betty.
Now, the best way to describe
our next three queens
is brassy, Brooklyn,
and Britney, bitch.
Good morning.
My name is Robbie Turner,
and I‘m the kindest queen
you‘ll ever meet.
♪ I want you to be hot
and saucy ♪
♪ ♪
-Yes, Marilyn.
-She‘s in a league of her own.
I would wear the hell
out of that jumpsuit.
-Oh!
Too real?
Whoo! Thorgy
with a T-H and orgy,
and I feel incredible.
I‘m colorful.
I‘m fun,
and I‘m a fashion clown.
This is harder on me
than it is for you guys.
No, it‘s not.
-[Thorgy] I can be campy,
but also I can be,
like, fucking fierce.
I‘m so proud of you.
Great job.
Yes!
It‘d Derrick, bitch.
-[Derrick] I may look angelic,
but I am not that innocent.
I also have a career
with my wigs on.
You‘ll have a career once
you start gluing yours down.
You have to give us more.
That is not a Britney reference.
-Oh!
That‘s how you go out
in style, girls.
Now, Robbie Turner,
how does someone so young know
so much about classic Hollywood?
My mother and father
wouldn‘t allow us to watch
contemporary films,
so we watched
classic Hollywood films
all the time, so I thought
they were contemporary.
So you can imagine
little baby Robbie
when she‘s like, "Judy Garland
died many moons ago,"
and it‘s like, "What?"
Now, what was your favorite
moment on the show?
On my birthday
I won the singing challenge
with the le chicken wings,
and Debbie Harry came back
and said happy birthday to me.
I‘m like, um,
I don‘t see the problem
with this birthday at all--
"Drag Race,"
Debbie, chicken wings.
[laughter]
Robbie, thank you so much
for all the classic sass.
Oh, and by the way,
I will be sending you a bill
for that broken light bulb
that you did.
Uh-huh.
Up next, hey, there,
Thorgy girl.
Hey, Ru.
Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
Now, like Michelle and I,
you and Bob
have a very complicated
relationship.
Tell me about it.
I love to argue
and fight about everything.
I love it.
There‘s always a way
to tear things apart
and make them better.
Bob can take it from me.
He‘ll just listen
to me talk and go,
"I still don‘t like you."
[laughter]
But when people see me
and Bob doing that,
they‘re like, "Oh, you guys
really don‘t like each other."
I‘m like, "I just love
fighting with him so much,"
but I‘m just in love
with Bob very much.
Now, you have dreams
of starting a thorchestra?
-Is that right?
-Yeah.
What is a--what‘s
a thorchestra?
Well,
ever since I was playing violin
and then I got into,
like, the art of drag,
I wanted to conduct, like,
a 40-piece orchestra.
I wanted to travel the world.
I want, like, Rufus Wainwright
to wheel out on a piano
and be like, "Oh,
my friend Rufus
is here to sing a song."
That‘s a great idea.
Will you play a little something
for us right now?
Sure.
Oh, my God!
[laughter]
[gentle melody]
♪ ♪
[high notes]
[cheers and applause]
Thank you, guys.
Well, Thorgy,
I cannot wait to see
what you‘re gonna do next.
Whoo!
Up next, the 100th queen
to prance into
my workroom--
♪ Hey, Derrick ♪
Whoo!
Now, you struggled to get
out of the Britney box,
-as it was called.
-Yes.
What‘s your relationship
with Britney now?
I will always do Britney.
I‘m not leaving that behind.
Of course I wanted
to come on the show
to expand what I already do
and take it to the next level,
and I feel like not only can I
do Britney now, I can do drag.
I‘m doing drag right now.
Now, Derrick,
throughout the season
you were not afraid
to speak your mind loudly,
especially with Bob and Naomi.
You have any regrets about that?
Everything?
Oh, gosh, it‘s hard
because I watch it back,
I‘m like, "Oh, wow,
I shouldn‘t have said that.
Probably shouldn‘t have had
that drink and untucked,"
[laughter]
and yes,
I have a hard time
taking criticism
because I‘ve never been
criticized like that before.
Doing Britney was
what I‘ve always done,
and I was praised for that,
and now coming
into this competition
it was almost looked down
upon that that was something
that I was known to do.
And I learned so much
from Naomi,
and she taught me
how to block my brows,
and I think I‘m doing it now.
Thank you, Derrick,
and I will always think of you
as my genie in a bottle.
Yes, I know
that‘s a Christina song,
but I‘ve run
out of Britney references!
-Give me a break.
-Yes.
We love you, Derrick Barry.
[laughing]
Now, we are moments
away from finding out
if Bob The Drag Queen, Kim Chi,
or Naomi Smalls will be crowned
America‘s next drag superstar,
but first the queen
who has turned this season
on its head.
Let‘s take a look.
Laissez les bon temps roulez.
My name is Chi Chi DeVayne,
and I don‘t get ready.
I stay ready.
[snapping]
-[Chi Chi] My drag is that
real southern dragged out style
of drag.
Prove to us
that you‘re a champion.
Not only have you guys
taught me how to be
a better entertainer,
but you have taught me
how to be a better person,
and $100,000 cannot buy that.
[snaps]
Yes, Louisiana glamour.
When you came to "Drag Race,"
you had quit two jobs
to be on the show.
How many jobs do you have now?
I have one job, Ru,
and I‘m a full-time drag queen!
That‘s what‘s up.
How do fans
react when they meet you?
Oh, my God, first time in
New York, I‘m in Times Square,
and the shortest little
Hispanic woman
stopped me in the street,
and she just instantly
start crying.
-Wow.
-She explained it to me
that I represented
all of the people
in the world to her
that are out there
struggling to make ends meet
and who have a dream,
and the dream has come true.
Dreams come true, y‘all.
Dreams come true.
And speaking of dreams,
the "Dreamgirls" lip sync
that you did,
oh, honey,
that was legendary,
and I‘m not the only one
who thought so.
Take a look at this.
You, Miss Chi Chi DeVayne,
are a true inspiration.
I tell you
that your heartfelt rendition
of "And I‘m Telling You"
moved me,
and honey, when those bees
start flying right
after you and I hit
our high note, honey,
you gave me life,
and I‘m gonna make you
an official Dreamgirl.
[cheers and applause]
Do you have anything else
you‘d like to say?
Thank you from the bottom
of my heart.
You have changed
my life forever.
Thank you.
You made my dreams come true.
That is the sweetest thing.
I really appreciate that.
I‘ve been watching you
for a long time,
and to have you finally
on the show is really my honor.
All right, now it‘s time
to announce the winner
of this year‘s
Miss Congeniality.
All the way from Moscow
by way of Boston
and a pit stop in Pacoima,
it‘s Katya.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[laughter]
[music resumes]
♪ ♪
-Hi, Katya.
-Hi, Ru.
Hey, listen,
I brought you some water.
Are you thirsty?
So Katya,
what have you been up to?
Oh, my God,
what haven‘t I been up to?
Listen, I learned
horseback riding.
I‘ve been doing macrame.
I visited, like, 6
out of the 12 continents
in the world.
It‘s been a whirlwind.
It‘s been a--
All right, yeah, well,
is there something
you want to tell me?
I mean--
- I--well, okay, yeah,
I‘m not technically bisexual.
I mean, I‘m open.
I‘m open--
No, no, no, no, n--no.
No, no,
I am open--listen, I am--
I‘m talking about
what you came out here for.
You remember?
You came--
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
-Oh, look at this thing. Okay.
-Yeah.
Oh, yeah, hold--will you hold
this water for me please?
Yeah, sure.
The winner of season eight
Miss Congeniality
and a cash prize of $5,000...
-[audience whoops]
-Yup.
Courtesy of the all-new
Fiat 500x crossover
is...
Cynthia Lee Fontaine!
♪ ♪
Cynthia, is there anything
you‘d like to say?
This is very important for me
because experiencing cancer
give me the opportunity
just only to be
stronger than ever
and represent my community
the best that I can,
and the only way
that we can do that is funny
and showing the cuckoo
to the world.
[laughter]
Thank you, RuPaul, so very much.
-Thank you.
-Thank you to my sisters.
And thanks
to all of you for voting.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
All rise for your top three--
Bob The Drag Queen...
["The Realness" plays]
Kim Chi...
♪ Real is what you feel ♪
Naomi Smalls.
♪ Put your money down ♪
♪ Place your bet
and spin the wheel ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The realness ♪
There are only eight people
on earth
that know what it feels like
to be the winner of
"RuPaul‘s Drag Race,"
and they‘re all here tonight
to share their words of wisdom.
Welcome back my champions.
BeBe Zahara Benet.
Cameroon welcomes you
to the royal family, darling.
Remember, always give them
face, face, face,
and more face.
Tyra Sanchez.
Be the biggest,
baddest bitch of them all,
a royal bitch.
Love, America‘s sweetheart.
Raja.
In the prophetic words
of a wise mystic,
express yourself.
It is now your duty
to honor a divine legacy
and to leave an indelible
imprint on herstory.
Sharon Needles.
My advice?
Just be yourself.
Well,
unless nobody likes you.
In that case, just be Alaska.
Chad Michaels.
Snap out of it, ladies.
Just do you,
or when in doubt,
just do Cher, bitch.
Jinkx Monsoon.
When the bitches
come for you,
murder them with kindness,
and don‘t forget,
the best thing
about monsoon season
is it happens annually.
[laughs]
Bianca Del Rio.
I‘ve got some advice
for this year‘s winner.
Enjoy the ride,
and pay your damn taxes.
Right, Sharon?
Jinkx?
Raja?
And America‘s reigning
drag superstar,
Violet Chachki.
♪ I‘m telling, I‘m telling ♪
♪ I‘m telling the truth now ♪
♪ We‘re all born naked
and the rest is drag ♪
♪ I‘ll say it again ♪
♪ It‘s never been
the clothes that make the man ♪
♪ Nothing can ♪
♪ Leave all your baggage
behind ♪
♪ And I said I‘m telling,
I‘m telling ♪
♪ I‘m telling the truth now ♪
♪ I‘m telling, I‘m telling,
I‘m telling the truth now ♪
♪ I‘m telling, I‘m telling ♪
♪ I‘m telling the truth now ♪
♪ We‘re all born naked,
and the rest is drag ♪
Wow.
Violet,
what has your year been like?
My year has been incredible.
I‘ve worked with some of
the best people in the industry,
the fashion world,
the burlesque world,
the art world.
I‘ve gotten validation,
people that I respected for
years and years and years,
so it‘s been the most personally
gratifying year of my life.
I am so thankful to RuPaul,
all the fans.
Thank you from the bottom
of my heart.
I love you guys.
Thank you, Violet.
Now, in addition to the title
of America‘s
next drag superstar,
the winner of
"RuPaul‘s Drag Race"
will receive a crown and scepter
provided by Fierce Drag Jewels,
a sickening supply of makeup
from Anastasia Beverly Hills,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
[cheers and applause]
Now, the time has come
to crown our queen.
Bob The Drag Queen,
Kim Chi, Naomi Smalls.
As always, I‘ve consulted
with the judges and the fans,
but the final decision
is mine to make.
The winner of
"RuPaul‘s Drag Race,"
America‘s next drag superstar
is...
[suspenseful music]
Bob The Drag Queen.
♪ If I dream
everything I wanna be ♪
all the possibilities ♪
♪ If you just believe ♪
♪ In your wildest dreams,
they will come true ♪
♪ They will come true ♪
My queen, is there anything
you have to say?
-Yes.
-I have too much to say,
but I‘m gonna keep it
to one thing.
Take whatever you love
about yourself,
and walk
into the world purse first!
♪ If I dream
everything I wanna be ♪
all the possibilities ♪
♪ If you just believe ♪
♪ In your wildest dreams,
they will come true ♪
♪ They will come true ♪
Listen,
if you can‘t love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get a amen up in here?
-[all] Amen!
All right,
now let the music play!
♪ If I dream
everything I wanna be ♪
all the possibilities ♪
♪ If you just believe ♪
♪ In your wildest dreams,
they will come true ♪
♪ They will come true ♪