Previously
on "RuPaul‘s Drag Race"...
We‘re having a Book Ball.
Ooh.
Am I the first person
who‘s ever said
anything like this,
ever, to you?
That has said my makeup
is not good?
I didn‘t say
your makeup‘s not good.
It‘s just not drag.
[dramatic music]
When‘s dinner?
Bob The Drag Queen.
I am not getting "book"
at all.
I‘m getting "cardboard."
Well,
I‘m still wearing books.
I‘m just not wearing pages.
Okay.
Derrick Barry.
I don‘t know
that you‘re at this level.
I have seen what you‘ve done
with your eyebrows,
but it‘s going to be a journey.
Kim Chi.
I felt something
from each look
and couldn‘t wait
for you to come out.
It was the artistry
I expect from you.
You are the winner
of this week‘s challenge.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
Bob The Drag Queen,
shantay, you stay.
Derrick Barry,
sashay away.
Derrick.
[applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[laughing]
Ooh, my goodness.
All right, girl.
Oh, my God, Derrick‘s message
is actually surprisingly short.
She‘s a champ.
I like her a lot.
I didn‘t think I would like her,
and I ended up
really liking her.
-Yeah, me too.
-I did too.
Long live Britney.
I got to say,
being in the bottom two
-is an experience.
-Mm.
Bottom two,
not a cute look.
I feel like there‘s a dent
in my armor now,
but it‘s time to pick myself up
by my wig straps
and get back in the game.
Congratulations, Kim.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
I finally won.
-(Him Chi)I feel really good
about how well I‘ve done,
but I can‘t be too secure,
because people who won
the challenge the week before
have gone home,
so no one is safe.
The judges told me
I have to work on being ugly,
and I don‘t think I know
how to do that.
Can you make an ugly face
right now for us?
Can you smudge your makeup?
Like, just rub your hand
across your...
Okay, ready?
Take the lashes off first.
That‘s too far.
See?
Here I come.
[exclaiming]
Wait a minute now.
[laughing]
There you go.
Be ugly, G.
Top freakin‘...
all: Four.
You know how close we are?
Mad close.
Major.
So now that it‘s the top four,
the stakes are fucking high.
Yes, we‘re all friends,
but unfortunately,
someone has to go home.
This is a competition,
and I want to be
in the top three.
♪ ♪
Bring it on.
[car engine starts]
♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
The winner
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
♪ Everyone can ♪
♪ Be someone ♪
[all cheering]
-Top four.
-Yes.
It‘s the final challenge,
and Ru told us to show up
in full face
and be ready
to hit the ground running.
Surprise, my top four.
-God.
-Oh.
I didn‘t know you bitches
woke up like this.
I want you to meet
director Jayson Whitmore.
Hello, ladies.
-Hi, Jason.
-Hey, Jason.
Now, Jason has worked
with some of the best
drag queens in the world,
like Alaska,
Adore Delano,
Kim Kardashian...
[laughs]
And now it‘s your turn.
For your final Maxi Challenge,
you‘ll star
in the official music video
for "The Realness."
Yes.
I‘m a video ho.
Goals.
♪ ♪
When it comes
to a music video,
it‘s not Kim Chi‘s forte.
I really hope that she can rise
to the challenge.
To not make it
into the top three with Kim...
it would just suck.
Now, Jason‘s vision
includes color,
fashion, mirrors, smoke, drama.
Well, basically, just a day
in your normal life.
[laughs]
Y‘all need to serve
some #Top3Realness,
because the queen
who gets eliminated tomorrow
will be edited out
of the final video
forever.
Yes, forever.
Churl...
I want to be in the top three.
You can‘t be America‘s
next drag superstar
if you‘re not in the video.
So, Jason, I leave my girls‘
charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
in your capable hands.
Just keep in mind, we don‘t
have a whole lot of time,
so we need to get through
our takes really quick, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
All right.
It‘s so important to do well
in this challenge,
because this is going to be
the determining factor
if you‘re going to be
America‘s next drag superstar.
♪ ♪
[upbeat club music]
Hi.
So now it‘s time to shoot
our first video segment
with Jason.
I love being in front
of the camera,
so I‘m super excited
for our music video.
Ladies, welcome to set.
This setup is going to be
all about float-ography.
You guys are required
to serve up a tight lip sync
while you appear
like you‘re floating on air.
You‘re gonna be playing
to the overhead camera
while you‘re lying
on your backs.
Up first, Naomi Smalls.
I‘m looking for the queens
to feel light and airy.
They have to pay attention
to the fabric
and looking really,
really beautiful
while they‘re floating
back into space.
Float-ography.
Action.
You‘re falling
into this whole fantasy world
that Ru is taking you to.
Give me those legs.
Oh, beautiful.
I want those nice, beautiful,
gorgeous long legs.
Cut, cut, cut.
Naomi, we want to
really watch those legs, okay?
Okay, so, like,
out like this, straight?
But we don‘t want it
to look like you‘re a board,
so use your abs
so it‘s more like this, right?
-Okay.
-So it‘s pretty, okay?
Uh-oh, she got to work out.
-(Naomi)I‘m starting to freak
out,
because my ridiculously
long legs
aren‘t floating,
and I can barely hold myself up.
Manual labor is not my thing.
[laughs]
And action.
♪ Put your money down ♪
Yeah, that pose is perfect.
Keep that pose.
Yes, love that.
♪ Put your money down,
place your bet ♪
♪ And spin the wheel ♪
All right, and cut.
Great job, Naomi.
It‘s awesome.
Thanks.
[grunts]
Bob, just remember
you‘re floating in air.
I am, like, dangling
off this thing.
And action.
♪ Catch it, touch it,
touch it, catch it ♪
♪ Flavor of this fever ♪
♪ The realness ♪
Don‘t put your legs like that.
It‘s not pretty.
Okay.
Ooh.
This shit is not easy.
I am fucking sweating.
I‘m going from looking
like Viola Davis
to looking like Patrick Ewing.
This shit is not cute.
Ooh.
Chi Chi, remember,
you‘re top four.
Lot of energy, face.
Mm-hmm.
[laughing]
And action.
♪ Put your money down ♪
Gorgeous.
Beautiful.
You‘re falling
into the world, yes.
I love that.
♪ The realness ♪
Your legs look stunning.
Love ‘em.
Chi Chi is doing great.
I was like, "Fuck you,
you fucking fit
prison trade bitch.
♪ The realness ♪
All right, so, Kim Chi,
you better turnt it out.
The hardest part about
this challenge is definitely
moving, period.
Action.
♪ Feelings aren‘t real ♪
♪ Put your money down ♪
Make sure you look
towards the camera, love.
♪ Feelings aren‘t real ♪
Find the camera, girl.
♪ Place your bet
and spin the wheel ♪
All right, cut.
-Hey, Kim Chi?
-Yes?
I‘m getting a lot of chin,
and I‘m not getting
a lot of face,
and I really would love it
to be, like, very graceful,
like you‘re falling
into this whole other world.
-Okay.
-And action.
♪ The, the realness ♪
Give me surprise.
Give me grace.
Kim Chi looks like a fucking
upside-down turtle.
Help.
[chuckling]
Watch those legs.
I‘m trying to give good face.
Keep the legs moving.
But as the clock ticks on,
it just gets harder and harder
to keep my legs up.
There you go.
♪ Gonna move into the house ♪
What--oh, shit!
[dramatic music]
Oh, shit!
Whoa, is she okay?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Drag queen down.
I‘m fine.
Classic Kim Chi.
She‘s fallen more than anyone
in Drag Race history.
♪ ♪
Sorry.
Oh, my goodness.
Poor Kim Chi.
I don‘t know, girl.
Your makeup might not save you
on this one.
All right, that‘s a wrap
on the float-ography.
Quick change, and I‘ll meet
you guys back here on the set.
♪ ♪
[upbeat techno music]
-Hi.
-Wow, welcome.
Look at you.
-(Chi Chi)It‘s time for our
second take of the video,
and it‘s avant-garde.
I have no idea
what avant-garde is,
but I‘ma do my damnedest.
This is actually going to be
all about you performing.
Avant-garde for the music video
is all about self-expression,
movement, face,
and art.
And action.
♪ ♪
♪ The realness ♪
More energy.
♪ ♪
Okay, cut.
Bob, you‘re at a five.
I want you at a ten.
Can you give me a little bit
more comedy, please?
Okay.
♪ I know what I feel ♪
Yes, love that.
♪ What I feel is real ♪
[chuckling]
Work it.
♪ Home, no, no ♪
♪ The realness ♪
Yes.
You did it, girl.
[laughing]
Yeah!
That was great.
All right, Kim Chi, you‘re up.
She‘s so cute.
Kim Chi‘s avant-garde look
is like
Colonel Sanders is about to
cut her head off
and pluck and fry her ass.
She look like a spring chicken.
And action.
♪ If real is what you feel ♪
Yes.
♪ Feelings aren‘t real ♪
Ooh, I love that.
With attitude for days, please.
♪ It‘s real ♪
Yes.
♪ The realness ♪
Beautiful.
All right, Naomi.
And action.
♪ Feelings aren‘t real ♪
Yes, mama, work it.
Whoo, sorry.
Okay, cut, cut, cut.
Let‘s do that again, girl.
Come on, Kim Chi.
Who can‘t walk
in heels now, bitch?
Action.
-♪ If real is what you feel ♪
-Yes.
♪ Feelings aren‘t real ♪
♪ Put your money down ♪
♪ Place your bet
and spin the wheel ♪
Oh, give me those legs
for days, girl.
Naomi‘s very mesmerizing
to watch.
Like, every pose she strikes
is very perfect.
-♪ The realness ♪
-Yes.
♪ The, the realness ♪
Paris is burning right now.
♪ Flavor of this fever ♪
Whoo.
Give me Ru fever glam.
Now, that is how you do it.
All right, Chi Chi,
you‘re up next.
And action.
♪ It‘s real ♪
-Yes.
-♪ It‘s real ♪
Little bit more dance.
Yeah, love it.
Yes, bitch.
♪ ♪
Okay, cut, cut, cut.
Let‘s untangle Chi Chi
from her gown.
♪ ♪
-Chi Chi?
-Mm-hmm?
Have you danced
in gowns before?
No.
Okay, well,
we better learn quick.
-Okay.
-And action.
-Bam.
-♪ Put your money down ♪
-Ah.
Give me fierce,
fierce avant-garde.
And pose.
Pull your dress up.
-Pull your dress up.
-All right, let‘s cut.
Let‘s cut, cut, cut, cut.
We got a wardrobe
malfunction again.
Again?
Fuck!
Like, I am the dancing diva
of "Drag Race,"
and this frickin‘ gown
it‘s pissing me off.
Okay, cut.
Ladies, we have one more setup.
Go get changed,
and I‘ll see you in a few.
♪ ♪
Bob, this is a scene
with your biggest competitor:
you and the mirror.
And action.
♪ Gonna move into the house ♪
-♪ Gonna move into the house ♪
-We‘re loving that.
-♪ Ain‘t never going home ♪
-Serving glamour.
♪ ♪
Give me fierce.
[laughs]
Yes.
Bob‘s glamour look
is really interesting.
His right hand looks like
he fisted a coal mine,
and his left hand looks like
he fisted a gold mine.
♪ Put your money down ♪
♪ Place your bet
and spin the wheel ♪
♪ ♪
Yes, work it.
Glamour.
♪ If real is what you feel ♪
-Fierce.
-♪ Feelings aren‘t real ♪
-Ooh, that‘s cool.
Then you see something
in the mirror.
[chuckling]
♪ I know what I feel ♪
Gorg.
Loving it.
We‘re feeling you.
And pose.
♪ It‘s real ♪
Perfect.
And cut.
Okay, we got it.
That‘s a wrap, guys.
That‘s a wrap.
[claps]
What‘s done is done.
Now it‘s up to Ru.
Judge, jury, and executioner.
All right, that‘s a wrap
on "The Realness," ladies.
-It was incredible.
-Excuse me, excuse me.
-Coming through.
-Oh, God.
Coming through.
-Perhaps you can help me.
-Okay.
I‘m here for the photo shoot,
the past winners‘ photo shoot.
[all laughing]
Oh, shit, Tyra,
you look horrible.
[laughing]
And Jinkx got a tan.
And you must be that sweet thing
that won season seven, right?
Whatever--oh, fuck.
This is season eight.
Bye.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
What the fuck?
[laughs]
Damn, bitch, you about
ten episodes late.
Where the fuck you been?
Is there no security
on the goddamn lot?
♪ Give your all ♪
♪ So what if you fall? ♪
all: It‘s the last day
of school.
Sign my yearbook, everyone.
It‘s our final day
in the workroom,
and it feels like
it‘s our last day of school,
and we‘re finding out who‘s
gonna get valedictorian
or something.
What do each of you think
you‘ve learned
about yourself
throughout the competition?
I‘ve learned that apparently,
I can come off as very arrogant,
but I attribute it
to confidence.
-(Bob)I‘ve not always been
this confident.
I was like
a little chunky kid.
I was really effeminate.
I had really dark skin,
and kids can be mean to you,
so once I found out
what I was good at
and I really embraced it,
people started to like me.
Find something about you
that you like,
and focus on that.
If I don‘t like my face,
if I don‘t like my skin,
if I don‘t like my weight,
but I think to myself,
"I have nice teeth,"
and it may just start
with one tooth.
"Look at that tooth.
That‘s a nice tooth, man."
And then once you can accept
that little thing
about yourself,
you can just accept you
for who you are.
I‘ve learned
that I can‘t walk in heels.
I can‘t dance,
and I have a lisp.
[laughs]
To be honest,
you could be overweight,
you could have a lisp,
you could have jacked-up teeth,
but you too can turn it around.
You know, people just, like,
like me for who I am
and I shouldn‘t try to be
anybody else.
First impression of Kim Chi,
I thought she was
very talented,
‘cause I already knew of Kim Chi
before I got here,
so I was, like,
already impressed
with her, and...
And then all that changed.
No, but, like, Kim is amazing.
Aww, you‘re amazing.
I was a huge fan of Kim Chi
before I came here,
and now she‘s one
of my best friends here.
She‘s, like, a big,
lovable panda.
I really don‘t know another way
to explain it.
DeVayne.
I--I didn‘t realize
how much I hated
where I was from
and how I talk.
I never, ever thought
I was funny.
Like, I never realized
all of that until I got here.
That‘s why I think you‘ve
grown the most, honestly.
-Yeah.
-This is why.
My journey in this competition
has been up and down.
Making the top three would be
a dream come true.
This means a whole lot to me.
I need to stop comparing
myself to others
and just appreciate what I have,
because what I have is amazing,
and I just need to own it.
I don‘t need to be doing
death drops
and stand-up comedy.
But you know who does
death drops?
Bob.
-[laughter]
-Known for her death drops.
I really did find myself here.
That‘s, like, the best prize,
and I‘m so proud of myself.
[upbeat music]
And probably all of y‘all
I do not want to go home.
I do not want to go home,
either.
I just hate the fucking food
in California.
It‘s gross.
Whole Food and bullshit.
It‘s so good.
Kim, you like all the food
in the world.
-I mean
-♪ All of the food ♪
♪ Of the world ♪
♪ All of the food ♪
♪ In all of the ♪
♪ People are going,
Oh, remember your egg rolls? ♪
[laughing]
While y‘all talking about me
eating turkey necks,
this bitch Kim Chi says she eats
fried chicken buttholes.
It‘s good.
I‘m kind of grossed out.
Yeah, that‘s gross, now.
You eat people‘s butthole.
Why is chicken any different?
[all laughing]
Touché, Kimberly.
Touché.
And those motherfuckers
are undercooked!
[all laughing]
♪ ♪
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And what? ♪
[laughing]
Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race."
Tonight, it‘s just family.
This week, we challenged
our top four queens
to star in the official
music video
of my song, "The Realness,"
and tonight, they‘re ready
to make us gag,
decked out in their
very best drag.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
♪ ♪
♪ The realness ♪
Up first, Bob The Drag Queen.
Not to be confused
with Bob the barista.
No foam.
This is it.
-(Bob)This is the final runway,
so I wanted to wear a tuxedo
and do a feminine version
of it,
so I‘m wearing this crazy,
sequined jacket.
This is quintessential
Bob The Drag Queen.
Tell me about it, stud.
[laughing]
Mrs. PG.
Pass it on.
Up next, Chi Chi DeVayne.
-Miss DeVayne, if you‘re nasty.
-Uh-huh.
Serving opulence.
She owns everything.
-(Chi Chi)I‘m going full-on
pageant.
I have big buns on my head.
To me, it just screams
"best drag."
I‘m trying to show the judges
that I‘ve gotten over
all of these obstacles
that I have gone through,
and I am worthy of this.
Oh, which way are you going?
-[mouthing] That way.
-Oh, that way.
Apparently, she goes
both ways.
Oh!
-Kisses.
-Mm.
If you like it, then you
should‘ve put a bun on it.
Okay, are you ready
for Kim Chi?
I‘m hungry.
Magnificent Maleficent.
-That‘s a cock-a-doodle-doo.
-[laughing]
-(Kim Chi)I‘m wearing a feather
corset
covered in goose
and pheasant feathers,
and I‘m feeling like
a dark, evil princess
who came here to destroy
my competition.
She‘s working that walk,
Michelle.
-She is.
-Mm-hmm.
Only took till the finale.
Well, kimchi gets better
with a little time.
It does;
it‘s--actually,
usually the next day,
it tastes a lot better.
-Yeah.
-[laughing]
"The Raven," Edgar Allan Ho.
Ha ha ha!
Are you ready
for Naomi Smalls?
Ooh, dark lady.
The notorious Twiggy Smalls.
-Uh-huh.
-Yes.
Well, she‘s also serving
a little Kendall Jenner.
She is, yeah.
-(Naomi)I am showing the judges
that I‘m not relying on sequins
and rhinestones
to zhuzh up my outfit.
This is Naomi Smalls glamour
to a T.
I refuse to blend in.
I want to be the star.
The beat goes on,
and so do those legs.
Thanks for Cher-ing.
[as Cher] Yes, gypsies,
tramps, and weaves.
♪ Realness ♪
Ladies, here
at "RuPaul‘s Drag Race,"
we have the luxury
of celebrating who we are,
but we must never forget
that even today, there are
little boys and girls
who feel they don‘t fit in.
So I want you to turn back time
and share the wisdom
you have today
with the child you were then.
So Bob The Drag Queen...
-[laughing]
-Aww.
-This is you...
-That is me.
-At four years old.
-Yeah.
What do you have to say
to little Christopher?
I say, "Hey, girl."
I would tell myself, "You‘re
gonna want to change for others.
Do not do that."
I just wanted to be like
my brother or like my uncles.
I was so different than
every other guy in my family.
I just wanted to blend in
and be like them,
but once I realized how
important it really is
to be me,
then I really shone through.
And I would also say,
"Don‘t take out
that student loan
-freshman year of college."
-[laughs]
"Just pay out of pocket
like you did the rest of it,"
because it‘s still haunting me
to this day.
Thank you, Bob.
All right, Chi Chi DeVayne,
this is you at six years old.
What do you have to say
to little Zavion?
I would tell
little Zavion Davenport
that "It doesn‘t matter
where you‘re from
"and how you grew up,
"the neighborhood
you grew up in.
"That has nothing to do
with how far you can go.
"Never be ashamed
of how you walk, talk,
because that is going to be
the key to your success."
Very sweet.
-Thank you, Chi Chi.
-Thank you.
Kim Chi, this is you
at three years old.
Aww.
What do you have to say
to little Sang?
"Hi, Sang,
when you grow up,
"you‘re going to experience
a lot of different cultures.
"People might shame you
for being too different
"and not fitting in
with the rest of the culture.
"At times, you‘re gonna
feel like
"you‘re trapped
in the wrong body,
"and you‘re trapped in a place
where you feel like
[crying] "you can‘t get out,
and you
"at times, you‘re gonna want to
think about harming yourself
"or even running away.
"But I just wanted
to let you know
"that it will all get better,
"and once you grow up,
"the things
that you are ashamed of
are going to be the truth
that other people love you for."
-And...
-It‘s all right, baby.
"And you‘re gonna be able
to embrace them.
"You‘re gonna find a group
of friends who‘s gonna love you.
"You‘re not going to feel
lonely anymore,
"and what you thought
was all just a dream
"will come true for you,
because life will get better."
[crying]
Lovely.
Kim Chi, you didn‘t just
get better.
You got fierce.
♪ ♪
"Oh, and go to a dancing class
as soon as possible."
Ha ha!
"You will really regret it
if you don‘t."
[all laughing]
All right, Naomi Smalls.
This is you at seven.
Aww.
What do you have to say
to little Davis?
"Davis, you‘re gonna go
through a really confusing time,
"where people are gonna make fun
of your mannerisms
"and the way that you look,
"but I just want you to know
"that you need to fucking
embrace it,
"because that‘s what
makes you special.
"Be proud that you‘re not like
all the other boys,
"and just do what you do best,
"and that‘s just being you,
‘cause that‘s what people
are gonna love you for."
Thank you, Naomi.
Condragulations, ladies.
Each of you made it
to the top four
the old-fashioned way.
You mother-tucking earned it,
but in very different ways.
Now it‘s time
for the judges‘ critiques.
First up, Bob The Drag Queen.
-You can really dance.
-Thank you.
You come to life
when you use dance moves.
And you had
such great elegance
and length to your body.
You made it look fabulous,
and I was like,
"Wow, Bob The Drag Queen
is giving us some glamour."
Tonight, on the runway,
because we‘ve seen leggings
a lot from you,
I wish it would have just
gone that extra notch
to do a gown.
I was sort of torn
on the leggings,
which, by the way, is what
I would do to those leggings
-if I tried to put ‘em on.
-[laughs]
But I think this is a really
good place for your drag.
Let‘s talk about your journey.
You‘ve managed to do
a really good job
of standing out.
You have managed to be hilarious
throughout,
and you‘ve also listened
to the judges and grown.
I see an evolution with you.
Thank you, Bob.
Thank you.
Up next, Chi Chi DeVayne.
Ooh, girl, you‘ve
come a long way
from Shreveport, Louisiana.
I heard that.
[all laughing]
Tonight, is it
the most creative thing
we‘ve ever seen
on the main stage?
No.
But you look stunning,
and I love the pageant hair.
It‘s one of my favorite things
in the world,
is that pageant hair
with the 18 buns on top.
The music video,
very nice job.
That was, like, your moment
where you were living,
‘cause you were, like,
in the mirror,
and you were all done up,
and it was just you being you.
The wind scene, you looked
gorgeous in that.
Because you dance,
you had the fluidity,
and you knew just what to do
on that black box.
[all laughing]
I have to talk
about some of your journey.
Your taste level was, um,
questionable.
Am I surprised
that you‘re here?
Yes, if I had a time machine
and came here now,
I would be shocked,
but you put in the work,
and I love a surprise ending.
You‘re like the M. Night
Shyama-lama-lan
of drag queens, right?
I didn‘t see this coming.
Our little girl has grown up.
Chi Chi, if I had moisture
left in my body,
I‘d probably
shed a tear tonight.
[all laughing]
But I dried up years ago.
Yes, everybody knows it.
Thank you, Chi Chi.
Up next, Kim Chi.
Even though we fought
this awkward body movement thing
this whole season,
I think you‘ve really
gotten to a place
where you can work it now.
For avant-garde, you were
like a glamorous,
Dame-Edna-inspired chicken.
It was so captivating.
And seeing your journey
of self-acceptance
and your journey
to challenge yourself
has been really impressive.
As a matter of fact,
in your entire journey,
I don‘t think there was one look
that you didn‘t kill,
and tonight is just the cherry
on top of the hot fudge sundae.
Thank you for bringing
your artistry
to the main stage
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race."
Up next, Naomi Smalls.
You look absolutely
beautiful tonight.
Of course, it‘s iconic Cher
for us,
so it makes us super happy.
-[as Cher]
-Snap out of it.
You have brought it,
and this music video
was no exception.
For avant-garde, I want you
to look like an alien,
and that blue look
with the white boots
gave that to me.
And what I love most about you
is you‘re so sweet.
You‘re that great
combination of, like,
you‘re a fierce bitch that could
cut a bitch on the street,
but you‘re also, like,
a sweet little, like, kitten.
I‘m so happy to see you here,
because I think
you bring something
really special and unique.
You listened, you worked,
and it paid off.
We all have those moments
when you decide to, like,
bust through.
I can think of times
in my career...
it was hearing "No"
when I just said,
"Fuck y‘all.
I‘m in,"
and there was just a moment here
when you just said, "I am in."
Naomi, to say that you
are the surprise...
it‘s no exaggeration.
It‘s just as surprising
as Chi Chi for me.
This is not the final four
that I would have predicted
the first week
in the competition,
and you did it,
and you earned it.
I want to say this
to all the girls.
The theme of the winner‘s circle
is adaptability,
but at the same time
staying true
to your own unique frequency,
and that‘s the truth
not only in this competition
but in everything in life.
Taking those cues
from the universe
and applying them
but without losing who you are,
and each of you represent that,
and I am so proud
of each of you,
and that is why you‘re standing
on this stage today.
All right, ladies.
Final question.
Why should you,
and not your competitors,
be crowned America‘s
next drag superstar?
[dramatic music]
Bob The Drag Queen.
I have, statistically,
done the best
in this competition,
and you reward the person
who has done the best
with the highest reward.
I don‘t just do what I do
for me.
I literally do it
for anyone who can come
within range
of my obnoxious, raspy voice.
I serve the people.
I serve the community,
and more than just
doing stand-up comedy,
and actually getting
my hands and feet
into the dirt of the community
and helping it grow,
because the community
has helped me grow,
and it‘s made me who I am today.
Thank you.
All right, Chi Chi DeVayne.
I should be America‘s
next drag superstar
because I feel like I possess
the talent,
the willingness to grow,
the willingness to take
your critiques
and apply ‘em.
I can be funny just as well.
I can make costumes,
and I can beat this mug out too.
I can work a runway.
I can work a music video,
and I‘ve just blossomed,
and I feel like...
that I should be
America‘s next drag superstar,
because I‘ve shown
the most growth
out of--out of all
of these girls.
Thank you.
All right, next.
Kim Chi.
Throughout this
whole competition,
I have shown consistent
and creative and detailed looks.
I have been professional
and courteous
throughout this whole
experience.
I have been willing to adapt
to myself
in any situation I am in.
None of the girls will ever come
up with the stuff that I do.
I don‘t want to be America‘s
next drag superstar.
I am America‘s
-Thank you.
All right, Naomi Smalls.
I love drag so much.
It is what, like, gets me up
in the morning,
and I have such a need
and a want to grow,
and I don‘t like
to pigeonhole myself
into just being either
a stand-up comedian
or a dancing queen
or a look queen.
I want to be able to do anything
and show everybody
that I can be successful
just being me
and loving who I am,
and that is everything
I want in the world.
Thank you.
Well, my queens,
I think we‘ve heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Now, just between us
squirrel friends,
what do you think?
Now, y‘all were doing
a lot of praising up there,
and these kids have come
a long way.
I understand that,
but I need y‘all to get real
for the realness.
-You know what I‘m saying?
-I can get real.
-I‘ll break it down.
-You know?
‘Cause, hey, this is still
a competition,
and somebody
has to go home tonight.
Bob The Drag Queen.
Spandex leggings...
not so much for best drag.
I would have loved
to have seen a gown.
The makeup has always been
-not great.
-Right.
There was some growth
with the looks,
but, you know, if I‘m buying
a ticket to Bob‘s show,
it‘s not to see glamour.
It‘s to be entertained.
She‘s been consistently smart
with her humor.
-The Snatch Game was stellar.
-Oh.
I also liked
the shady politics ad.
I thought that was really funny.
I think my number one
Bob moment
was "chocolate chip cookie."
Shut it down in the acting.
Really every challenge,
Bob rose to the occasion
and was able to inject
Bob The Drag Queen
into that challenge.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Look at how far she‘s come.
She had to lip-sync
for her life twice,
and she not only saved herself,
she, like, killed it.
Like, we had
a "come to Jesus" meeting
during "I‘m Telling You
I‘m Not Going."
The Bitch Perfect challenge.
That was a high point.
She was upside down,
lip-syncing.
-Uh-huh.
-Twerking.
-Yes.
-I mean, come on.
Also, the Book Ball
was a shining,
glorious moment
for Chi Chi DeVayne.
As great as she looked,
looking at the four queens
on that stage today,
I didn‘t know
if she‘s as original
as the other ones, you know?
-Chi Chi I‘ve seen done before.
-Mm-hmm.
-But I‘m in love with Chi Chi.
-Right.
As a judge, I don‘t know
what to do with that.
She is one of the kids
who come from the sort of
backwoods of drag.
She doesn‘t have to do
the outfits
that people in big cities
come to expect,
but in this competition,
judges wanted to see more,
and she delivered more.
Kim Chi.
She can definitely
serve a look
better than nobody‘s business.
I loved the Wonderful
-Wizard of Oz challenge.
-Yeah.
And what she did with the
stripes, with the little woman,
I thought it was really,
really smart.
When she did the Book Ball
and created the paper wig
out of pink pieces of paper,
it‘s phenomenal.
My favorite moment
with Kim Chi
was the first time I saw her,
and I thought, "What in the hell
am I looking at?"
The interesting thing for me
was watching the struggle
of not loving
who she is in her skin.
I kind of went through
a very similar thing
when I did "Queer Eye."
It was like that thing
that I was hiding.
It was like, "Oh, my God,
you‘re the queer guy?"
Then it was, like, celebrated,
and you‘re like,
"Wait a minute."
I think that‘s gonna happen
with her owning it
and saying,
"Wait, I‘m being celebrated
for who I am,
lisp and awkwardness,"
and she will get there,
but does she have the ability
to command a stage
and work a crowd?
I don‘t know.
She has the capability
-to change drag a little.
-Mm-hmm.
-You know what I mean?
-Yes.
To really sort of shift it
in a very new,
-2000-something...
-Yes.
Sort of way,
and I‘m curious to see
where it goes.
All right, let‘s move on
to Naomi Smalls.
She has upped her game,
and she has brought it to us
on a different level.
The Wizard of Oz moment
was such a game changer.
-Yes.
-My God.
That was really
the turning point for her.
-I mean, haute couture.
-Yeah.
High-end fashion.
Now, in the video,
I really loved
-her avant-garde look.
-Mm-hmm.
I love that she knows
her brand.
I think the turning point
for me
was in the black-and-white movie
runway look,
and she did that beautiful
gray makeup.
And then out she comes
in the Book Ball
in that paper dress,
which was straight off
of a runway somewhere.
Her POV became OMG.
-[laughing]
-For me.
LOL.
She‘s one that
in a year or two
will be killing it,
but I think she‘s just
not there yet.
I don‘t believe that at all.
-Really?
-We can all get better.
But compared
to the other girls
at this point in time,
-I don‘t think she‘s there yet.
-I do.
Her drag is really good
and polished.
And she‘s fashion.
She‘s posing,
which gives me the chills
every time she does that thing
that I wish I could do,
but my belly gets in the way.
I--guess what I‘m about to say?
-I agree with Michelle.
-[exclaims]
-What?
-I know, I know.
I know, but I...
I think what she did this season
is worthy of being
in the top three
and maybe even taking the crown.
well, I‘ve just got to say
for the room, you know,
you guys have been
no help whatsoever.
[all laughing]
Silence!
I‘ve made my decision.
Bring back my girlssssssss...
[dramatic notes]
Ladies, before I can decide
who makes it to the top three,
there‘s just one more thing.
This is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself...
from elimination.
[dramatic music]
The time has come...
♪ ♪
For you to lip-sync...
For your life.
♪ ♪
Good luck,
and don‘t fuck it up.
♪ If real is what you feel ♪
♪ Feelings aren‘t real ♪
♪ Put your money down ♪
♪ Place your bet
and spin the wheel ♪
♪ If real is what you feel ♪
♪ Feelings aren‘t real ♪
♪ Put your money down ♪
♪ Place your bet
and spin the wheel ♪
[techno music]
♪ The realness ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Gonna move into the house ♪
-(Naomi)Drag is about
pushing boundaries
and pushing yourself.
This is what I love doing,
and I just want to do this
for the rest of my life.
I should go forward
into the top three
because I‘m a performer.
I‘m a supermodel.
I‘m a fucking drag queen.
♪ Feel it ♪
-(Chi Chi)I am the dancing
queen of this season,
and I have that country swing.
I can act.
I can do comedy.
I‘m ready for it.
I am America‘s
next drag superstar.
♪ Catch it,
flavor of this fever ♪
♪ I know what I feel ♪
Making it into the top three
would mean the world to me,
-(Kim Chi)because I am proving
to myself,
to the world, and my mother
that all the work
and all the crazy stuff
I‘ve been doing
for all these years
has not been a waste.
I have never, ever
wanted anything more.
I want this so bad it hurts.
♪ Put your money down ♪
I am living my dream.
-(Bob)I actually got into drag
because of "Drag Race."
I‘m a "Drag Race" baby boom.
Right after season one,
I started doing drag,
so this is important.
I came here to show America
why I think
I‘m one of the best drag queens
in the land.
I need to make top three.
Like, I have to.
♪ Is is real? ♪
♪ The realness ♪
-♪ My love is real ♪
-♪ The, the realness ♪
♪ The realness ♪
[laughing]
[cheers and applause]
-Oh, my God.
-God.
-Yay.
-It‘s the last day of school.
Yeah.
Ladies,
I‘ve made my decision.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Chi Chi DeVayne.
I‘m sorry, my dear,
but you will not be moving on
to the top three.
Chi Chi, you used
your Louisiana glamour
to charm the world.
Take what you‘ve learned here
and let them have it.
I just want to thank
each and every one of you
from the bottom of my heart.
Not only have you guys taught me
how to be a better entertainer,
but you have taught me
how to be a better person,
and $100,000 cannot buy that.
Thank you, Chi Chi.
Now, sashay away.
♪ ♪
It‘s a knife in the heart,
the back, the ass.
It‘s a hurting feeling,
to know that you‘ve
put your all and...
it didn‘t pay off.
I‘ve learned how to love me,
my country accent,
so I‘m happy, but I‘m sad
at the same time
that I didn‘t win the crown.
♪ ♪
All right, world.
Meet your top three queens.
Who do you think should be
America‘s next drag superstar?
Are you #TeamBob,
#TeamKimChi,
or #TeamNaomi?
I want to hear from you.
Sound off across
all social media,
@RuPaulsDragRace,
#DragRace.
Tweet it.
Comment on Facebook.
Blow up Instagram.
Call your mother.
Hire a skywriter.
Leave a lipstick message
in the restroom at work.
I don‘t care,
just do it now,
and tune in two weeks
from tonight
to watch the grand finale
of "RuPaul‘s Drag Race,"
where I will crown a winner.
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen.
All right, now,
let the music play.
♪ Die tomorrow ♪
♪ Live tonight ♪
[shimmering chimes]