Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race:
Countdown to the Crown,
Fashion Edition.
Ginger Minj. Pearl. Violet Chachki.
Which of our top three cover girls
deserves to be America's drag superstar?
To help you make up your mind,
we're doing some investigative reporting
and dig deep into the charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent.
Still hungry for more?
-Okay
-Good.
Because we're going to break down
all you want to know about season seven.
-But were too shy to ask.
-[high-pitched screaming]
Too shy. Too shy, my ass.
Some of you bitches
were real thirsty on social media.
-Saying stupid shit.
-Rude.
Tonight, we'll be joined
by our extra-special guest editors,
fashion mavens Raja and Raven,
and our reigning queen, Bianca Del Rio.
Plus, a who's who of queenly contributors
who are going to get
to the bottom of this story.
I just said "bottom."
I feel very uncomfortable right now.
Get ready for fierce fitness...
-Put your legs...
-I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[RuPaul] Hair-raising drama...
-Snatched queens...
-Mm-hmm.
[RuPaul] Sexy celebrity secrets...
I've got a full-blown boner right now.
I'm that excited.
[RuPaul] Runway rashasha...
Plus exclusive unseen footage...
Tell me if my nipples
pop out, Joshy. Thanks.
And the world premiere
of Born Naked: The Music Video.
♪ Tell me the truth now ♪
Honey, we are going vogue
as we prepare to read season seven
from cover to cover girl.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[RuPaul] The winner receives a year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
May the best woman, best woman win ♪
Hello.
I'm RuPaul, editrix in queef
of the Drag Race empire.
With just one week until the grand finale,
let's flip through the glossy pages
of the most fashionable season ever.
Is this the most fashionable season ever?
It is.
This season, my girls had the skinny
on how to be a mean, lean queen.
Coming in at number four,
abs everywhere! Abs everywhere!
I'm here!
Jasmine Masters' abs.
You could do your laundry on those.
You'd think her costumes would be cleaner.
-How did you get this body?
-Girl, I don't know.
Abs everywhere. Just abs.
Boop, boop, boop.
I hope she markets
a Jasmine Masters Ab Master.
Get it? 'Cause her last name is Masters.
[RuPaul] Number three:
Serving Sleek Chic!
Miss Fame is sleek and slim.
Miss Thing is giving me supermodel.
She should be called Miss On Fleek.
Her body's on fleek,
her brows are on fleek.
Fuck Fame. Just be Fleek.
I'd like to thank Mexico
for the tapeworm that snatched my body.
These girls are making me feel fat.
[RuPaul] Number two:
No Pads, No Problem!
Was padding out this season?
What's going on?
-Pearl.
-Uh-huh.
Now that you've come out of your shell,
maybe you could use that as a butt pad?
Is she allergic to foam? I don't get it.
If you are not wearing pads,
you are not doing drag.
I don't have to wear pads.
Pearl's body is fine.
She doesn't need pads. She's gorgeous.
Of course she needs to use pads.
You mean pad her personality? Oh, no.
I don't mind a skinny queen.
[RuPaul] Number one: Cinch It!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh, Violet Chachki. That bitch.
She needed a breathing machine.
Iconic, legendary. That was epic.
I really could die, bitch.
I'm giving you realness.
I never want to meet you.
I hate you. Skinny bitch.
Violet's a lovely girl.
It's a shame she's so morbidly obese.
-Hey, Violet, did you cinch?
-No, I have a hog body.
You call that a hog body, bitch?
Fail. #fail.
Thin may be in, but don't get it twisted.
Fat is where it's at.
[RuPaul] Large is still in charge.
At number three: It Do Take Curves!
Kennedy is a perfect example
of a curvy queen.
[RuPaul] She has got
quite a backstory going on there.
She wears this horse's ass as pads,
and I fucking love it.
She's talented.
Big hair, pageant, Texas drag.
[RuPaul] The rainbow leads
right to her pot of gold.
Her ass.
Come on, badonkadrrrrrk.
[RuPaul] Number two:
Binge on the Minj.
I like to describe myself
as a glamor toad.
I love a glamor toad. [croaks]
I'm envious
of a woman that's got the curves,
and just the cheeseburgers
and the ham hocks all around her.
You owned being thick-ums.
Come on, thick-ums!
I'm suffering from Ginger-vitis.
And I love it.
[RuPaul] Number one:
May the Fierce Be With You!
How y'all doing?
Jaidynn walked in
jiggling from left to right.
I love a big bitch. Work, mama.
[clicks tongue]
[Ross] Oh, Beyoncé who?
[Jaidynn] I'm giving the judges curves
and swerves and plump-a-liciousness.
We've got to cook together.
I can throw down in the kitchen.
Fried chicken, corn bread, green beans.
J'adore Jaidynn Diore.
My girls always give good face.
But this season, they took it up a hair.
Let's hear it for our hairy Marys. Ooh.
Ooh, girl, you know Willam was pissed
for missing out on that beard challenge.
[RuPaul] Number five: Abe-solutely!
Yowza, Baberaham Lincoln.
Katya came out as Abraham Lincoln,
who has one
of the most famous beards in history.
His wife, Mary Todd Lincoln.
[RuPaul] Number four: Red Alert!
I really liked Pearl
in her little papier-mâché beard.
[RuPaul] It's the devil made her do it.
[Jinkx] She kind of looked
like the villain from the Powerpuff Girls.
The one who's like,
"Yes, Powerpuff Girls."
[RuPaul] Number three:
Use Your Head!
I haven't had any complaints.
Kandy Ho had this amazing
box of hair on her head.
-[RuPaul] Who doesn't love a hairy box?
-[Michelle] My husband.
Which actually happens to me a lot
when I put wigs in suitcases.
You pull them out,
and that's how they look.
[RuPaul] Number two: Hello Dalí!
-[Mel B] I love the beard.
-My favorite beard look was Max.
He just looked like avant-garde.
Although I don't know what it is.
Number one: Good Golly, Miss Molly!
It's rock and roll legend Little Richard!
If you're wearing facial hair in the game,
you'd better be the biggest queen there.
♪ A-wooo! ♪
Good golly, Miss Molly,
you might want to shave the upper lip.
-You can't do that.
-Why?
'Cause it's a man.
It was crazy that the other girls
were complaining about it
because there was a Needles impersonator
who happens to be a man,
and an Alyssa Edwards impersonator,
who happens to be a man.
♪ Wooo! ♪
Shut up.
When it came to showing skin,
my girls were born naked,
and they stayed that way.
You're born naked and the rest is awful.
[RuPaul] Now touch all this skin, Henny.
Number four: Show Your Assets.
She just bent over
and gave you the whole story.
-Emphasis on the hole.
-[Michelle] What an ass.
I hope she had shaved.
[RuPaul] Number three:
She's a Real Cut Up!
Ginger ripped it all off
in that conjoined twin lip synch.
That bitch pulled out scissors
and cut herself away from Sasha Belle.
Where was she holding them?
Were they under her wig?
Sometimes you have to allow
your audience to see you bare it all.
Even if that means that your titties
are hanging out and your wig is off.
That was a titty-twister.
[RuPaul] Number two:
When in Doubt, Whip it Out.
There is some stuff in that workroom
you do not want to see.
I mean, some of y'all do.
[Pearl] Trixie's back,
that uncut dick hanging out.
[Pearl] Let's see your wiener.
We haven't seen one in a while.
-It's not in a good place right now.
-Show us your dick!
-It's shriveled up now.
-I want to look.
Can I fluff for a second?
Hold on, I need to think good thoughts.
[RuPaul] Number one: You Do You!
For Violet's nude illusion,
she just came out nude with a little tape.
[judges gasp]
[Violet] I'm comfortable being naked
with a piece of duct tape on and a smile.
If I was doing nude illusion, I'd come out
naked and say, "This is what you wanted."
And then I'd lift up my penis,
and there'd be a disco ball underneath.
Panties, bitch!
My fashionistas, with just one week until
the grand finale of RuPaul's Drag Race,
which one of these top three cover girls
should be America's next drag superstar?
Are you Team Ginger Minj?
Team Pearl? Or Team Violet Chachki?
Let your voice be heard.
I think I was confused by the assignment.
-More nudity!
-Okay, girl.
This has been
our most snatched season ever.
Basic witches not wanted.
What keeps my girls looking good
and feeling gorgeous?
Well, they got their secrets.
[RuPaul] Fitness is fierce.
Health tips from drag queens?
Are you crazy?
[RuPaul] Fit tip number five:
Don't Forget to Stretch.
♪ All I ever wanted
All I ever wanted ♪
Katya, that bitch can spread
her legs like peanut butter.
[Katya] I pounded my vagina into the stage
so hard that the building shakes.
Katya's very limber.
[Bianca] Katya has amazing muscle control.
She must be
the most popular hooker on her corner.
I'm kidding. Nobody fucks her.
[RuPaul] Number four: Don't Act Your Age.
Sissy that walker?
That is All Star 2055.
Senior citizens' edition.
[RuPaul] Girl, your pacemaker is on fire!
[laughter]
Ru is shady, making them dress up
like old ladies so he looks young.
Don't you wish your granny
was hot like me?
Another challenge
where Max never dropped character.
I think he remained an old lady
for the rest of the season.
I love the smell
of Bengay in the morning.
We know what they're going to look like
in about 20 years, some in five.
Shade goggles.
[RuPaul] Number three:
Get Plenty of Rest! But not too much.
Pearl, you've been sleepwalking.
A drag queen who's sleepy
all the time. Original.
[RuPaul] It's like a runway on Ambien.
I think Pearl just sleep-lives.
You just have those personalities
that are just natural stoners,
even if they've never picked up a blunt.
Wake up, Pearl.
Wake up.
Wake the fuck up, Pearl.
Pearl, honey, it's time for school.
Wake up.
Ah! Okay, I'm awake.
[RuPaul] Number two:
Dance Your Padded Ass Off!
♪ Strawberry, kiwi, peach
Tongues tied, slur your speech ♪
Dancing is important exercise.
Well, actually, I don't dance.
I just have sex.
♪ When I shake my ass
I'm makin' money, money, money ♪
That shit looked hard. I can't do that.
I thought I was watching
So You Think You Can Dance?.
♪ Can I get it to go?
Can I get, can I get it to go? ♪
From the house of Beyond Belief
Dance Company, two thumbs up.
Ding!
[RuPaul] Number one: Fly Girl, Fly!
Flinging yourself off a stage
and landing in a split is always in vogue.
Kennedy served all the fitness.
Calisthenics and Pilates was happening.
And the facial muscles were all working.
Roar, Kennedy! [growls]
[meows] That's my roar.
Whew, that was a workout.
But if getting physical isn't your thing,
you can always get some good work.
I've never thought of that before.
'Cause Plastic is Fantastic.
Tape: it's not just for tucking anymore.
[Bianca] Those tape face-lifts
looked so natural.
Just like Miss Fame's face
in the first episode.
Who knew looking this good
could be this cheap?
This is the nose
I have always dreamed of.
It's like Phantom of the Opera
meets Joan Rivers. Oh!
How do I sleep at night?
Ask your husband.
[laughs]
[chewing]
People always ask me,
"What's your diet secret?" It's simple.
A mint for breakfast,
a mint for lunch, and for dinner...
-a glass of water, no mint.
-Really?
[RuPaul] I'm proud to present
the Drag Race Diet.
Eat it!
Now here's some real useful advice:
never skip meals.
There's always room for Jell-O.
[groaning]
What in Fantasia Barrino
is going on up in here?
-Cut!
-Oh, my fucking god.
[Pearl] I was sitting
in 40-degree Jell-O. I'm freezing.
Miss Fame has a total erection
rubbing on me.
Just get me out of here.
I actually heard red wine
is quite good for you... by the box.
-[Michelle] Leopard line, box of wine.
-[RuPaul] Yes.
I don't drink wine,
but if I were on the stage and it's
all that's there, let's get classy drunk.
He better have that boxed wine chilling.
Pinkies up, girls.
My number-one diet tip? Protein.
I like long walks on the beach,
big dicks, and eggs.
♪ Eggs, eggs, eggs
All I want is eggs ♪
She's the egg queen.
Coo, coo, ca, choo.
This season, everyone is wearing eggs.
♪ All I want is eggs, eggs, eggs ♪
Your country breakfast is ready.
When it comes to coining an expression,
my girls are real trendsetters.
That's right.
So pay attention
and get ready to sissy that talk.
My pussy is trending on Craigslist.
What are these kids
coming up with nowadays?
[RuPaul] Number eight: Better Call FEMA!
When I see Jamal there,
I about flood my basement.
Bring out the sandbags.
-[all cheering]
-[Violet] Oh, my goodness!
Santino Rice.
I flood my basement, bitch.
That's going to be a mess to clean up.
Mildew and mold.
You need, like, the Rug Doctor.
[RuPaul] Number seven: The Chachki Cheer.
[Violet] Aaah! Come through!
[RuPaul] Come through, mama.
[Violet] That waist, bitch. Come through!
Come through, long hair.
Come through, psoriasis.
[RuPaul] Number six: Cooking with Pam.
[Jaidynn] No, ma'am, Pam. No turkey.
-No, ma'am, Pam.
-Yes, ma'am, Pam.
Yes, ma'am, Pam.
No, ma'am, no ham, no Pam,
no cauliflower, no cornbread, no beans.
Who's Pam?
[RuPaul] Number five:
Build that Brand, Girl.
Miss Fame is a fucking brand.
I'm like, ew, I don't, bitch. My brand.
I'll call myself a brand every day.
I'm a goddamn brand.
You a brand, a brand.
A brand what, muffin?
Miss Fame's brand...
Well, she's a hand model.
Isn't she? She always doing this.
-Miss Fame.
-Oh, the brand.
Miss Fame claims to be a brand.
Yeah, so is Kirkland, bitch.
[RuPaul] Number four: The Kennedy Curse.
Child, the struggle is real.
Clearly, the struggle is real.
You know what's real? The struggle.
The real struggle she's having
is getting her ass in pantyhose.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, okay.
[RuPaul] Number three:
When Life Gives You Lemons.
No tea, no shade, no pink lemonade.
Ooh, I love me some pink lemonade.
Bitch got me thirsty.
[Jasmine] No tea, no shade,
no pink lemonade.
Why's she taking all the beverages away?
-Don't be mad.
-Ding!
[RuPaul] Number two: Pearls of... Wisdom?
We're probably the two most,
kind of, flazéda sort of, like...
-The most what?
-Flazéda, it's a new hashtag.
She sleeps. When she wakes up,
she's talking shit nobody understands.
-[RuPaul] Well, flazéda.
-How you spell that?
F-L-A-D... No.
F-L-A...
Give me a pen.
F-L-A-Z, E with a hyphen over it, D-A.
Make sure that you hyphenate that "E."
It's very important.
-[RuPaul] Number one...
-Shit RuPaul says.
Hey, that's me.
She done already done had herses.
She done already done has herses.
Is that correct?
She done already done had herses.
What does "herses" mean?
Um, okay. I was coming from the club.
And I went to Krystal Burger
in Atlanta, Georgia.
And we would go and get our food on after,
you know, partying and everything.
Somebody had come up to pick up a bag,
but it actually didn't belong to them.
And this girl behind the counter said,
"Uh-uh, no, no, no.
She done already done had herses."
And of course, I've, you know...
taken that to the bank.
With one week until the grand finale
of RuPaul's Drag Race,
which one of the top three cover girls
deserves the crown?
Sound off now,
because if you snooze, you lose.
-Right, Pearl?
-[blows raspberry]
Our cover girls weren't the only ones
who exposed themselves this season.
Our judges and extra-special guest judges
kept it real,
served it raw, and got it twisted.
Get ready for Star Secrets Exposed.
-Am I giving too much today?
-No.
-Look around.
-Okay, good.
-Yeah, true. What am I saying?
-Look around.
You're young to have hot flashes.
[Mel] I'm not that young.
I'm 39. I was like, shit.
So Victoria was
the first one who turned 40?
[Mel] Geri. But then again,
nobody really knows how old Geri is.
She holds that passport so tight.
How dare you, Michelle?
She comes out here in crutches
with some Amadeus realness, right...
Darling, it's always the same silhouette.
You can throw crutches on it,
still the same silhouette.
-That silhouette with the powdered wig--
-Snatch waist. The same thing.
No dessert for either of you tonight.
Poop is natural. Everybody poops.
[Demi] I don't.
Ever.
This season, the fashion was on fleek.
But in a season of killer looks,
which bitch wore it best?
Let's hear from Raja and Raven
on how to look like a winner, baby.
We're talking about our favorite looks
of season seven of RuPaul's Drag Race.
And one that we didn't quite... get.
One of my top picks was Miss Kennedy
in her leather and lace gown.
[Raja] Oh, yes.
Very Kennedy. Very LaGuardia.
Probably more Newark, but still cute.
Here's my first favorite.
Katya in the Death Becomes Her challenge.
I always love a bit of a sight gag.
It's like the banana peel in comedy.
If I were in that challenge,
I would've done something more glamorous.
Asphyxiation via a fabulous silk scarf
from a floating chandelier above me.
And then I would sing
"Chandelier" by Sia.
Cue music. Oh, no, we can't afford it.
My next look was Violet Chachki
in her Hello Kitty extravaganza.
Other-worldly, very reminiscent
of Hello Kitty herself.
Isn't Uranus the planet
with the ring around it?
-No.
-That's Jupiter.
-[Raven] Now, let's talk about RuPaul.
-[Raja] The goddess herself.
My favorite was the black velvet dress
painting of herself with the white afro.
[Raven] Honey, this look featured
naked RuPaul riding a black panther.
-It was different.
-Yeah.
She never brings
anything up around the neck.
Maybe she just had a hairy chest that day.
Whatever. She looks great.
I love this look. Yes, God.
Now, my least favorite look
from the entire season
had to be Kennedy's look
for the Death Becomes Her challenge.
-What was that?
-A huge WTF.
[Raja] #chickenorwhat, remember that?
Her explanation of the outfit
did not make sense.
Something about being a hooker
and a phoenix rising and...
-Crystallize.
-Oh, my God.
She just looks like a crystal meth addict
in Phoenix, Arizona.
-Can we go to break?
-No.
The biggest prize of all is still to come.
Which of our top three cover girls
deserves the crown?
Let me and the world know all about it.
Scientists have discovered
that honesty isn't just the best policy,
it adds years to your life, which means
these bitches are going to live forever.
Realness rules
in our top three moments of truth.
Is honesty the best policy?
Of course.
At number three: Mad About Michelle.
I hate Michelle Visage.
Yeah, you're gonna win now.
Some of these queens,
I feel like they bitchy-osed this season.
What contestant that young goes on
a reality show competition like RuPaul's,
which is a lot of work,
and says, "I hate the main judge"?
Like, that is punk.
Girl!
She probably has a bigger man-body
than I do without her implants.
[Jasmine] Come on, don't go there, girl.
I like her.
How are you going to win the challenge
and then get back in the workroom...
and done try to sneak one in
on Michelle Visage?
Honey, we all hate Michelle Visage.
We just don't say it with cameras around.
[RuPaul] Number two: Queens Go Clean.
-How long have you been sober for?
-I've been sober for nine years.
But counting days in here
feels like being a newcomer.
That's what it feels like.
It's nice to see drag queens
talking about their sobriety
because partying and drinking excessively
have been a part of the gay community,
but it doesn't have to be.
You're being so hard on yourself.
You're in it, but you're not alone.
I'm here with you
having those same fears and feelings.
I mean, good for Katya and Miss Fame.
I love sobriety.
I mean, good on them.
Clean streets are the best streets.
[RuPaul] Number one: Motherly Love.
Pearl had that sort of really scary,
uncomfortable moment
with RuPaul.
Well, you kind of told me
I had no personality.
I mean, that doesn't make me feel good
or give me confidence.
I said, "Oh, girl.
Don't do it, Jackie. Don't do it."
Stop, stop, stop it, stop, stop.
No, no, no, no, no, no, stop.
[Bianca] Don't look at Ru in the eyes.
You're turning into stone.
She is taking your soul.
Do I have something on my face?
Bitch! Ow! No.
No, I'm just not convinced.
And I want you to do well.
That's why I brought your ass here.
I was uncomfortable.
Clutching my pearls.
I didn't even mean that like that.
You know, FYI, for all you girls up there,
I don't want to hear any goddamn excuses.
Ru got into it this season too.
She let them have it after that challenge.
Be prepared.
-We didn't have time to re-rehearse...
-Make it work. Make it work.
If Ru yelled at me like that,
I would have just cried.
I'd be like, "I'm Jasmine Mastering it up.
I'm packing all my shit, and I'm out.
I'm not wanted here anymore."
Fucking make it happen. I don't want
to hear any goddamn excuses anymore.
The last thing you want to do
is piss off Ru. Mm-mm.
I still can't look her in the eye.
She's terrifying.
[laughs]
It's hard for viewers to truly appreciate
what our girls go through each season.
I'm sorry, I need to relax.
[RuPaul] So I've called
a professional to break it down.
Coming from a place of love,
light, and understanding,
please welcome... Bianca Del Rio.
Aw, who needs a hug?
Kidding. Don't come near me.
Let's start with Tempest DuJour.
[grunts]
I saw a drag queen in a Mexican restaurant
do that exact same entrance.
Except it wasn't a baby.
-That's disgusting.
-[Ru laughs]
Which leads us to Mrs. Kasha Davis.
I'm home!
Miss Kasha Davis is from Upstate New York,
where they produce winners
like Pandora Boxx and Darienne Lake.
-What?
-There's no talent in the water.
-Trixie Mattel.
-So...
It was really so sad to see Trixie go.
Twice. Ha-ha!
Max.
I don't want to rely on grossness or
sexuality. That's what people always do.
Max is always complaining
that drag queens are too vulgar.
You know what's vulgar?
That fucking accent, bitch.
And that brings us to Miss Fame.
I'm hitting a wall, and I'm finding myself
having a conversation with myself.
Her personality is so amazing
that, growing up,
her only friends were chickens.
Some people would say I love cock.
Ca-caw! And then there's
our distinguished top three.
Ginger Minj claims to be the glamor toad,
but when you look at her,
she's been eating more than flies.
Pearl. The best thing about Pearl's drag?
She's cute as a boy.
[Bianca] Violet Chachki.
[Michelle] Her waist is so small!
I was really shocked when I saw
Violet come out with that oxygen tank.
-'Cause that meant Ru wasn't using it.
-Bitch!
-And who can forget Michelle Visage?
-Mmm...
She's constantly saying that,
"RuPaul is my best friend."
Funny thing is you don't hear Ru say it.
The opinions expressed
by Bianca Del Rio do not represent
those of RuPaul's Race,
Logo TV, World of Wonder,
the NAACP, or the Friends
of the Pacoima Public Library.
Except the part about Michelle Visage.
I kind of agree with that one.
Now, our top three queens,
Pearl, Ginger Minj, and Violet Chachki,
have each made it this far
thanks to a certain thing
we call je ne sais quoi,
which in French means
"their pussies are on fire."
-Hi, fellas.
-[RuPaul] Ginger, a plus-size powerhouse,
a killer comedian,
and a natural-born performer.
-I love you, Justin Bieber.
-[laughs]
Ginger can serve up some strong tea...
We don't mean any harm, girl.
Except when we do.
And still leave you gagging for more.
Ginger Minj for the crown.
This girl has it all.
She can sing, act, dance...
Nope, not so much dance.
Boom, boom, boom.
She is confident, funny,
and she just looks like she smells good.
Pearl, your razor burn is so bad
the only way I can read you is by braille.
She can read a bitch for filth
with a beating heart underneath it all.
I can't believe I'm crying on fucking TV.
What Ginger has that no one else has
is that extra...
fifty pounds.
[laughs]
I cannot wait to see
a big girl win RuPaul's Drag Race.
I always thought Jinkx Monsoon
was the first plus-sized winner.
This season,
Ginger accomplished the impossible.
She got gay men everywhere screaming...
I love the minj.
[RuPaul] But does Ginger
have the right amount of sugar, spice,
and show-stopping skills
to snatch the crown?
In one week, all will be revealed.
Next up, a precious gem
who took her own sweet time
to come out of her shell.
-'Sup?
-But once she did...
-she sparkled.
-Thank you.
-Pearl.
-Pearl is beautiful.
This porcelain mug.
You can't mess with that.
Pearl has
a very New York approach to drag.
She always puts
that high-fashion twist on it.
Bitch, you can wear fur in spring, okay?
I mean, Pearl's hot. As a boy, goddamn it,
she can get me pregnant.
Totally. I'll raise it.
I think the turning point for Pearl
was she started listening to the judges.
And she, like, took her Adderall.
It's neat to see
vulnerability come out of Pearl.
I didn't know that tears
came out of them sleepy eyes.
What would Pearl
have to say to little Matthew?
You're going to enter
the toughest years of your life.
It makes you want to hug her.
And everybody grows.
I mean, she's growing. She grew!
You're a star, baby.
I love her.
Sleeper queen Pearl had the tenacity
to rise and shine her way to the top.
Her attitude and edgy looks
have fascinated the nation,
leading many to believe
the jewel in the crown will be a Pearl.
Yeah!
Uh-oh. Ooh, la, la, la, la, la.
-Last...
-Yay!
But by no means least...
She's young, beautiful, and outspoken.
That's right.
With a sophisticated knowledge of fashion
well beyond her years.
When it comes to style,
she just might have this competition
all cinched up.
This is Violet Chachki.
I love her style. She has a great eye.
She does a beautiful makeup.
Violet should win based purely
on the fact that she had a black thing
and took off the belt,
and it turned into a plaid thing.
Oh, that look was everything.
-Miss Thing.
-[tongue pops]
That ho's been reading some magazines.
The internet happened.
Have you heard of it?
Oh!
Violet is a bitch.
I don't trust a drag queen that isn't one.
[Violet] People think I'm mean,
but everything I've done comes
from a place of humor or a place of truth.
She's not bad.
She's just painted that way.
I want you to know that I'm going
to be working on the way I come across.
She's like Courtney,
you got to get to know her
to know that there's no malice.
-You have something that I don't have.
-Beauty?
She's still a bitch,
but she's a bitch with a heart of gold.
Like Bianca Del Rio.
Violet evolved
from a fiery-tempered fashionista...
-What?
-To a glamazon with grace.
But in a race
that's tighter than her corset,
can Violet snatch the crown officially?
Come through!
There you have it. Your top three queens.
But which one of these cover girls
will be America's next drag superstar?
It's anybody's guess.
Are you Team Ginger Minj?
Team Pearl? Or Team Violet Chachki?
Hashtag it now and tell the world.
It's your chance to break the Internet.
Who do you want to snatch the title
of America's next drag superstar?
Are you Team Ginger,
Team Pearl,
or Team Violet Chachki?
And one week from tonight,
I'm reserving you a front-row seat
to the grand finale of RuPaul's Drag Race.
All right, girlfriends. Loosen your tuck.
Let it all hang out
for the world premiere
of Born Naked: The Music Video.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself naked,
how the hell you going to love
somebody else naked?
Can I get an amen up in here?
[all] Amen.
Now, let the music video play.
["Born Naked" playing]
♪ Who you waiting for, another savior? ♪
♪ Always lookin'
But you never find, never find ♪
♪ Waking up from another night gone ♪
♪ Always lookin'
But you never find, never find ♪
♪ Going downtown
You know where you're going ♪
♪ Throw your top down
Like you know where you're going ♪
♪ Tell me one thing
Do you like where you're going? ♪
♪ Ignoring all of the signs ♪
♪ I'm telling the truth now
I'm telling, I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ I'm telling, I'm telling,
I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ We're all born naked
And the rest is drag ♪
♪ Who, who, who do you think you ♪
♪ Who, who, telling the truth now ♪
♪ We're all born naked
And the rest is drag ♪
♪ A lonely highway
You drove the wrong way ♪
♪ Always chasing down a fantasy, fantasy ♪
♪ A sexy muscle car under the radar ♪
♪ Always looking
But you never see, never see ♪
♪ Going downtown
You know where you're going ♪
♪ Throw your top down
Like you know where you're going ♪
♪ Tell me one thing
Do you like where you're going? ♪
♪ Ignoring all of the signs ♪
♪ I'm telling the truth now
I'm telling, I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ I'm telling, I'm telling,
I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ We're all born naked
And the rest is drag ♪
♪ Who, who, who do you think you ♪
♪ Who, who, telling the truth now ♪
♪ We're all born naked
And the rest is drag ♪
♪ I'll say it again ♪
♪ It's never been the clothes
That make the man ♪
♪ Nothing can leave your baggage behind
And I said ♪
♪ I'm telling the truth now
I'm telling, I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ I'm telling, I'm telling,
I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ We're all born naked
And the rest is drag ♪
♪ Who, who, who do you think you ♪
♪ Who, who
I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ Who, who, who do you think you ♪
♪ We're all born naked
And the rest is drag ♪
[RuPaul] I wore a lobster dress.