[RuPaul] Previously on RuPaul's Drag Race.
This week's maxi challenge: Snatch Game!
Whoo!
Aaah!
Wrong note, sugar. Shut up!
I said, "Haunted house."
You have the look down 100%.
What was missing was everything else.
Don't come as Chaka's sister.
That's all she has to say about that.
Kennedy Davenport, Ginger Minj,
first tie in Snatch Game herstory.
Jaidynn Diore Fierce, shantay, you stay.
Max, sashay away.
-Oh, my God.
-Ooh, child.
"Love you, darlings."
My Max is gone. I'm so sad.
-It's getting real now.
-It is.
Can we talk about what RuPaul said
at the end about someone coming back?
I fear I've let
one of the eliminated queens go home...
...too soon.
-I want Jasmine to come back.
-I don't!
She's been gone for too long
to come back now.
-What about Kandy Ho?
-She can't lip-sync four times.
How can I say this delicately?
I don't want anybody to come back.
Nobody wants that.
Nice to know you. You're beautiful.
Stay home.
[engine starts]
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash price of $100,000!
With True Blood's Nelsan Ellis
and LeAnn Rimes!
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
May the best woman, best woman win ♪
[Ginger] Come on, girl.
-[Jaidynn] Good morn-ting.
-[Violet] Then there were seven.
I mean, eight.
Can we just say that we'll all
band together and go on strike?
Yes, baby.
♪ We shall not, we shall not do drag ♪
[RuPaul] Ooh, girl.
She done already done had herses.
Be careful, my pretties.
What goes around comes around.
And that bitch
that you threw under the bus
might be the one driving the Greyhound
next time your ass needs a ride.
[horn honking]
[Violet] Damn!
-Hello, hello!
-Hi!
-Are you decent?
-Yes.
-Because we've got company.
-No!
Here we go.
Come on out, company.
Latrice! It's like seeing Sharon Stone,
except, you know...
fat and black.
[RuPaul] Ladies, let's face it.
Competing on RuPaul's Drag Race
is a lot like being in a women's prison.
So, for today's mini challenge, you need
to prove that "orange is the new drag".
Oh, pit crew!
-[Pearl] How sexy.
-[RuPaul] Hey, Latrice,
would you like to inspect
the pit crew's underwears?
Get those nuts away from my face.
All right, kitty girls, you need
to drag up these prison uniforms
using supplies from the commissary...
plus any contraband that you smuggled in.
You have 20 minutes.
Ready, set... Attica!
Welcome to Tuckahoe Prison for Ladies.
[Latrice] Drag queen walking.
You angry, ain't you? Just mad.
-I never expected to be in jail.
-Looking the way you look,
you didn't think that was a crime?
Do the time, don't let the time do you.
Don't drop the soap.
[RuPaul] All right, time's up, ladies.
It's time for the Tuckahoe Prison
fashion show.
First up, Ginger Minj.
But the others call her Wide Receiver.
-[Latrice] I know that's right.
-[RuPaul] She's in here for burning bush.
Her dream conjugal visit
would be from the NBA.
The whole NBA.
Kennedy Davenport,
A.K.A. Ho 'N' Good Stuff.
-[Latrice] Working that side ponytail.
-[RuPaul] Sure is.
Her prison job is washing
tray underwear and cooking ramen noodles.
Ooh, look at them ashy knees.
Next up is Pearl, A.K.A. Lil' Bitch.
-[RuPaul] I wonder who Big Bitch is.
-That would be me.
Lucky you. Her prison job is nail tech.
Actually, she did my nails.
-Does she do toes too?
-She do toes too.
Miss Fame, A.K.A. Bam-Bam,
A.K.A. Sad Eyes, A.K.A. Pinky.
She got a lot of A.K.A.'s.
Call her Sad Pink Eyes for short.
Yeah. She smuggle
weave bond inside a cake.
She do weaves? Yes, girl,
no good weave goes unpunished.
Katya, A.K.A. Olga.
Now, her favorite prison activity
is having gingivitis.
That explains that smell.
Dental damn, girl.
She's in here for 30 years
for smuggling geese out of the Ukraine.
Violet Chachki A.K.A. Princess.
She's a bad bitch.
Her prison job is crack dealer.
I know what kind of crack she's serving.
Hey. Jaidynn Diore Fierce,
A.K.A. Slutisha.
She's here for selling something for sale.
I know what that means.
She's from Cell Block XXX.
-[RuPaul] Oh, damn, girl.
-[Violet] Yes, Beyoncé.
[RuPaul] Yes, mommy.
Nice job, ladies.
We'll be posting all of your mug shots
at logotv.com. But the winner
of today's mini challenge is...
-Kennedy Davenport!
-Oh, my God!
Boom. I look good in orange, don't I?
Well, thank you, Officer Latrice Royale.
-Bye, Latrice.
-Bye, girl.
Now, as I promised last week,
one of the eliminated queens
is returning to the competition.
Do you want to know who?
-No.
-Not really.
All right. Are you ready?
Come on out, kitty girl.
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, no.
[shouting]
[Trixie] Oh, my God!
-Hi, Trixie.
-Hi.
Looks like I'm gonna trade some girl
some soap for some new makeup.
But wait a minute. Wait a minute.
[Miss Fame] Oh, my God!
Tempest?
-Tempest DuJour.
-Hi, Ru.
[RuPaul] Why, you old geezer.
Now, I've got this sneaking feeling
that...
-Oh, my God!
-It ain't over.
-[Jaidynn] Are you serious?
-[Sasha] What?
[laughs]
Lo and behold.
-Hey, bitches!
-What?
[Kennedy] That's when all the bitches
start coming through the door.
God damn it!
Everyone is back.
All 14 of us.
[woman screams]
Oh, my gosh.
The whole gang's back together again.
Didn't we get rid of these girls?
Why is they back?
I'm a lil' bit con-fursed.
That's right. I invited back
all of the eliminated queens.
Which one gets to stay?
Well, that's up to you.
For this week's maxi challenge,
each of you will be paired
with an eliminated queen.
And you'll be in charge
of making her over as your twin.
-As your... conjoined twin.
-[Jaidynn] Oh, my God!
-[Sasha] Oh, my...
-#ConjoinedQueens.
[Violet] Real makeover.
Two queens sharing the same charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent,
because the eliminated queen
in the winning pair
will return to the competition!
[RuPaul cackling]
Kennedy Davenport, since you won
the challenge, you get to pick your twin.
And then you get to pair
everybody else up.
Oh, bitch.
Damn!
-Kennedy, who's going to be your twin?
-Jasmine.
Why he got to be black?
-Who do you choose for Ginger?
-Sasha.
[Ginger] Hey, girl!
-Who do you choose for Pearl?
-Trixie.
Yay!
-Who do you choose for Miss Fame?
-Kandy.
-All right, Kennedy. For Katya?
-Kasha.
[Katya] Hello, darling.
-Who do you choose for Violet?
-Max.
[whispers] We're gonna kill this shit.
The suspense is killing me.
-Who did you pick for Jaidynn?
-Tempest.
Kennedy knows exactly what she's doing.
I could see the cogs turning.
There's nothing physically alike
about the two of us.
And I'm not doing blackface.
Gentlemens, start your engines.
And may the best women win!
All right, I'm glad you're back.
If anybody had to come back
and be my partner, I'm glad it's you.
That's a fucking lie. I'm not happy to see
any of these bitches walk back in,
because I have fought too hard
for my spot here
to have somebody go take a vacation
to come back and join the race.
So, it seems like everybody else
will be joined at the hip or at the head.
We got to do something that stands out.
Okay, okay, we can do this.
We can make it work.
What if we connect at the boob?
Like, just share one big boob.
Yeah. No, I like it.
Yes, we need to be funny,
but we actually have to look good too.
[Ginger] Sasha Belle don't sew.
I don't sew. So...
I don't know what the hell we're gonna do
to make this sewing challenge work.
We should do something gorgeous but gross,
just like my drag.
It's pretty but nasty at the same time.
-Yeah.
-We can be beauty queens...
Like in a beauty pageant?
-Like, little kids, though.
-Yes.
-Absolutely.
-But creepy.
There's so much to do. I'm stressed out.
But if I'm gonna be doing all of this,
I'm really happy it's for Trixie.
We can give you acne,
and I'll have perfect skin.
Yeah, okay.
-Hello, hello.
-Hi.
Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited.
Violet and Max.
-Hello.
Max, you have a chance to come back,
so the stakes are very high.
-Yes, ma'am.
-What is your strategy to win?
You know, taking Max's style
and really amping it up,
-and turn it a little tchotchke, tacky.
-So you're in the driver's seat.
-Yes, ma'am.
-You're still in the competition,
so you're calling the shots.
-Where will you be conjoined?
-We love corsetry.
We'll be completely hourglass together.
Girl, please,
we don't need to see how small
you can make your waist
with this damn corset every challenge.
-Get back to work.
-I.J.S. I'm just saying.
Miss Fame.
-Hi, Ru.
-Kandy Ho.
-Hi.
-You're an unlikely pairing.
-Did you all connect before you left?
-We never got a chance to connect at all.
But I wish I had a bit of Kandy.
She's fearless, and I'm full of fear.
There's an energy she exudes on stage
I need to have in my life to be better.
I said, "I wish I'd have had the chance
to get to know more about you,
and here's our chance
to really know who one another is."
Miss Fame, she talks so much.
Her answers are paragraphs.
She's got such a balance
and a fearlessness about her.
Her energy is what I need. There's been
moments in my life where conversation,
it's like it goes right through my head,
and I want to be able to show who I am.
Girl, just shut the fuck up. Just shut up.
Miss Fame, you've talked about
being too cerebral and in your head.
-Yeah.
-And, in fact, how is your head?
-You know, I was talking with her--
-See, that's it right there.
-You missed that joke.
-I missed--
Wait a minute. Stop it.
You have to listen.
I've said that to you several times.
"How is your head?"
The answer's roaming around,
but you have to listen.
So I'm gonna ask you again.
Miss Fame, how's your head?
Fine.
Are you kidding me?
No, but knock it out of the park.
Can't wait to see you as twins.
-Thank you, Ru.
-All right.
-Ginger and Sasha.
-Hey.
Isn't this crazy? It's totally wacko.
That's kind of how I feel.
I'm not gonna lie.
So you're not happy about this.
What is your strategy to win?
We said, "Let's do something
that's completely outside of the box,
and let's be joined at the nipples."
-Ex-squeeze me?
-Exactly.
Yeah, we want huge, huge boobs.
Y'all better not try to have no kids.
No kids gonna suck on them titties.
-This is what keeps us together.
-This is gonna be quite interesting.
Girl, I'm worried. I feel
this looming presence over me saying,
"Something's about to knock you down
to the bottom, and this might be it."
All these hoes will make me feel
like it's day one all over again.
I know, day fucking one.
We have to make up the bitches
that went home to be our conjoined twins.
-Katya.
-Hi.
-And Mrs. Kasha Davis.
-Hello, darling.
-This is your big chance to come back.
-I know.
-So what's your idea?
-We're aging hookers from Atlantic City.
-Aging hookers?
-We were born connected by our vaginas.
-But we make do with the other orifices.
-There's several other options.
And we have worked together,
which wasn't my best work.
That's right.
I don't mean to harp on negativity,
but you two worked together
when you got booted.
We have worked together,
and it never really flowed that well.
We want to welcome... welcome you
to the first annual Despy Awards.
I'll let you get back to work.
-You have lots of conjoining to do.
-Conjoining.
If I have to go home,
and one of those eliminated whores stays,
I'm gonna have a wonderful time
going to their house and burning it down.
-Well, Kennedy and Jasmine.
-Hey.
Jasmine, how happy are you to be back?
As happy as a ship full of sailors
and one hot hooker.
-That's real happy!
-Yes.
Why did you choose Jasmine?
We come from the same background
as far as drag is concerned.
-Okay.
-And I can make her look like me.
If you're really good,
Jasmine gets to stay.
I would really like that.
She has a lot to offer.
I hope we are the winners,
so she can come back.
-Wow.
-We gonna whip it good.
Whip these hoes' asses, honey.
-Bitch, don't fuck it up.
-Yes, ma'am.
Get back to work,
and I'll see you in a minute.
-Right.
You see where the fire is, all right.
Bitch, I'm back up in this piece.
-Tempest and Jaidynn.
-Hey, Ru.
I got to say, of all of the twins here,
you two are the oddest couple.
Yes, honey.
-What are you planning?
-We're gonna do some disco divas,
-some disco mammas.
-Really?
Our back story
is that our mamma was the whore of 54.
And then one night, she had
multiple partners that created us.
We wanted to play on our size differences,
so my "business" is in her back.
-[Jaidynn] Like this.
-[Tempest] You can see us both.
-This time, you got to bring it double.
-Double duty.
-Duty, duty, duty.
-Yes.
-Hashtag "double duty."
-Okay.
-We ready, boo.
-Get back to work.
-All right.
-Thanks, Ru.
We have to slay this,
because I ain't going home.
-Pearl and Trixie.
-Hi, Ru.
-Hi, RuPaul.
-Together again.
-I know.
-Again.
Let's see. Trixie, what more
do you have to show us?
Before I left in a lip-sync accident,
I was told by the judges,
"You're funny, but you're not going for
gold." And so that's what I want to do.
Every chance you step out on that stage
is your chance to do it.
There are no dress rehearsals in life.
You've got to take those opportunities.
-So what's the strategy?
-There's always a prettier twin.
-Yeah.
-That's us.
We want to look related,
but possibly in an in-breeding accident.
All right, you kids get back to work.
Cannot wait to see your conjoined twins.
I'm bringing everything I had before
with new fire under my ass,
because I know what it's like
to fucking lip-sync and go home.
It's not cute. It's not cute at all.
[Violet] Is this you guys
making it sexy? Or very slutty.
That was a compliment, not a read.
Now I tell people when it's a compliment.
-You have changed the most.
-Do you think so?
-That was sarcasm.
-No, in a positive way.
I am most impressed
with the change in Violet. I'm blown away.
She's much nicer. She's not just biting
and sending out insults.
She's a contender,
and I think that's a great thing.
[Sasha] Temp, I'm so happy to see you.
Can I get a cut?
[Sasha] Ooh, I like that fabric.
-Girl.
-[Sasha] How's the game been for you?
I'm pulling the look together
for the both of us. We should be a team.
-[Sasha] Are you insane yet?
-I was gagged.
[Violet] You have no idea.
Come with me.
I need to take a moment
to process my feelings
before I go all Yosemite Sam and explode.
I love Sasha, but she's not pulling
her weight. I'm not a sewer's sewer.
-I'm not good enough for two people.
-Yeah.
If I went home,
I wouldn't expect to be brought back.
They went home for a reason.
I'm just freaked out.
[Jasmine] She look
like her nerves are bad.
-Who?
-Ginger.
She don't want none of us back.
This is the most nervous I've seen Ginger.
She's almost completely shutting down.
If I go home, I want it to be
because of something I did or didn't do.
We've really got to do something
to pull this together
-Good morning.
-Back in the messy workroom.
Come on, wig.
Today is our conjoined twin runway.
Someone's staying,
and it could possibly be Max.
-Are you ready for the challenge?
-I'm ready, honey.
-We're gonna be sickly now.
-Yes.
It's awesome to be back
with my bitch Jasmine.
But she's been a lot of sadness
ever since she left.
I told her to hold her head up.
You still have your dignity.
You still are Jasmine Masters.
And Jasmine tells me that no one
has ever told her to keep her head up.
Bitch, if I get back up in here,
I'm slaying, bitch.
I ain't holding my shit back.
She had a bad run,
but everybody deserves a second chance,
and I do believe she has
a lot to offer this competition.
-Has anyone ever painted you before?
-No, especially someone who looks like me.
I'm thinking about what my sweet...
devout Mormon mother
is gonna be thinking about all this.
-She's never seen the show but...
-Oh, yeah?
I did the whole reparative therapy thing,
trying to turn straight.
-Oh, dear!
-Yeah.
I did the whole conversion
to be straight therapy.
It was horrible. It's all about,
"You've got to pray harder, fast harder,
and date girls." Like it's suddenly
gonna turn you straight.
-Damn.
-It nearly destroyed me.
Talking about personal issues
and upbringings gives us an opportunity
to show those kids who are struggling
that there's someone who can empathize.
You know the suicide rate in gay kids
is way above the national average, right?
-It...
-It breaks your heart.
-It's crazy.
-It destroys lives.
Lucky for you, you had a realization
about who you were in reality.
It's kind of a miracle, and it's something
I'm really grateful for every day.
If you can help one kid
live another day, then it's worth it.
[Miss Fame] Is your mom
the closest person you have?
-Oh, yeah.
-Was she a single mom?
No. They broke up when I was young,
but she's been married for 16 years.
-[Trixie] Talking about your family?
-[Kandy] My step-father.
[Trixie] I had a step-dad too,
but we weren't close.
He was super abusive. I was over it.
The police actually took me out
of my home when I was 15.
-That's pretty sad.
-Yeah, it kind of sucked.
You don't really have a clear perception
of abuse, because it's all you know.
Right, exactly.
I had a hard time with my step-dad.
If I was being too sensitive or acting
too feminine, he would call me a trixie.
For years, that was one of the worst words
I could think of, so I took that name
and it used to have all this hurt to it,
and I made it my drag name,
and now it's something I celebrate.
If I hadn't gone through all that shit,
Trixie Mattel might not even exist.
[Cover Girl playing]
♪ Cover girl, put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe, let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
Welcome to main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, you brought the twins.
I did. They wanted to come out
and say, "Hey, kitty girl."
Super judge Ross Mathews,
are you up for some double trouble?
-Is it triple-X?
-Ha-ha-ha!
And one of my favorite actors,
Nelsan Ellis.
Baby, this ain't True Blood.
This is Ru Blood.
-Hi, Ru-alicious, dipped in beauty.
-So happy you're here.
-It's good to be here.
-And LeAnn Rimes,
-how are you? You look gorgeous.
-Thank you, I'm so good.
I don't know what I got myself into,
but I can't wait.
This week, our queens were challenged
to reconnect with former rivals.
And now, they're ready to make
their conjoined runway debut.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best twinsies winsies.
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
[RuPaul] First up,
Miss Fame and her twin, Kandy Ho.
[Michelle] Sexy, sexy sutures.
This look is a staple on the runway.
[RuPaul] Yes.
[Miss Fame] I'm in love with
this fierce surgical sisters look.
I'm giving you full surgical realness.
[RuPaul] Conjoined twins are like buses.
You don't see one all day,
and then two come at once.
[Michelle] Exactly.
[RuPaul] Jaidynn Diore Fierce
and her twin, Tempest DuJour. Disco divas.
Tempest is my plus-one.
[Jaidynn] We done tripped out of Studio 54
right onto the runway. Get into the disco.
[Tempest] I feel like a pioneer woman
who's being pulled by an oxcart.
[LeAnn] Jaidynn, don't have
Mexican for dinner.
[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport and her twin,
Jasmine Masters. Sister, sister.
Take that, Tia and Tamara.
[Kennedy] We are giving
fashion model turns
and we are serving up
Cotton Club realness.
[Michelle] One Beyoncé short
of a Destiny's Child.
[LeAnn] Oh, my gosh.
[RuPaul] Pearl and her twin,
Trixie Mattel.
Come on, let's go.
[RuPaul] Mama always said
Pearl was the pretty one.
[Michelle] And she wasn't lying.
[Pearl] We're doing this weird routine
where she won't cooperate.
[Trixie] I'm taking every opportunity
to reach for the joke.
I need to show the judges
that they made a mistake.
-[RuPaul] Trixie, how's your head... gear?
-[Michelle] She gives good headgear.
-[RuPaul] Violet Chachki and Max.
-[Nelsan] They have a Chicago look.
-[RuPaul] Yes, they do.
-[Ross] Roxie Hard-on.
[Violet] We're trying
to move symmetrically.
We are serving Carnivàle,
Cirque du Noir, and I'm living.
[LeAnn] I'm jealous of their asses.
[RuPaul] What a two-faced bitch.
Ginger Minj and her twin, Sasha Belle.
-[Michelle] Milk time!
-[RuPaul] Yes.
[Ross] Naomi and Wynonna Jug.
[Ginger] Sasha Belle and I are giving
new meaning to bosom buddies.
We are attempting to serve you
some Peggy Bundy realness.
[RuPaul] They definitely win
breast in show.
Katya and her twin, Mrs. Kasha Davis.
It's so good to see Joan
and Jackie Collins back together again.
[laughter]
[Katya] We are giving old, Atlantic City,
pussy-connected, leather-skin realness.
-[Michelle] They'll hit the slots.
-[Ross] They'll play the slut machines.
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
[RuPaul] Welcome, ladies.
Now it's time for the judges' critiques.
First up, Miss Fame
and her twin, Kandy Ho.
It's been done a few times,
the whole plastic surgery thing.
I agree. It's the least creative
of the conjoining, just at the hip.
Miss Fame, how's your head?
I've never had any complaints.
Got it!
-I am so proud of you.
-It took me weeks!
Next up, Jaidynn Diore Fierce
and Tempest DuJour.
Your legs stretch up to the heavens.
-Are you talking to me?
-Yeah.
I thought the concept was really cute.
It's a bit basic.
It's a tough stage
for y'all to be on tonight.
[RuPaul] Next up,
Kennedy Davenport and Jasmine Masters.
I know you're both pageant girls,
which is why this is predictable for me.
Michelle, I just disagree.
You walked out here,
and you held your poise and your face,
but in that great kind of stupid I love.
We was thinking
Miss Ella and Miss Billie Holiday meet up,
and we're fighting for the mic,
and she always singing my note.
When you describe that, I totally get it.
I wish you would have brought that more.
Next up, twisted sister Pearl
and her twin, Trixie Mattel.
Good evening,
distinguished panel of judges.
This storyline is magical. I can't look
without cracking up at you, Trixie.
That's to your detriment, Pearl.
She's stealing the show from you.
It was nice to see Trixie shine.
And Pearl, you were in there with it.
-Thank you.
-Next up, Violet and her twin, Max.
-Oh, my God!
-Yeah, yeah!
It took Violet to get Max
to give me what I wanted.
-Honestly, I'm feeling this.
-She's gorgeous!
-I thought y'all told your story.
-Thank you so much.
But there was a lot of pressure to do
something that would make us bust a gut.
-And you didn't do that.
-Next up, Ginger Minj and Sasha Belle,
A.K.A. A Tale of Two Titties.
I love the idea.
I'm not crazy about the execution.
There's something white on the bottom
of your boobs, Ginger. What is it?
It might be hot glue.
I hot-glued this to me.
The boobs,
I wish they looked more like breasts.
Next up, Katya and her twin,
Mrs. Kasha Davis.
Listen, she's older than dirt,
but I know true talent when I smell it.
And she smells
like she just pissed herself.
I haven't laughed as hard
as I did tonight when you guys came up.
I've seen these women up at the casino
at the slot machines.
-The casino, the bingo hall.
-Yes!
-Sometimes you got to get ugly to win.
-High five. Ugly-beautiful.
-Miss Fame did our makeup. Can you tell?
-I know, she's so good!
Thank you, Katya. Thank you, ladies.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I will deliberate.
Between us quintuplets, what do you think?
Let's start with Miss Fame and Kandy Ho.
In this season, we've seen
a plastic surgery thing already.
Really, that's the best that you can do?
It's too easy, and the stakes
are too high to go so basic.
Jaidynn Diore Fierce and Tempest DuJour.
Standing next to the other queens
on this stage, it didn't stack up.
I wanted something more
and I think they could have brought it.
[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport
and Jasmine Masters.
I wish they'd gone over the top
with crowns, sashes, and flowers
and did the whole thing, over the top.
If they had connected at the head
or something a little weirder,
it would have worked better.
-[RuPaul] Pearl and Trixie Mattel.
-They were absolutely stunning.
-How fun was this?
-They were the best storytellers.
-[RuPaul] Violet Chachki and Max.
-They could've gone over the top,
but it would have taken away
from their beauty.
The biggest moment was me seeing Max
in a different light, and I loved that.
[RuPaul] Ginger Minj and Sasha Belle.
I couldn't get past the costume,
the construction.
I don't think I minded how shoddy it was
because it looked a bit like John Waters,
and that was always low-budget.
-But he attitude didn't sell that.
-It just felt, no pun intended, flat.
[RuPaul] Katya and her sister,
Mrs. Kasha Davis.
They brought the funk and the fun.
They brought the house down.
-Not to mention they were conjoined...
-[both] At the vagina!
-[Ross] Yeah.
-What's better than that?
Silence. I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Pearl, as a conjoined twin,
the judges found you creepy and sad.
Pearl, condragulations.
You are the winner of this challenge.
Trixie Mattel, that means
you're back in the race, girl.
I'm back, yay! I thought I was,
"Fourth episode, queen, bye."
I thought I was Mimi Imfurst.
Now I'm, "Me, me, I'm second chance."
Pearl, you've won your very own
custom website from Squarespace,
-plus a fabulous weekend in New York...
-Oh, hey!
...where you'll meet
with the Squarespace team
-to make your portfolio and online store.
-Yes!
This story has come full-circle,
taking Trixie out and bringing her back.
-Katya, you're safe.
-Thank you.
-Kennedy Davenport, you're safe.
-Yes!
Jaidynn, your disco inferno
did not set the judges' pussies on fire.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you're up for elimination.
Violet Chachki.
-You're safe.
-Thank you.
Miss Fame,
your plastic surgery story needed work.
Ginger Minj, you served tatas with hahas,
but the execution was... wah-wah.
Ginger Minj, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Frankly, I'm not surprised.
Stevie Wonder could see this one coming.
[RuPaul] Miss Fame, you're safe.
Two sets of conjoined queens
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me and save yourselves...
from elimination.
The time has come...
for you to lip-sync...
for your life!
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ Children, behave ♪
♪ That's what they say
When we're together ♪
♪ And watch how you play ♪
♪ They don't understand
So we're running just as fast as we can ♪
[Jaidynn] I got this big girl
strapped to my back, and I'm serving
hashtag "the best I can do
right now in the situation."
♪ And then you put your arms around me
We tumble to the ground, and we say... ♪
[Katya] Ginger and Sasha
are giving themselves a mastectomy.
Tempest and Jaidynn look like Larry Bird
and Raven-Symoné in a butt-fuck position.
This is the most epic lip-sync ever!
♪ Running just as fast as we can ♪
♪ Holding on to... ♪
No matter how much fun we are having,
this is my last chance.
This is The Hunger Games of drag,
doing whatever the hell it takes to win.
♪ I think we're alone now
There doesn't seem to be anyone around ♪
[cheers and applause]
Wow. That was outrageous!
Now, I've made my decision.
Ginger Minj, shantay, you stay.
Thank you.
You may join the other girls.
Jaidynn Diore, your first, middle,
and last name should be Fierce.
Your passion brought you here.
Share it with the world.
Now, sashay away.
Thank you so much. I'm just so happy
that I got to have this experience.
Thank you.
[Jaidynn] Love y'all.
I love you, baby.
Work that puss.
[Jaidynn] I'm a little bit devastated,
but I stayed as strong as I could,
and I learned a lot about myself.
I learned that I just want to be loved
and accepted for who I am, truly.
[RuPaul] Condragulations, ladies.
And remember, if you can't love yourself,
how you gonna love somebody else?
Unless, of course,
that somebody else is attached to you.
-Can I get an "amen" up in here?
-Amen!
All right, now let the music play.
♪ Take me up, up, up ♪
♪ Up, up, up, we can fly tonight ♪
[Michelle] Bye.