Previously, on RuPaul's Drag Race...
We're paying tribute
to the legendary director John Waters.
[applause]
-♪ It's time for me to play with... ♪
-♪ Don't, don't you play with... ♪
-♪ Yeah, come on and touch that hook ♪
-♪ Touch that poo ♪
Okay, cut!
It was hard to jump in with my lines
when the bitch before didn't say hers.
Ginger Minj.
Your performance as Edie
was a masterpiece.
-You're the winner of this challenge.
-Thanks.
-Pearl.
-I didn't realize you're the good Divine.
[RuPaul] Miss Fame.
As an actress, you don't have to say:
"Look at me, I'm bad." [growls]
It should come naturally.
Who deserves to go home tonight and why?
-[RuPaul] Fame.
-[Pearl] Fame.
-[Ginger] Fame.
-Fame.
Trixie got to come back so she should be
looked at with a magnifying lens.
There's a part of Pearl
that's too cool for season seven,
and she knows what I mean.
I don't know what she means.
I don't think I'm too cool
for season seven at all.
Pearl, shantay, you stay.
Miss Fame, sashay away.
[laughter]
Back in the workroom after elimination,
Fame's gone home.
"Continue to inspire. You're incredible.
I love you. Fame."
Oh, I'm gonna miss her so much.
With that being said,
take that shit off the mirror.
[laughter]
Fame probably felt really attacked,
because she was nice to everyone.
Everyone is throwing her under the bus.
It sucks.
Fame was really trying.
There are less deserving queens here.
-So congratulations, winner.
-Thank you.
Of all challenges to win,
that's fucking awesome.
[Ginger] Girl, how about Fame
throwing you under the bus?
I didn't expect that at all.
"Pearl knows what I'm talking about."
It's like: "No, I don't."
But her calling me out
gave me an extra kick in the ass
to floor the bitch in the lip-sync.
It was really, like, such a close call.
I really could have been lip-syncing.
Violet should be very, very grateful
that her Lisa Frank couture kept her from
being in the bottom two this week,
because her performance was abysmal.
Even if it kills me, I'll fucking come out
on top the next challenge.
Violet's strengths are her runway
but at this point in the competition
you have to be versatile.
If you only have one strength...
...you're fucked.
The winner receives a year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With our special guest judges, comedienne
Rachael Harris and Alyssa Milano.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
May the best woman, best woman win ♪
[music]
-Top six!
-[Trixie] It'd be five without me, sorry.
[Kennedy] Yeah, we are too.
It's very humbling to be in the top six
because you never know
when it's your turn.
-[Katya] Fame left me a note.
-Me too.
-Me too!
-[Violet] What does yours say, Pearl?
"Pearl, I love you.
See you in New York City."
[Blows raspberry] I can forgive her.
But I'll never forget.
-[Ginger] What do your notes say?
-[Kennedy] "My girl, you are a class act
and I'm honored
to have been a part of this with you."
Oh, you can read.
-"Stay strong, girl. You are so talented."
-"Violet, you are perfect."
It's so real!
You know what's real? The struggle.
-[alarm sounds]
-[RuPaul oohing]
[RuPaul] She done already
done have herses.
-Ladies.
-Hi.
Want to prance for somebody?
Somebody who loves you?
Well, if you can't love yourself,
switch partners!
Because it's time to look at drag
from both sides now.
Cha, cha, cha!
-[Katya] It's dancing!
-We're about to twerk!
-Hello, hello, hello!
-[all] Hi!
-You're all getting free cosmetic surgery.
-[Pearl] Ooh.
But you'll be doing it yourselves.
Sorry about that.
For today's mini challenge, you'll serve
some rich bitch reality realness.
Using clear plastic tape,
you need to nip and tuck your mugs
to plastic perfection.
And then you'll be shooting a stiff
and unnatural title sequence
for my latest series,
The Fake Housewives of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Now, you've got 20 minutes,
so ready, set, let it rip!
-Bitch, I look fishy as fuck.
-[laughter]
Katya has built a forehead out of tape.
She is serving Herman Munster realness.
Kennedy looks like she usually looks.
Girl, did you put any tape on?
[RuPaul] All right, ladies, time's up!
Masterqueef Theater presents
The Fake Housewives of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Some people call me a slut
but I'm also an alcoholic.
[RuPaul laughs]
I'm not the best cookie in the cookie jar,
but at least I taste good.
[RuPaul laughs]
When times get tough,
I just breathe through my nose.
[RuPaul laughs]
The secret to success
is being God's favorite. Shh.
[RuPaul laughs]
How do I sleep at night? [laughs]
Ask your husband.
[RuPaul laughs]
What's the best part
about being married to a sociopath?
The constant threat
of danger keeps you so thin.
[RuPaul laughs]
Ladies, you've never looked so... unusual.
The winner of this week's
mini-challenge is...
Violet Chachki.
The winner is Kelly Mantle!
[RuPaul] We'll be posting
these gifs at logotv.com.
-Now, are you ladies ready for more?
-Yeah.
For this week's maxi-challenge,
you must prance your padded asses off.
#Prancingqueens.
In pairs, you'll dance to mash-ups
like the Tango Vogue, the Charleston Twerk
-and the Country Robot.
-[laughter]
And there's just one more little detail.
For the first time in Drag Race herstory
you'll be decked out
in half-man and half-queen drag.
Think Dr. Jekyll and Mrs. Hyde Your Can.
Violet, you won the mini-challenge,
so you get to assign the couples.
Now this bitch gets to pair up
the teams. [scoffs]
-First, pick your dance partner.
-Katya.
Sorry. No way, bitch. You're on your own.
Unless you can help me win a challenge.
-How about the other queens?
-They're already paired off.
I'm gonna do Ginger and Trixie.
[RuPaul] And you're pairing
Kennedy with Pearl.
[Katya] So Violet chooses my partner,
Ginger.
I'm a little frustrated because
I can sew and dance, and she can't.
Now, tomorrow you'll get into half drag
using makeup provided
by Anastasia Beverly Hills.
Now, to win this challenge,
you'll need to apply the rhythm method.
Your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best half-woman win.
Yes!
-Do you know how to tango?
-No.
Arnold Schwarzenegger
and Jamie Lee Curtis.
It's, like, Spanish.
Violet and I are pairs for the first time,
and I'm not sure how this will go.
What's this? Okay, hold on.
Come back here! [chuckles]
This week's maxi-challenge makes me
wanna slap somebody's mama.
We have got to do
a prancing with the queens ballroom dance
as half a man and half a woman.
What the hell?
-Do you not dance at all?
-[laughs] Heck, no, ma'am!
-Not even the truffle shuffle.
-Can you robot at all?
Is this good? Is this right?
When I say: "I don't dance",
I mean: "I don't dance!"
-We could do the electric slide.
-What is that?
I mean, that's for the win.
-Hello, hello, hello!
-Hi!
-How are my prancing queens?
-Fabulous.
-Hey, Kennedy. Hey, Pearl.
-Hey, Ru.
-Now, do you dance?
-It's been a while since class.
But I do have it in my spirit.
I love it. I love it.
Pearl, are you good with choreography?
-Mm-hmm.
-I think you just answered that one.
Well, this is a great opportunity for you
to go outside of what you normally do,
'cause I want to see that.
[Kennedy] Pearl can't dance.
Choreographed dance and dancing
in the club are two different things.
I hope her personality shines through
and she just plays it out.
-Ginger Minj.
-Hi!
-Trixie, back together again!
-Ginger and Trixie, the sequel.
-I like to call it "the revenge".
-Oh!
What's the hardest part of this challenge?
What are you not looking forward to?
-We'll do it live.
-Mm-hmm.
So I think the pressure of that,
with me not being a dancer,
that's the one part
that keeps playing over in my head.
Yeah. What are you most worried about?
I hate to say
I got outshined by Ginger last week.
I'm not trying to have it happen again.
Okay.
-All right, well, get back to work.
-Thank you.
-Hey, ladies!
-Hi, Ru!
-Now, Violet, do you dance at all?
-I actually... I'm an aerial performer.
If I recall right, in the last challenge,
you had problems with rhythm and timing.
-I did.
-How will you work through that?
Own it, work through it.
I'll turn it out.
Those are famous last words around here.
I already said 'em once, I'm still here.
Yeah? Well, okay. All right.
Violet is sexy as hell,
but she has to bring something else.
[RuPaul] Ladies, gather round!
Soon you'll rehearse with Kym Johnson
from Dancing with the Stars.
And...
our very own Carson Kressley.
So, ladies, good luck and...
five, six, seven, eight,
don't fuck it up.
All right!
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha,
cha-cha-cha, to me.
And...
-And good, we have visitors.
-Oh, hello!
-Hi, guys.
-Hi!
So today I brought my really fantastic,
amazingly talented friend Kym Johnson.
She taught me on Dancing with the Stars.
She's brought great assistants today.
-You're doing the Charleston Twerk?
-Yes.
-Then let's get started with the routine.
-Let's do it.
And so with tricks and stuff,
can you do the splits?
-I can split, flip.
-Can I see it?
-[Pearl] Oh, my God!
-[Kym] Give it to me.
Whoo! Oh! Amazing!
-Yes, Kennedy.
-[Kym] Oh, my goodness!
-You can't do that?
-No.
I'm not gonna dwell on the fact that
Kennedy does a back handspring double axel
with a twist landing into a split
and I can't. I'll give them the energy
they've been asking for over and over.
-Grab ahold of his waist.
-Like this?
-Child's play!
-Walk it through.
-Try to keep your core really tight.
-[Pearl] Okay.
[Kym] In.
-[Carson] Pearl...
-[Kym] Yes.
-[Carson] A little gangly.
-Yes, she has to straighten those legs.
Her legs bent up in the air like that,
they weren't so attractive.
-Good luck with that.
-Mm-hmm.
-Pearl, have you twerked before?
-Never. [laughs]
-Never?
-If you can't twerk, shake your legs.
-Yeah.
-Like this?
Can we bring Ambrose out to show him?
-You wanna go hop, hop.
-See how cool that looks?
-No problem.
-Can you do that?
-Pop, pop, pop, pop.
-[Kym laughs]
Yeah, no, not so much.
As far as the choreography,
it's the technique that's lacking, so...
We got work to do, Miss Pearl.
-Hi!
-Hello!
I feel really good going in with Katya.
We have a good grasp on the vibe
and the style so we're gonna work it out.
I'm going to need Ambrose to come in here.
He's the voguing expert.
One, two, three, four.
Open it up on five, six.
Touch your cheekbone, seven, eight.
Sharp to the front on one.
Three, four, five, six, and Madonna.
Seven, eight, one.
-Totally!
-[Katya laughs]
-[Kym] I know it seems simple but--
-No, we know it's not.
[Kym] Oh. [laughs]
We start the choreography and immediately,
I'm totally freaked out.
Okay, fuck! No, sorry.
-Yeah? Good?
-It's just...
It's a lot. It seems really complicated.
-Lunge, dip.
-Oh, shit, fuck.
-[Katya] Sorry.
-[Kym] No.
With choreography, I can get it,
if I have about three to four months.
So then we're gonna walk.
One, two, and flick. Good.
-[Katya] Okay.
-[Kym] Want to try together?
One, two, up and down.
So like you're hopping over something.
Ooh! Ooh!
Just hop over.
You'll get it. Left, flick.
But then... almost-ish.
Keep breathing, keep trying.
You're gonna get this.
Violet cannot get this goddamn leg flick.
It's just flick your fucking legs,
try to kick your butt, do-- [groans]
It's very frustrating.
-[Kym] Fast, fast, turn! Get down.
-[Carson] Yes!
-Come up. Come up!
-[Violet cries]
Face, face, face! Turn!
Up! Yep.
[Kym] Madonna, walk, walk!
Katya, is that terror or confusion
on your face?
It's a little bit of both.
It was just pandemonium.
This could really be a disaster,
or it could be absolutely incredible.
-[Carson] We have a medic. They'll be OK.
-[Kym laughs]
-You'll have your work cut out for you.
-Yeah, no shit.
-Hi.
-Hello!
Our mash-up is country robot,
which is perfect
because this is like a kind of funny,
campy piece.
-So are you guys good dancers?
-No.
-I'm not.
-You look like you're worried.
Lord be with me!
You're gonna go bah, bah.
Keep your head to the front.
-Now, your head goes last.
-Oh, okay.
-Yes!
-[Kym] Yeah, how did that feel?
Terrible.
In the country we don't move like this.
We move nice and slow and fluid.
Slow being the key word.
And up, there, out, up. Feet together.
-[Kym] Almost. We'll get that.
-[Ginger] Hey, girl!
Ginger.
-How's it going?
-I'm okay.
-Yeah?
-I'm not in meltdown mode yet.
-I'm okay.
-Okay.
Let's try the country two-step.
One, two, three. One, two, three. Flick.
-Right, left, right, right, left, right.
-Good!
-Very nice.
-Very nice, then...
You're gonna jump off.
Oh, God!
-Put your left arm around her shoulder.
-[Ginger] Don't lean back.
[Trixie] I do yoga, I got it.
-I do frozen yogurt.
-[Kym laughs]
I look at Trixie like:
"I hope you've been working out, girl.
I'm a delicate flower. You're lifting me."
[Ginger] All right.
[Kym] One... oh, oh, oh!
No, no, no. Sorry.
Maybe a little more graceful.
-One, two, three--
-Ooh! I'm sorry.
-Ginger, is your insurance up to date?
-[laughter]
-Thanks, Obama.
-I won't drop her.
This is a chance for the judges to go:
"Trixie lifted Ginger. It was awesome."
So we jump one...
No matter what I do, I won't drop Ginger.
-[Kym] Oh, and arms...
-[Ginger] Aah!
-I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-Are you OK?
And then I dropped Ginger.
-Just rehearse like crazy.
-[Kym] Yeah.
We will, absolutely.
[Pearl] Oh, just another day
in the workroom, girl.
For this challenge, we have to dance
in pairs dressed as half man, half woman.
With only six of us, it's a one
in three chance you'll lip-sync.
So it's a different air in the room today.
-I did not sleep at all last night.
-Really?
No. I was literally up all night
doing the robot.
I have no clue what I'm doing, girl.
I'm like, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Yeah. I'm not a dancer either.
It's all about selling it.
It'll be who performs their song best.
I'm just afraid I'm gonna look like
Honey Boo Boo meets Rosie O'Donnell.
My biggest challenge with choreography
is going to be selling it as a sexy woman.
[Ginger] I don't see myself like that.
I am trying to pull everything together,
because I don't want to go home
and I don't want to set Trixie up
for failure.
I'm exhausted.
I thought it'd be some cha-cha shit.
But this is like legit-ass choreo.
-Lifts and dips...
-Lifts and dips.
Running around. You know what?
-It's really a pleasure to work with you.
-Oh! [laughs]
Violet is more likable than I thought.
I admire her confidence.
I'm ten years older than the bitch,
and I don't have that yet.
When you picked me, I thought:
"This will be interesting."
-And it's been so much fun.
-Yeah, I'm trying to be nice.
-[Ginger] Why start now, girl?
-[laughter]
The old lady brigade is still kicking,
honey, and talking shit.
[music]
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl, put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
Welcome to the main stage
of Rupaul's Drag Race.
A girl who always clears the dance floor,
Michelle Visage.
The thigh's the limit, baby.
Take it all the way up.
Style superstar and Dancing
with the Stars alum, Carson Kressley.
How did dance class go yesterday?
There were some good dancers and some...
how shall we say?
-Not so really good dancers.
-Oh, good. I can't wait.
The always hilarious Rachael Harris.
Hey, Kitty Girl.
Hello, milady, how are you?
-I hear you're a fan of the show.
-I am a big fan of The Snatch Game.
-We're big fans of your snatch game, too.
-Oh, thank you.
-Your snatch game is on point, girl.
-It is. It is. It's no joke.
Who's the boss, applesauce?
Alyssa Milano!
-Dear Lord, you are gorgeous.
-Aw, thank you!
-Hey, are you having a boy or a girl?
-Could you tell I'm pregnant?
I'm having a girl.
And I think we're gonna name her RuPaula.
Oh, my goodness, I love it!
This week our queens had to prance
in half man, half queen drag.
First, they're gonna shake their thing
on the runway.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
-Up first, Pearl. Oh, what a pretty lady!
-[Carson] Oh, hello, sir.
[RuPaul] Oh, yes.
Meet Pearl's better half.
[Rachael] I'm sorry. Is that
Justin Timberlake meets Keira Knightley?
-[RuPaul] Yeah.
-[Rachael] Wow.
For my masculine side, I painted
on more beard than I'm capable of growing.
For my female side,
I'm going for a classic roaring '20s look.
Both of them are gorgeous.
[Carson] -I got mixed feelings about this.
[RuPaul] -Do you, really?
[RuPaul] Drag queen has two faces.
-[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport.
-[Carson singing] Half a dream girl.
[laughter]
[RuPaul] Goodness, that's Peaches &amp; Herb!
I'm feeling very Save the Last Dance fish,
Vanessa Williams gussied all up.
And then turn around and give them Bubba.
[laughs] I'm feeling it, honey.
[RuPaul] She's really got personality,
split personality.
-[Alyssa] And a great ass.
-[Carson] I think it's half-assed.
[RuPaul] She done already done have
herses, and hises.
[RuPaul] Trixie Mattel.
She's country, and he's rock and roll.
[Carson] Half Dwight Yoakam,
half Loretta Lynn.
My gentleman character loves Jesus,
his pickup truck, and his girl.
And when I turn to my girl's side
in my square dancing dress, I'm adorable.
I'm giving them hoedown...
♪ Sissy that walk ♪
Instead of "that hoe fell down."
[Michelle] Is that a gun in his pocket
or is he just happy to see himself?
[RuPaul] You could tell this ain't
her first time at the rodeo.
-[RuPaul] Ginger Minj.
-[Rachael] What's up, Sass?
[RuPaul] Ooh, bam!
I am stomping down this runway
like a Clydesdale in heat.
Honey, I'm serving you
some country girl realness.
Queen of the double-wide trailer.
I flip to my boy side
and I'm trying to pick up Michelle Visage.
[Carson] Two tastes
that taste great together.
[RuPaul] Loretta Lynn and Conway Twitty.
[RuPaul] Violet Chachki.
-[Carson] Drama.
-[Michelle] Erté.
-[Rachael] Ooh, very stunning.
-[RuPaul] He missed a spot shaving.
I'm feeling like a mamacita.
I'm feeling like a Spanish prostitute.
And then, bam, Pablo.
I nailed the look, but what else is new?
[Michelle] "You must pay the rent!"
"I can't pay the rent!"
[laughter]
-[Alyssa] They'd have cute babies.
-[Michelle] They would.
[RuPaul] Katya.
She comes from a drag house divided.
-[Michelle] Meet me halfway.
-On one side, flamenco flapper
and on the other, her abusive boyfriend.
My feminine side is very coy and demure,
and then, bam, it's a man!
[Carson] It'll be a split decision.
-[RuPaul] Yeah.
-[Rachael] Oh, nice.
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
Let's get this disco ball rolling!
Now, prance, I said!
[music]
I'm in the Form Decor Lounge,
the queens are ready to let you have it.
First up, doing the Charleston Twerk,
it's Kennedy Davenport and Pearl!
[Charleston music]
["Freaky Money" plays]
♪ All up in the club I'm makin' money ♪
♪ Walkin' down the street
I'm makin' money ♪
♪ When I shake my ass
♪ Even when I sleep
I'm makin' money ♪
[Charleston music]
["Freaky Money" plays]
♪ I want your money, money, money ♪
♪ Crank it, m-m-money, money, money ♪
[Charleston music]
[applause]
Back in the Form Decor Lounge,
we're getting ready for a hoedown.
[Michelle] Dancing the country robot,
it's Ginger Minj and Trixie Mattel.
[upbeat country music]
["Lick It Lollipop" plays]
♪ Strawberry, kiwi, peach
Tongues tied, slur your speech ♪
♪ Cherry, grape, lemon, lime
Lick it slow, take your time ♪
♪ Strawberry, kiwi, peach
Tongues tied, slur your speech ♪
[upbeat country music]
["Lick It Lollipop" plays]
♪ Lollipop, lollipop, lollipop
I'll let you lick it ♪
♪ Lollipop, lick it, lick it ♪
[upbeat country music]
[applause]
Back in the Form Decor Lounge,
grab a rose and strike a pose.
[Michelle] Doing the tango vogue,
it's Violet Chachki and Katya.
[tango music]
["Adrenaline" playing]
♪ Shot ♪
[tango music]
["Adrenaline" playing]
♪ Can I get it to go?
Can I get, can I get it to go? ♪
[tango music]
[applause]
Oh, my gag. Amazing job, ladies.
Tonight, you're making our job
incredibly difficult.
That being said,
it's time for the judges' critiques.
First up, Pearl.
Okay, Pearl, you're a good-looking man
and a good-looking woman.
You're like a bisexual's dream date.
The dancing,
you are a little rhythmically challenged.
The stiffness helped with the Charleston,
not so great with the twerking.
Fantastic. What you lacked in technique,
you made up for in enthusiasm.
-It's clear you were having a good time.
-Yeah.
-That speaks volumes.
-What was it like working with Kennedy?
Oh, my God, we're probably the two most,
kind of "flazay da" sort of like...
-The most what?
-"Flazay da" sort of...
Are you saying laissez-faire?
I think he's trying to say blasé
and add la-di-da on the end.
-But he said "flazay da."
-Yeah, a little "flazay da".
Well, I asked
because I have an Aunt Flazay Da.
-All right, thank you, Pearl.
-Thank you.
Next up, Kennedy Davenport.
For the dancing, a bit of the energy
was a little laid-back.
-I felt that it looked effortless.
-Thank you.
I love the wheelbarrow move.
That's how I got pregnant.
I had a great time watching.
-Next up, Trixie Mattel.
-Howdy, y'all.
Trixie, I think you definitely nailed
the runway look
and you kept true to Trixie with that
dangling bottom eyelash, so...
-It's a bit campy. Obviously.
[Trixie] -Yeah.
-Just a bit.
-Just a little.
Your dancing was technically strong.
Maybe not so much robot,
but you nailed the country.
Next up, Ginger Minj.
I loved the attempt to butch up
when you showed the guy side.
-I coached her. I coached her.
-And it shows.
The dancing this week,
it seemed off for you.
Not that you were bad, 'cause you weren't.
Um...
This was so hard for me.
I was at my full mental capacity
because it was so out of my comfort zone.
-Where are the emotions coming from?
-My biggest fear is dancing in public.
Because I feel people are going
to judge me poorly
for how I look and the way things jiggle.
I didn't know any of your insecurities
and you could not tell.
-You were absolutely magnificent.
-I second that.
We just see this beautiful,
talented person that's having a good time.
All right, thank you.
-Next up, Katya.
-I loved seeing you with this black hair.
We're used to seeing Katya
in red hair and blond hair.
We haven't gotten the black fantasy yet.
-Ooh, girl.
-Well, I've had it many a time,
-but not from you, Katya.
-When I saw you come out on the runway,
I was like: "Oh!" You were coquettish.
And then when you turned,
and I mean this as a compliment,
it was very, like, hot, douchey guy.
-That is amazing.
-All right, "V" is for Violet.
-You were an absolute work of art.
-Thank you.
You are so exquisite.
Like, I kind of want to be you.
-Am I weird?
-Have your baby first.
-Maybe I'm gonna name my baby after you.
-RuPaula Chachki.
[Alyssa] There you go, perfect.
Technically, your tango,
you had just the right tone for it.
On some extensions, you got really low.
It was very tango, congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you. While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I will deliberate.
Now, just between us dance moms.
What the hell are we gonna do?
They were all good,
but we must choose the best and the worst.
We're gonna start with Pearl.
Of all of them,
Pearl made the hottest guy.
And she exuded confidence.
We usually see a zombie.
She's crossed over this line now
and she's really in the game.
I love that aloof attitude that she had.
Very "flazay da".
[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport.
-Did you get a look at her ass?
-[Michelle] Oh, yeah!
Must be jelly 'cause jam don't shake.
Kennedy was shining tonight.
She clearly was the strength in the duo.
The dancing was the con.
I know you guys think it was very strong.
There wasn't enough razzle-dazzle for me.
-But I liked that it looked effortless.
-Really?
-She was on fire!
-She looked bored.
She was a great twerker,
but there wasn't much energy in her dance.
-[RuPaul] Trixie Mattel.
-I might be alone in this one
but I had a really good time with Trixie.
I don't have the same enthusiasm
that Michelle has for Trixie.
For me, honestly,
it just left me a little like "meh."
I didn't see that glint in her eye
of, like, "I really want this".
-[RuPaul] Ginger Minj.
-I think her look on the runway was okay.
-[Michelle] The girl half wasn't exciting.
-Let's discuss them as a pair.
I know you're in a difficult position
and you're splitting hairs, but...
watching that performance, it felt jokey.
It just wasn't my cup of tea.
-[RuPaul] Katya.
-She looked gorgeous on the runway
but her boy side was just kind of "meh."
-Blah.
-Katya's choreography was very correct.
When I said that she was hot,
douchey as the male,
it impressed me
that she was able to go that masculine.
-[RuPaul] Violet Chachki.
-Tonight, her runway was the best for me.
-What artistry!
-[RuPaul] It took my breath away.
-[Michelle] Yes.
-She's a little bit like Bambi.
Very pretty, big eyes,
but when you ask her to move, it's like--
-Like Taylor Swift in heels.
-Yes.
But the tango's not an easy dance.
So for her to pull off what she did,
I think she did a great job.
Silence! I've made my decision.
I think.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your prancing and runways,
I've made some decisions.
And this week, I'm judging you in pairs.
Pearl and Kennedy Davenport,
we flipped for your flappers.
But were you one step
behind the competition?
Trixie Mattel and Ginger Minj
took us for a roll in the hey, girl, hey.
But was it a barn burner?
Katya and Violet Chachki.
You two make a striking pair.
But could this be your last tango?
Katya and Violet.
Condragulations.
You're the winner of this challenge.
I'm so fucking happy! You fucking bitch!
Sorry. I'm sorry.
[RuPaul] You've each won an original gown
from Mountbatten Concepts
and a gift card from Klein Epstein Parker,
made-to-measure suits.
You may step to the back of the stage.
Katya and I won, and I cannot believe it.
Actually, yeah, I can.
Pearl and Kennedy...
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Trixie and Ginger, I'm sorry,
my dears, but you are up for elimination.
It is breaking my heart,
having to go against Trixie.
But as much as I love her,
I am here to win.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies,
this is your last chance to impress me
and save yourself from elimination.
The time has come...
for you to lip-sync...
for your life!
[Trixie] I have déjà vu.
It sucks to do this again
but I'll sell it anyway, so let's do it.
Good luck
and don't fuck it up!
♪ Ahh... yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Heartbreaks and promises
I've had more than my share ♪
♪ I'm tired of giving my love
And getting nowhere ♪
♪ Nowhere ♪
♪ It's been so long
Since I touched a wanting hand ♪
♪ I can't put my love on the line ♪
♪ That I hope you'll understand ♪
[Ginger] I am so in this moment.
I'm feelin' this song.
[Ginger] You better believe
I have brought it.
♪ Words are so easy to say ♪
[Trixie] The last time I lip-synced,
I went home. Fuck that.
I'm channelling all my energy
into this performance.
♪ You've got to give it to me
Give it to me, give it to me, yeah ♪
♪ I need your love ♪
♪ Show me, show me, show me, baby ♪
♪ Give it to me, give it to me ♪
♪ If you're looking for devotion
Talk to me ♪
♪ Because my love is guaranteed ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
[cheers]
Come through!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Ginger Minj, shantay, you stay.
Thank you for seeing
something in me that...
makes you want me
to go a little bit further.
You may join the other girls.
Trixie Mattel,
you put the "try" in "country",
and I am so glad we got to see
more of your talents.
-Now, sashay away.
-Thank you so much.
[Trixie] Getting eliminated twice
is just as fun as the first time.
If they ask me back,
I'll stay home and play video games.
That's enough for me. That's a wrap.
My fierce five queens, condragulations.
And remember, if you can't love yourself,
how the hell you gonna love somebody else.
-Can I get an amen up in here?
-Amen!
All right, now let the music play.
["Fly Tonight" playing]
♪ Take me up, up, up, up ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, up
Whoa, oh, up ♪
♪ We can fly tonight ♪