[RuPaul laughs]
[music playing]
Greetings, earth queens.
I come in peace.
I'm Miss Fame, I'm 29 years old,
and I'm beyond-this-planet beautiful.
Well, it looks like I'm the only one here.
Thank God.
My brand is classic,
chic fashion model.
I think I might choose a center spot.
Center stage, it feels appropriate.
I'm ready to show everybody
what I'm meant to do,
which is leave a beauty mark
on the face of the planet.
Hi, fellas.
My name is Ginger Minj,
and I am a overweight, asthmatic,
chain-smoking cross-dresser
from Orlando, Florida.
I like to describe myself
as a glamour toad.
-You look gorgeous.
-Something subtle for groceries?
Just a little something
to pick up some apples.
I know that I will never be
the prettiest one,
but I will always be the beautiful one.
How are y'all doing?
My name is Jaidynn Diore Fierce,
capital F-I-E-R-C-E,
because I am what? Fierce.
Hi, gorgeous.
-How you doing? Come on, Miss Sickening.
-Okay, girl.
And is there another big girl?
I can only be the only big girl.
She's gonna serve you body. She's gonna
serve you everything you need to survive.
I'm always gonna give you life.
[laughs]
[Jaidynn] Uh-oh... Who is it?
Oh, la, la, la, la, la, la.
I'm Violet Chachki, I'm 22 years old,
and I am a one-of-a-kind collectible.
-Hey, gang.
-Come on, shoes.
How are you doing?
[Violet] My biggest strength
is probably aesthetics.
I'm very visually appealing.
Is that conceited?
-Miss Fame.
-Violet Chachki.
Violet Chachki,
you can't forget that. [laughs]
I've seen Miss Fame's work before, and I'm
pretty impressed, but not that impressed.
[Violet] Tall fish.
Well, it's about time.
My name is Max,
and I'm a starlet on the rise.
-And you're Max?
-Yes, I'm Max.
-Period? Just Max?
-Max, period or capitalized,
or any way you want
to say it or spell it.
Cool.
I do drag because I have the yearning
for old Hollywood glamour.
-Where are you from, Max?
-I'm from Wisconsin, actually.
[Violet] Wisconsin.
Well, yes, this is a contest for queens,
but not the Queen of England, girl.
-Can I look at your paper?
-Of course.
[Miss Fame]
Let me teach you a beauty trick.
[Miss Fame] Blot away that shine.
I don't know if that came across shady,
but thank you, Max.
C'mon season seven!
-[Miss Fame] Is this Russia?
-[Katya] With love.
My name is Ekatarina Petrovna Zamochkova,
but you can call me Katya.
[Jaidynn] Come on, accent.
I'm just your average, run-of-the-mill,
Russian, bisexual transvestite hooker.
Is this the Shulman Bar Mitzvah?
[speaking Russian]
Katya is at the intersection
of glamour and comedy.
You can find her right on the corner,
selling her ass.
-Is this Soviet Union inspired?
-It's my great-grandma's army uniform.
[laughter]
-I'm here! We made it, bitches!
-[all] Yes!
I'm Jasmine Masters,
and I'm 37 years old. Ding!
-How did you get this body?
-Girl, I don't know.
Jasmine is class and elegance.
Jasmine is... [snapping fingers]
...it.
-Where are you from?
-Nashville.
-Nashville, I'll be there. And you?
-Atlanta.
All right, Atlanta. Hotlanta, girl.
No one says that, but yes.
Okay, work.
Hi, my honeys, I'm home! [laughs]
Are there any other queens here?
Oh, just me, I guess. [laughs]
My name is Mrs. Kasha Davis. [laughs]
I'm an international celebrity housewife,
because of that one time
I performed in Canada.
-Nice to meet you.
-I like your tits.
-Mine are still bigger, though.
-[all] Whoa, whoa!
-Jiggle, jiggle, jiggle.
-I'm jealous.
I don't have any fat to push together.
This isn't Maury Povich.
My name is Trixie Mattel,
and I'm 24 years old.
Oh, my goodness!
Well, here's another comedy queen.
She has her overdrawn lips
and clown makeup. She is ready to go.
I'm a hair and makeup artist.
So...
I think a lot of the queens don't
necessarily get where I'm coming from.
Drag queens always say,
"Paint for the back row."
I paint for the check-cashing place
down the street.
I hope you girls have a sweet tooth,
because Kandy is
in the motherfucking house.
[Jaidynn] She's got a tag line.
I'm Kandy Ho, and I'm 28 years old.
-From Puerto Rico.
-[all] Puerto Rico!
Kandy is hot.
Kandy is candente.
If you touch her too close,
you might get burned.
[cheering]
-[Jaidynn] Look who walked in, bitch.
-'Sup?
I'm Pearl. I'm 23 years old.
I would describe Pearl as some kind
of robotic, Stepford Wife bitch.
-[Pearl] Hey, girls.
-[all] Hi, welcome.
I notice this black trim around her chin,
I'm thinking, "What the hell is that?"
But hey, you like it,
rock your own boat.
Come on, chin strap.
-Well, hello.
-[cheering]
I'm Kennedy Davenport,
and I am the dancing diva of Texas, honey.
-Wait, Kennedy!
-Yes.
-Oh, my God!
-That's me.
I spin, I kick, I flip,
I jump off the stage in 6-inch heels.
That's what puts the diva in it.
Get over here.
I wanted to meet you forever, girl!
I'm a big fan of Kennedy Davenport.
I've been wanting to meet her for so long.
Like, Ru turned the party for me.
Oh, my God! [laughs]
For real, y'all,
I'm geeked the fuck up.
I'm geeked! I'm geeked!
Hey, it's me.
Say hello to my little friend!
I'm Sasha Belle,
I'm 28 years old,
and I have been mentally preparing myself
for this for years.
[Miss Fame] Just anywhere will do.
I could tell you every episode,
what the challenge was, who went home.
I feel like I've cracked the code.
Hey, girls, what's going on?
I'm the next Drag Superstar
because I've done my homework.
Girl, please. No, sorry.
Next.
Who's ready for some hot tuna casserole?
'Cause mama's home.
Ugh!
[laughter]
[Jasmine] No, ma'am.
I'm Tempest DuJour,
and I'm 46 years old.
[Miss Fame] A baby!
My drag style
is influenced by Phyllis Diller
and the campy
and kitschy people of the world.
-Your baby is adorable.
-Thank you. It's Amber, Amber Alert.
[Max] Amber Alert.
Tempest, she's an old-fashioned drag.
She tries to be funny, I guess.
-So how old are you?
-[Jaidynn] Oh!
[Tempest] How old am I?
Really?
Who the hell does that?
Who in their first meeting says
"How old are you"?
[Tempest] You don't stop dreaming
at a certain age.
[alarm sounding]
[RuPaul] She is all ready to have hers!
Welcome, bitches.
-Your Ru-Ru here.
-[cheering and laughter]
You want to grow up
to be supermodel of the world?
You'd better learn how to sissy that walk,
girl, 'cause you're born naked,
and the rest is... Balenciaga!
Oh, my God.
What do you think it means?
Hello, hello, hello!
Fabulous!
Welcome, ladykins.
Now, I hope you're tucked tight
and ready for the ride of your life.
[all] Yes.
Because everything you think
you know about RuPaul's Drag Race
-is about to change.
-[all gasp]
Your first challenge
isn't just a photo shoot.
Oh, hell, no!
It's a fashion week extravaganza.
Presented by DKoye
the product, hair care.
To make
an unforgettable first impression,
you need to dig in your trunks
and model two
of your very best looks,
one from your spring collection
and one from your fall collection.
This is right up my alley, and I can't
wait for everyone to gag on my eleganza.
Your runway will be part
of this week's final evaluation.
Kill it on the catwalk
or end up fashion roadkill.
Your choice.
Dang, this is a lot for the first day.
They got us doing runways.
Hashtag too much.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[sighs] Why do fashion shows
always start so late?
For today's mini challenge,
we have to showcase
our spring and fall looks on the runway,
sponsored by DKoye, the product for hair.
This is not a mini challenge.
This is a maxi mini challenge...
with wings.
Oh, wait a minute, it's starting.
[RuPaul] Serving spring glamour,
Ginger Minj.
[Ginger] I'm doing runway for Michelle
Visage, RuPaul and Carson Kressley.
I think I can see her tool.
[laughter]
[Ginger] I know I can excel
at anything I put my mind to.
[RuPaul] Kandy Ho.
Milan, Paris, New York...
Pacoima.
[Kandy] I'll give you face, I'll give
you ass, I'll give you legs.
This Latina,
she's coming for all of you.
[RuPaul] Max.
[Carson] Yes, darling. Sell the garment.
I'm making sure that I'm delivering,
and I get to fully portray the character.
[Alaska] I've had pelvic exams
more thrilling than this.
[RuPaul] Jaidynn Diore Fierce.
[Carson] It's very Apollonia.
Apollonia six and seven.
-[RuPaul and Carson] And eight and nine.
-[Michelle] All the girls.
-[RuPaul] Katya.
-[Carson] Oh...
-[Carson] I do love a onesie for spring.
-[RuPaul] Yes.
-Excellent use of the cape.
How dull.
[RuPaul] Mrs. Kasha Davis.
[RuPaul] I love you,
but give me Park Avenue.
[Michelle laughs] Yes.
Mrs. Kasha Davis is a lady.
Anybody can be a girl,
but it takes a lot of balls to be a lady.
[RuPaul] Mitzi Gaynor.
Trixie Mattel.
[Michelle] We finally know
what happened to Baby Jane.
My family's Native American.
We grew up very, very poor.
But Trixie, she has it all.
The biggest problem in her life is
what to wear the next day.
[RuPaul] Next up, Pearl.
-[RuPaul] Fur for spring.
-[Carson] Yes.
[RuPaul] Blame it on climate change.
Bitch, I'm from New York,
and you can wear fur in spring, okay?
[RuPaul] Tempest DuJour.
[Michelle] Who is under that skirt?
[RuPaul] My first guess
would be Jimmy Hoffa.
[Michelle]
Oh, Geraldo should have gone there.
♪ Sexy, sexy drag queen ♪
[RuPaul] Miss Fame!
[Carson] I would read her,
but she's red all over.
My strongest suit is modeling. Ideally,
that will carry me to get that crown.
-I see a red bottom, and it's not a shoe.
-Oh!
[Miss Fame] I'm giving you
just a gag-worthy moment.
[RuPaul] Jasmine Masters.
[RuPaul] No jacket required.
[Jasmine] Jasmine Master is
bright as summer. I am here.
H-E-R-E, bitch, I'm here.
[Carson] Simple midriff.
It's tasteful.
[RuPaul] Violet Chachki.
[Michelle] Oh, dear, she has a toothache.
-[Carson] I can see her spleen.
-[RuPaul] Spleens are very in this year.
-[Carson] Spleens are the new orange.
-[RuPaul] Yes.
[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport.
Niecy Nash.
I'm old school and
a touch of new school.
[Kennedy] Everything is bigger in Texas,
and I fit right on in.
[Michelle] She needs a casserole.
[RuPaul] But not tuna.
[RuPaul] Sasha Belle.
I see those judges,
give 'em a little look.
I need to show them
how much I want this.
[Carson] She already has a fan.
[Alaska] Who uses fans anymore?
Now it's time to do our fall look.
Child, the struggle is real.
[RuPaul] Let's see what they're
serving for fall. Ginger Minj.
Ginger Minj is a plus-size diva.
She always wants to look
neat, petite, and ready to eat.
-[RuPaul] She's like a magazine editor.
-[Carson] Yeah, popular wildlife.
It's so hideous,
I think I'll put it on the cover.
[RuPaul] Kandy Ho.
Fur again.
[Carson] More fur.
It's shaved beaver, I believe.
[Michelle laughs]
[RuPaul] Max.
[Carson]
I'm having Jil Sander flashbacks.
-Yes, right?
-And I like it.
-[RuPaul] Very Tilda Swinton.
-[Carson] Very.
[RuPaul] Jaidynn Diore Fierce.
I see Chaka Khan.
[Carson] She's every woman.
This is definitely a signature
Jaidynn Diore Fierce look.
[Jaidynn] I'm the other,
other, other Tyra.
-[RuPaul] Katya.
-[Carson] Fur's back.
[RuPaul] Yes, fur is back.
[Katya] I'm giving you dead animal
camouflage, Duck Dynasty realness.
Pamela Anderson, I'm so sorry.
[RuPaul] Oh, my God, she killed it.
I mean, she really killed it.
[Michelle] Literally.
[RuPaul] Mrs. Kasha Davis.
-[RuPaul] Look at those curves.
-[Michelle] These are not for sale.
[Carson] I'm thinking Colombian
mother of the bride.
[Michelle chuckles]
[RuPaul] Trixie Mattel.
-[Carson] The handbag matches.
-[Michelle] Is that a sequins dress?
-[RuPaul] That is a sequins dress.
-[Michelle] Yes.
[Michelle] It's like two pigs
fighting under a blanket back there.
[RuPaul] Next up, Pearl.
You can't lose with black, you know?
[Michelle] She's a lady DJ.
[Michelle] Eat your heart out,
Paris Hilton.
I'm sure she's listening
to Born Naked, my new album.
-Of course.
-Can you hear us right now?
[Carson] Hello? Nothing.
[RuPaul] Tempest DuJour.
[Tempest] The look I've chosen
is intended to show
that I can have more than one kind
of campy, kitschy look.
-[Carson] I like the quilted poncho.
-[Michelle] It's a car cover.
[RuPaul laughs]
Please make it stop.
[RuPaul] Miss Fame. Wow.
-[RuPaul] Golden lady.
-[Carson] It's not lame, it's lamé.
[Michelle chuckles]
[Carson] I do like the fascinator.
-I'm fascinated by fascinators.
-Me too, I could talk about them for days.
[RuPaul] Jasmine Masters. Wow.
[RuPaul] Purple Rain.
[Jasmine] Jasmine is
in a purple trench coat with black fur.
Well, not really fur.
Just some old carpet I straightened out.
[Jasmine laughs]
[RuPaul] Violet Chachki.
[Carlson] Looking smart in tartan.
[Michelle] Getting a reveal.
[all] Oh!
[RuPaul] Bay City Roller.
I'm giving you tartan eleganza. Being able
to serve two looks in one is a talent.
It's okay.
[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport.
Yes, she's going back to her roots.
-[Michelle] All that green.
-[RuPaul] She's a sexy choir master.
[Carson] Yes.
[Michelle] Exactly what I was thinking.
[RuPaul] Sasha Belle.
Oh, my word!
-[Carson] Fan's back. Wow.
-[Michelle laughs]
-[Carson] What's going on in front?
-[Michelle] The underbelly of a lobster.
♪ Cover girl, put the bass in your walk
Head to toe, let your whole body talk ♪
-[RuPaul] I want one in every color.
-[Carson] Now we know what to wear.
-[Michelle, RuPaul] Yeah.
-I'll be wearing lobster.
Yeah. I go for my first
shell fitting next week.
[Carson] Oh, God!
Hi, everybody.
It's so nice to finally meet all of you.
Everybody's taking off their drag, and I'm
like, "Who the fuck are these people?"
Trixie... Did somebody from the crew
just wander into the workroom?
Pearl? Trade.
Ginger's transformation is remarkable.
She goes from Kathy Bates to Bob Hoskins.
-Hello, hello, hello, ladies!
-[all] Hi!
Well, well, well. This is the most
draggedy season premiere ever!
And we're just getting started. Pit crew!
[cheering, applause]
-[applause]
-Oh, my goodness!
Oh, my goodness!
I think the new pit crew member
may be Jewish.
[cheering]
Mazel tov.
All right, ladies,
the pit crew arrived in the buff
because for the first time
in Drag Race her-story,
you'll be making your
main stage debut...
naked...
-...and afraid.
-[hooting]
[screams]
You need to create a resort-wear look
that tears away to reveal
a nude illusion.
Because you were what?
Hashtag, born naked and the rest is drag.
No tea, no shade, no pink lemonade,
but looking at some of these queens,
I'm thinking, "Ru, you don't want to see
these girls naked. I know you don't."
The Maxi Challenge this week is
to create resort wear that has a tear-away
to reveal a nude illusion.
I pride myself on utilizing literally
none of my natural features,
so a challenge where I compete
with these beautiful fishy girls
with perfect bodies
is a worst-case situation.
I'm just hoping
this looks expensive.
My brand that is Miss Fame is
runway shows, fashion magazines, glamour.
So I love this challenge.
I really want to win badly.
That looks resort-y.
Does anybody have scissors?
Be a good Christian and let me use them.
-Hey, cutie girl.
-[all] Hi.
-How are my nudie-patootie?
-[Jasmine] Nude.
-Well, Tempest DuJour.
-RuPaul.
I'm excited to see what you come up with.
I know you're a costume designer.
I am. I teach it,
so I feel a little pressure
from my students who'll be watching this.
When you auditioned a few years ago,
you were still heavy.
-Yeah. I was just under 400 pounds.
-Ex-squeeze me?
I'm trying to lead by example.
That was the catalyst for the weight loss.
Part of it was,
I gotta be alive for these kids.
I've been with my husband now
for eight years,
and I have two amazing
and beautiful adopted children.
I'm at a place in my life now where
my children are more important to me
than that bucket of fried chicken.
I'll let you get back to work.
I want to see what you come up with.
-Thanks, Ru. Bye.
-Thanks.
-Kandy Ho.
-Hey, mamas.
From the Ho family of products.
Tell me about your nude illusion.
Traditionally on our show,
Puerto Ricans like to show a lot of body.
I love to show body.
I think this runway is right on my alley.
-It's on your alley? [laughs]
-Yes.
-Okay. Do you know how to sew?
-I don't.
How do you become a drag queen
without knowing how to sew?
I think it takes more than sewing,
because you can know how to sew,
but you can have
the worst taste ever.
Any sensible queen should know
how to make a dress.
You know, it's part of the game
you have to play.
Oh, bitch!
-Why, Jasmine Masters!
-Yes, mother Ru?
What are you planning
for the reveal on the main stage?
It's like a butterfly in a cocoon.
-I've heard of those, yes.
-I'm going to be
some type of a cocoon that grows.
So, as I'm walking down the runway,
I'm gonna grow.
The butterfly is actually in the cocoon.
This is the cocoon.
-Right...
-Which is me, the butterfly.
-You know, like a butterfly in a cocoon?
-Uh-huh.
Every step that I take down the runway,
the butterfly inside is growing.
Oh, yeah.
So once I get to the end of the runway,
the butterfly is there.
Okay, great. Great.
Well, keep working. All right.
Jasmine's resort tear-away
is two hula hoops with fabric around it.
Who the hell is going
to a resort wearing that?
All right, ladies. Get ready to
put on a show, and then take it all off.
Good luck!
And remember, don't fuck it up.
-[Trixie] Your partner, are you married?
-Yeah. We got married last year.
[Trixie] My boyfriend's family,
last Christmas, they really liked me.
Then they found out about drag
and called him in a panic.
-"Don't be with somebody like that."
-[Miss Fame] For real?
They don't like drag.
I don't understand how they don't get
that it's just me playing a person.
His mom said, "Trixie's clown drag
makes me sick to my stomach."
[Miss Fame] Oh, my God.
They were right about one thing.
[laughter]
-This is really happening.
-[Violet] I know. Someone's going home.
I am terrified for this elimination.
We have to be naked,
and I have the body
of a 55-year-old Irish rock climber.
Give me a fucking break!
[First chords of "Cover Girl" playing]
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl, put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe, let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race. Well, look at you!
-It's like the gay Mount Rushmore.
-[laughter]
My bosom buddy, Michelle Visage.
You're serving a little Britney there.
It's either this or a snake.
I chose this.
Carson Kressly.
I'm so glad you joined the queen-dom.
I'm glad to be here.
And look who's back,
the other Miss Ross,
Ross Mathews. I'm glad to have you
in my big opening.
-[Ross] That's a first.
-[all laugh]
And our extra special guest, the funniest
woman in the universe, Kathy Griffin.
Ru, I brought my real smile
and a lot of fake hair.
[RuPaul laughs]
-[in a deep voice] Me too.
-[all laugh]
This week, our queens were challenged
to show off
their best spring and fall fashions.
Tonight, they're ready to debut
their tear-away resort wear
in the first ever naked runway.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
[RuPaul] Up first is Russia's own Katya.
[Ross] Katy-awesome.
[Katya] It is my dream to walk
down this main stage runway,
and I have to do it naked!
-I rip off the thing...
-Oh!
[Katya] And I'm giving you
Russian red hippie realness.
I think they're buying it. When in doubt,
show 'em your asshole! I don't know!
[Michelle] She dropped something.
-[Kathy] What an ass!
-[Carson] Thanks.
-No, her.
-[RuPaul] Her fringe matches the drapes!
[laughter]
[RuPaul] Mrs. Kasha Davis.
[Michelle] Mrs. Roper Realness.
[Kasha] The runway is surreal. I get
to center, pull the Velcro, and I'm naked.
I slipped it off because my husband
was on the side of the pool.
[Kathy] I could put
a saddle on that camel toe.
[laughter]
[RuPaul] Remember that time
Jo Anne Worley posed for Playboy?
[Michelle, Carson] No.
[RuPaul] Sasha Belle.
[Michelle] Diane von Fistenberg.
[Sasha] I'm feeling amazing.
[Sasha] I'm giving you J-Lo just waking up
from a one-night-stand in the Bahamas.
[RuPaul] Well, it looks like everybody's
got a little bit of black in them.
[RuPaul] Sasha Belle,
you could ring my bell, girl.
-[RuPaul] Miss Fame.
-[Michelle] I want to live forever.
[Miss Fame] I'm wearing a custom Miss Fame
fashion poncho. And then: bam.
-[Ross] Hello.
-[Miss Fame] And I'm shining like a star.
-I'm a Goddamn brand.
-[RuPaul] She serves Eve. Summer's Eve.
[laughter]
[RuPaul] LaGuardia, Newark, Kennedy.
-[RuPaul] She's almost there.
-[all] Oh!
[Michelle] That's not a Brazilian,
it's an Egyptian.
[Kennedy] Honey, I am feeling it.
Beautiful, sexy, the runway is mine.
[RuPaul] She has quite
a back story going on.
[laughter]
-[RuPaul] Tempest DuJour.
-[Kathy] She is of the day.
[Michelle] Let me just take this off.
It's a little warm in here, isn't it? Oh.
[Tempest] I don't have fish to serve,
so I'm gonna give them crabs.
-[Carson] They might as well be gold.
-[Kathy] Where did you get your belt?
-[Michelle] Red Lobster.
-[Ross] I love their cheese biscuits.
-[RuPaul] Trixie Mattel.
-[Ross] She can't play with no balls.
[Trixie] I'm valley girl,
she's at the resort, playing tennis.
-[Michelle] Show your birdie.
-[Trixie] Surprise!
It kind of looks like a doll,
so I'm giving you hinges.
Life in plastic is fantastic.
[Kathy] A living doll.
[Rupaul]
She's like Skipper's sister, Stripper.
-[RuPaul] Pearl.
-[Michelle] Oh.
[Carson] That's what I call
Greek Goddess dressing.
[Michelle] Let's see your clam, Pearl.
[Pearl] My resort tear-away look
is tacky, '90s, Versace-inspired,
and bubblegum pink pearlfection.
[RuPaul] It's like a runway on Ambien.
[Kathy laughs]
-[RuPaul] Max. Brace yourself, ladies.
-[laughter]
[Max] Nothing says resort like polio.
-[all] Wow!
-[Michelle] Yes!
[RuPaul] She can strip! It's a miracle!
[Max] As I'm walking down the runway,
I'm clinging for dear life to my crutches
like a wounded predator.
[Michelle] This is Helmut Newton's
Nadja Auermann shoot.
-[RuPaul] Yes, it is.
-[Carson] Using her props as a crutch.
-[RuPaul] Ginger Minj.
-[Michelle] Good morning, star shine.
-[Ross] Look at her.
-[Michelle] Sweet little lemon drop.
-[all gasp]
-[Ross] We have a crack problem.
[RuPaul] That's the kind of crack
you'd find on the street.
[Ginger] My concept is to be naked,
but still classy.
I'm southern. I like to be classy.
-[RuPaul] Impressive pearl necklace.
-[Kathy] They can be so messy.
[Michelle]
Especially when they're layered.
[RuPaul] Jasmine Masters.
♪ Now, sissy that walk ♪
[Jasmine] I drop the cocoon
and a butterfly is coming out.
[Ross] She got circumcised, look.
[Jasmine] You see a little tits,
a little ass and a little cuh-cuh.
When I dropped that cocoon,
baby, it was all she wrote.
-[Ross] Afro, she did it.
-[Michelle] Yes, she did.
[RuPaul] Now, Jasmine appeals
to our fringe audience.
-[Carson] Yes.
-[laughter]
-[RuPaul] Kandy Ho.
-[Carson] What did you call me?
[Kandy] I'm giving you Greek Goddess.
[all gasp]
[Kandy] I take my tear-away off,
and I'm just giving you curves.
I'm giving you this sexuality
that none of the other girls have.
-[Carson] Nice buns, all three of them.
-[RuPaul] Moon over Puerto Rico.
[Kathy laughs]
[RuPaul] Jaidynn Diore Fierce.
-[Ross] Oh, Beyoncé who?
-[Kathy] Hi, gorgeous.
[Ross] She wishes she had those curves.
[Kathy] Oopsies, nudity!
[Ross] Was that supposed to happen?
[Jaidynn] I'm giving the judges curves
and swerves and plumpiliciousness,
and I got to show the judges
how sexy I am.
[Michelle] Touch all of this skin, honey.
[RuPaul]
I like big butts and I cannot lie.
[Kathy] No.
-[RuPaul] Violet Chachki.
-[all] Aw.
-[RuPaul] Blanche Dubois.
-[all nod]
[Ross] Bam, there it goes. Yes.
-[Carson] Take it easy.
-[all gasp]
-[RuPaul] The devil wears "nada".
-[Kathy] Uh-huh.
[Violet] I feel great. I love being naked.
I love my body.
I'm comfortable with just a piece
of duct tape on and a smile.
[Carson] This reminds me
to never eat, ever.
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
Welcome, ladies. When I call your name,
please step forward.
Ginger Minj.
Jaidynn Diore Fierce.
Pearl.
Mrs. Kasha Davis.
Katya.
Max.
Trixie Mattel.
You...
are all safe.
[RuPaul] You may leave the stage.
And while you're at it,
put some Goddamn clothes on!
[Kathy laughs]
[RuPaul] Ladies, it's time
for the judges' critiques.
-[RuPaul] First up, Sasha Belle.
-Your fall look, crustacean chic.
-It was a little overwhelming.
-[Michelle] You're doing a nude illusion.
Why are you showing huge,
black undergarments?
I think I was confused
by the assignment.
Well, to be fair, all of the girls
were told the exact same thing.
All right, next up, Miss Fame.
On the runway, the looks are fantastic.
They're bold.
You look frighteningly fierce.
And I love a pointed shoulder.
Let's go back to Dynasty while we can.
I thought the little blue number was cute.
I just expected a little bit more.
Next up, Kennedy Davenport.
In that spring look, you are giving me
Oprah Winfrey. [imitates Oprah] Kennedy...
-Davenport!
-Yes!
I loved your Bob Mackie butterfly.
-If you readjust the girls, the nipples--
-I can't. It's the way it's painted.
-Michelle's surgeon can fix you right up.
-Yeah.
[laughter]
Next up, Tempest DuJour.
How did it feel walking the runway?
I just recently lost a ton of weight,
so doing nude body
is a cathartic moment for me today.
-Condragulations on your weight loss.
-Thank you.
On that note, your runway look tonight,
you're wrinkly, you're droopy.
You're a thin girl now.
Let's talk about your runway numbers.
I'm not a fan of quilt-like materials
because they tend to make us look bigger.
You just lost all this weight,
and you just put on 50 pounds.
Next up, Jasmine Masters.
How are you feeling up there?
I am so happy, I'm shitting out
happiness to be here.
I loved your "Cirque de So-Gay" tube
that you popped out of.
Then I was like,
"Take off the fringy thing!"
I want to see that gorgeous body.
More nudity!
And your fall look, I don't get it.
It just looks old and dated.
[RuPaul] Kandy Ho.
Nothing says resort
like a tunic with no pants.
And I was just like, "Oh, God, I can see
her chocha." That's Spanish for vagina.
You're a beautiful queen.
You've got the body.
Your contouring on the other hand...
Girl, this is not a nightclub. This is TV.
It looks like you literally
contoured on a beard.
No.
[RuPaul] Up next, Violet Chachki.
In the tartan look, when you put your
thing down, flipped it, and reversed it,
-I almost fell off of my chair.
-And speaking about a reveal...
I would've somehow liked to have seen it
jujed a little, 'cause I'm getting boy.
I actually really enjoyed
seeing your real boy body.
You had that essence of those crazy skinny
models that may or may not have boobs.
Thank you, Kathy.
Ladies, I have one final question,
and I want the naked truth.
Which queen has least
impressed you thus far?
-Sasha?
-I'd have to say Pearl.
-[RuPaul] Miss Fame?
-Jaidynn.
-[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport?
-Trixie.
-[RuPaul] Tempest DuJour?
-Ginger.
-The naked truth, Jasmine.
-Sasha, because she just came out plain.
-All right, Kandy Ho?
-Tempest. He is mature,
but I think in drag, you have
to upgrade yourself to not bore people.
Interesting. When we did introductions
the first day, she didn't say hello.
Her first response was, "How old are you?"
I wanted to know your age because you look
older, and your look wasn't my favorite.
I just wanted to know
where you were coming from. That's it.
-All right, Violet Chachki?
-Sasha.
-She kind of faded into the background.
-How did I fade into the background?
-I wore a lobster dress.
-[laughter]
Well, thank you, ladies.
Now, while you untuck backstage,
the judges and I will deliberate.
Okay, now, just between us
gay icons, what do you think?
-[RuPaul] Sasha Belle.
-Her nude-illusion look was kind of messy.
That body suit sucked.
Come on.
It had a black bra.
Misunderstanding, my ass!
-[RuPaul] Miss Fame.
-The fall-spring looks made a statement.
She's just so pretty.
I like a little stank on my drag queens.
The proportions of Miss Fame's body
reminded me of Marlene Dietrich
in the later years.
-She had a little stank on her then.
-Yes.
-[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport.
-I just ate her with a spoon.
She might get a little costume-y.
-Why is that a bad thing on a drag queen?
-No, I--
It's not like a star-trooper costume
from Party City.
I'd like to see that.
Tempest DuJour.
Her body suit was all saggy.
I wish she could pull it all together.
-But here's the thing, she's a costumer.
-Yeah.
The style's wrong, but the heart is right.
[RuPaul] Jasmine Masters.
I love the sassy kind of sister
with the NeNe Leakes hair.
-But the other outfit was so wrong.
-I want to see some fabulousness.
-Is that too much to ask for on this show?
-[all] No.
-[RuPaul] Kandy Ho.
-Girl, are you painting on a beard?
I had a beard once. She was wonderful,
but I don't bring her here.
[laughter]
Kandy Ho, Kandy who?
Look, don't you talk
to a 53-year-old comedian about age.
You picked the wrong panel, bitch.
[RuPaul] Violet Chachki.
Her fashion looks were high fashion,
and that's what I want to see here.
Tonight, I am getting boy
with a tape tuck.
I could not disagree with you more.
She took a risk!
-It wasn't feminine enough.
-[RuPaul claps]
Silence! I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Kennedy Davenport,
you're safe.
Violet Chachki, on the runway
and on the main stage,
you took fashion risks,
and they paid off big time.
Condragulations, you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
[applause]
You'll receive a gag-worthy supply
of DKoye the product, hair care.
[applause]
Yay, I won! I'm the winner.
I feel like I'll be saying that a lot.
Miss Fame,
you're safe.
Sasha Belle,
[sobbing]
Tempest DuJour, your runway presentation
left the judges feeling...
crabby.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Kandy Ho,
your fashion looks were worn,
and your nude illusion was,
shall we say, overshadowed.
Jasmine Masters,
your personality is off the hook,
but your runway fashions
looked off the rack.
Jasmine Masters,
-you're safe.
-Thank you.
Kandy Ho, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
What the fuck?
I did an amazing job.
There are other girls
who should have been in my place.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself from elimination.
[dramatic music]
The time has come...
for you to lip-sync...
for your life!
[Tempest] I'm thinking to myself,
"Hold your head up high.
Just show the best you have to show."
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ Geronimo, Geronimo
They're falling like they're dominos ♪
♪ Please believe it
And let that be the reason ♪
♪ Geronimo, Geronimo
They're falling like they're dominos ♪
♪ Sight beat the world we shall see ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Geronimo, Geronimo
These girls are falling dominos ♪
♪ They, they call me dynamo
But I be yelling vámonos - what? ♪
♪ And they be slain
I slay these bitches Double Dutch ♪
I slay these bitches, so what's up? ♪
♪ Jump ♪
I don't know what Miss Crab Lady
is doing in that lip sync,
but the bearded Ho is turning it out.
♪ Up and down jump ♪
♪ Now make your bootie bounce ♪
Miss Tempest, she got these squiggly
arms going on, and she is living,
so I'm living for her gig, baby.
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
[Ginger] Kandy's dance moves are fierce,
but it looks like she's gonna meet you
on the playground after school
and beat the shit out of you.
What's next, bitch, the Macarena?
[RuPaul laughs]
[cheering]
Ladies, I've made my decision.
[dramatic music]
Kandy Ho, shantay, you stay.
-You may join the other girls.
-Thank you.
Tempest DuJour,
this may not have been your day,
but I expect you
to take the world by storm.
-Thank you.
-Now,
sashay away.
I could not be more proud of myself.
You know, what means most to me
is what my kids see.
I want them to see
they can live their dreams,
have a chance to do whatever they want.
You're never too old or too anything.
Condragulations, ladies.
You have been reborn, naked.
Now remember: if you can't love yourself,
how the hell will you love somebody else?
-Can I get an "Amen" up in here?
-[all] Amen.
Alright now. Let the music play!
♪ Take me up, up, up, up ♪
♪ Up, up, up, up, up up ♪
♪ We can fly tonight ♪
Bye!