[RuPaul] Previously...
For this week's maxi-challenge,
you will prance your padded asses off.
-So are you guys good dancers?
-No.
-I'm not.
-You look like you're a little worried.
-Maybe a little more graceful.
-Ah!
[Carson] Your tango was very correct.
Katya and Violet.
Condragulations,
you're winners of the challenge.
[Katya] Oh, my God!
Ginger Minj. Shantay, you stay.
Trixie Mattel, sashay away.
Son of a bitch, girl.
Ugh. "Stay plastic, Trixie Mattel.
P.S. Spoiler alert:
Trixie doesn't win. LOL."
Oh, God.
It really hits home
when I see Trixie's message.
I'm sad that she's the one
that I had to send home,
but I'm happy that I'm still here.
But enough of this sad shit.
Congratulations to our winners.
-[Pearl] Yes!
-[Katya] Yes.
-[Ginger] You seemed surprised, Katya.
-I didn't know what happened.
-[Violet] We worked our asses off.
-[Katya] We worked really hard.
And I'm so proud of us.
Does being the only one
who has not had to lip-sync scare you?
Do y'all think my time is coming?
I just want to see you lip-sync,
'cause I haven't seen it this season.
Really, girl?
[Violet] How does it feel
to have a weakness?
I feel you've been strong
this entire competition,
but I feel like I've really got to see
your weakness this week.
I've got plenty of weaknesses.
What you don't see is when I go home,
I sob like a fucking baby,
and I come back in with my game face on.
-Never let 'em see you sweat.
-That's what the competition is about.
And don't rest on your laurels, bitch.
Because we all know that with only
one thread hanging, your ass is packing.
-Because there's how many now?
-Five!
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[RuPaul] The winner receives a year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With our extra special guest judges,
shake the dice, Santino Rice,
and Rebecca Romijn.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
May the best woman, best woman win ♪
[electronic music playing]
-[Pearl] Let's do this.
-[Katya] Ooh...
The old lady brigade has made it.
Can we hear it for senility?
Top five. You can count 'em on one hand,
and I'm one of them.
This one.
You came in
in this whole Russian doll thing.
I thought you were from Russia.
I was like, "They flew this bitch in?"
Most people who come to my show
don't know that I'm not Russian,
'cause I talk in this Russian accent.
Does anybody else do
other languages, accents or anything?
No, I can barely speak fucking English.
-[alarm sounds]
-Here we go, honey.
[RuPaul] She done
already done had herses!
-Hey, queens.
-Hey.
From Tuckahoe to Tokyo, whether you're
a couture queen or somebody's BFF,
make sure you stand by your brand.
Konnichiwa, bitches.
[laughter]
-Hello, hello, hello.
-[all] Hi!
Come through, ruffles.
[RuPaul] Ladies, at this point
in the competition,
you probably know what the other queens
are gonna say before they do.
So for today's mini-challenge,
it's your chance to prove it...
with puppets!
-Because why?
-[all] Because everybody loves puppets.
See?
Pick a puppet that represents
one of your competitors and drag it up.
All right. First up, Katya.
Step over to the gloryhole-elujah.
Dig deep for a puppet.
-Who'd you get?
-Ginger Minj.
All right. Next up, Ginger Minj.
Don't be scurred.
-Violet.
-Bitch, my hair is layered.
I don't know what they're talking about.
-[RuPaul] Pearl.
-[Pearl] There's something slimy in there.
[Pearl] Yes!
All right, Kennedy. You're up.
All right, Violet.
Get over there and stick it in the hole.
[laughter]
I don't have that much hair.
All right.
It's time to drag up your puppet
using supplies
from the Fabric Planet wall.
Go!
[electronic music playing]
Can I borrow one of your regular outfits?
I think it'll fit this doll.
-Try making something.
-I'll learn sewing when you learn acting.
Done.
The key to capturing my essence
is capturing my scent visually.
[RuPaul] Time's up.
All right, ladies.
Let the bitch-fest begin.
Hi, Kennedy. Start by telling us
where you got this inspiration from.
Girl, this is what happens
when a bad trick goes wrong.
He threw me into the embers
where I arose as a phoenix.
What was that look?
It's gonna go down in history
as the deranged Tony the Tiger.
Hi, everybody.
I want you to meet my girlfriend, Pearl.
Why don't you have any titty pants on?
I mean...
This is how we do it in New York.
-Does her mouth move at all?
-Oh, look at me.
[Kennedy] I love it.
I don't have to wear pants.
-Yes, you do, miss thing. This is drag.
-I mean...
-[snoring]
-[Kennedy] Miss Pearl.
Miss Pearl!
Miss thing!
These bitches need some new material.
I woke up a long time ago, goddamn it.
-Oh, wow, and who do we have here?
-That looks just like me.
-Hi, I'm Katya Slobonanobblebitch.
-Is that Russian? Are you from Russia?
No.
Go you, Katya.
I can't wait to see more from you.
Yeah, I can't wait too.
I'm gonna go smoke something.
Meth.
-Hi. What's your name?
-Ginger Minj, from Leesburg, Florida.
About three minutes north of Gatorland,
which is where I learned to do my makeup.
Wow! So alligators
taught you how to do your makeup?
I spray my forehead black, let it
drip down and blend that into my cheeks.
Wow. That's revolutionary.
Your name, Violet Chachki, is interesting.
Where does that come from?
I wanted to figure out what was beautiful
and completely worthless.
A tchotchke!
I'm trying to train myself
with this corset.
I'm really trying to get down to 2 inches.
-Why haven't you gotten there yet?
-Your wrist is fat and shoved inside me.
I'll never get down to 2 inches.
-And scene.
-Oh, my God!
Ooh, y'all some shady ass ladies.
But one of you
was quite the puppet master.
The winner of today's mini-challenge is...
Ginger Minj!
Ah! I take credit.
I'll post all the best bitch-fest moments
at logotv.com.
Ladies, America's next drag superstar
needs to know how to brand her charisma,
uniqueness, nerve and talent.
For inspiration, you'll be joining forces
with a global marketing phenomenon
-worth over $8 billion.
-Is that a real number?
A girl who's besties with Miley Cyrus,
Lady Gaga, and Nicki Minaj,
and has her own line of makeup,
jewelry, dolls.
Ladies, please give
a big drag-race welcome to...
Hello Kitty!
Hey, Kitty Girl. Come on down here.
Konnichiwa, bitches.
-Oh, my God.
-Hi!
It's so great to have you on the show.
For this week's maxi-challenge,
you'll be designing and creating
your very own runway eleganza,
using products provided
by Hello Kitty herself, #HelloKittyGirl.
Although your dress
will be made with Hello Kitty items,
the final look needs to scream you.
Now, Ginger Minj, you won the bitch-fest.
So you get a head start
on grabbing all the goodies.
-Are you ready?
-I'm ready.
-Go!
-Ooh!
I don't know what I'm gonna make
because I'm not a costume designer.
So I just start grabbing
whatever I can find.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Let's go this way, darling.
[electronic music playing]
I have had my fill
of these damn design challenges.
Please don't make me sew again.
This is the part of Drag Race
I don't like.
Kennedy's stressed about this challenge.
Katya seems stressed about this challenge.
These bitter old ladies
got a lot of work cut out for them.
Take your Metamucil, girls.
This is gonna be a rough one.
[electronic music playing]
Ugh!
We have to create a couture look
entirely out of Hello Kitty materials.
I'm all about having concepts
and having them executed flawlessly.
I'm excited to do this fucking challenge.
You have no idea.
I'll do black and pink, and then do
my thigh boots and juice them up
with my fishnets
and give that kind of look.
I want to make it look sexy,
like, Becky, who's 21 years old
with a hot boyfriend
and who have a fetish for Hello Kitty.
-What's your plan?
-I don't know.
I'm into period looks,
and I haven't done a '60s thing yet.
-Oh.
-So I want to go, like, mod.
-What about you?
-I don't know. I have no fucking idea.
I could use this to shield
the judges from my horrible outfit.
-Like really fierce.
-Oh, my God. How avant-garde is that?
-It looks so great from the side...
-Yes, Gaga, come through.
Lady Gaga, you look amazing.
Work! Oh, it's Katya.
-We'll get some inspo.
-I'm working on it.
-Maybe I can help.
-Don't pressure me!
Katya has relied on humor her whole life.
Presenting a fashion thing is a struggle.
She has so much talent,
and I just wish she would focus.
-You have something I don't have.
-Beauty?
You have this hairy mole on your back.
No, you have this unshakeable confidence.
-I so admire that.
-Thank you.
Drag is all about confidence, I feel.
That's why I like it.
I'm gonna try to absorb
a bit of Violet's confidence.
This is my confident face.
[hinges squeak]
-Hello, hello, hello. Look who's back.
-[all] Hi!
-[Violet] Oh, my God!
-[Kennedy] Oh, my goodness!
It's Santino. He's here to help you
with your Hello Kitty eleganza.
Santino Rice walks through that door,
and I flood my basement, bitch.
That is one sexy man.
Newark. LaGuardia. Kennedy.
This looks gorgeous, these little bows.
-I'm accessorizing with the bows.
-Uh-huh.
I'm dying that their bows are gone.
-I want to know what's Kennedy's style.
-Kennedy is a catsuit queen.
-I'm an entertainer. I dance, so...
-Yeah.
-Do you know how to make a catsuit?
-No.
Oh. Okay.
Like somebody who love enchiladas
but don't know how to make 'em.
In my head I'm like, "I am not creative,
but what do you want to do?"
You are creative. That's why you're here.
So let's see something.
Get back to work. I cannot wait
to see what you come up with.
Thank you very much.
-Violet Chachki.
-Hi, RuPaul.
-Hi. Meet Santino.
-Hi, Santino.
-Hey, how are you?
-You look so dapper.
Thank you.
Now, I wanted you to meet Santino
because he also studied fashion,
knew all of the silhouettes.
-Do you have any questions for Santino?
-Can we go to Red Lobster?
I want to do something kind of...
bubblegum pop mod meets Harajuku.
Everything you described to us
is really incredible.
This boning you're using,
that's for your head?
[RuPaul] Oh, my goodness. Wow.
Violet looks like the human gaydar, bitch.
What the hell?
Now, you've set the standard really high.
-Let's see something amazing out of you.
-I will do my very best.
All right, get to work,
and we'll see you out there.
-Hi, Katya.
-Hi.
You won the challenge last week.
How will you keep the momentum going?
I'm just-- I don't know.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
If you start doing something,
it will lead you to where you need to be.
But if it stays in your head,
you're not gonna get out of the gate.
I would say first and foremost,
if you can somehow incorporate Hello Kitty
into who Katya is,
you're gonna be all right.
-Listen. The clock is running out. Okay?
-Make it work.
I don't want to fuck up this challenge,
and I have no idea what I'm gonna do.
-Hey, Pearl.
-Hi, RuPaul. Hi, Santino.
-So, flazéda.
-Flazéda. It's the new hashtag.
-It's spreading like wildfire.
-It sure is. It's all the rage.
-Did you make that up?
-I guess so. I thought it was a real word.
-Maybe I thought of it in a dream.
-Yeah.
Just because you dreamt it
doesn't make it any less real, Pearl.
What can Pearl bring to this challenge?
Maybe some sort of pooled skirt,
maybe even like a hobble dress.
-[RuPaul] Very flazéda.
-Very that.
-The skirt's gonna be out of this blanket?
-This plush, yeah.
I'm interested to see
how Pearl's gonna do with this,
because she is always long,
drapey and flowing.
None of this fabric
is particularly long, drapey, or flowing.
Hello Kitty, good-bye, Pearl.
-Ginger Minj.
-Hi.
You don't sew?
-No. I don't.
-How far along are you in this?
-I cut out this panel so far.
-That can be a problem, Ginger.
-You've been in the bottom two twice.
-And both of those design challenges.
Do you have
a foundation garment that you wear?
I have shorts with the hips
and the ass built into them.
-And you cinch your waist or...
-I don't.
When I first started drag,
my drag mother said to me,
"It looks stupid when big girls corset
and got stuff bubbling here and there."
If you make something for your body,
it will accentuate the positives
and eliminate the negatives.
I would really encourage you
to cinch in your shape a little bit.
You look a little defeated here.
-I'm trying to figure out my next move.
-Well, we're running out of time here.
So get to work and let those juices flow.
I want to crawl underneath
the workstation and fucking die.
All right, ladies, gather around.
Tomorrow, Santino will be back
on the judges' panel to let you have it.
So good luck, and don't...
Wait a minute, wait.
I almost forgot.
There's one more thing.
Oh, pit crew!
[gasps]
[RuPaul] In addition
to your Hello Kitty eleganza,
you need to create a second look.
That's right, you need
to turn yourself into a character
that Hello Kitty would be proud
to call her new BFF.
And by all means, help yourself
to supplies from the Fabric Planet wall.
[Katya] I don't have a first outfit,
and I have to make
a new character and outfit to go with it.
Ah... Fucking fuck.
-Good luck, and...
-[both] Don't fuck it up.
I want to throw my hands up in the air
and say,
"It's been real, y'all.
Peace. I'll see you at the reunion."
[electronic music playing]
Ugh! So now there's a twist.
Not only do we have to create
a Hello Kitty-inspired look for ourselves,
we have to create
an entirely new Hello Kitty character.
Ugh...
-[Violet] These aren't easy to see out of.
-[Pearl] You can't see?
-[Ginger] I can't see.
-[Violet] You can't see shit.
-[Pearl] Is this a joke?
-[Violet] We have to walk like this.
[Ginger] How? Oh, my God.
It's really impossible
to try to serve face in this head.
What kind of nose
does a cow have?
Like a snout.
I don't know
how the hell I'm gonna pull this off.
[electronic music playing]
Oh, my gosh. Okay. So...
I don't I have my first outfit,
and I have to make
a new character and outfit to go with it,
and I have no idea what it is.
[Pearl] Ah! Oh, my God.
-How does this look?
-Gorgeous.
-How you doing over there, Katya?
-[Katya] Ugh...
I'm okay.
The other girls have no idea
what's happening in my mind right now
because I am a master
of hiding my turbulent emotions,
but I am flipping the fuck out.
I just feel like I'm fucked.
-[Ginger] Ouch!
-[Kennedy]  Girl...
Kennedy] Don't be pushin' on me.
I'ma tell!
I feel pretty good.
I'm pleased with my look so much.
I think it's flawless.
How's yours coming, Katya?
Um, well...
I think in the pantheon
of bad decision-making...
I think my runway outfit is like...
-The one?
-The one.
Commit to your look.
Yesterday, I had a total panic attack,
but last night I started working
on my Hello Kitty BFF character,
and I love what I'm coming up with,
but I have to finish my main stage outfit,
and I have like, no time.
I need another cat head.
I love makeup, but we're not all
legendary makeup artists like you, Pearl.
-No, I'm not.
-You're known for your makeup.
I've been drawing Pearl since I was ten.
Pearl was a character I would draw 'cause
it distracted me from the horrible things
that I felt were going on around me.
As I got older
and started to realize I was gay,
I just realized that all the things I love
when you boil it down, it's drag.
And then one day just...
painted her on me instead of the paper.
[Violet] You're so flazéda, Pearl.
My makeup today's gonna be flazéda.
I'm gonna channel that.
Fuck. Right. Off.
["Cover Girl" playing]
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl, put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe
Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage. Hey, Kitty Girl.
Well, Harajuku to you too.
A real cool cat, Carson Kressley.
Well, hello. Konnichiwa.
Domo arigato, hairy asshole.
Shake the dice and steal the fried rice.
It's Santino.
Kawaii, Ru.
And my BFF, from Skin Wars,
the ravishing Rebecca Romijn.
-[speaking Japanese]
-What's new, Pussycat?
Oh, you know.
I'm ready for a pussy party.
Oh, we're in some big trouble tonight.
This week, we challenged our queens
to transform Hello Kitty swag
into drop-dead gorgeous drag.
But first, they're making
their runway debut
as Hello Kitty's newest BFFs.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Tonight, we have an extra special guest.
It's Hello Kitty!
["Cover Girl" playing]
Oh, my God! She's coming for me!
-[Carson] I love her bloomers.
-[Michelle] Her little knickers.
Wait, what the fuck
did you just call me?
[RuPaul] Category is...
Hello Kitty BFF Realness.
-[RuPaul] First up, Hello Violet.
-[Michelle] She's got a mirror and a afro.
[Rebecca] Perfectly purrty.
[Violet] Hi. My name is Hello Violet,
and I'm Hello Kitty's new BFF.
My nickname is Lavender Trinket.
Everyone loves my honesty and my shoes.
One special thing to know about me
is that I love to look in the mirror.
I dream of one day becoming a fairy
or maybe even a model.
That's why Hello Kitty and I
will be the best frenemies forever.
[laughter]
[RuPaul] Bye-ee!
[RuPaul] Hello Ginger. Holy cow!
[laughter]
[Ginger] Hi, y'all.
My nickname is The Country Cow.
My utterly charming personality
makes people smile.
And everyone loves my milkshake.
Hello Kitty and I love to chew cud
together and play Moo-nopoly.
I dream of one day becoming
a designer handbag,
or maybe even a filet mignon.
[laughter]
[RuPaul] Oh, she was so moo-ving.
-[RuPaul] Hello Pearl.
-[Michelle] Madonna, is that you?
[Pearl] I am Hello Kitty's new BFF.
My nickname is Banji Beatdown.
And I'm from the magic land of Brooklyn.
I dream of becoming a nail technician
or maybe even a rocket scientist.
My ratchet personality makes people smile
and everyone loves my brass knuckles.
That's why Hello Kitty and I
will be the best felons forever.
[laughter]
-[RuPaul] Hello Kitty, stay away from her.
-[Michelle] She's trouble.
[RuPaul] Hello Katya.
[Carson] She's Putin her money
where her mouth is.
[Katya] Privyet. My name is Hello Katya,
and I'm from the magic land of Siberia.
And everyone loves my bad breath.
One extra special thing about me is
I'm the sweatiest woman in show business.
I feel my socialist side will balance out
Hello Kitty's decadent capitalism.
That's why Hello Kitty and I
will be best comrades forever.
[RuPaul] She's not Russian.
She's taking her time.
[RuPaul] Hello Kennedy.
-[RuPaul] Oh, yeah! Tap that weave.
-[Santino] Pat, pat yo weave.
[Kennedy] I'm Hello Kitty's new BFF.
My nickname is Sweet Hips.
I'm going to serve the runway,
so watch out!
Hello Kitty and I love to fry chicken
and play on the monkey bars.
That's why Hello Kitty and I
will be the best judies forever!
[RuPaul] Girl, yeah.
You got to move all of that.
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
[RuPaul] Kittygory is...
Hello Kitty Eleganza.
First up, Violet Chachki.
Yes, she must've liked it,
'cause she put a ring on it.
[laughter]
[Violet] I'm giving you
the '60s Harajuku Barbarella space cadet.
There's a lot happening,
but it looks chic.
[RuPaul] I know
why the caged queen stomps.
[laughter]
-[RuPaul] Ginger Minj.
-[Michelle] Hello, Titty.
[Carson] Yes, pussies galore.
[Ginger] I am walking down this runway,
showing them that I am pure pussy
with all of these kitty cats, honey.
[Rebecca] She's a crazy cat lady
saying, "Check me out."
[Santino] What does
her apartment smell like?
[RuPaul] Next up, Pearl.
She's got a lot on her mind.
[laughter]
-[Rebecca] She's a tall kitty.
-[Pearl] I love the shape of my dress.
It's a perfect combination
of cheesy little girl
and something totally grown-up
that can be photographed for a magazine.
[RuPaul] She woke up like that.
Actually, she literally slept in that.
[laughter]
-[RuPaul] Katya.
-[Carson] It's a catsuit.
-[Carson] Duh.
-[Michelle] It's a catsuit.
[Katya] I'm giving you '60s housewife
as a stuntwoman.
Maybe in space.
Could be an aerobics teacher.
I'm owning this batshit crazy look,
and I'm just trying to sell it.
[RuPaul] That's what I call
a puss in boots.
[laughter]
[RuPaul] Newark. LaGuardia. Kennedy.
She's serving a little Eartha Kitt.
-[Rebecca] Eartha Kitty.
-[Michelle] That is one giant puss.
[Kennedy] I am advertising
for Hello Kitty, honey.
Flipping my hair
so they can see the detail in the back.
-[Kennedy] Just feeling fish.
-[RuPaul] Are those kneepads?
[Rebecca] She's ready
for the Hello Kitty Ho Stroll.
[laughter]
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
Hello, my pretty kitties.
It's time for the judges' critiques.
First up, Violet Chachki.
Let's talk about your BFF.
She was super fun, still vain.
-I think you did a good job tonight.
-I love this look.
-[Rebecca] I'm having waist envy.
-It's Barbarella. It's beautiful.
What I love most about it
is it's different for Violet Chachki.
Thank you so much.
Next up, Ginger Minj.
I love what you did with your BFF.
I loved your voice-over.
For me, where this fell short...
It's just a tiny bit too literal.
I love it. It's fun.
You look like a basketful of kitties.
It's like you're overflowing with kitties.
If you bent over, more kitties would fall.
[laughter]
Ginger's having a problem
with a fucking horsefly that's landing...
It's so great to actually be here.
-[Violet] Got it.
-[RuPaul] She got it.
[RuPaul] It's right there.
Thank you, Ginger.
Next up, Pearl.
The easiest way to my heart
is to pull a Madonna out of your pocket
and basically
that's what I got with your BFF.
[Carson] But like, if Madonna
and a marshmallow had a baby.
-Sounds delicious.
-[Carson] It does, doesn't it?
The first thing that comes to mind
when I see your outfit
is when Giorgio di Sant'Angelo
went into the desert with Veruschka.
All he did was wrap blankets around her
and gave really beautiful face.
-That's what I was actually going for.
-Really?
-What was the toughest part of this?
-My looks are very minimal.
I just didn't want to throw
a bunch of Hello Kitty trinkets on me
to get the point across, so...
-Was that a read?
-Yes, it was.
-Thank you, Pearl.
-Thank you.
-Next up, Katya.
-Privyet.
For your BFF, loved your voice-over.
I loved that you added
some international flavor to the Meow Mix.
Then we have the look, the eleganza.
I'm a bit confused by it
because the hair to me
doesn't go with the outfit.
You're giving us hot futuristic
space mom who loves Hello Kitty.
[laughter]
-Was that it?
-Get out of my head.
So, 1960s stuntwoman
coerced into prostitution
on her way to fashion week in Chernobyl.
You could've taken it even further,
gotten your point of view across better.
Thank you, Katya.
Next up, Newark. LaGuardia.
Kennedy Davenport.
On the runway, it's a miss for me.
It's basic what you did on the bodysuit.
[Santino] To cut out all these bows
and then sew them on in rows.
I thought you were doing
an amazing flourish.
The challenge was to stick
to who we are, and this is me.
It could be a bit more adventuresome
for you to try some more daring looks.
That transferred over to your BFF.
It was a little bit sassy.
-But it wasn't enough for me.
-What kept you from going further with it?
I wish I had
some creativity like these ladies.
Actually, you do.
And that's why it's strange for us.
Because we see you in a way
that you're clearly not seeing yourself.
Well, thank you, ladies.
While you go untuck backstage,
the judges and I will deliberate.
For tonight's deliberation,
we have an extra special guest.
Just between us kitty girls,
what do you think?
Let's start with Violet Chachki.
Her Hello Violet character
was more tame than her extravaganza look.
I actually appreciated that she was
a little tame on her Hello Violet
because you are dealing
with such an iconic brand like that.
Her Hello Kitty couture was fabulous.
She really delivers what we've asked for.
She has a great eye for proportion.
Violet's a creative powerhouse.
She has a million silhouettes in her head,
and she's brought it to us every time.
-Why are you gagging so?
-She bring it to you, every ball.
-[RuPaul] Ginger Minj.
-Her BFF look was amazing.
She's very detail-oriented.
I don't have any beefs with this look.
It really moo-ved me.
It worked beautifully with the brand.
That being said, I was not blown away
by the Hello Kitty couture.
I would've liked to have seen
some more whimsicality.
How could she be more whimsical?
She had hair, ears,
a bow in her head,
stuffed animals on her boobs.
-That's not whimsical enough?
-Are we talking about Ginger or you?
[RuPaul] Pearl.
She created for her couture look
a glamorous, dramatic, plushy character.
It's a wraparound blanket.
Only somebody who weighs
82 pounds wet could pull that look off,
where you could wear a blanket
and call it a dress.
Hello Kitty BFF.
The Madonna vibe made me so happy.
She was having fun,
which is a really big deal for Pearl,
who always looks like she's half-asleep.
-But Kitty wouldn't hang out with her.
-And shoplift.
So, Hello Kitty,
would you hang out with Hello Pearl?
[RuPaul] No, no...
[RuPaul] Katya.
I loved her Hello Kitty BFF.
It was so wrong, it was strong.
It was hilarious and irreverent,
and I think drag should do that.
There's no way Hello Kitty's allowed
to hang out with this Russian hooker.
Hello Kitty, would you hang out
with an older Russian woman
who smokes cigarettes from Siberia?
[Santino] Oh. Oh, wow. Maybe. Huh.
The eleganza. I didn't like it at all.
None of it went together.
I actually get what she was going for
with the hairdo and the pearls.
I thought it looked like futuristic,
like, Jetsons.
[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport.
Her character, it never delivered.
She had an idea that just fizzled.
Her look was a basic ho-stroll outfit.
She just glued bows and pincushions.
You're gonna mutilate a hundred
Hello Kitty dolls and take their bows off,
and you're gonna use them like that?
No, you're not.
Ask Hello Kitty what she thought about
how she used all those bows.
Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my litter.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your Hello Kitty presentations,
I've made some decisions.
Pearl...
you're safe.
Kennedy Davenport,
your round-the-way girl
could've used more twirl.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Violet Chachki. This week,
you were a real glamor-puss.
Condragulations,
you are the winner of this challenge.
You've won
a Hello Kitty extravaganza package,
featuring accessories
to add Hello Kitty realness to your life.
Thank God.
I'm the winner,
and I feel it was well goddamn deserved.
Ginger Minj, you grabbed
a hold of this challenge and milked it
for all it was worth.
You're safe.
Katya, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me and save yourself
from elimination.
-The time has come...
-[thunder clap]
...for you to lip-sync...
...for your life!
I want to perform
the shit out of this number.
I want to be in the top four so badly.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
[Katy Perry's "Roar" playing]
♪ I used to bite my tongue
And hold my breath ♪
♪ Scared to rock the boat
And make a mess ♪
♪ So I sit quietly, agree politely ♪
♪ You held me down, but I got up
Get ready, 'cause I've had enough ♪
♪ I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter ♪
♪ Dancin' through the fire
'Cause I am a champion ♪
♪ And you're gonna hear me roar ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter ♪
♪ Dancin' through the fire
'Cause I am a champion ♪
♪ And you're gonna hear me roar ♪
[RuPaul shouts]
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, ro-ar... ♪
♪ I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter ♪
♪ Dancin' through the fire
'Cause I am a champion ♪
♪ And you're gonna hear me roar ♪
♪ Oh, louder, louder than a lion
'Cause I am a champion ♪
♪ And you're gonna hear me roar ♪
[cheers and laughter]
[Violet] Yes! Come through!
Wow!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Kennedy Davenport, shantay, you stay.
-Bitches better beware.
-Thank you.
-You may join the other girls.
Katya, you may doubt yourself sometimes,
but I have no doubt that you are a star.
And a hammer. And a sickle.
Now, sashay away.
I don't know all the words to express
how insanely fucking grateful I am.
[in Russian]
Thank you very much. I love you so much.
[cheers]
[Katya] I don't want to go home,
but I don't have any regrets.
Regret is a dish best served cold.
No, that's revenge. Fuck.
Please stay tuned for my one-woman show,
Love Stories from My Vagina.
[in Russian]
I forgot that only birds have wings.
That means my diaphragm just fell out.
Will you pick it up for me?
[in Russian] See you.
Ladies, you are the best of the best.
My final four queens.
Remember, if you can't love yourself,
how are you gonna love somebody else?
-Can I get an amen up in here?
-[all] Amen!
All right. Now, let the music play.
♪ Take me up, up, up, up
Whoa, oh, up ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, up
We can fly tonight ♪
[RuPaul] Bye-ee!