[RuPaul] Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll portray Merle,
myself, and Michelle Visage,
as you reenact our Ru Hollywood Stories.
Mother does not play!
-That.
-Fuck!
You two are...
I forgot my line!
[Katya] I think we're gonna need
a bigger boat.
-[RuPaul gasps]
-Oh, my God!
[Michelle] Is she a chicken or a horse?
-Max, what was it that I asked you for?
-Not to wear any gray hair.
I'm waiting, and I'm becoming impatient.
Katya, you're the winner
of this week's challenge.
Jaidynn Diore Fierce. Shantay, you stay.
Miss Ho, sashay away.
-I survived!
-[Katya] Ugh, bitch!
[Jaidynn] "Everything happens
for a reason.
Kandy Ho."
I survived the lip sync,
and no, ma'am, Pam, no ham,
no turkey, no cauliflower.
I can't do that again.
I'm fixing to do one wig that's not gray,
and then I'm going right back to gray.
Sorry, Michelle. She was like,
"What did I tell you last week?"
If they gave me specifics,
I would fucking do it.
Miss Max still choose
to pull out them dust-ass gray-ass wig.
I'd like to see her at the bottom,
so she can get a reality check.
I.J.S. I'm just saying.
Let's talk about you in this corset.
How does she breathe?
I don't get it.
I feel amazing!
Are we gonna sit around and talk,
or are we gonna get out of drag?
[Violet] Collect all them stones, girl.
I'm over Kennedy missing
the mark on these looks.
Didn't look like she was dead
nor like a woman.
Kennedy's look is like, "What?"
She was like...
"The fuck, what am I supposed
to do for this one?"
I honestly think Kennedy just needs to go.
She looks like Tony the Tiger on crack.
[tiger growling]
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[RuPaul] The winner gets a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With our extra-special guest judges,
Michael Urie and Tamar Braxton.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
May the best woman, best woman win ♪
-Oh, God!
-Another day, another dollar.
Another day, another drag.
[Katya] It's a new day,
and it's down to eight girls.
My game plan going forward is to kill
a few of them to make it to the top.
-[alarm blares]
-[RuPaul] Ooh, girl!
She done already done had herses!
-Hey, racers!
-[all] Hi!
Like my mama used to say,
"If you ain't got nothing nice to say
about someone, don't say nothing at all."
Or just ask Bianca Del Rio
to say it for you.
Oh, look at you guys. I hope
you're not as stupid as you are ugly.
Listen, I've got one tip for you.
You're a drag queen. Be funny!
-I have nothing to say.
-For once.
[Ginger laughs]
-Hello, hello, hello.
-[all] Hi.
[Violet] A vision in polka dot.
For weeks, you have been encouraged
to show us the real you.
And you know what?
I've had about all of that I can take.
So today, it's time to find out
who else you can be.
-That's right!
-[Max] Oh, no.
This week's maxi-challenge...
Snatch Game!
Now go on and hashtag that.
Snatch Game is the challenge
that every fan has been waiting for.
We put on giant, latex frog costumes,
and we go through a fiery obstacle course.
Okay, all right. I'm sorry.
You compete on a live game show,
a parody of the Match Game.
You need to impersonate another star's
charisma, uniqueness, nerve, and talent.
But be careful whose you choose.
'Cause it could be a very hairy situation.
I know that feeling.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Okay, Snatch Game. Down to business.
-Who are you doing?
-Donatella Versace.
I'm doing Donatella Versace!
I've been working on this
for eight months.
I should be out there.
This would be a great chance to push
myself out of the pretty little box.
I'd been planning to do Donatella
since the first time I auditioned.
I mean, come on, girl.
One of you has to be
the bigger person and just bow out.
-[Miss Fame] Do you have a backup?
-Not at all.
I literally don't have
any other choice. I'm doing it.
-[Katya] Who are you gonna do?
-I was thinking about...
doing Little Richard.
-But he's a man.
-You can't do that.
-Why?
-'Cause it's a man.
But I'll be in drag.
He been in drag his whole life.
-No, ma'am.
-No Richard.
It's a man!
Snatch... Vagina!
[Ginger] Why don't you do Sweet Brown?
She only has one line.
-She's got a monologue.
-She's got, "cold pop,"
"bronchitis," and,
"ain't nobody got time for that."
It's funny,
and people are gonna know who it is.
I'm really torn. I just don't know
who I'm gonna do at this point.
[Violet] Who are you gonna do?
[Max] Sharon Needles.
Max is doing Sharon from season four.
She has a darker side to her.
I'll do Disney Sharon Needles.
Really? Sharon's shocking and punk-rock,
and that's kind of
out of character for Max.
Hello, hello, hello.
[all] Hello.
-[RuPaul] Jaidynn Diore Fierce.
-[Jaidynn] Yes.
-Who are you gonna be?
-Raven-Symoné.
How are you gonna channel Raven-Symoné?
She's just kinda high-pitched,
and she's always like, "Oh!"
Girl, no comment.
If we met, we could be best friends.
But what does that have to do
with Snatch Game?
We sitting in the audience have to say,
"Ah, that is so Raven!"
You get back to work.
Hey, good looking. What you got cooking?
I had an unexpected turn of events today.
-What happened?
-Two of us had the same character.
-What queen is it?
-It's Violet.
We were both gonna do
Donatella Versace, but...
I've chosen to do Theresa Caputo,
the Long Island Medium.
Yeah, yeah.
Was it a discussion, or she said,
"I am doing Donatella"?
-She didn't have a backup, and--
-Listen, Miss Fame,
the competition is narrowing down.
So you've got to go for the jugular.
You were kind enough
to change your first choice,
But being kind is one thing.
Being the winner is completely different.
Do what's in your best interest,
not in the best interest of others.
Well, shit, I'll be Versace.
This is a competition. Sometimes,
you have to step over other girls
to get where you wanna go.
So... Sorry, girl.
Today's maxi challenge is Snatch Game,
which is a Drag Race version
of the original show, Match Game.
-Hello, Katya.
-Hi.
-Who are you?
-Suze Orman.
-Have you done her before?
-No.
I know that you do a Russian accent,
'cause the Katya character is Russian.
Why didn't you do a Russian character?
'Cause you do it so well.
What is it you're afraid of?
I don't know. I think my whole life,
I've been riddled with anxiety,
-fearful of things that aren't a big deal.
-Ah.
I'm afraid to show
this character because it's...
the thing that I do best,
and I am terrified of failing at it.
You have an addiction to the anxiety.
I've never thought of that before.
I've been addicted to alcohol,
crystal meth, cocaine.
You're here because you're super talented.
-Don't be afraid.
-Okay.
[Katya] Addicted to anxiety.
LaGuardia, Newark, Kennedy.
-Who are you doing?
-I've been trying to figure it out,
so I came up with Sweet Brown...
-"Ain't nobody got time for that."
-Or Little Richard.
Uh-huh. Is that what you're gonna go with?
I just... I don't really know.
I'm torn, really.
Well, I'm gonna leave that to you.
I can't decide for you,
and that's all I'm gonna say.
I think it's very risky
going with Little Richard.
The stakes are very high going into
the Snatch Game, so I'm just debating.
-Violet Chachki.
-Hi, RuPaul.
I heard a little rumor
that you're doing an Italian superstar.
-I am Versace.
-She's been funny in skits on television.
How will you avoid doing
what someone else has done?
I think I can execute a better look than--
Look is one thing.
There is a different skill to be funny.
-Let me hear your Italian accent.
-A woman should feel confident, sexy.
She should put something on her body
and feel like she owns the world.
All right.
What other ideas did you have?
I was thinking of even doing
Alyssa Edwards maybe.
Can I see your Alyssa Edwards?
Real once, done. Top, bottom, done.
That's good. You might want
to consider switching to Alyssa.
Motherfucker. Stir the pot, RuPaul.
Do you want a spoon?
All you gotta do is make me laugh. Okay?
-Get to work.
-Thank you.
All right.
Can I get a time check?
I cannot believe this shit.
[Pearl] If you're more comfortable
doing Donatella, then do it.
I'm more comfortable doing
Donatella when there was just one.
I guess I'm gonna fucking do
Alyssa Edwards then.
[Pearl] You don't have to do it
just because RuPaul said you should.
Am I gonna do better than her?
Or is it gonna be competition?
It will definitely be a competition.
Ladies, later today, I will meet you
on the set of Snatch Game.
So good luck and don't fuck it blank.
[RuPaul] Welcome to Snatch Game.
Let's meet our contestants.
A talented actor
who's spent more time in Barbra
Streisand's basement than she has.
Michael Urie!
-Hi, Michael.
-How are you?
Good to see you.
And all's fair in love and war
with the real Miss Tamar Braxton.
Are you ready to meet our stars?
Let's go.
Our first star is drag superstar
from the House of Haunt,
Sharon Needles.
Have you been to any good séances lately?
I just got back from one.
[dramatic music]
[chuckles]
All right, down to our next star.
This Cosby kid is all grown-up.
Welcome Raven-Symoné.
-I just had a vision.
-Really?
-I'm a lesbian now.
-[RuPaul] Oh, my goodness!
-That's so Raven.
-That is so me.
Next up, financial adviser Suze Orman.
Hello, my darling dear
little chickadee RuPaul.
Now, Suze,
I make $8 an hour hosting this show.
-Can I afford a yacht?
-How about a little rubber ducky?
I'll throw in
a hot bag of nickels just in case.
You've got a deal!
Now, from the hit web series
Alyssa's Secret,
-Alyssa Edwards!
-[pops tongue]
I'm Alyssa Edwards, and this...
is Snatch Game.
I've always wanted to ask you,
what is your secret?
-I'm sitting on it.
-[RuPaul] Oh, okay.
[cackles]
-[Violet] Almost got me there, bitch.
-Oh, good to know.
From the Genovese crime family,
it's Big Ang!
Hi, RuPaul. I'm feeling very excited.
-What is your bra size?
-It's a medical mystery.
From the House of Versace,
it's Donatella Versace.
Donatella Versace how's them boots?
How are you?
I'm doing great. Is it pronounced
"Ver-sayz" or "Ver-sa-chi"?
It depends on where you come from.
I would have had an Italian accent
instead of a Russian accent.
I don't mind.
But... hey.
Good golly, Miss Molly!
It's rock and roll legend Little Richard.
Are you feeling a little more tutti
or a little more frutti?
A little more tutti, baby!
[holds a note]
Shut up.
Last but not least,
music superstar Adele is here.
-Hey, girl!
-Could I buy vowels?
-What is that, darling?
-No whammies!
No, this is the wrong show.
Okay.
Are you ready to play the Snatch Game?
[Kennedy] It's time for Snatch Game!
Whooo!
Shut up.
[RuPaul] Welcome back to Snatch Game.
Here's how the game works.
I ask a question, you give an answer
that you think will match
our celebrity contestants'.
First question is
for the beautiful Tamar Braxton.
Quentin Tarantino is remaking
The Wizard of Oz as an action movie.
In this new version,
Dorothy "blanks" the Tin Man.
-All right, Tamar.
-She kills him, okay? Good-bye.
Now let's go to our stars and hear
what they have to say. Big Ang?
You know what, in my family,
we like to do it the old-fashioned way.
You gut 'em like a fish.
-That's a match!
-Yes. Ding, ding, ding!
-Big Ang!
-Yeah! Yeah!
Financial adviser Suze Orman.
In this new version,
Dorothy "blanks" the Tin Man.
Of course she bangs him,
which is what I'd like to do
to most of these women here on stage.
Except for this one down here,
Miss Donatella.
She looks like a skeleton
made out of beef jerky.
[laughter]
I love you, Justin Bieber.
Let's move on down
to rock and roll royalty.
Little Richard!
Dorothy "blanks" the Tin Man.
She tightens the screws.
'Cause we all love a tight screw. A-whoo!
-[RuPaul] Sorry, that is not a match.
-Shut up.
[Kennedy] Whoo!
Raven-Symoné. That's so Raven!
-I just saw it.
-What is it?
-She blows him.
-Unfortunately, that is not a match.
I'll try again.
-No, I saw the same thing.
-Same thing?
Let's move on down here to Adele.
-Where in England are you from?
-My house.
-All right. Dorothy "blanks" the Tin Man.
-Well, if it was me,
I would say she rips out his heart
and then sings a whole album about it
and gets really popular, but...
-it's not me.
-No, no.
So I said she polishes his chrome.
It's a good answer, but not a match.
Well, could I get a match, please?
It's a fake cigarette.
All right, Donatella Versace.
This is not
a doctor prescription refill card?
I must be confused.
But I did say,
"Hose down Versace boots," eh?
[RuPaul] Interesting answer.
Honey, that wig was a bad investment.
That's read.
All right, this one's for Michael.
Rumor has it that they're making
a gay version of Batman &amp; Robin.
In this movie, the dynamic duo convert
the Batcave into a "blank".
-A bed &amp; breakfast.
-I would stay there.
-I would too.
-Let's go to Sharon Needles.
I said haunted house!
[RuPaul] I'm sorry, but not a match.
Moving on down to Raven-Symoné.
The dynamic duo convert
the Batcave into a...
Weave shop!
Oh, Jaidynn, I just got a vision.
You might be lip-syncing
for your life tomorrow, baby.
I'm sorry, raven.
Moving on down to Suze Orman.
I was looking over here at Big Ang,
and I thought of a foreclosed mobile home.
You know what, that's fucked up.
[RuPaul] All right, Alyssa Edwards.
The dynamic duo convert
the Batcave into a...
A dance studio, baby.
Hashtag, beyond belief.
Not a match, but a nice plug
for your dance studio.
-All right, Big Ang.
-Well, I don't know
about Batman and Robin,
but I love money, yacht, and mansions.
-Mansion.
-It's underneath a mansion.
-[RuPaul] It is.
-I had a rough childhood.
I wasn't watching
fucking Batman and Robin.
What say you, Little Richard.
You know, me and Batman and Robin
have a lot in common, baby.
I said a bathhouse
in a dark room with glory holes.
There'll be a lot of singing
going on up in there, honey. Whooo!
I'm sorry, Little Richard.
That is not a match.
Shut up.
Next question is for Tamar Braxton.
Portia says Ellen is so hilarious
even her "blank" makes her laugh.
I'm gonna have to say coins,
honey, makes them laugh.
-Even her coins.
-They so rich they pee pennies.
Pssh, pennies.
Let's go over here to Sharon Needles.
I said temper tantrums.
-You know why?
-Why?
Because Ellen never has temper tantrums.
[RuPaul] Wait a minute.
Her temper tantrums make her laugh
because Ellen does not have them.
She does, but everything she says
is so damn funny. You can't even tell.
Not a match for Tamar. All right, Adele.
Adele, how much food
do you have down there, girl?
-Smorgasbord.
-I have low sugar.
-[RuPaul] Low sugar.
-[Ginger] I do.
She's using my EBT card.
-[RuPaul] Oh, Lord!
-[Kennedy] Whooo!
-Oooh!
-Wrong note, sugar.
Portia says Ellen is so hilarious
even her "blank" makes her laugh.
Sad, sad tears of a clown.
-Like the Smokey Robinson song.
-Yeah.
I'm so sorry, Adele. That is not a match.
-But it's a song.
-[RuPaul] It is a song, but--
-Did I sing it?
-[RuPaul] No, you didn't.
So it's not a good song.
Probably still won an award for it anyway.
[RuPaul] Probably, yes.
Oh, my stars! Time is up.
Which means our winner is...
my therapist.
We'll be tweeting more questions
@RuPaulsDragRace.
So you can keep on playing at home.
-Say good night, stars!
-Good night, stars!
[RuPaul] See you next time
on the Snatch Game! Bye-ee!
Child!
Sir, what do you want me to do today?
It's time for another elimination,
and people are really feeling the pressure
because there's only a handful of us left.
[Katya] I'm second-guessing myself
about my performance.
I don't know where I stand
in the eyes of the judges.
All I can hear is the voices in my head
telling me how terrible I am.
-Can I talk to you?
-I'd love to.
Okay.
What's going on?
I am kind of freaking out.
I've been completely sober
for the past year and a half.
Most of the time, I'm fine. But being away
from my support network has been brutal.
I know that Fame is sober, so she's
the only other person who can understand
exactly what I'm going through.
-How long have you been sober for?
-For nine years,
but counting days in here
feels like being a newcomer.
That's exactly what it feels like!
Like, it's hard.
-I've never seen that of you.
-I'm pretty good at hiding it.
-I am terrified of failure.
-Yeah.
And my sense of humor is just, like...
-It's been a smoke screen for that.
-Yeah.
And I have to tell you,
the first day I came in here,
the first thing I thought of was,
"You don't belong here.
You're not good enough."
I didn't realize how badly...
I've actually never been able
to love myself, and it's like...
You are, love. You are loved.
I'm having to deal
with the insecurities I don't wanna face,
and I did not expect that.
You're being so hard on yourself.
You're in it, but you're not alone.
I'm here with you,
having the same fears and feelings.
My character defects are on fire,
and people are seeing me,
and they're like, "Girl talks a lot."
That's my obsessive mind running!
There's a lot that I'm relating
with Katya on an emotional level.
To connect and let go of those fears
makes me feel stronger.
This moment is what I needed.
-I needed it too.
-Thank you so much.
-Let's go put some war paint--
-I'm Miss Fame, and I'm an alcoholic.
My name is Katarina Zamolodchikova,
and I'm a drug addict and alcoholic. Ugh!
After my talk with Fame,
I feel like a weight has been lifted.
-Oh, God!
-I can't go back!
Let's go paint.
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl, put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe, let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Well, if it isn't my favorite
female impersonator, Michelle Visage.
And Ross Mathews.
Do you do any impersonations?
-I do a mean Morgan Freeman.
-Can I hear it?
[high-pitched]
Hi, Miss Daisy!
Hi!
-You wanna take a ride?
-That's so good.
And the fabulous Michael Urie.
Did you enjoy playing with my dolls?
Only my therapist knows for sure.
And Tamar Braxton. Are you ready
for some Drag Race family values?
Yes, God!
This week, we challenged
our queens to fill in the blank
with their best celebrity impersonations.
And tonight, they're serving up
a two-for-one special of leather and lace.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
-[RuPaul] Ginger Minj.
-[Michelle] Yes.
[Michelle] Nice day for a white wedding.
[Ginger] Girl, I'm spinning,
I'm turning, I'm posing.
I am giving them Elvis "Prissley" now.
-[Tamar] Runway Roseanne.
-[Michelle] Drag is a religious activity.
[RuPaul] Ginger has a real cross to bear.
-[RuPaul] Katya.
-[Michael] Oh!
[RuPaul with British accent]
Samantha Fox is such a wild dame.
[Katya] I'm trying to just serve
sexy and confident whore.
Slutty cougar on the prowl.
Third-rate Faith Hill impersonator.
Eighty percent sexy,
20 percent disgusting.
[Michelle] Look out, Tawny Kitaen.
We got a new Whitesnake, bitch.
[RuPaul laughs]
[RuPaul] Newark, LaGuardia,
Kennedy Davenport.
Call her Miss Ross.
[Kennedy] I'm presenting body,
face, leather and lace.
[RuPaul] Kennedy Airport,
permission to land.
[Michelle] This is my black box.
-[RuPaul] Violet Chachki, girl.
-[Tamar] Hallelu.
[Ross] "S" and "mmm-mmm good."
[Violet] I'm giving you 1940s
John Willie vintage smut for your nerves.
Soft, hard, all mixed
into one amazing runway walk.
[RuPaul] The dominatrix sleeps tonight.
Max. Oh, the merry widow.
[Michelle] The "why it gotta be black"
widow.
-[Michelle] Oh, look at that stinger.
-[RuPaul] Yeah.
[Max] Today, I'm giving
the not-so-remorseful widow
whose husband just happened
to have died mysteriously,
and I want to be very surreal.
Of course, as usual.
-[Michael] She doesn't seem so sad.
-[Tamar] Uh-uh.
[RuPaul] Jaidynn Diore Fierce,
aka Chaka Khan.
[Jaidynn] I have my lace nude illusion,
along with hair
for months and weeks and years.
[Ross] That's not a carry-on wig.
You gotta check that.
[RuPaul] Here comes Pearl.
[Ross] We're both wearing pink.
I think that's two in the pink.
-[RuPaul] That's right. Oh, my God.
-[Ross] Yeah.
[RuPaul] It's perfect.
[Pearl] I'm feeling super confident
as I walk down the runway,
wearing sort of, like, Grease,
but it's still totally me.
-[RuPaul] We're gonna rule the school.
-[Michelle] Rizzo is PG.
[RuPaul] Pass it on.
Miss Fame. Dark lady, snap out of it.
[Miss Fame] This is a new look for me.
It's a fresh, sexy take on Miss Fame.
I'm loving this face,
I'm loving this lace,
and I'm loving my hair.
-[RuPaul] Cagney and Lacey.
-[Ross] "Gag me" and Lacey.
♪ Sissy that walk ♪
Welcome, ladies. It feels like
a convention of ex-Prince protégées.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Violet Chachki.
Pearl.
You are both...
...safe.
You may leave the stage.
Now it's time for the judges' critiques.
Starting with Ginger Minj.
I thought you were truly brilliant
as Adele.
You never left character,
and it was a complete transformation.
Today, you owned being thickums.
It was like, "This is me, eat it."
The only thing that I would change
is your hair is a little too triangular.
I was trying to do
like an Elvis "Prissley"
-kind of thing.
-I would've gone all the way.
-I usually do.
-I heard that about you.
I'm the one that wrote it
on the bathroom wall.
-[RuPaul] Next up, Miss Fame.
-You look stunning.
It's not '40s, it's something different.
And that's really refreshing.
Snatch Game. You had so many
missed opportunities, and I wanted more.
It felt like you were 20% there.
You'll never have this opportunity again.
Be here in the present,
and don't let this moment pass you by.
All right. Newark, LaGuardia, Kennedy.
I am not a fan of anybody
doing boy drag. You know this.
You killed it.
I was like, "Who let
meetratchetpeople.com in here? What?"
But you gave me all the light
that I needed yesterday.
I didn't expect this risk from you.
You're my pageant queen.
I'm not always head to toe.
I like to get messy too.
-Oh, okay.
-And this gown, I would climb you.
-Oh!
-[RuPaul laughs]
-Can we go to break?
-Shut up.
-[RuPaul] Next up, Max.
-Thank you for the new hair color.
You know what I miss?
Is the gray hair. You look fantastic,
but I think you look normal.
[Michelle] Snatch Game.
You had the look down 100%.
What was missing was everything else.
Sharon's got a twisted sense of humor,
and that was missing,
-and I hate to say--
-It looks like Max is coming apart.
Yeah, I just really needed
to loosen the corset.
-Okay.
-I apologize.
Can we get some help for Max?
[Ginger] Oh, bitch, here we go.
Cue the dramatics.
You can tell she's an actress.
-Max, are you okay?
-♪ So I can't quite recall ♪
♪ All the night's sensation ♪
I took advantage of the moment.
[Miss Fame] Is this a strategy?
Because this is one of the first times
that she's not been a shining star.
-Yes.
-[exhales]
-Next up, Jaidynn Diore Fierce.
-[Tamar] Today...
I'm still trying to put it all together,
the look. Somehow, it just...
falls flat.
As far as being Raven-Symoné,
it became real like,
"Okay, she's gonna see a vision."
Once, it was funny.
The second time, it was cute.
The rest of the time, it died.
[RuPaul] Next up, Katya.
To go from Suze Orman
to Xena the Warrior Princess,
you look so beautiful and...
I'm losing my train of thought.
You really strutted your stuff,
and you were like Britney at 45.
And yesterday was just "hilarical", okay?
I really laughed the whole...
I just wanted even more.
I know I'm always asking for more,
but y'all can take it further, so push it.
Thank you, ladies. We've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I will braid
each other's hair.
Oh, fun!
You may leave the stage.
Just between us squirrel friends,
let's talk about Ginger Minj.
She chose a character
that was creative and also challenging.
She came out in all white,
and everybody was in all black.
Only superstars know
to do things like that.
-There's no cons.
-No cons.
I bet there's been a con in her
-once or twice, you know.
-[RuPaul] Miss Fame.
She looked the part of Donatella,
but she didn't deliver comedy.
She's not breaking through.
She doesn't feel solid in herself.
-[RuPaul] Kennedy Davenport.
-[Michael] The way that she walked,
look at the spot she would stand in,
even point at the spot,
and then circle it and leave it
and not even stop.
And then Snatch Game,
it was such an over-the-top caricature.
It just worked.
The giant Bea Arthur shoulder pads.
-The lip gloss.
-[Tamar] She changed Little Richard.
She killed it for me.
-[RuPaul] Next up is Max.
-When she came in looking so great,
and then there was no characterization,
that was a real bummer for me.
Max likes to stay in a comfort zone.
I think that Max has more potential.
She just needs to find it.
-[RuPaul] Jaidynn Diore Fierce.
-The Snatch Game was one note.
-I was over it... dot com.
-Okay.
If I'm on RuPaul's Drag Race,
don't come as Chaka's little sister.
You come as Chaka.
-That's all she has to say about that.
-Okay.
-[RuPaul] Katya.
-Her Suze Orman was spot-on.
I understand that it didn't go full-tilt,
but I loved it.
Like, she gave me futuristic
Britney Spears tee-hee-hee, honey,
and Whitesnake tee-hee,
and, you know, Guns N' Roses.
Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girlses.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Katya.
You're safe.
Kennedy Davenport. Great gosh almighty.
You rocked the Snatch Game.
Condragulations, you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
[applause]
Thank you.
I won another challenge. Yay!
Ginger Minj, your Adele
had us rolling in the aisles.
Condragulations, you are also
the winner of this week's challenge.
That's right, ladies. First tie
in Snatch Game herstory.
I won! If there was ever
a challenge to win, it is this one.
[RuPaul] You've both won fabulous
feather accoutrements from Mother Plucker.
You may join the other girls.
Ebony and ivory.
Jaidynn Diore Fierce, your vision
of Miss Symoné was not so Raven.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Miss Fame, "don't-a-tella" me
that was your best impersonation.
Max, your Sharon Needles missed the point.
Max...
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
[Max] Damn, damn, damn!
I can't get over the feelings in my head
of disappointment in myself.
It's really sort of overwhelming.
Miss Fame, you may join the other girls.
Two queens stand before me.
This is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lip-sync
for your life!
I can't go home. I refuse.
I gotta protect my spot here.
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
♪ Hello? ♪
♪ Hello? You're special
You know I love you ♪
♪ You say you love me
And I think that it's true ♪
♪ But every night my girlfriend tells me
That I should watch you ♪
♪ Now, I say I trust you
But I want you to know ♪
♪ Want you to know ♪
♪ I'm not a sucker, chill out
Your nose is growing, Pinocchio ♪
♪ So now I'm leaving
And you know I tried ♪
♪ You don't appreciate the time I take ♪
♪ All right, baby, no more lies ♪
♪ Hello? ♪
-♪ You're the only girl for me ♪
-♪ No more lies ♪
♪ You're all I think about
You're the only girl ♪
♪ No more lies ♪
♪ So now I'm leaving
And you know I tried ♪
♪ You don't appreciate the time I take ♪
-♪ All right, baby, no more lies ♪
-♪ You said ♪
-♪ You're the only girl for me ♪
-♪ But I don't need ♪
♪ No more lies ♪
♪ You were trying to take me for a fool
And, baby, that ain't right ♪
♪ No more lies ♪
♪ You know I love you ♪
[RuPaul laughs]
[cheers and applause]
Ladies, I've made my decision.
-Jaidynn Diore Fierce, shantay, you stay.
-Thank you so much.
You may join the other girls.
Max, you are a true original.
Thank you for taking us all to the max.
Now, sashay away.
[Max] I was able to represent myself.
I stayed as classy as I possibly could.
I feel like I've been in a dream.
For me to go back to Kansas from Oz,
it's all so surreal.
But there's no place like home.
My seven sisters,
I have a confession to make.
I fear I've made a terrible mistake.
That I've let one of the eliminated queens
go home... too soon.
Ru, girl, what?
I'm just not sure which one.
Could it be Tempest DuJour,
Sasha Belle,
Jasmine Masters, Trixie Mattel,
Mrs. Kasha Davis, Kandy Ho, or Max?
Ah, shit.
No, no, no!
Well, I'm sure it'll come to me.