- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You will be designing
a couture dress
inspired by these cakes.
Ooh!
You need a 12-step program
to deal with that lava.
- The reality of it
is that she looked awful.
- I would like
to see Shangela go.
She's just a loudmouth,
and she's always halleluing.
- Shangela, get the fuck out.
- Raja.
You're the winner
of this challenge.
Alexis Mateo,
you're a sweet talker,
but your cheesecake couture
struck a sour note
with the judges.
Shante, you stay.
Stacy Layne Matthews,
sashay away.
And tonight...
break out your library cards.
Reading is fundamental.
- Ow!
Eat it, eat it, eat it, ow.
- And a comedy of errors.
- I said,
"Bitch better have my money."
- With extra special
guest judges
comediennes Rita Rudner
and Arden Myrin.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive
a lifetime supply
of Kryolan Professional makeup;
headline Logo's Drag Race Tour,
featuring cocktails
perfected by Absolut;
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win!
[car engines racing]
- Whoo-hoo.
It's so empty in here.
Hello.
[imitates echo]
Stacy is gone.
"Be a lady.
You're all amazing.
Stacy Layne 'Bryant' Matthews."
- The last challenge,
being in the bottom two,
I think it was a fluke.
So right now
I just have to concentrate
in what the judges
are looking for.
- Well, Stacy's gone.
Now you're the only big girl.
- Stacy probably shouldn't have
been here to begin with.
She didn't meet the criteria.
But now I have a whole other
can of worms to worry about.
For the most part, all the
strong competitors are here.
And it's really hammered in
that now
the competition is super tight.
At this point,
it's getting very personal.
- I wanted to ask you
about yesterday.
When you said you're so tired
of hearing my voice,
my reaction was,
like, I was shocked.
- It came off a lot harsher
than I intended.
- As I'm having this
conversation with Manila,
it's a complete 180
from what she was delivering
on the runway.
I know that Manila
has more faces
than my foot has blisters
after a show.
- And I don't want you to think
that I'm attacking you...
- No.
- But I am attacking you.
Because ultimately
this is a competition,
and I want to beat you.
[alarm wails]
- Ooh, girl.
You've got shemail.
Hello, lady-boys.
- Hi.
- Drag is a serious business,
but sometimes a queen can take
herself a little too seriously.
Remember, laugh, and the world
laughs with you.
Bomb, and the joke's on you,
honey.
- Whoo!
Yeah.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hello.
- My legendary children.
A drag superstar needs to
develop a pretty thick skin.
So in the great tradition
of Paris Is Burning,
break out your library cards.
- Oh, god.
- Because reading is what?
Fundamental.
Now, for today's mini challenge,
you'll take turns
reading each other.
Or throwing shade.
Ladies, the library is open,
okay?
- Okay.
- Yara Sofia.
La biblioteca is open.
Put on your reading glasses
and read these bitches
for filth.
- Manila Luzon.
It's not because you're Asian.
It's because I need some
patience to deal with you.
Delta Work, is that your tits
or your feet?
- Oh!
- Raja,
you think you're fashion?
You should go to old...school.
- Next up, Manila.
- Ow, eat it, eat it, eat it.
Ow!
- Put on your reading glasses.
- Oh, god.
- Ooh, Yara.
Your blue contacts are so creepy
that it makes my skin itchy,
itchy, itchy...pa'lante.
- Oh!
- It's dinner time, Delta.
And you are serving
body-ody-ody.
Well, I guess
that solves the problem
with all them starving kids
in Africa.
- Thank you, Manila.
Up next is Miss Delta.
- Oh, my gosh.
Yara, isn't it interesting
that when your flight
came into town
the sightings of chupacabras
increased?
[laughter]
Manila, what are we gonna do
when the hurricane
hits all of Asia.
You won't have
any material left.
- Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
- Raja,
when you're on the runway,
do you keep the 800 number
for suicide?
Because those toes
are ready to jump.
- Whoa!
- Bring your library card,
Miss Alexis Mateo.
- Get ready, bitches.
Miss Shangela, girl,
can we have some water?
Her hair is thirsty, baby.
- Uh-oh.
- Delta, just grow a neck,
honey.
- Whoa!
- All they can read is my size,
and that's so obvious.
Now tell me something funny.
- Raja, should I call you Raja
or grandma?
- Ooh!
- Oh!
- Raja, you are up.
- Shangela,
I hope you still have
your phone card to Middle-earth,
'cause the hobbits are calling.
- Ooh!
- Fat.
Who cares?
Syphilis.
[laughter]
- Carmen, the library
is open to you, my dear.
- Word.
- Yara, what the fuck are you
saying, girl?
- Alexis, girl, I been thinking
about you all day.
I was at the zoo.
- Ooh!
- All right, last but not least,
Shangela.
Yes.
- Oh.
Mimi Imfurst.
[laughter]
Raja, I know you call yourself
Top Model,
but I think Tyra Banks and I
would agree
you're just fashion roadkill.
- Ooh!
- Manila Luzon,
Asian role model.
Well, I hope you're referring to
the rolls all over your body.
- Ooh!
- And, aw, Carmen Carrera.
Honey, just go
jump in the ocean.
You won't drown.
Silicone floats.
- All right, girl.
The library
is permanently closed.
All right, ladies, good job.
But I think we have a winner.
Shangela!
For this week's main challenge,
you need to develop
a stand-up comedy routine.
To help you create
a winning routine,
you'll each take
a one-on-one comedy workshop
with legendary funny lady
Miss Rita Rudner.
- Oh, wow.
- Oh, my god, Rita!
I can't wait to meet
Rita Rudner!
- Now, for your
stand-up performance,
you'll need to put together
a funny outfit
worthy of a queen of comedy.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the funniest bitch win.
- All right.
See y'all later.
- Oh, my.
Yes, I am a little terrified.
My heart stopped, actually,
when she said that.
It's frightening,
'cause I'm just hoping
that I don't bomb,
and that happens a lot
with comedians.
If you don't have
the perfect timing,
you could really fuck it up.
Shangela's an amazing comedian.
She's been doing it for a while,
so I'm sure she's gonna do
really well in this one.
- Well, damn sure I was right
when I said,
"I want that bitch to go."
- Well, no, because comedy
is hit or miss.
It's a lot of pressure.
- We all kind of
have to be good,
the three of us, because their
group's still the same size.
Our group is getting smaller.
- It's like our workroom
is now divided into two groups.
We got team talent
and team look.
Raja, Delta, Carmen, and Manila
all put the emphasis
on their look.
They can't perform.
- Today we have to do
a stand-up routine,
and we have to create
a drag look
that goes with
our stand-up routine.
- I'm gonna have to do some
brainstorming here.
- Well, that's gonna be hard.
You see what time she's having
with it.
The workroom today
is very quiet.
There's no sewing.
Everyone is digging
deep inside their brains,
trying to find
what about themselves is funny.
- I'm--I'm afraid.
- You can't be afraid.
You got to go in or go home.
- It's hard
to make people laugh,
but I'm gonna do it.
I'm so funny.
Funny enough
that you gonna laugh.
- A lot of people here
host a show,
so everyone here is gonna be
strong competition,
and that's, like,
when they tell me that
my makeup's not the best,
you know, it's important to me
to look--
have the look right.
When I get
in front of the judges,
it's never a question
about talent.
It's always something
regarding my makeup.
- The purpose for the makeup
is not to look...painted.
- What about when I'm doing here
and sculpting the face?
You know how you talk about
a round face?
- From here up, I don't use
a lot of foundation.
I don't need it there.
- Oh, it's not even
all the way across?
- No.
Because then you're
creating a mask.
Everything that Shangela said
is exactly
what you never should do.
- You don't put on powder
between steps?
- No! No!
[laughter]
How do you--no, no.
- Hello, funny ladies.
- Hi.
- Funny girls.
Hey, Carmen.
- Hey, hey.
- Now, you're obviously
from New Jersey.
You have sort of
a Jersey accent.
- Do I?
- Yeah, you do.
Are you gonna play up sort of
the stereotypical things
that people may think of you?
- No, I'm not typical Jersey.
So...
- How do you know you're not
typical Jersey?
- I don't think I am.
I don't see it.
Am I that Jersey?
Like, what does that mean?
I mean, is that an insult?
- A lot of comedy
comes from stereotypes,
and if you play on that,
it can be very funny.
People can relate to it.
Because, really, you want to
invite people into your world
and make them feel comfortable.
But it's up to you whether
you're willing to let us in.
- I don't really like
to let anyone in.
- Well, you got to
get over that.
Hey, Manila.
- Hi.
- You know, this seems like
a shoo-in for you.
You're very funny.
- I'm going back
to my childhood.
As an adult looking back,
how gay some of the things
I used to watch on TV were.
Sesame Street?
- Right, right.
So now, in the past,
I've heard jokes
about Sesame Street.
- Um, maybe.
I don't really know.
- I want to hear something
that we haven't heard before.
Get back to work.
- Thanks.
- See ya.
Hey, Alexis.
- Hi, Ru.
- Have you done comedy before?
- No, we have never
do stand-up comedy.
- I see.
And you're gonna tell
some jokes?
- Yes.
- As Alexis, or as a character?
- As Alexis Mateo.
And it's gonna talk about
my coming to America experience.
It was a big change.
It was the problem
with the language.
- No one else
has your life experience,
so if you draw on that,
how could you go wrong?
Especially if you can
laugh at yourself.
- I love making fun of myself.
- I am so excited.
I can't wait to laugh,
laugh, laugh.
- Thank you for stopping
by my office.
- All right.
- Bye, Ru.
- Bye.
Hey, Delta.
- Hi, Ru.
- I have a feeling
you're gonna be very funny.
- Um, I am.
- They say that comedy comes
from, you know, a dark place,
and I have a feeling that
you've spent a lot of time
where, uh,
maybe people have said
some nasty things to you,
and you've had a lot of time
to think about getting back
at them.
Am I right?
- Yes, that's very true.
But I don't want it to seem
like,
"Poor me, poor me, poor me."
I want it to be like, "Poor me,
pour me another one."
I'm so excited.
I think if I'm clear
and concise about the jokes,
I think that I could win.
- I can't wait.
- Thank you.
All right, ladykins.
Gather around.
In a moment you'll meet
with guest judge Rita Rudner,
who will help you with your
chutzpah, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
Now, Shangela, since you
won the mini challenge,
you get an extra ten minutes
with Rita Rudner.
Plus you get to choose
the order of the lineup.
- This is where the real shade
is gonna happen.
- Now, tomorrow,
on the main stage,
we'll be joined by guest judge,
the sassy comedian from
Chelsea Lately and Mad TV,
Arden Myrin.
- Whoo!
- Oh, and one more thing.
You'll be performing
your stand-up
in front of the harshest critics
of all--
a live audience.
So don't fuck it up.
I'll see you later.
- All right, bye.
- I work in front of
an audience at my shows.
It's the best place
to get energy.
The problem is sometimes
that energy is good,
and sometimes it's bad.
- You guys want to come over,
'cause I got the order of
the show set up for tomorrow.
- Okay.
- I know how it is to work
at a club.
When you go to work
at a drag show,
they usually put the girls
who they don't like
in the beginning.
- Opening the show's
gonna be Raja.
She's, what we call
in the comedy world,
biting the bullet.
And then Carmen, Alexis.
I put Carmen second.
If she's great, she follows Raja
and makes Raja look horrible.
Alexis, you'll introduce me,
and then I'll introduce Manila.
Then Yara and Delta,
you'll close the show, okay?
I put Manila directly after me.
If she's intimidated by me,
let her be
really intimidated by me.
- Why did you put me in the...
before the last one?
- I know you probably
wanted to be
toward the end of the show,
but I don't want you
to be the last one.
Yara wants to go last,
but I put her next to last.
If she knocks it
out of the park,
that puts Delta
at a disadvantage,
because then she has to
close the show
and go after Yara.
- If the intention
is to fuck with people,
it's not gonna work.
This is my make it moment,
because this is what I do
for a living, and...
- Yeah.
- Is entertain people
on the microphone.
- What do you think
about the order?
- I think it's a setup.
- For you, like, if I were to go
right after Shangela,
I'd be a little bit nervous.
- If I go out there and bomb,
it's gonna be like,
"Oh, fuck."
- They should have never told me
they saw me as a threat.
I will see each one of them
go home.
- Hi, Manila.
I'm Rita.
- Hi, Rita.
I'm a huge fan.
Rita Rudner is going to be
giving us stand-up advice.
She's one of the funniest people
in show business.
- And what are you going to do
for us today?
- Looking back at
some of the PBS programming
that I used to watch
and how gay
it actually seems now.
- Let's hear you
do the first joke.
- So looking back at Mr. Rogers,
I don't know
if he was on the down-low,
because he had a second house.
And every show started out
with a costume change.
Comedy's hard.
I'm just nervous that, like,
other people's routines
are gonna be,
like, so much funnier than mine.
- My life is funny.
- And now tell us
some of the funny things.
- I am from Puerto Rico.
Since I was just a little girl.
You know.
- That's funny.
- [clicks tongue]
I went all the way to Florida.
- Maybe let's make a joke
about that.
You say, "I came to Miami.
"I was in first class.
I was in the front of the raft."
- I was in the--in the what?
- In the front of the raft.
- In the raft?
- Yes, that's a raft.
- Girl, I don't know
if I can pronounce that.
- My, um, act is gonna be based
on the film Carrie.
- I haven't seen Carrie
in 40 years.
I always worry about
a specific movie reference.
If no one has seen, uh,
the movie, she is in trouble.
- And my outfit that
I'm wearing, actually,
it's sort of this
blood-drenched,
like, you know, gown.
- You come in--"Did anyone else
just get their period?"
- See, I wanted to do
a period joke.
Anybody else get their period?
- "Did anyone else just get."
- "Just get their per..."
So did anyone else
just get their period?
- But stay still
while you're doing it.
- Anyone else
just get their period?
- There you go.
I laughed.
- So I think what I do is
I want to kind of start out
by maybe
I should drop some weight.
- Good.
- And basically, like, that's
kind of what it's about.
A fat chick's like a unicycle.
Every guy wants to be with one.
They want to take one on a ride.
They just don't want to be seen
doing it.
Ultimately, I think what I want
to do is maybe not, like, love,
and maybe not just, like,
a one-night stand.
I think what it is is I just
want to sit on a guy's face.
- You're not really talking
about how to lose weight.
- Right.
- You know, you have to decide
what it is that you're going to
talk about.
- I'm a post-modern pimp ho.
I've never performed
as a character
on the stage other than myself.
- You've got it right away.
When you come out and say, "Yo,
you know, bitch..."
you've got that--
you've got the character
perfectly right there.
- Great.
But I'm feeling more pressure,
and definitely a little nervous.
You always want to shine,
especially when people think
it's what you do.
- Hi.
- Hello, Yara.
I'm supposed to be
a little person.
- Right.
- Yes, I want to make a story.
This girl from Spain.
It's hard to live here
in States,
and I miss the guy.
This gorgeous guy.
And I follow him.
You know, I'm a little person,
and I have to poop.
[imitates flatulence]
Get out, get out, cabron.
Get out, get out, get out,
cabron.
Get out, get out, get out.
- That is the most unusual act
I've ever seen.
- Oh.
It's so weird hearing my voice.
- Now, Carmen, are you doing,
um, something personal about you
or other people?
- Haven't really pieced together
what I'm gonna do yet.
- Just say some things you have
on that lovely sheet of paper.
- Um...
- Come on.
You have to say something
in the mic,
otherwise we can't help.
- Okay, well,
I'll see you tomorrow.
- You silly boy.
Come over here.
- Like, I just have, like,
a bunch of topics that I...
- Okay, what are some more
of your topics?
- Okay, I'm the only queen
that's really here
from new Jersey,
and I don't look at myself
in the mirror
and see a stereotypical
new Jersey person.
- So did you always
feel out of place?
- Never.
- But you should,
because that's gonna be funny.
There's nothing funny about
a good-looking person
doing well,
who's confident.
So think of something that
you're insecure about,
and share it with us.
- Let's see...mm...
- I didn't understand where
her humor was going to
come from,
so I'm gonna worry about Carmen
tonight.
- [alarm beeps]
- Buenos dias.
- Let the funny come out.
- We're back
in the workroom today,
and the challenge this week
is to come up with a hilarious
outfit for the runway
and then perform
a stand-up routine
for a live audience.
- She sounds like--like a goat.
- Girl, I got to learn
this thing by memory.
It's so loud in here, it's still
hard to commit stuff to memory
when everyone's talking,
you know.
- [moans]
- [sighs]
- Delta's a little bit shaken
at this point,
because this is a
really high-pressure challenge.
She's struggling, and I really,
really feel for her.
- I'm terrified,
and I'm scared as shit.
I'm so worried, you know?
- Relax.
Don't stress.
We got this.
We're the Heathers.
- Yep.
- We're the Heathers.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, babe.
Your face looks so much better.
- 'Cause I'm gonna be a clown,
'cause I'm gonna be hilarious!
- Before, you was painted like
a motherfuckin' ghost, honey.
- Why are you making fun of me
so hard?
I just want to be a fierce
drag queen like the next girl.
- Hey, Manila,
are you going to speak
in, like, your Asian accent?
- Are you gonna speak
with an Espanol accent?
- I can't help it.
[laughter]
- You know what you should do?
You should do
that British accent
you were so successful at.
- Fuck you.
- So funny to me.
- Isn't it funny?
- It is funny.
- Manila told Ru that
she's so tired of my mouth.
But you'll never
see her shut up.
I don't even think
she takes air.
- Okay?
This show is gonna start out
with a bang.
- I see Carmen in her fat suit.
It's just--it's so too much.
It's so weird.
I was like, "Really, girl?
This is what you're gonna do?"
- Bitch, and I want to
lay on it, honey.
- I know that everyone is,
like, "Oh, well, Carmen.
I'm worried about Carmen."
My mentality is,
this is going to work.
- She just signed the paper.
She's on her way home.
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Hey, guys.
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle,
how is your funny bone?
- Oh, being tickled
as we speak.
- Hey, Billy B.
Are you related to Celine Dion?
- No.
- Then why the long face?
[laughter]
Rita Rudner.
Thank you for giving my girls
a master class in comedy.
- I was very impressed,
and I think
it's going to be a lot of fun.
I can't wait.
- Arden Myrin.
- Hi.
- I hope you're wearing
your iPad,
because the fun
is about to flow, girl.
- I never go anywhere
without it.
- [laughter]
For this week's main challenge,
we asked our girls
to make us laugh out loud
with their own
stand-up routines.
Tonight,
headlining on the main stage,
let's welcome RuPaul's
drag queens of comedy.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
- Hello.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Anybody else on their period?
You know, I'm a little bit into
the horror movies.
Can you guess which one?
Carrie, yes.
How many people have seen
Carrie, actually?
Well, see, good, good.
The real special thing
about Carrie
is that she has
telekinetic powers.
Telekinesis means that you can
move things with your mind.
The last time I moved anything
with my head,
it was in a motel room.
The john threw $40
on my come-slick tits
and told me
to get the fuck out.
I was like,
"I'm leaving, fucker,
I'm leaving."
Good god.
You ain't got to yell at me
like that.
I'll see you at home, dad.
[laughter]
- I'm a drag queen.
When you first start doing drag,
it's, like, you want to be
the fishiest.
You want to have the best body.
But now I want to be a fat girl.
I want to be a fat girl.
You can get dick
from anywhere.
Every guy wants to secretly
fuck a fat bitch, number one.
So I'm not gonna have
no man problems, okay?
I want to be, like, really fat.
I want to get pregnant
and not even know it.
[laughter]
You know, have you seen those
specials on TV?
And it's usually a big girl.
It's, like,
of course she didn't know
she was fuckin' pregnant.
You know what I mean?
I want to go to the bathroom,
sit on the toilet, and become a
mother, okay?
No matter what size I am,
I will be the body beautiful.
Always, okay?
You want to see?
A little preview?
[cheers and applause]
And I will still [bleep]
turn it, darling.
Always.
- Whoo!
Yes, bitches!
It is not Angelina Jolie.
It is not Beyoncé.
It is your girl, Alexis,
all the way from Puerto Rico!
[speaking Spanish]
Yes, ma'am, honey!
And I am so excited,
because I always wanted to be
a star, honey,
so I left Puerto Rico behind,
and I moved to united states,
all the way to Florida.
I did travel in first class.
Right in front of that boat,
baby.
Honey, I'm a Latina girl,
and I only have two options
in this country--
being a housekeeper
or being a stripper, bitches.
And you all know I didn't came
here to clean toilets, baby,
so I became a stripper, baby!
Yes, ma'am, honey.
If god give it to you, baby,
you better make some money.
Yes, ma'am.
I am here and I'm queer, baby.
- Mm-hmm.
I said, "Bitch
better have my money."
Right?
Let me tell you something, baby.
They call me Laquifa.
Laquifa the P.M.P.
Now, that stands for
the post-modern pimp ho.
Post-modern pimp ho means, yes,
I'm still a pimp,
but I'm also my own ho.
That's right.
'Cause of the recession, y'all,
I'm telling you,
I done had to scale back.
You know, and sometimes I don't
even pay myself my own money.
Uh-huh.
If I did, maybe
I could get some shoes
where my toes wasn't hanging
five inches off the edge.
Yeah.
I know you tried to clown me
for my cliffhangers.
Yeah, I saw it.
You know, they always try
to clown me on the block, baby.
They always saying, "Laquifa!"
I say, "What?"
They say, "Laquifa,
where your hoes at?"
I said, "Bitch, don't you see
"I'm wearing four pair of hose
right here,
holding back my dick?"
Ugh!
Boy, you know,
I had a dumbass girlfriend
that went and joined PETA?
She came screaming at me
last week
talking about, "Laquifa!"
I said, "What?"
She said, "Laquifa,
don't you know
how many innocent animals
had to die
for you to have that fur coat?"
I said, "Bitch,
do you know how many
rich animals I had to fuck
to get this coat?"
Stupid bitch.
- Hi, everyone.
My parents weren't really big
about the TV.
I really only had, like,
PBS and Sesame Street.
Sesame Street
was one gay-ass block.
Okay, obviously we have
Bert and Ernie.
I mean, they're so gay,
they practically
are board members of GLAAD.
Um, now,
one of my favorite people
that lives on Sesame Street
is the Count.
He's one of those old,
Liberace gays,
and he loves
collecting tchotchkes,
like Faberge eggs.
[imitating Count]
One Faberge egg,
two Faberge egg,
three Faberge egg.
Ah, ah, ah.
- Whoo!
- Hi, I'm Yara Sofia.
I'm gonna make
a long story short.
I met a guy in a club,
and he took me
to wonder restaurant
he call McDonald's.
"You want chicken sandwich?"
I go, "What the hell
is chicken?"
She told me,
"Chicken means pollo."
Pollo means
"cock" in Spain!
So I don't want to eat
a fucking dick sandwich.
After that, he took me
to the apartment,
and he took her clothes off.
"Oh, my god,
what the hell is that?"
He was huge.
The difference between an onion
and a 14-inch dick,
both makes me cry.
[laughter]
[imitates flatulence]
Get out, get out, get out,
get out, get out!
Get out, get out, cabron.
There was shit
all over the bed.
I felt like a Willy Wonka
Chocolate Factory.
[cheers and applause]
- My name's Delta Work.
I'm in my early to early 30s,
and, um, I'm here in southern
California
just kind of looking for love,
you know,
and it's kind of hard
for a big girl like me,
because it's so
body-conscious in L.A.,
and it freaks me out to think--
who is gonna want
a girl like me?
What?
Is that funny?
Like, I see these stories
about these girls
that they go out running
and then they get,
like, abducted and assaulted,
and, you know, it's, like,
I have to eat frozen burritos.
I have to watch the marathon
of Hoarders.
Because if I go out
and exercise,
I'm gonna get raped.
You guys have been
an amazing audience.
Thank you so much
for coming out.
We appreciate you coming out.
- Welcome back, ladies.
It's time for
the judges' critiques.
Let's start with Raja.
How'd you feel out there?
- [exhales noisily]
I'm so glad that's over.
It was really challenging.
- What I loved
about your performance
was that you had a topper
of your topper line
when you said the dad.
- Yeah.
- When did you think of that?
- Today.
It was good.
The makeup is flawless.
I could go on and on, but wow.
Your face is by far the most
beautiful you've ever looked.
- I notice you had a lot of
setup;
not a lot of punch lines.
- Overall, I thought
you did a great job,
and it's not easy to go first,
and you look...
♪ Fantastic ♪
- ♪ Thank you ♪
- Next up, Carmen Carrera.
- Hey, guys.
- You didn't share your act
with Rita yesterday.
Was that a strategy you had?
- No, not at all.
My way of thinking
is very weird.
Some people, I guess,
think that I might be,
like, not paying attention
and not focusing,
but I'm always in my head.
- How is your head?
- My head is good.
- Haven't had any complaints
yet.
[laughter]
- Rita, what'd you think?
- Well, I was so proud of you.
I couldn't figure out where
the jokes were gonna come from,
and you figured it out.
- I thought that you were pretty
and you relied on that,
so that performance completely
changed my opinion of you.
- I love the hair and the
outfit.
It's like Wonder Woman meets my
favorite shag rug.
If you can be beautiful and
funny, there's your super power.
- I thought you were gonna suck.
Honest to god.
I am so proud of you tonight.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Carmen, are you actually
wearing anything
underneath that jacket?
- I kind of wanted to
show you guys my real body.
- [laughs]
If I looked like that,
I would never
take that outfit off
or put clothes on.
- Thank you, Carmen.
Up next, Alexis Mateo.
- I loved your reveal,
and they are big.
There's "a", "b", "c",
and Volkswagens.
I think maybe you relied
a little bit too much
on the visual gag.
- In radio,
you call it a crutch.
It's when you repeat something
over and over
'cause you don't know
what to say.
In Alexis' case it was "honey."
"Listen, honey.
"Let me tell you something,
honey.
No, honey.
Honey, honey, honey."
but be aware of those crutches.
- All right, Alexis.
Thank you.
Shangela Laquifa Wadley.
The pimptress.
- All right.
- I loved your concept.
It was so strong.
You kept on that theme.
And there was absolutely
no dead air.
- I just felt like people
were really with you,
and we felt like we
were in the hands of a pro.
- You look better tonight
than I've ever seen you look.
- You blended,
and I see the major difference.
- Thank you.
- So kudos to you, Shangela.
- I think that
that act and your talent
is money in the bank.
- Next up, Manila.
Now, the Sesame Street jokes
were very funny.
Did you think of those, or had
you heard them somewhere else?
- No, I just kind of, like,
quick made it up.
I mean, maybe someone else
suspects it too?
- I think the audience
took a beat to get to know you.
And especially
following Laquifa.
You know, you had to really
readjust the whole energy
of the audience.
- The content that you had
for the jokes
and what they were based on,
some of them were lost
because when we were
sort of laughing,
you were onto the other one.
- Were you nervous?
- I kind of was.
- You did feel the most
rehearsed of everybody.
Like, maybe in a stiffer way.
- Everything about you visually
is right on point tonight,
Manila.
But I feel like I've heard
a lot of those jokes before.
I mean, the Bert and Ernie joke,
let's be honest.
Everybody has been telling that.
- Up next, Yara Sofia.
- Yes!
Yes!
- What was
your character's name?
- Blara.
I have a friend
that is a little person,
and he pushed me to do it.
- And he would not be offended
by this at all?
- No.
I did it with the respect.
This is the stand-up comedy
that comedians do
in Puerto Rico.
- I was wondering if
it was going to be too graphic,
but I knew your energy
would take care of it,
and we loved watching you.
- I don't know
what you talked about,
except chicken and some shit.
- I have to say,
I love the character,
and your capacity
to stay on your knees
could earn you a lot of money
somewhere.
- Up next, we've got Delta Work.
You seemed a little bit nervous.
- I loved the beginning,
but at the end,
we kind of went a bit of
a distance without a laugh.
- I did notice going off-track
of what I thought
I was gonna do,
and I guess in some--
somewhere in my mind,
I thought
that was being organic.
- It started off sort of strong.
It felt very defined.
And then, I feel like
maybe you lost your way.
And then I felt like
there wasn't a payoff.
- Just remember, when
you're portraying a character,
you got to go
all the way with it.
So pump it up.
Get out of your head.
- Okay.
- All right, ladies,
I think we've heard enough.
Now, while you all
enjoy an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
[car engine starts]
- Just between us girls,
let's start with Raja.
- First of all, I love the
bucket of blood on her head.
She didn't really go inward
for her comedy.
- We didn't get to know
anything more about Raja.
- Had she incorporated
or paralleled
her own story
with Carrie's story,
it would have been funny.
Let's talk about Carmen Carrera.
- She was the one
I was worried about.
She didn't tell me one joke.
And she thought about it
and came back with it.
I was so impressed.
- Tonight she did
a great performance.
I was very happy to see
that personality come out.
- Honey, Alexis Mateo.
I was a little disappointed
that she rushed through it.
She didn't let her routine
breathe.
- It just seemed
super amateur to me.
- I liked her physicality.
She had some fun dance moves,
but I don't remember her act.
- Shangela.
She was very confident
and comfortable on the stage.
- What she had was a character
I've never seen before,
and she has a catchphrase
that I want to hear
over and over.
- To me, as a stand-up,
the audience wants to know
that they're in good hands.
With Laquifa, we wanted to go
along on the ride.
- Her makeup was a lot better
tonight too.
- It really was.
- I think she did a good job.
- Manila Luzon.
A lot of people
recognized her routine.
Or it just felt very familiar.
- I do think
she added some things
that I'd never heard of,
like Mr. Rogers and the mailman.
I've never heard that.
But it didn't seem fresh.
- Yara Sofia.
That bitch was crazy.
She reminded me of Andy Kaufman,
who did things that sort of
just freaked people out,
but they still laughed.
- I always say, when you do
something, do it 110%.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I think she did it 120%.
- I felt like it could be at,
like, the Whitney Museum as,
like, a performance.
- The Whitney and Bobby Museum.
- [laughs]
- Delta Work.
- It started out good,
and then it just went
all over the place.
- It was kind of dark,
wasn't it?
- And it was a bit sad.
- She's thinking way too much
about everything that she says.
She's got a constant sadness
around her.
- All right, silence!
I've made my decision.
Send in the clowns.
- Welcome back, ladies.
Now, based on your ability
to tickle our funny bones,
I've made some decisions.
Alexis Mateo,
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Raja...
bloody well done.
You are safe.
- Thank you.
- Manila, your presentation
was stiff.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- When Ru says I'm in the bottom
two, I'm in shock.
At this point in the game,
like, where we're all so good,
like, any little fuck-up
is now magnified.
- Shangela,
as a post-modern pimp,
you bitch-slapped
the competition.
Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
You've won an original
custom-designed gown
from Miami Elite Designs.
- Hallelu.
[laughter]
I'm almost speechless,
and the judges' response to me
makes me just feel like
I'm going
in the right direction.
Thank you.
- Yara Sofia, you're safe.
You may join the other girls.
- Aah!
[laughter]
- Carmen Carrera, you're safe.
Delta Work, my dear.
This week, you lost your way.
I'm sorry, but you are
up for elimination.
- Okay.
I'm pissed off because this
should be my first time
in the bottom.
This shouldn't be my third time
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and to save yourself
from elimination.
- Oh, my god.
I don't want Delta to go.
- The time has come
for you to lip-synch
for your life.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
[intro to Macarthur Park plays]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Spring was never waiting ♪
♪ For us, dear ♪
♪ It ran one step ahead ♪
♪ As we followed in the dance ♪
♪ Macarthur Park is melting ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
♪ Someone left the cake out ♪
♪ In the rain ♪
♪ I don't think ♪
♪ That I can take it ♪
♪ 'Cause it took ♪
♪ So long to bake it ♪
♪ And I'll never have ♪
♪ That recipe again ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ Ah-ha ♪
- [laughs]
- ♪ I recall ♪
♪ The yellow ♪
♪ On the ground ♪
♪ Beneath your knees ♪
♪ Macarthur Park ♪
♪ Is melting in the dark ♪
♪ All the sweet, green icing ♪
♪ Flowing down ♪
♪ I don't think ♪
♪ That I can take it ♪
♪ 'Cause it took so long ♪
♪ To bake it ♪
♪ And I'll never have ♪
♪ That recipe again ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
- I'm looking at Manila,
and I'm going, "Wow.
This is Broadway."
♪ ♪
- ♪ Oh, and after ♪
♪ All the loves in my life ♪
♪ You'll still be the one ♪
♪ And I'll ask myself why ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
[applause]
- That is what a lip-synch
for your life
is all about.
Now, I have made my decision.
Manila, shante, you stay.
- Thank you for everything
you've given me.
I love you.
[crying]
- Fuck.
- Delta, you are a great queen,
and this experience
will propel you
into a phase where you can trust
your god-given instinct.
You know what?
I love you.
I adore you.
- Thank you.
- Now, sashay away.
- Thank you very much.
[applause]
- I'm gonna miss you.
- [crying]
- I took some risks.
Um, it didn't work in this case,
but I'm not disappointed
in myself.
I'm so happy
to have made it this far,
and I'm just glad
to have lost to a Heather,
not to one of the boogers.
- Condragulations, girls.
You are all one step closer to
becoming America's next
drag superstar.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen!
- All right,
now let the music play.
[upbeat music plays]
♪ ♪
Grand prize contributed in part
by AlandChuck.travel.