&gt;&gt; Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll need to perform in
a ladyboy music festival
we're calling RuPaul-a-Palooza.
&gt;&gt; I think she's gonna rely on
what she's been relying on
this whole time:
being a loudmouth.
[out of tune] ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ All of the glamour ♪
♪ And all of the fame ♪
&gt;&gt; Can I get a halleloo?
&gt;&gt; ♪ Now that the time has ♪
♪ Come ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Waited what seemed like ♪
♪ Forever ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Mama please don't look ♪
♪ Back ♪
&gt;&gt; God save the queen.
Raja.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
&gt;&gt; Fuck Yes.
&gt;&gt; Ladies.
I've made my decision.
Shangela.
Shante, you stay.
Carmen Carrera.
Sashay away.
And tonight...
I'm gonna give you an
opportunity to really wig out.
&gt;&gt; [cursing in Spanish]
&gt;&gt; Wigs fly.
And a tangled twist.
[hissing like a cat]
With extra special guest judges
Fantasia Barrino,
and Wayne Brady.
[cheers and applause]
The winner of RuPaul's
Drag Race will receive
a lifetime supply of
Kryolan professional makeup,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut,
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win.
&gt;&gt; ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ Start your engines ♪
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman win ♪
♪ Start your engines ♪
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman win ♪
[car tires squealing]
&gt;&gt; Good morning.
&gt;&gt; We're back again.
&gt;&gt; Top five, bitches.
&gt;&gt; Oh, she wrote notes
for everyone.
&gt;&gt; Says, "Raja, I love you."
Oh, my girl.
&gt;&gt; Bye, Heather.
&gt;&gt; I'm gonna miss her.
&gt;&gt; In the workroom this morning
there's a huge, huge, void...
that used to be taken up
by Carmen's giant ass.
So I guess Raja, it's up to you.
You're the bitch now.
I appoint you.
&gt;&gt; Gladly.
You know what, I've been so nice
this whole time.
And I'm not holding back
anymore.
If I win something
and I deserve it,
why not show it off
a little bit?
So I won.
&gt;&gt; Watch out, darling.
Anything could happen.
One day you're in,
and the next day you're out.
&gt;&gt; Suck it, bitches,
suck it, bitches.
I win, I win.
&gt;&gt; I really don't give a fuck
about raja.
He just want to become a model,
but he's old,
and he looks like a man.
Shangela, you was
in the bottom two again.
&gt;&gt; Oh, Lord have mercy.
&gt;&gt; How was that, girl?
&gt;&gt; You start to feel like,
I'm here again, why?
But you just gotta go back to,
you know--
&gt;&gt; Yeah, wi to fi, you know?
&gt;&gt; Who you are.
You gotta fight.
I feel like I have to work
harder to prove to everyone,
you know, that I deserve to be
here.
&gt;&gt; And they keep talking
about you.
Like, they keep attacking you.
&gt;&gt; 'Cause they want me gone,
sister.
If Raja and Manila
really didn't think
that I was competition,
they wouldn't be
bothered about it.
They'd embrace me like Carmen.
[alarm sounds]
&gt;&gt; Ooh, girl!
You've got shemail.
Hello, ladies.
all: Hello!
&gt;&gt; However you dippity-do it,
the next drag superstar has got
to keep her hair bouncing
and behaving.
It takes just one bad blowout.
You could be hair today,
and gone tomorrow.
And parting is such
sweet sorrow.
&gt;&gt; Whoo.
&gt;&gt; What?
&gt;&gt; Something about hair, honey.
&gt;&gt; Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hey!
&gt;&gt; Hey, Ru.
&gt;&gt; Now, every now and then,
we all have a bad hair day.
And that's when a ladyboy
really has to improvise.
Now for today's mini-challenge,
you need to make a dramatic
headpiece,
using only materials swiped
from the gay beach.
all: Ooh!
&gt;&gt; Now, ladies.
You've got crabs,
beach balls,
grass skirts,
and a whole bunch of fun stuff.
Now there's 20 minutes
on the clock.
Ready.
Set.
Go!
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Ooh, look at the fishy!
[high-pitched muttering]
I'm making this headpiece
with a fishy lace front.
[laughing]
&gt;&gt; I want mine to be chic.
&gt;&gt; Well, good luck, honey.
'Cause that looks busted
and crusted, girl.
&gt;&gt; Honey, this is a Philip
Treacy Alexander McQueen, honey.
&gt;&gt; Oh, you bitch.
Mama, stand up straight.
My headdress is falling over
and dying.
But at least it doesn't look as
jacked up as Shangela's.
&gt;&gt; Ooh!
Oh.
&gt;&gt; What kind of headpiece
is that?
Like, a parrot with a dolphin?
What the hell?
&gt;&gt; All right, lady-kins.
all: Whoo!
&gt;&gt; First up, let's take a look
at Raja's head.
Wow.
Now, have you had crabs before?
&gt;&gt; Um, yeah, I actually pulled
these right out of my panties.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
Yara Sofia.
&gt;&gt; Yaaaay!
&gt;&gt; Beach party.
&gt;&gt; Girl, you are so fishy.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
It looks so real, right?
&gt;&gt; Manila.
Showgirl.
It's very Ziegfeld.
&gt;&gt; Although I need
a little Viagra,
or the pit crew to give it
a little inspiration.
'Cause she's starting to sag.
Like Raja!
&gt;&gt; Alexis Mateo.
&gt;&gt; Pat...
all: Ooh.
&gt;&gt; I steal the head fish, bitch.
Look how I float.
&gt;&gt; Yes, you are floating.
&gt;&gt; I feel like in a boat fat.
Pfft!
[laughing]
&gt;&gt; Shangela.
all: [giggling]
&gt;&gt; Is that a parrot
humping a dolphin?
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; Mm-hmm.
&gt;&gt; I don't know how natural
that is,
but somehow I'm strangely
stimulated by it.
Ladies.
You all had fun
with this challenge.
But...
I'm gonna have to go with Raja.
&gt;&gt; Oh, shit!
&gt;&gt; Raja is the winner of this
mini-challenge.
[laughing]
&gt;&gt; She can jump around
and celebrate everything
that she wants to,
but I won too.
Hey.
&gt;&gt; Ladies.
A queen's crowning glory
is her hair.
Now I'm gonna give you
an opportunity
to really wig out.
[cheers and applause]
&gt;&gt; Oh, God.
&gt;&gt; Oh.
&gt;&gt; For this week's
main challenge,
you'll be competing
in a fantasy hair show.
You need to create
three distinct hairstyles.
First, a classic look
from another era.
Second, a modern look
worthy of a red carpet event.
And third, a far-out fantasy
hair extravaganza.
&gt;&gt; Mmm, hey.
&gt;&gt; Now, Raja.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Because you won
the mini-challenge,
you get a five-second head start
at the wig bar.
&gt;&gt; Oh!
&gt;&gt; Provided by Wilshire Wigs.
So get going.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
&gt;&gt; [screams]
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; What are you doing?
The extravaganza?
&gt;&gt; Mm-hmm.
That's the one
I'm gonna work on first,
'cause I think that'll
take me the most time.
She ain't slick.
I know what she's doing.
Yara is brushing that wig,
and walking around,
looking at
everyone's creations.
Getting ideas.
What am I gonna do?
Hmm.
&gt;&gt; I love doing hair.
&gt;&gt; I think Yara's gonna do
really good at this one.
&gt;&gt; Mm-hmm.
&gt;&gt; 'Cause you always have, like,
the craziest, wackiest hair.
&gt;&gt; And Manila, how do you think
I'm gonna do with this
challenge?
&gt;&gt; Um, I think you'll do fine.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; Shangela, this is a comb.
&gt;&gt; Ooh, girl!
&gt;&gt; Oh, yeah.
&gt;&gt; It goes through the hairs.
Mm-hmm.
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Manila.
&gt;&gt; Just sharing the knowledge,
Honey.
&gt;&gt; These girls don't expect me
to have any creativity
or ability when it
comes to this.
It's a fire in me
to prove them wrong.
&gt;&gt; Our main challenge is
creating
three different looks
of hair,
matching with
three different outfits--
the classic from another era,
a modern red carpet look,
and then we have
a fantasy creation.
&gt;&gt; Alexis.
&gt;&gt; What happened, boo?
&gt;&gt; Which one are you working on
right now?
&gt;&gt; My fantasy look.
That's gonna be my hardest part
of the challenge--
is going to be
to get that look together.
I normally work with my own hair
as a base.
So I'm gonna have to see
how it goes tomorrow,
because I can
actually style the pieces
that I'm gonna wear.
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh.
&gt;&gt; But it's not until it's
on my head
that you actually see
the final product.
&gt;&gt; Right.
&gt;&gt; Alexis is probably gonna have
this weird-looking Elvis
pompadour
with, like,
an Avatar ponytail.
I mean, this is what she does.
Shangela, au naturale.
Do you know what you're doing
for your era?
&gt;&gt; Donna Summer
meets Diana Ross.
&gt;&gt; Work.
&gt;&gt; Yara.
&gt;&gt; Huh?
&gt;&gt; How you doing?
&gt;&gt; This is my '80s look.
&gt;&gt; An '80s look?
&gt;&gt; Fros seem to be really
popular for a classic era.
&gt;&gt; Hello, hello, hello.
&gt;&gt; Hola.
&gt;&gt; Hello.
&gt;&gt; Hi, how are things
shaping up?
&gt;&gt; Fierce, honey, fierce.
&gt;&gt; Well, hello there.
Alexis.
Which is your classic look?
&gt;&gt; I think I'm going for
the 1940s.
&gt;&gt; Well, now, during the '40s
there was a rationing
on latex titties.
&gt;&gt; Are you serious?
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; '40s look.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Do you have it here?
&gt;&gt; No.
&gt;&gt; No?
What about your
red carpet hair?
&gt;&gt; I'm going to go for
the evening modern mohawk.
&gt;&gt; An evening
modern mohawk style.
And where's that?
&gt;&gt; It's not ready yet.
&gt;&gt; It's not ready yet?
Oh, Miss Thing.
Let's talk about your hair
fantasy-stravaganza.
&gt;&gt; I saw this pink,
and it reminded me
of that cotton candy
that you get
when you go to the circus.
&gt;&gt; Yes, yes.
&gt;&gt; And that's my inspiration,
the circus.
&gt;&gt; Your inspiration is
cotton candy from the circus.
&gt;&gt; For the circus.
&gt;&gt; Ah.
Hi, Shangela.
&gt;&gt; Hey, Ru.
&gt;&gt; How you doing?
Oh, this is
your hair fantasy?
&gt;&gt; This is it.
We're on it today.
&gt;&gt; Wow.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, it's kind of like
an alien princess
from the future.
&gt;&gt; It is quite the fantasy.
And you've got
your classic hair?
&gt;&gt; Classic hair is very
Diana Ross meets Donna Summer.
&gt;&gt; I'd love to wear that hair.
That is beautiful.
So you not being a hair queen,
are you asking for advice
from the other girls?
Just how to put things together?
&gt;&gt; No.
I know and I'm learning
what looks great on me.
&gt;&gt; Mm-hmm.
&gt;&gt; And no one can tell you
what looks best on you
but yourself.
I mean, I know it's okay
to ask for help,
but I've kind of
gotten some feedback
from the other girls
that they're over me
asking for help.
&gt;&gt; Right.
&gt;&gt; So I can do things on my own.
&gt;&gt; Good, good.
You got to, 'cause, you know,
we're down to the wire now.
&gt;&gt; That's right.
&gt;&gt; Yara Sofia.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Hi, darling.
&gt;&gt; Tell me about your
classic hair look.
&gt;&gt; I made this with braids.
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh.
&gt;&gt; On the cover.
And I mixed two afros,
two tones.
&gt;&gt; I see.
&gt;&gt; Oh, wonderful, wonderful.
You know, um, Shangela is doing
a little bit
of a--sort of a '70s afro.
It's big, curly hair.
Are you worried
about that at all?
&gt;&gt; No, well, I made it first.
And when I see Shangela's
classic hair,
it looks like mine.
Even the brunette color.
I think Shangela's a copycat.
&gt;&gt; Hey, Raja.
&gt;&gt; Hi.
&gt;&gt; So tell me,
what are you planning
for your red carpet look?
&gt;&gt; I am taking some inspiration
from Janice,
from the Muppets.
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh.
She's my favorite muppet,
I think.
&gt;&gt; [imitating Janice]
"Hey, man.
Yeah, it's gonna be cool."
&gt;&gt; Yeah, uh-huh.
Artistically,
what is your fantasy?
&gt;&gt; Well, my fantasy would never
really involve a wig,
'cause the wig would be
pulled off, but...
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh, no...
I really don't know what my hair
fantasy is, to be honest.
&gt;&gt; Now, listen.
I just want you to know
that we expect something
truly out of this world.
&gt;&gt; Ru wants to see something
that's just gonna wow him
and, you know, take him
to another, like,
another realm, really.
And I definitely feel
a lot of pressure.
I am about to lose my mind.
&gt;&gt; Hey, Manila.
&gt;&gt; Hi.
&gt;&gt; How you doing?
&gt;&gt; Good.
&gt;&gt; What you got there?
Sort of a rock me disco Amadeus,
isn't it?
&gt;&gt; This is my classic look.
&gt;&gt; That's your classic look.
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
I thought it may be kind of cool
to do,
like, the mix of, like,
'80s meets 1800s.
&gt;&gt; This is not
your fantasy look?
&gt;&gt; This is my classic look.
&gt;&gt; 'Cause that's pretty fantasy.
That's--that's out there,
isn't it?
&gt;&gt; It's a lot to explain.
&gt;&gt; Some of the other girls
have gotten in trouble
for having to explain
what it is they're doing.
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; You know, it should be clear.
&gt;&gt; Hits you over the head.
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Make sure that everyone
gets it.
&gt;&gt; Well, to quote Alexis Mateo,
it should say, "Bam!"
&gt;&gt; The jig is up.
&gt;&gt; You know what I'm saying?
&gt;&gt; I will.
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; All right, ladies.
Gather around.
Now tomorrow, we'll be joined by
our extra special guest judges--
the talented and hilarious
Wayne Brady...
&gt;&gt; Whoo!
&gt;&gt; Wow.
&gt;&gt; Brady.
&gt;&gt; And my favorite baby mama,
Fantasia.
For real.
No, for real, though.
I'm for real.
&gt;&gt; Fantasia won American Idol,
and I can't wait.
&gt;&gt; In addition to debuting
your three hairstyles
on the main stage,
there's just one more
little detail
I neglected to mention.
I want you to create
a runway outfit
made entirely out of...
hair.
&gt;&gt; [gasping] Oh, my god.
What am I going to do?
&gt;&gt; You'll get more hair pieces,
toupees, falls, and merkins.
So y'all can really
get wiggy up in here.
&gt;&gt; Like, really, Ru?
Really?
&gt;&gt; Listen, the competition is
getting pretty hairy in here.
So don't fuck it up.
&gt;&gt; Our main challenge today
is that
we're creating three
different hair looks
that has to correspond
to three different outfits,
and we have to create an outfit
out of hair!
There's so much to do,
and so little time.
You can feel the pressure on.
&gt;&gt; We have to make a dress out
of nothing but wigs?
This is insane.
You gotta be kidding me.
&gt;&gt; It's crazy,
that's what it is.
&gt;&gt; That kind of changes
my whole, like, look.
&gt;&gt; Me too.
&gt;&gt; It's a giant challenge,
but yet it's like,
they tell you, like, later.
&gt;&gt; Isn't that crazy, though?
That there's always a twist?
Just when you think
you have it down.
&gt;&gt; Ooh!
Oh!
I almost melted my face.
Sabotage!
Ooh, girl!
It's jumping up in here.
[hysterical laughter]
&gt;&gt; Are you losing it, girl?
Quit sniffing all those
adhesive fumes.
Yara is being wacky.
&gt;&gt; [cursing in Spanish]
&gt;&gt; But a part of me goes,
"Is she doing that
to distract the other girls
in the room?"
Oh, okay.
Miss Girl's got a strategy
of her own.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Be-deep, be-deep ♪
♪ Be-deep, be-deep ♪
Ay! Ay! Ay!
&gt;&gt; Oh, Christ on crackers.
&gt;&gt; Aaiiee!
Oooh!
Aaah!
I mean, come on.
&gt;&gt; Hee-hee-hee!
Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
&gt;&gt; Really?
&gt;&gt; I feel like I'm in some,
like, weird alien petting zoo.
It's, like, shut up.
&gt;&gt; If you guys had a chance
to kill one of the other queens
in this competition,
who would it be?
&gt;&gt; Yara Sofia.
&gt;&gt; I never win the challenge.
And this time, I have to win.
Fuck, it's about time for me.
Um, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Darling, I need help.
&gt;&gt; What, Yara, what?
&gt;&gt; Do you like the combination?
&gt;&gt; I like it, I like it since
you made it.
Yara is coming to my station
every five seconds
to ask me how her look is.
I mean, we're the top five.
Ain't no time to be
talking around
or playing with each other.
This is some real shit
right now.
You'll be all right.
&gt;&gt; I hope so.
&gt;&gt; If Carmen was still here--
&gt;&gt; Mm-hmm.
&gt;&gt; She would have just taken
two wigs,
glued them to her titties.
&gt;&gt; Called it a day.
&gt;&gt; I'm always having problems
with the proportions of my body.
Um, the wrong way.
And this challenge, I have to
wear my body, plus hair.
So for me to actually have
a silhouette on stage,
it's gonna
be very difficult.
My fantasy dress was not going
to the right place
that I want it to.
&gt;&gt; Alexis finish her garment,
and now she's changing the dress
and cut it.
&gt;&gt; Oh, you changed it,
like, fiercely, huh?
&gt;&gt; It doesn't look like circus.
&gt;&gt; I was wondering why you cut
it all apart.
It's important for me to do well
in this challenge because,
bitch, it's the top five.
I mean, I wanna be
part of the top four.
&gt;&gt; It's good, but I don't know
if this could bother you.
&gt;&gt; I put it on so it sits,
like, right here.
Fits okay.
&gt;&gt; Can you glue hair?
&gt;&gt; This is a creative high
for me.
I don't want to look
outward for help.
&gt;&gt; It doesn't have to cover
the entire front.
&gt;&gt; Okay, awesome.
&gt;&gt; Just a design.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Shangela's outfit is a mess.
Hey, girl, listen.
You should learn
some new things.
&gt;&gt; Have you tried your wig
on yet?
&gt;&gt; I haven't even started it.
&gt;&gt; This is all good in theory,
but let's see if it
actually stays on my head.
&gt;&gt; This wig is, like, super,
like, Halloween-y.
I don't know what the fuck
I'm doing anymore.
In Drag Race history, this might
be the craziest and hardest
and most stressful
challenge ever.
Time is getting shorter
and shorter and shorter.
&gt;&gt; Piece of shit.
&gt;&gt; Ow, son of a mother fucking
bitch!
It's do it or die.
[alarm clock buzzing]
&gt;&gt; Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God.
&gt;&gt; Today, the clock is ticking,
honey.
Nobody's ready yet.
We are going crazy.
&gt;&gt; I'm nervous,
'cause I still have to do
my modern, worthy of
a red carpet look.
&gt;&gt; There's just so much
for everyone to do,
that everyone's really feeling
the pressure right now.
&gt;&gt; I'm stressed out of
my fucking mind.
I can feel the veins
in my temples
and in my neck just pulsating
with, like--
[inhales]
I just need to get it done.
&gt;&gt; Ready or not,
here comes mama.
&gt;&gt; Manila, you're getting ready
already?
What about your modern look?
&gt;&gt; Honey, I'm gonna
make it work.
It's gonna be a shake and go,
honey.
&gt;&gt; Did you finish everything?
&gt;&gt; Stop talking to me.
&gt;&gt; Ha ha!
Bitch.
&gt;&gt; I just wanna
get myself painted,
'cause if I'm in the bottom
and I have to lip-synch,
I at least want to be pretty
when I do it.
&gt;&gt; I don't feel like
I'm gonna be there.
I've worked really hard.
I'm confident
in what I'm bringing.
&gt;&gt; This has to be the most
difficult challenge so far.
But I'm actually finding
that I'm a lot better
at doing hair
than I thought I was.
&gt;&gt; I've always wanted to be
in drag,
even when I was a little boy.
I used to sneak into
my sister's closet
and take all of her clothes
and wear them around.
&gt;&gt; Drag made me be
who I want to be
whenever I wanted it to be.
It just gives me that freedom.
&gt;&gt; Freedom.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, it's like a vacation.
You can take a vacation
every night.
&gt;&gt; Exactly.
And you get paid for it,
and it's even better.
To me, it's like
my artistic expression.
&gt;&gt; It's--I know,
it's your creation.
&gt;&gt; Everybody cannot do drag.
&gt;&gt; I think everybody
should have the right
to do drag if they want to,
even if they look busted.
I'm here.
&gt;&gt; Mm-hmm.
When I started it,
like, I was kind of like,
"Am I an attractive person?"
&gt;&gt; I look pretty, and that's--
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
And that's it.
&gt;&gt; Some people use drag
as an escape.
Like they don't feel
that they--
&gt;&gt; Yes, it's true.
&gt;&gt; I agree.
'Cause I started so young.
I needed something to boost
my self-esteem, you know?
And people--people finally
told me I was beautiful.
The biggest difficulty for me,
though,
has been, like, people
who you know or knew people
don't know the real you.
They only know your character.
So they start only calling you
by your character name,
or, like, they only want to
see you in drag.
And then if you show up
and you're not in drag,
they're like,
"Oh, where's Shangela tonight?"
&gt;&gt; But for Alexis,
that's not a problem.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; No, I don't--
I don't know if that's true,
because, I mean, RuPaul, like,
you know, half the time here--
&gt;&gt; I'm not talking about RuPaul;
I'm talking about me.
&gt;&gt; It all starts to become
one person after a while.
&gt;&gt; Raja's first picture of her
in drag is an oil painting.
[laughter]
&gt;&gt; No, bitch,
it's a cave painting.
&gt;&gt; No, it's one of
those pictures
where they have to have
the big flash that explodes
when you take the picture.
&gt;&gt; My problem with drag
is the dating scene.
&gt;&gt; It is kind of hard.
&gt;&gt; My situation that, every time
you're gonna date somebody,
you feel like you just--
&gt;&gt; Have to hide it.
&gt;&gt; You just have to come
out of the closet.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
And then when you're going out
for the night,
and you intend on going out
and hooking up with someone,
you have to make sure
that you put all your drag
up in the closet
and all the sequins
off the floor,
all the rhinestones.
&gt;&gt; It is true.
But that was at the beginning.
&gt;&gt; Now I don't care.
&gt;&gt; Ha!
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And, what? ♪
Hey, guys.
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Hey, Michelle, we're going back
to our roots tonight.
&gt;&gt; Aren't we, baby?
&gt;&gt; Santino.
Now are you gonna be
splitting hairs
with our girls tonight?
&gt;&gt; Oh, you know this.
&gt;&gt; Wayne Brady!
I'm so glad you're here.
&gt;&gt; Hey, you.
I am so happy to be here.
And Fantasia.
&gt;&gt; Ooh!
&gt;&gt; Hi, Ru.
&gt;&gt; This week, our queens
were challenged
to compete in
a fantasy hair show
and create three
distinct hairstyles,
which includes a runway outfit
made entirely out of hair.
Gentlemen...
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
The first looks are their
classic hairstyles
from a past era-era-uh.
Yara Sofia.
Oh, she's got a disco feeling.
&gt;&gt; I'm bringing this '70s look.
With such an inspiration.
And I feel flawless.
&gt;&gt; She loves the nightlife.
&gt;&gt; Studio 54.
&gt;&gt; Alexis Mateo.
Bring the fur, baby.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; My classic look
is all glamour.
Hollywood.
The golden age.
&gt;&gt; The drama.
&gt;&gt; Looks like she was outside
trapping some animals too.
&gt;&gt; A girl's gotta eat.
&gt;&gt; Look at Raja.
Very '60s.
&gt;&gt; Ooh!
&gt;&gt; Yes, hey!
&gt;&gt; Twiggy!
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; That girl.
&gt;&gt; I just wanted her
to feel really sweet,
a little bit like
a sex-cretary in the '60s.
A little Mad Men.
&gt;&gt; Oh, I love a nude pump.
That's Raja from
the secretarial pool.
&gt;&gt; Sex in the '60s.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; Shangela.
Uh-oh, I smell a costume change.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; I'm a Spanish flamenco sister
all the way from Barcelona.
And I'm loving it.
&gt;&gt; Ooh, el motivar.
Toro, toro!
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Ole.
&gt;&gt; Oh, and she popped the fan.
&gt;&gt; Yes, she popped that fan.
&gt;&gt; She popped something.
&gt;&gt; Manila.
&gt;&gt; She's giving you
Marie Antoinette meets Shaft.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Blonde Venus.
&gt;&gt; Is she "rock me Amadeus"
from the '80s?
&gt;&gt; I have a powdered wig going.
I have my little, like,
curls on the side.
And I'm feeling fierce,
and the judges are living.
Oh, look at all the cameos.
&gt;&gt; And look at the candelabra
in her hair.
&gt;&gt; Oh, yes.
That's a candelabra.
This is their modern
red carpet look.
From Yara Sofia.
Wow.
Desperate housewife.
&gt;&gt; There's a little J-Lo
in that one.
&gt;&gt; I'm giving the judges
a very strong haircut
like Rihanna, for example.
&gt;&gt; I'm going to the Emmys.
&gt;&gt; It's very Roberto Cavalli.
&gt;&gt; Sexy urban camo.
&gt;&gt; Yes, it is.
Alexis Mateo.
She's ready for the ALMA awards.
&gt;&gt; For my red carpet
modern look,
I make an evening mohawk.
And it's very modern,
it's very couture.
&gt;&gt; A little new school Mae West.
&gt;&gt; Yes, she is.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, there you go.
She's trying life as a blonde.
&gt;&gt; Just a little bit at a time.
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Raja.
Britt Ekland.
Ooh.
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; Easy breezy.
&gt;&gt; I cut this hair.
This is something
that I razored on my own.
And I am ruling that runway.
All I can hear in my ears are
electric guitars and keyboards.
&gt;&gt; Vidal Sassoon.
Shangela.
Miss Diahann Carroll is
in the house.
&gt;&gt; Yes, she is.
&gt;&gt; I'm daytime class.
So I'm coming down the runway
giving you Diahann Carroll
at the Oprah's Legends ball.
And I'm feeling fierce.
&gt;&gt; Red carpet.
&gt;&gt; Oh, she gave you a wedge.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
I think she's pumpin'
to bump it.
Manila.
&gt;&gt; Audrey Hepburn there.
&gt;&gt; Well, she's more
Jennifer Love Hewitt's version
of Audrey Hepburn.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; I'm walking down the runway,
and I feel like Audrey Hepburn
in Breakfast at Tiffany's,
or Barbara Streisand.
&gt;&gt; She has borrowed those jewels
from Harry Winston.
&gt;&gt; Of course.
&gt;&gt; The security guard
is backstage.
&gt;&gt; Waiting for me.
&gt;&gt; This is their fantasy hair
extravaganza.
Yara Sofia.
&gt;&gt; Oh!
&gt;&gt; Take that, Bjork.
&gt;&gt; How much is that poodle
on the runway?
&gt;&gt; For the fantasy,
I'm wearing this hairy dress.
It's like a scorpion on the top.
I feel so fabulous.
&gt;&gt; I made a purse out
of Shirley Temple.
&gt;&gt; Oh, yes.
&gt;&gt; Won't get out of place.
&gt;&gt; I see her fantasy
is doggy style.
Alexis Mateo.
&gt;&gt; Oh!
&gt;&gt; Phantom of the drag queens.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; I look like a ballerina
in a circus.
I'm loving it.
It just screams Alexis Mateo
from far away.
&gt;&gt; Thighs wide open.
&gt;&gt; Yes, hunty.
Wild, wild west.
Miss Kitty never looked so good.
Raja.
Hair fantasy.
&gt;&gt; Wow.
&gt;&gt; I'm so happy with
what I've created.
It looks like this beautiful,
like, cotton candy
frothy milkshake.
&gt;&gt; Earth girls are easy!
&gt;&gt; Yes.
Yes, Rainbow Brite.
&gt;&gt; She's like a snow cone.
&gt;&gt; Oh, my gosh.
&gt;&gt; Shangela.
&gt;&gt; Ooh!
&gt;&gt; Mad Max.
&gt;&gt; Ooh, She-man the barbarian.
&gt;&gt; The minute I hit that runway,
I am alien warrior princess,
and I'm coming for you.
&gt;&gt; Two queens enter,
one queen leaves.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; Beyond the merkin-dome.
&gt;&gt; Ooh!
I wanna see that in 3-D.
&gt;&gt; Mm-hmm.
&gt;&gt; Manila.
&gt;&gt; What you buzzin' 'bout?
&gt;&gt; Yes, honey.
Honeybee.
&gt;&gt; I'm feeling cute
and floating around
on the runway, like,
from flower to flower.
&gt;&gt; She's pollinating the runway.
&gt;&gt; She is.
&gt;&gt; Buzz, buzz, buzz.
Welcome, ladies.
Your runway was absolutely
hair-raising.
And now it's time
for the judges' critique.
Let's start with Yara Sofia.
Tell me about
your fantasy extravaganza.
&gt;&gt; For me, the word
"extravaganza" means an animal.
&gt;&gt; The word "extravaganza"
to you means an animal,
like a scorpion and a poodle.
&gt;&gt; Scoodle.
&gt;&gt; I made this, um, scorpion,
um, curve.
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh.
&gt;&gt; And I feel very hairy.
Very hairy.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
Well, girl, you are hairy.
&gt;&gt; [raspy groan]
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; It's very Dr. Seuss.
You're like a beautiful woman
from Whoville.
&gt;&gt; Don't take this the bad way,
but, like, you're like the ho
of Whoville.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; A "who-ho."
&gt;&gt; Yeah, a "who-ho."
Horton heard a ho.
Who--I love that.
&gt;&gt; Right. Right.
&gt;&gt; I love that.
&gt;&gt; Fantasia, what did you think
of her classic look?
&gt;&gt; Um, it reminds me so much of
my aunties.
How, you know,
how they used to do it.
And they used to rock it well.
And I want the outfit.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Do you think I can wear
that outfit?
&gt;&gt; Yes, I can make a few ones.
&gt;&gt; I got a lot of junk
in my trunk.
&gt;&gt; Don't worry, darling.
&gt;&gt; Okay, good.
&gt;&gt; Next up, Alexis Mateo.
Hi, mami.
&gt;&gt; Hi, Ru.
Hi, judges.
&gt;&gt; Let's start with the best,
which is this look here.
Your fantasy look.
When you came out,
I totally got circus girl.
Your red carpet look that was
supposed to be very modern,
the hair was kind of like
budget RuPaul, in a way.
I mean, it was like, uh,
I don't know what award show
you would have worn that to.
&gt;&gt; What I don't understand is,
you do the modern red carpet,
and it looks like you're wearing
the red carpet.
You know, all along I've been
telling you,
I don't understand why certain
things you wear
that makes your body look bigger
and malproportioned.
&gt;&gt; But I felt like a star
walking on that runway, so...
I would wear my dress with my
mohawk to my red carpet event.
And I would wear this
for the circus as well.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; So bam!
[all laughing]
&gt;&gt; Up next, Raja.
Hi, Raja.
&gt;&gt; Hi.
&gt;&gt; What inspired your look?
&gt;&gt; The big mission I had
with this
is to make it
not look like hair.
&gt;&gt; I love the outfit.
You have beautiful legs.
&gt;&gt; They're wooden, by the way.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
I'll take them, I'll take them.
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Fantasia.
Now all the way from
the Colombian coffee fields--
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; Let's go to Juan Valdez.
&gt;&gt; You look completely, like,
Japanime art.
And as for your red carpet look,
I liked your take on it.
It was definitely like
a young rocker.
Love the hair.
The razor cut.
If I could have one critique,
it's that I think you look
even more beautiful
with less makeup on.
&gt;&gt; Your '60s look,
I put that you're like a sexy,
dark Goldie Hawn,
circa Laugh-In.
And you looked really natural
and real,
and that looked like that could
be you walking the streets.
&gt;&gt; Next up...
Shangela.
&gt;&gt; Hi, Ru.
&gt;&gt; Where'd you get
the inspiration
for your fantasy outfit?
&gt;&gt; You know,
I love sci-fi films.
I love horror,
scarier films.
&gt;&gt; Wait, what did you call me?
&gt;&gt; Ooh!
&gt;&gt; For the classic look,
I felt the dress
was a little too big.
I just would have loved to have
seen it be a little tighter,
'cause this figure that I'm
seeing right now...
[clicks tongue, imitates sizzle]
Hot.
&gt;&gt; Sometimes, just having one
solid look
works better than having kind of
like two mediocre looks,
because after you took
that big coat off,
you still had kind of
a big gunny sack of a dress on
underneath it.
Your modern red carpet look,
it looked more kind of like the
high-class executive secretary.
It just wasn't quite there
to a red carpet event.
&gt;&gt; I felt like I was going to,
like, Oprah's Legends ball.
&gt;&gt; Montecito.
&gt;&gt; That's right.
It was a daytime look.
&gt;&gt; Why would you pick a daytime
red carpet?
&gt;&gt; I'm an E! fan.
They have carpets all day long.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, you could wear that on
the red carpet.
Would E! stop you
to talk to you and ask you,
"Who did your hair?"
No, they'd probably go,
"Eh, she did her hair."
But you appear to be
very fearless
just like your dressed--
you know, when I was a kid,
I was a big fan of D&amp;D,
and you look like a D&amp;D heroine.
&gt;&gt; Wait a minute, that's
Dungeons &amp; Drag Queens?
&gt;&gt; Yes, that's
Dungeons &amp; Drag Queens.
&gt;&gt; Next up, Manila.
&gt;&gt; Hi, Ru.
Hi, judges-zzzzzz.
&gt;&gt; Hi, Manila.
&gt;&gt; I loved the classic.
I want the dress.
I want the boots.
I loved everything about
the classic look.
&gt;&gt; Who wears a tiara
to a red carpet?
&gt;&gt; I would.
&gt;&gt; Hey, girl.
&gt;&gt; Hey!
&gt;&gt; We queens, Santino.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Get into it.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
I really just felt that, uh,
enormous central necklace
made your beautiful neck
and this whole area just
kind of look a little mannish.
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Pancho Villa.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; So, Manila, I can just
eat you
with a spoon tonight.
And what I love most about you
as a drag queen
is your ability
to theme couture.
Like, you always have these
great themes.
&gt;&gt; A love of fashion
and insects,
you don't find that
in a woman.
&gt;&gt; No, you don't.
&gt;&gt; Good job.
&gt;&gt; Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you go and untuck
in the Interior Illusions
lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
[car engine starting up]
Okay, kids.
We're gonna start with
Yara Sofia.
She was our scorpion poodle.
&gt;&gt; Scoodle.
&gt;&gt; She really brought it
to the fantasy level.
&gt;&gt; I thought she tore it up.
The '70s look was
out of control.
The hair was gorgeous.
I loved the big gold hoops.
I want that outfit.
&gt;&gt; Is it wrong that I think
that the booty is so amazing?
&gt;&gt; No.
&gt;&gt; It's juicy, honey.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, you know, this kinda
messes with
your perception of things.
&gt;&gt; It does.
&gt;&gt; Oh, my goodness.
&gt;&gt; It wrecks your head, honey.
&gt;&gt; Now you see what happened to
Eddie Murphy.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; What?
&gt;&gt; Alexis Mateo.
&gt;&gt; She looked like she was
coming from
a Bell Biv Devoe video.
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
She didn't look like--
she didn't look like
a Hollywood starlet.
&gt;&gt; That '40s look, there was
nothing '40s about it.
Maybe $40.
&gt;&gt; Oh, okay.
&gt;&gt; And that's about it.
&gt;&gt; All right.
Do think that her red carpet
look was too regional?
&gt;&gt; She wore the red carpet
and spangled it.
&gt;&gt; Miss Raja.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Raja, raja, raja ♪
all: [laughing]
&gt;&gt; I love her.
When she walked out,
it was that look of,
"Even if you don't like it,
"the way I'm about to walk out
here with it,
you're gonna like it."
&gt;&gt; Sell the garment.
&gt;&gt; I would say, although
she really worked it
and gave us that rock and roll
kind of
first time at the Grammys
kind of young rocker look,
I do wish maybe
she would have brought it
in a more conventional way,
because I would love to see
what Raja
would wear to the Oscars.
&gt;&gt; It's probably more realistic
to think that she would
do something
that looks like
a red carpet gown,
instead of going Miley Cyrus.
&gt;&gt; Shangela.
&gt;&gt; You know what?
She reminds me
so much of myself,
just with being the underdog.
With going into something
and saying,
"You know what?
"I might not have this,
"I might not have that,
but I'm gonna give it my all."
&gt;&gt; All of those things
that you said,
Fantasia, I love about her.
And that's really why
she's still here.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Because as far as her
fashion sense, her style...
she is clueless.
&gt;&gt; Is anybody else seeing
the five o'clock shadow
consistently?
&gt;&gt; It's not
a five o'clock shadow,
it's actually
the shade of makeup,
and it's her highlighting.
&gt;&gt; So it's picking up where--
&gt;&gt; She's not blending it
very well; that's what it is.
&gt;&gt; I do think that Shangela has
an amazing spirit
and I think may be pursuing
the wrong thing,
because there are clearly
other people
who eat, breathe, sleep this,
and it comes out of their pores.
&gt;&gt; Manila.
&gt;&gt; Wasn't a big fan
of the fantasy.
Love, love, love the classic.
She had an afro and she had some
curls on the side.
I'm thinking, "Who does that?
And who pulls it off
like she did?"
&gt;&gt; As for her red carpet look,
I think she just kind of
overworked the jewelry.
&gt;&gt; I don't know, she did it
for me tonight.
&gt;&gt; All right.
Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back...
my girls.
Ladies.
Based on your performance
and your presentation
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Raja.
You served three hot looks.
And your cotton candy fantasy is
truly delicious.
You're safe.
&gt;&gt; Thanks.
&gt;&gt; Yara Sofia.
This week, you scoodled
your way to victory.
Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
&gt;&gt; [cursing in Spanish]
&gt;&gt; [laughing]
&gt;&gt; And you've won an Alaskan
cruise for two
from America's number one
gay travel specialist,
alandchuck.travel.
&gt;&gt; Do you know what, darling?
It's about time.
It is so good to finally
win a challenge.
&gt;&gt; Alexis Mateo.
You are a timeless queen.
But some of your hairstyles were
a little dated
and off the mark.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
&gt;&gt; I don't wanna go home.
I wanna stay in this competition
all the way till the end.
&gt;&gt; Manila.
You rocked
three very different looks.
And your fantasy bee was killer.
You're safe, honey.
Shangela.
You are a sharp queen.
But I'm afraid your hairstyles
didn't make the cut.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
&gt;&gt; Wow, I'm back here...again.
And, you know, it's really tough
having to lip-synch against
a friend in this competition.
&gt;&gt; Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourselves...
from elimination.
The time has come for you to
lip-synch for your life.
Good luck.
And don't...
fuck it up.
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ I'm driving in circles ♪
♪ Should have bought that ♪
♪ New phone ♪
♪ Can't find my way to ♪
♪ All the places I call home ♪
♪ I'm on my own ♪
♪ I'm at the station ♪
♪ Pumping gas ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm taking out
the trash ♪
♪ I'm all alone ♪
♪ And who's there? ♪
♪ Who's there? ♪
♪ Since you've been gone ♪
♪ I learned how to move on ♪
♪ How to be myself ♪
♪ I don't need nobody's help ♪
♪ I'm doing so good ♪
♪ I forgot that I could ♪
♪ Live like this ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ First step ♪
♪ Take a deep breath ♪
♪ You don't need a reason why ♪
♪ And you can take ♪
♪ Take time, you can ♪
♪ You can walk, run, dive ♪
♪ Close call ♪
♪ You think you might fall ♪
♪ But all you gotta do is try ♪
♪ Even angels ♪
♪ Even angels
learn to fly ♪
&gt;&gt; The lip-synch is a beautiful
song by Fantasia.
Shangela is doing
the best she can,
but Alexis is, like,
feeling it with her body,
and it's timeless and beautiful.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Close call ♪
♪ You think you might fall ♪
♪ All you gotta do is try ♪
♪ Even angels ♪
♪ Even angels learn
how to fly ♪
[applause]
&gt;&gt; Yes!
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Ladies.
I've made my decision.
Alexis Mateo.
Shante, you stay.
&gt;&gt; [whispers] Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Shangela.
No one can say you didn't
try your hardest.
And it's that drive
that will take you far.
Live your dreams, mama.
Now, sashay away.
&gt;&gt; Thank you all.
Thank you.
[applause]
&gt;&gt; Halleloo!
It's a sad feeling because
I definitely came back
into this competition
wanting to win.
And it's not been easy.
But I'm leaving a winner.
And it's just a lesson
for everyone
who's ever wanted to pursue
any dream they've had.
Live your passion.
And live it to the fullest.
Halleloo!
&gt;&gt; Well, ladies.
As you know, each week
I consult with the judges,
but the final decision
is mine to make.
It seems that I've been
criticized
for sending some of my queens
home too soon.
Michelle.
&gt;&gt; Yes?
&gt;&gt; I want you to confer
with Santino and Billy B.
to decide which of
the eliminated queens...
deserve to return
to this competition...
next week.
&gt;&gt; Oh, my God.
Are you freaking kidding me?
&gt;&gt; And you may pick from
any of the queens
eliminated this season.
Will it be...
Venus D-Lite?
Phoenix?
Mimi Imfurst?
India Ferrah?
Mariah?
Stacy Layne Bryant Matthews?
Delta Work?
Carmen Carrera?
Or Shangela Laquifa Wadley?
Now.
Remember...
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen!
&gt;&gt; All right!
Now let the music play!
[dance music]
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; Grand prize contributed
in part by alandchuck.travel.