- Previously on RuPaul's
Drag Race...
I'm gonna give you an
opportunity to really wig out.
- Yes, Rainbow Brite.
- She-man the barbarian.
- A little new school Mae West.
- How much is that poodle on
the runway?
Yara Sofia.
Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
Ladies,
I have made my decision.
Alexis Mateo.
Shantay, you stay.
Shangela,
sashay away.
Michelle.
I want you to confer with
Santino and Billy B.
To decide which
of the eliminated queens
deserve to return.
And tonight...
I want you to to meet
some real athletes.
- Come on in.
Whoo!
- It smells like testosterone.
- With extra special
guest judges,
Sharon Osbourne
and Margaret Cho.
- All: Whoo!
- The winner of RuPaul's
Drag Race will receive,
a lifetime supply of Kryolan
Professional Make-up...
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected,
by Absolut...
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ Start your engines ♪
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman win ♪
♪ Start your engines ♪
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman win ♪
- Pffft!
- No hair, no hair.
- Hello!
- Aw, it's a message from
Shangela.
We're back into the work room
today,
and Shangela is gone.
I'm gonna miss Shangela.
- Halleloo, Shangela.
- I'm gonna wipe it up.
- While you do that,
I'm gonna do one of these.
Woo-hoo!
- [laughing]
- Shangela's gone.
Good God, I feel like
the sky has parted.
♪ It's just us ♪
I feel like I can frolic
through the woods
and perch a little bird
on my finger.
Sorry about it, Shangela.
- We are the top four.
- Not so much.
- When Ru said last week
on the runway
that another queen
is coming back,
I felt like, "All right,
we're top five again."
- Who do you think is coming?
- Um, I don't know.
- It could be Stacy.
Nah.
Mimi Imfurst.
- Oh, I hope not.
- Nah.
[alarm sounds]
- Ooh, girl.
You've got shemail.
Is the next drag superstar
a catcher or a pitcher?
- Ooh.
- Does she have a tight end
or a fullback?
Well, get ready
for a little one-on-one,
man-to-man action.
And remember...
if you can't be an athlete,
you can at least be
an athletic supporter.
- Aah!
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hey, Ru!
- What's up, Ru?
- Boy, oh, boy.
Now as you know,
I gave the judges
a one-time opportunity
to bring back
one of the eliminated queens
if they could come to
a unanimous decision.
So...
let's see which queen,
if any,
is behind that door.
The moment of truth is upon us.
- I can't,
I don't wanna look.
- Oh, my God!
- I'm back, bitches.
- Whoo!
- It's a heather,
it's a heather.
- The Jersey girl is back.
- It's fucking Carmen.
- Carmen Carrera.
- Hey.
- Now is your head
back in the game?
- Yes.
I'm really happy that, you know,
the judges wanted me
to come back.
Like, that makes me feel
even more confident.
I feel like
I have to bring it now.
- Now for today's
mini-challenge,
we'll be headed outside...
to the padunkadunk
dunking machine.
[cheering]
- Oh!
- Woo-hoo-hoo!
- Now each of you
will get a turn
to dunk the queen
of your choice.
- Carmen.
Carmen three times, honey.
- The doll who dunks her victim
the most times
in two minutes, wins.
So put your suits on
and I'll meet you out there.
All right, ladies.
Raja, you throw first.
Choose your victim.
- Carmen.
- [laughing]
- On your mark,
get set...
padunkadunk!
- Go Raja.
- Go Raja, go!
- Raja, Raja!
- No, no, no, no!
- I have a feeling
Carmen's used to
having balls thrown at her face.
- So I'm sitting there
and I'm a little nervous.
I'm, like, "Damn,
she's gonna get me."
But she throws like a girl.
I mean, come on, miss thing.
[laughter]
[buzzer buzzes]
- Time's up.
All right, Alexis?
- Yes.
- Choose your victim.
- Yara.
- Ay!
Oh, ho, ho, hmm...
No, no, no, no!
- Get her, get her!
- All: Ooh!
- [screaming]
- Oh!
- Damn!
- Oh, my God!
- Fuck you!
[laughter]
- Bam, bitch!
Get it!
- Yara, you're up next.
Who do you pick
to be your victim?
- I don't know,
but I think Alexis.
- Alexis?
- Oh!
- Now, darling,
it's my turn.
- This is the revenge of Yara.
And go.
- Work it, Yara!
- Get her, get her!
- [laughing]
- Taste that water, darling!
Taste it!
- Oh! Oh!
- [laughing]
[buzzer buzzes]
- Time's up.
You got seven.
- Yes.
- Condragulations.
- Thank you.
- Up next is Manila.
- Let's go up there, honey.
- Yes!
- No!
- My bitch.
- I just got warm, and now I
have to get back in that bitch.
- Ah!
- No!
- Stay behind that line.
- Come on, Manila,
you can do this, girl!
- Missed!
- Aaah!
- Carmen's getting pretty dry
up there.
- Thank goodness,
Manila sucks.
- No!
- All: Oh!
[buzzer buzzes]
- Up next, of course, is...
Carmen, hmmm.
- I think I'm gonna
have to choose Raja.
- No!
- Yeah!
- I want her to gag.
- Dunk her ass
like a donut, okay?
- Nooo!
- Aah!
- [laughing]
- Raja!
- All: Whoo!
- The harder you throw,
the more you look like a dude,
okay?
That's all I'm saying.
- Oh, my God!
[buzzer buzzes]
- Oh, time's up, time's up.
All right, ladies.
With a total of 14 dunks,
the star pitcher
of RuPaul's Pink Sox is...
Alexis Rodriguez Mateo!
Condragulations, Alexis.
Now you kids go dry off
and I'll see you back in the
you-better-work room.
See you in a minute.
- Bye!
- Bye, Ru!
- Okay, kids.
Now that you're all warmed up,
I want you to meet
some real athletes.
- Oh, shit!
- Whoo!
- Hey!
- Come on in, babies.
Come on in.
Whoo!
- There's five guys
coming into the work room
and it smells like testosterone.
- For this week's
main challenge,
you'll be transforming these
straight jocks
into drag queens for a day.
- Oh, my God!
- [laughing]
Now using your own drag,
hair from Wig USA,
and other materials
we've provided,
I expect to see
a strong family resemblance.
Think of them as the Venus
to your Serena.
Gentlemen,
please introduce yourselves
and tell us your sport.
- Hi, I'm Matt.
I'm 29, and I play baseball...
hard.
- Ooh!
- Sorry about it.
- I'm Drew, I'm 23,
and I play rugby.
- My name is Slava, I'm 23,
and I play water polo.
- Hi, I'm Chevy, I'm 27,
I play baseball.
- My name's Christopher,
I'm 32,
I play basketball
from San Antonio, Texas.
- Yes.
- And yes, everything is bigger
in Texas.
- Now, Alexis, since you
won the mini-challenge,
you get to pair up
the guys and dolls.
- Heh, heh.
I love this part.
Come with me.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
Raja, meet your partner.
- Hey, my baby.
Come to mama.
- Manila, meet your partner.
- Hey!
- Bam!
You, come on.
Heh, heh, heh.
Yara.
- Oh!
Thank you, darling.
- Carmen.
Meet your partner.
With Chevy's body,
it's going to be very difficult
for Carmen
to stand on stage
naked like her.
And you're mine, yay.
I keep the best one for me.
Slava.
- Now turning these jocks
into drag queens
will take every ounce
of charisma,
uniqueness, nerve and talent
that you've got.
So put some muscle into it.
Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- Yeah!
- Can I hit one out there?
- Nope, no baseball.
No sports today,
you're a lady.
- Yes.
- Oh, really? Doesn't matter.
- [laughing] Yeah.
- Sell it.
Hands on your hips,
hands on your hips, always.
- Hands on my hips.
- Yes, yes, yes.
I'm liking this shit.
- Yeah, you have, like,
a boner a little bit.
- It's a little one?
I think it's 'cause
the air is in there.
[laughing]
- I was like, "Okay, kill it."
It's not the first time
I got a straight guy excited.
- [laughing]
- Oh!
- So the challenge today is
we have to transform
these straight jocks
into our drag sisters.
- Yeah, those are gonna be
your tits.
- [laughing]
- I hope so.
It's like water polo.
- [gasping] You have to shave.
- I'm not shaving that.
That's my jungle hair over here.
- Drew, he's afraid
of what are we going to do.
- I have to be a jock
for a second.
- So now you're gonna play.
- Yes, I just--
I'll work a little,
and I'll play a little,
you know?
- I have a lot of work to do.
- Carmen, are we gonna have to
teach these boys how to tuck?
- I have to.
- Have you ever put your balls
up above your penis?
- Ooh.
- There's, like, a cavity
up in your body,
that sometimes
your testicles can--
they go up there
any time you want.
Like, it's a winter cabin
they can go hang out in
if it gets too cold.
- I'll show you so you can see
the contours on my body.
I'm welcoming him into the house
of Carrera.
The minute you tuck,
the minute you pull that pee-pee
back,
you feel like a woman.
You need to, like,
put your penis away.
- Put my penis away.
- Okay.
- So where does the shaft go?
- That's the one that goes
between your legs.
- And you've been doing this
for how long?
- A while now.
- And you're not all
tuckered out?
- Oh, hell no.
- These are my titties.
- Oh, my God.
- Be gentle with them.
They're so soft.
They feel better
than the real thing.
- Slava is flirty, flirty,
flirty.
- I wanna hear about
your first guy kiss.
- My first guy kiss?
Oh, my gosh.
I was 15, he was 26.
He was straight.
Bam!
- No way.
- Yes.
- I respect that.
- Things that come out
of his mouth,
I'm going, like, "Really, dude,
focus right here.
We're trying to make you
a woman, not a husband."
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hi, darling.
- Hello, there.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hi, Chris.
So Raja,
now what are you doing
that's gonna make you sisters?
- I'm gonna put my little stamp
as far as styling him,
and making him really feel
a little bit more like Raja.
- Do you have any surprises up
your sleeve, Raja?
- Not just yet.
I've gotta, like,
really dive in,
and we're gonna play with
some makeup
and then the surprise will
probably come at the end,
I hope.
I am looked at by the judges
as being someone
who puts on the funny, cool,
fashion-y costumes,
and does a fierce runway.
How do I make this guy
do the same thing that I do?
Dear God,
please help me.
- Carmen Carrera and Chevy.
It's like a car dealership,
isn't it?
- [laughing]
- How will we know
that the two of you are sisters?
- Well, we're gonna both be
serving body and sex.
- [laughing] Oh.
Well that sounds like
a Carmen Carrera sister.
- Yeah, the one and only
body queen.
- What are you the most
concerned about
in this challenge?
- He uses that sexuality.
- True.
- That's a tough one
right there.
- But it's many years
in the making.
- I don't think it's just
about the look.
I have to kind of transfer
that essence of Carmen Carrera
into this guy.
- Hey, Yara.
- Hi.
- Oh, my goodness.
You're shaving him.
- Yes.
- Are you shaving Drew all over?
- No, I didn't...
- [laughing]
No, no.
- He doesn't let me.
- What worries you
the most about this?
- I'm not much of a dancer
or anything,
so getting the footwork down
is really my main concern.
- But you play rugby.
Can we see you do
a little twirl?
You're wearing your heels now.
- Try it. Go, go.
[indistinct]
Hey, hey, whoa.
Walk, walk, walk, aah!
- But you know what?
I don't see much challenge
there, Yara.
I expect your sister
to have higher heels.
I want to see Liz Hurley,
fuck-me pumps on the runway.
- Okay.
- She's gonna reflect on you.
- Yes.
- So you have to call the shots.
- Yes, I will.
- Good luck, you guys.
- Thank you.
- All right, I'll see you later.
- Bye.
- Hey, Alexis.
- Hey, Ru.
- You have a sister, don't you?
- Yes.
- Do you get her into drag?
- No, she's a butch lesbian, Ru.
- What's your biggest challenge
in turning Slava into your
sister?
- Making him concentrate
while we have to work.
- It's focus.
Slava plays water polo.
You have to have focus
in sports.
Help him transfer that focus
into doing drag.
- Hey, Manila.
- Hi, Ru.
- What do you have planned out?
- Well, I'm going to be
putting him in, like,
this little kimono.
- Oh, my.
And will so much body
be showing?
- So much body will be showing.
- Wow.
What's your biggest challenge?
- Fuchsia's kind of a brick.
- Uh-huh.
- So I'm gonna have to
break down her face,
and make her as feminine
as possible.
Attractive manly men,
don't make attractive
drag queens.
Fuck. This is gonna be hard.
- Gather around, everybody.
Tomorrow,
on the main stage,
we will be joined
by our guest judges,
actress and comedian
Margaret Cho...
- All: Ooh!
- And the always cheerful,
Sharon Osbourne.
- Yay!
- Ooh!
- Oh, and one more thing.
In addition to the glamorous
looks you've been working on,
you need to style...
cheerleader outfits.
- Oh, okay.
- And then come up with
a fun fight cheer
that supports safe sex.
- [laughing]
Not only walking
on the runway as models,
now we have to cheerleading?
Oh.
- You'll both perform
your cheer tomorrow
on the main stage.
Go team go.
And remember,
don't fuck It up.
- Ready?
- Both: Okay!
- This week's main challenge
is to turn straight jocks
into our drag sisters.
And the twist is,
we have to do a cheerleading
routine about safe sex.
- Wrap your dick,
wrap up your dick.
- Wrap your dick!
- [laughing] Yes!
- Then we're gonna do the
♪ Safe sex ♪
And we're gonna switch.
- What's up, bitches?
- Oh, my God.
Wow.
This is disturbing.
♪ Waa waa waa waa ♪
Raja's jock look a mess.
- Yaay!
- I don't know
what the bitch was doing.
But girl,
you don't look that good.
- I don't know about
Raja's sister.
She's supposed to be a heather.
I don't know, she kind of looks
like a Sprepper.
It's basically a Sprite mixed
with Dr. Pepper.
It's not necessarily
a good thing.
It's usually, like,
a booger quality.
Like, oh!
Like, "That's such a Sprepper."
- It's time for me and Slava to
go to the runway and practice.
Look at the judges.
You give them poses.
- Oh, God!
- Keep the balance,
keep the balance.
Alexis Mateo always known
by the "Bam!"
So I'm making him
say it as well,
'cause he better show the judges
that he is part of
the fa-mi-ly.
Bam!
- Bam!
I'm a drama queen, bitch!
- No, you're not a drama queen.
You're a drag queen,
God damn it.
Come on, say it!
- Bam! Bam!
I'm a drag queen.
- I hope that everything
goes well
and he doesn't show more diva
than me tomorrow.
'cause we're gonna
have a problem.
- Mm-hmm.
- Bam!
- Look at the judges.
Seductive.
You want to fuck the judges.
I wanna fuck You guys.
Yes, I'm here.
Eat it, bitch.
You know what I mean?
Grab your waist.
Right.
Left.
Echa pa lante,
look at the judges.
- I'm looking.
- And then left.
No, we're gonna do right again.
Left.
I'm a little worried.
Get him the attitude.
- You better not complicate it.
- No, no, no.
- You're gonna regret this.
- I'm scared to go home.
- Ready, one, two, right foot.
I'll go slower.
Chris in heels,
it's a little funny.
It's not sexy yet.
- I just gotta learn
the count thing.
Are you gonna actually tell me?
- I'm just gonna tell you when.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna be, like,
"Let's go, Chris," all right?
So make sure that you're--
- Or, you mean my stage name.
- Yeah, Enigma.
Sorry, girl.
I know that he has
really good intentions.
But I know that I can only
do so much.
I don't want you to forget this,
'cause it's kind of important.
I'm just hoping that Chris
remembers the few steps
that I taught him
in front of the judges tomorrow.
- Titties up, titties up.
- Titties up.
- When you get here
and you do your twirl,
like, you can look down at your
ass and then look up at them.
- What about my titties,
is that just not cool?
I mean, I love titties.
- No, because I'm not, like,
a titty girl.
I'm like a butt girl.
- [laughing]
- Let's do it again.
- All right.
I only got about two more walks
down here in me.
- All the pain that
you're feeling right now
is the man leaving your body.
You're just becoming more
feminine and more feminine.
- How about my toes
leaving the shoe?
- Yeah.
He's just, like, complaining,
and he's just, like,
"Oh, my God."
And then give us a twirl
to show us body.
No, that's butch.
Be, like, really girly, like...
- When you're walking,
like, look at the judges.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- If you catch one of
their eyes, that's good.
- Can I point?
- Ladies don't point unless
they're picking out shoes.
I want those pairs.
- How's this?
- Well, don't--
what woman do you know
stands like that?
Oh!
Practice on this line,
by putting one foot
over the other
like you're doing a drug test.
Work the runway, fish!
- Fish?
- And strike another pose.
Matt has a really huge
personality.
Okay, you're gonna strike
a feminine pose.
- Oh, okay.
- Not like you're poppin'
a squat in the woods.
- Okay.
- Okay?
It gets annoying.
We'll work on the poses
when we're not on the runway.
I just want you
to get comfortable with--
I just want you to get
comfortable with the runway.
And if you do this
to me tomorrow,
I'm going to seriously
hunt you down...
- All right, all right!
- And kill you.
- I'm just having fun
on the stage, man!
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Does your family know
that you're straight?
- [laughing]
Yeah.
My little brother's gay.
- Oh, no way.
- Yeah, yeah.
He's one of those angry
gay people.
- Why?
- He just thinks that
everybody hates him
'cause he's gay or whatever.
Did you ever do drag
in high school?
- No, hell no.
I didn't come out
in high school.
I think people knew
that I was gay.
They didn't have the balls
to come and ask me.
I didn't have a sense of pride
in being gay.
- Uh-huh.
'Cause it was still taboo
to you.
- Yeah, that's why I was, like,
really angry at the world
for a little bit.
You feel wrong
for the most of your life.
And then you don't know why
you feel wrong.
And then you just get mad
at people.
Like, "why do you make me feel
wrong?" You know?
Well, how old is he now?
- 19.
He's 19 now.
- Oh, he's still really young.
- Just a kid.
- He'll get over all of that.
Trust me.
- I hope so.
- He will.
Once he sees his big brother
in drag.
- It's kind of a motivator
For me to do this, you know?
- Yeah.
He's gonna love it.
- Make sure that you don't eat
anything
that's gonna make you bloated
for tomorrow.
- Okay.
- But you're trying to make him
look like you.
So why wouldn't he be bloated?
- Ooh!
- Tell her her mom's bloated.
- You're--
- So we're teaching our sisters
to read.
- It's a natural talent
in a Luzon family, honey.
- You've got the perfect
daughter, Manila.
- Matt is just like Manila.
Completely obnoxious.
- Yo, you guys like
my lobster hat?
- Manila, meet your cell mate,
Matt.
- Do women really slap tables?
- I just slap tables
all day long,
you don't even know,
for real.
- Good morning.
- Challenge day.
We're back into the work room
and it's so much
that has to be done.
- Let's make you into a fish.
- I'm nervous as hell.
- No, no, you can do it.
You can do it.
- All right, all right.
- We are teammates, you know?
- All right.
- We need to practice.
Rush. Come on.
- Both:
Ready? You're gay.
- Keep your peeker--
Pecker.
Fuck.
- Pecker.
- What is a pecker?
- Keep your pecker--
- Pecker is your dick.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- We have the exact same amount
of time that we usually have,
except that this time, we have
to get ourselves in drag
and then a person that has never
been in drag before in drag.
[exhales]
All right. I'm ready for you.
- Whoa.
You're gluing his brows?
- Mm-hmm.
- What's it do?
- It lays them down and then
I can, like, cover them,
and then I can draw them
wherever I want to put
new eyebrows.
The most intimidating part
of this challenge
is that it's not just me.
I now have to, like,
completely do an overhaul
on this masculine straight guy.
- Ancient Chinese secret.
- Ancient drag secret.
- Did you have people who
came out in high school?
In your school,
in Puerto Rico?
- No, I was the only one.
- I had a really hard time
in high school.
I was, like, really close to,
like, being suicidal.
It was, like, left and right.
I couldn't, like,
walk around the school
without being, like,
tormented.
- But you know what,
I went to my ten-year
high school reunion in drag.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- How was the reception?
- Awesome.
- Yeah?
- We all had a blast together
for the first time in my life.
Like, I had a great time
with people I went to
high school with.
- [laughing]
- So you're legally married?
- Legally, yeah.
- So if you move--
- It would be invalid.
New Jersey's the only state
that really gives a lot
of the same rights
that they give
a straight married couple.
- So you're stuck
in the armpit of America
because you're gay.
- I think that straight people
take a lot of things
for granted.
You can settle down
with any girl and have kids
and live the American dream,
but it's, like,
so much harder for gay people
to do that.
- Turn around.
It's not that difficult.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
When I first saw myself
transformed,
my heart just stopped.
My breath just gasped,
and I was, like, whoa!
I can't even believe this.
Oh, my God.
- Alexis' jock...
he's a drag queen.
This is your first time?
Mm-hmm.
- We're gonna run out together,
shake your pom pom's like crazy.
Just be, like, aaaah!
And then we stop at the edge
of the stage--
- Oh, we perform on stage?
- Yeah.
- Oh, wait, wait, please.
Please just--please don't.
Really, honestly.
Dude, focus!
Please!
Like, I'm on the line, here.
- Are you angry at me?
- No, I'm just really,
like, freaking out.
- You'll be all right.
Take a deep breath, bro.
- Thank you.
- [laughing]
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
- Well, hello there.
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
you're looking sporty.
- Yay, team!
- [laughing]
- Mike Ruiz,
A-list photographer.
Welcome back.
- Oh, thanks for having me back.
- Margaret,
you're Cho beautiful.
- Thank you.
Well, I was raised
by drag queens,
like some are raised by wolves.
So I know drag.
- Well then,
welcome home sweetheart.
Sharon Osbourne,
the coolest mom ever.
Welcome to the show.
- Thank you, my darling.
- How's Ozzy?
- All I can tell you is, Ru,
he absolutely adores you.
- [laughing]
Welcome.
This week,
our queens were challenged
to turn straight jocks into
their glamorous drag sisters.
But first, we asked them to lead
a fun fight cheer
in support of safe sex.
Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- Both: Whoo!
Divas, divas, here we go!
Safe sex is the way to go!
Ooh, you wanna moan?
Ooh, you wanna growl?
Make it safe!
And make us proud!
- I love you.
- And you love me.
- Both:
Safe sex fraternity!
Whoo!
- Safe sex mother fuckers!
- Wrap that dick!
Safe sex, don't get pregnant!
- Both: Ready?
You're gay!
- B-A-R-E!
- B-A-C-K!
- Both: No bareback,
no bareback!
No, no, no bareback!
- I need a C!
- C!
- I need an O!
- O!
- Give me an N!
- N!
- How bout a D?
- D!
- Another O!
- O!
- Another M!
- M!
- What's it spell?
- Both: Safe sex!
Woo-hoo!
- All: [laughing]
- Both: Ready?
Let's go!
- Give your back a cleaning!
- Have that rubber
catch that semen!
- Give me that W!
- W!
- Give me the R!
- R!
- Give me the A!
- A!
- Give me the P!
- P!
- What that spell?
- Both: Wrap your dick!
Wrap up your dick!
Wrap your dick!
- Both: Hey, hey, you, you!
You need to get a clue!
Be safe, don't chafe!
Your dick will turn dark blue!
Uh-oh, she said,
my pussy's turning red!
- Ooh!
- Both: They'll burn when they
pee.
Protection is the key!
Safe sex!
- [laughing]
- Well, that was short.
[laughing]
- All: [laughing]
- Both: Ready?
Okay!
Always wear a condom,
and use a dental dam.
Abstinence is for boogers,
but we love our diaphragm!
- [laughing]
- A diaphragm?
- A what?
A diaphragm!
- A who?
- Both: You can use a diaphragm
with spermicidal lube!
Safe sex!
Whoooooo!
- All: [laughing]
- All right, kids.
We are gonna do us some runway.
First up,
Alexis and Avals Mateo.
Sisters in the name of love.
- Those outfits are to die for.
- Some birds did.
- Me and Slava are walking
on that runway
like we are true divas.
He got my style,
he got my walk.
He got my signature move.
- Look at that bum!
Gorgeous.
- Unidentified flying asses.
Raja and her sister Enigma.
- Enigma, please.
- Ooh, girl!
It's the Cheetah Girls.
- It is!
- I know for a fact that
Chris is doing the best job
that he can.
And I hope that
the judges can see that.
- I think Enigma looks
very vulnerable.
Her face is vulnerable
but her legs look like sailors.
- Up next, we have Yara
and Drewlita Sofia.
Goldfinger.
- This is real Mandrell sisters
realness.
- Yes.
- We are doing our catwalk,
and I feel so great.
He's doing everything
I taught him.
- Drewlita has that
"don't fuck with me" look
on her face.
- She does.
- I think it's real "Madonna
after yoga" look.
- It's Kabbalah Madonna.
Up next, Carmen and Lolita
Cruz-Carrera.
- Jujubee is back.
- We're walking down the runway
and he's serving it.
We're giving a lot of body
right now.
We're giving attitude.
We're giving pretty.
We're definitely representing
Carrera.
- This is just like
the Miss New Jersey Pageant.
- Representing Miss Patterson,
New Jersey.
- She sells sea shells
by the Jersey shore.
Last but not least,
the Luzon sisters.
Oh!
- Oh, snap it, Lagerfeld.
- Geisha to go.
- We're walking down the runway
just as we practiced.
Except that Matt is really
serving it fiercely.
He's truly a Luzon.
- I think it's murder
on the orient runway.
- I think it's more
Kill Bill 2.
- Kill Bill 2 meets To Wong Foo.
- Memoirs of a gay-sha.
- China dolls.
- Welcome, sisters.
Thank you for giving us
something to cheer about.
Now it's time for
the judges' critique.
Let's start with Alexis
and Avals Mateo.
Hi, Avals.
Are you chilly up there?
- Chilly?
- Yeah, your nipples are hard.
- Oh, that's 'cause
I'm a little horny.
- [laughing]
- You really embraced
your feminine side.
You're really getting off on it,
aren't you?
- I really, really am.
- You've probably got a stiffy
going on under there somewhere.
- [laughing]
- I think that Alexis
did a great job on the makeup
and the hair.
- I think the cheer was sloppy
at points.
I think because you tried to put
too much into it.
- You have this
family resemblance
that's in the body,
it's in the face.
You were giving me Kardashian.
I'm keeping up with you.
- Next up, Raja
and her sister Enigma.
- We discovered that we both
have a mutual love
for old movies.
And we thought of maybe
a little bit more
of an old Hollywood glamour.
- What old movie
did you pattern her after?
Tarzan?
- It feels a little jungle.
It felt a little bit more like
La Dolce Vita.
- The walk, however.
It's a bit like a sailor.
- You know, I would
have expect Raja to instill
a little bit more of your
ability in Enigma.
- I thought the cheer
was quite athletic.
I can't remember what you were
cheering about though.
- Um, about bare backing.
- What does that mean?
- It means when you, um,
are fucking without condoms.
- Okay.
Well, that--see I've learned
something new today.
- Which we don't encourage,
we don't encourage.
- No, no, no, no.
Actually, I'm wearing a condom
right now.
- [laughing]
- Next up, we've got Yara Sofia
and her sister, Drewlita.
- Did she resist?
- Yes.
- What did she resist?
- Hair removal, tucking,
dancing, singing.
- So you resisted everything?
- Well, I'm historically
relatively shy.
So I'm just glad that I got out
here to try something new--
- But you have your sister now.
- Exactly.
- So you felt more outgoing once
you were walking the runway?
- Absolutely.
- I thought the cheer was quite
sweet.
You were, like,
fanning your bums.
- [laughing]
- Thank you.
- Well, you guys look amazing.
You look like Heart,
circa 1982,
you know, right when
they were going disco?
- You did such a beautiful job
giving Drewlita that sort of
Madonna face.
Which I think is fierce.
- And they both have man-hands,
just like Madonna.
- Yes.
- [laughing]
- Up next, Manila
and her drag sister Fuchsia.
- She's a true Luzon.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, this personality
is driving us nuts.
- You did an amazing job,
Manila, with the makeup.
Because the before and after
is just really incredible.
And Fuchsia, you seem to have
embraced the whole process.
- Hey!
- [laughing]
- I love this look.
Just giving me that perfect
Hong Kong garden restaurant...
I'm ready to order.
- [laughs]
- Would you date you?
- Yes. Hard.
- [laughing]
Up next, Carmen Carrera
and her sister, Lolita Cruz.
Do you feel pretty?
- Yes, absolutely.
I threw a little swagger into my
step be all right.
- Now Carmen, because
your sister is beefy,
very masculine,
did you ever consider maybe
doing something that sort of
feminized the body
a little bit more?
- You know, I don't care
what kind of body you have.
You know, you can be--
you can do naked.
If I was, you know,
100 pounds overweight,
I would still do my pasties
and get naked.
Because that's how much
confidence I have inside.
And I want to bring that out.
- From the head up,
there is some similarity.
It's just the arms the shoulders
that are still, like--
you know, like...
- [laughs]
You know, He-Man.
- You took care of yourself and
you're like, "Here, sister,
"try this on, girl.
Put this on.
You'll look fierce."
You're known for your body,
I know in your head you think
if you're 100 pounds heavier,
you'd still rock it.
I don't really buy that.
- Now sisters, while you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
Just between us girls.
Let's start with Alexis
and Avels.
- They had a connection.
And I like that.
- The pro is, they did work
in synchronicity,
but I didn't understand
3/4 of it.
- Slava might have surpassed
Alexis.
- [laughing]
- Raja and Enigma.
- Raja is such a beauty.
And then you had this big,
strutting bloke.
- I didn't really feel
a sisterly connection.
It was more like a
mother-daughter kind of thing.
- I got, like, Mommie Dearest
in Christina.
Didn't you?
- Yes, I did.
- This is one of the bottom two
for me tonight.
- Yara Sofia and her sister
Drewlita.
- Love the outfits.
But I didn't think that there
was such a great connection.
- Drewlita, you know, is an
incredible transformation.
- Yeah, she was really pretty.
- I didn't really get a sibling
thing from them.
- Manila and her sister,
Fuschia.
They had a lot of fun with this.
- Mm.
- And Fuschia was a gas.
- Manila and him
were really good together.
You could tell that they were
enjoying each other.
- The biggest transformation
for me was Fuschia tonight.
Matt is a big ol' jock.
- Carmen and Lolita
Cruz-Carrera.
I don't know if she threw Lolita
under the bus.
Lolita's build was so stocky.
- It was more like
he was trying to help
his less attractive sister,
you know, get laid.
- Was Carmen meant
to dress down?
She has such a magnificent body
on her.
- And that made the awkwardness
of their bodies together
more pronounced.
- There are a million tricks up
Carmen's sleeve, you guys.
- Sure.
- Trust me.
She looked out for herself
all night.
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back the sisters.
Welcome back, ladies.
Now based on
your jock transformations,
and your presentations
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Alexis Mateo.
- Wait, wait, shh.
- You were a real player
this week.
And I thought
I was seeing double.
Double-D.
You're safe.
- Thank you, guys.
- [exhales]
- Manila.
You served up two China dolls.
And 20 minutes later...
we're still hungry for more.
Condragulations.
You are this week's MVP,
and the winner
of this week's challenge.
- Yeah!
That's my girl!
- You've won a cruise for two
to the Bahamas.
Courtesy of alandchuck.travel.
And for helping you
with your win,
we are awarding your jock
the same prize.
- Oh, ho, ho!
Shit! Yeah!
I'm going on a cruise!
- Raja.
You were off your game.
And your sister act was
none the better for it.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- Ru tells me that I have to
lip-synch for my life.
I couldn't believe it.
- Yara Sofia.
You're safe.
Carmen Carrera.
Your look was a home run.
But you left your sister
sitting on the bench.
I'm sorry, but you are up
for elimination.
- I don't know what to feel
right now.
If I go home,
I'll be upset about it.
I'm just gonna be Carmen
and do what I do best.
I'm just gonna turn it out.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
to save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lip-synch...
for your life.
Good luck.
And don't fuck It up.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Lost in a dream ♪
♪ I don't know which ♪
♪ Way to go ♪
♪ Oh, let me say ♪
♪ I've been fooled before ♪
♪ Wouldn't like
to get my love ♪
♪ Caught in
the slamming door ♪
♪ How about some ♪information,
please ♪
♪ Straight up now tell me ♪
♪ Do you really wanna ♪
love me forever? ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ When I'm caught ♪in
a hit and run ♪
- I've worked so hard from day
one since I've been here
and I would hate to go home.
I had to muster up
all the fierceness
I could find within me
and just go for it.
[cheers and applause]
♪ A buh-buh-buh-buh-bye! ♪
- Raja's getting naked.
I'm, like, this is gonna be hot,
'cause Carmen is nudity,
and they're gonna thrown down
right now.
- ♪ Do, do you love me baby ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
- Ooh!
- ♪ Do do you love me ♪
♪ Tell me baby ♪
♪ I've been fooled before ♪
♪ Wouldn't like
to get my love ♪
♪ Caught in
the slamming door ♪
♪ Are you more than hot
for me ♪
♪ Or am I a page ♪
♪ In your history ♪
♪ Look, I don't mean
to make demands ♪
♪ But the word and the deed ♪
♪ Go hand in hand ♪
♪ How about some ♪information,
please ♪
♪ Please, please,
please, please ♪
- This is just soft porn.
It's kinda hot.
- ♪ Straight up now tell me ♪
♪ Straight up now tell me ♪
♪ Do you really wanna ♪
♪ Love me forever ♪
- Woo-hoo!
- Wow!
Ladies,
We've had 28 lip-synchs
for your life
and that was by far,
straight up,
the most surprising one eva!
I've made my decision.
Raja.
Shantay, you stay.
- [crying]
I'm glad to be here.
Thank you so much.
It's just an overwhelming
emotion
that comes over you.
And I'm thankful to Ru.
And I'm a very, very lucky
person.
And I just--you know what?
I'm just thankful.
- Carmen Carrera.
Baby, you don't make it easy
to say good-bye.
And you will be missed.
Now...
sashay away.
- Thank you.
- Love you, darling.
- For real this time.
Don't come back, okay?
- [laughing]
- I feel honored that Ru
asked me to come back.
But if my time is up,
my time is up.
- To the final four.
Condragulations.
The race for the crown
has never been so close.
Now remember.
If you can't love yourself...
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
- All: Amen!
- All right.
Now, let the music play!
♪ This is the main event ♪
♪ Are you ready ♪
♪ Just let the music ♪
♪ Dance into your soul ♪
- Grand prize contributed
in part by alandchuck.travel.