- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
I want you to meet some real
athletes.
- Come on in, babies!
Come on in!
Whoo!
both: Divas, divas, here we go!
Safe sex is the way to go!
- Keep your pecker clean, man!
- Have a rubber catch
that semen!
both: Protection is the key!
both: No, no, no bareback.
both: Safe sex. Whoo!
- Manila, you served up
two china dolls.
Condragulations.
You are the winner of this
week's challenge.
- Yah!
- Ladies, I've made my decision.
Raja...
Shante, you stay.
- [sobs]
- Carmen Carrera,
baby, you don't make it easy
to say good-bye.
Now, sashay away.
[laughs]
And tonight the dolls hit
the jackpot...
- What?
- And go for broke.
It is time for the most
expensive challenge in RuPaul's
Drag Race her-story.
With extra-special guest
judges La Toya Jackson
and Gigi Levangie Grazer.
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut, and a cash prize of
$75,000.
And may the best woman win.
- Top four again!
- Yoo-hoo!
- Déjà vu.
Carmen left the competition.
I love Carmen, but, darling,
at this point, it's you or me.
Oh, there's a message.
- Good-bye again.
Best of luck to everyone.
Turn it out and don't be
a sprepper.
- Don't be a sprepper.
Sprepper is this combination
of Sprite and Dr. Pepper.
It's sweet, but it's not
delicious.
- Raja, it's your turn.
- I've never done this before.
You guys have all done this
before I have.
Oh, BGB, girl.
Bye, girl, bye.
See ya later, Carmen.
I'll give ya a call.
I lost my cherry to being the
bottom two.
- Finally, people.
- Did you cry?
- I did a little bit.
I thought I was gonna go home
because of some guy that I'd
only known for two days.
It was pretty close.
It was almost me.
My only game plan at this point
is just to kick everyone's
asses, and I'm so close.
I am so close.
[siren blares]
- Ooh, girl, you've got
she-mail.
Hey, big spenders.
all: Hey!
- I own everything.
[laughs]
Or at least I act like I do.
You gotta fake it till you
make it, honey.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Get that coin, girl.
'Cause if you don't,
there ain't nothing going on
but the rent.
- What?
- Prostitution.
- Hello, hello, hello!
all: [cheer]
- My ladies.
- You know, most drag
performers make their money
in tips, but to be America's
next drag superstar, you need
to make your moola selling it
to the masses.
Now, for today's mini challenge,
you'll become host for the
newest, hottest home shopping
channel--RuVC.
all: [laugh]
- You'll each have three
minutes to pitch one product,
an item you choose from your
own drag, and the one queen
who convinces me to order
her product will win.
You've got 20 minutes to put
together a quick drag
spokesqueen look.
And I'll see you on RuVC.
All right.
- Oh, my god.
Ah!
- Everybody in the room
including me look a mess.
Raja looks like Rainbow Brite.
Manila actually was pretty
with less makeup.
And Yara, I don't even have
a clue.
- The first thing I thought of
was you're not my tucker.
It's fresh out of my own drag.
It's something that I rely on
most often,
and why not sell it?
- I don't know if I look good in
brown hair, but...
- What are you wearing?
- Welcome to RuVC.
I wanna tell you about a product
today that has aromatherapeutic
powers, healing powers,
it can feminize you,
it could increase your libido.
Be right back. My gaff.
You take this part that would
normally cover your genitals,
and you stretch it over your
face, and it has invigorating
powers that immediately wakes
you up.
That's $6,934, uh, 60 clams
from a tribe in Africa,
and 4 goats, and you, too,
can own this--Raja's gaff.
Start ordering, everyone.
- Hi, my name is Manila Luzon.
You may have seen me on such
shows as RuPaul's Drag Race
or Cops.
I'm here to tell you about
this new product Man-ila.
You can use it for hair,
tabletop cleaner,
makeup finisher,
when you get these, like,
horrible runs in your nylons.
If you call right now,
we'll send you this free travel
cap that goes on top.
Thank you. Good-bye!
- Hi, America. I'm Yara Sofia.
It's kind of hard to find
the perfect hair.
And you can wear a perfect
pop-it-on.
See how gorgeous it is?
You can wear it like this,
and you can put it like this,
you can scrub yourself,
your body.
You know, we are drag queens.
You can use the pop-it-on
to clean your table.
Only 100 payments of $1.
You have to buy the pop-it-on.
Now, bye.
- My name is Alexis Mateo,
and I have a secret that I wanna
share with you--the hip pad.
If you always want the perfect
body but you cannot have it,
I got the magic solution
for you.
They are handmade
and hand-painted just by me.
For only two payments of $19.95.
But wait. If you call right now
in the last ten seconds,
I'm gonna give you handmade pads
for your ass Alexis.
The booty, the pads, everything
that you need to be a complete
drag queen for only two payments
of $19.95.
This is Alexis Mateo for RuVC.
- Hi.
all: Hi!
- Wow, wow. Ooh!
What do we have here?
Let's see what I ordered.
This is always so exciting.
- Yeah!
- Open it, open it, open it.
all: [cheer, applaud]
- It's a pop-it-on!
- A pop-it-on!
[laughs]
Say what, the pop-it-on!
Ah, she bought the pop-it-on!
Finally I--I win the mini
challenge.
- Yara, your prize for winning
the mini challenge is...
$1 million.
- What?
Gee! Whoo!
- Well, well, actually,
darling, it's 1 million Ru
dollars.
- Oh!
- Yes.
- What happened?
- Now, the pit crew was up
all night cooking up this dough
at Cat Print.
While these may not pay your
bills, they could come in handy
a little later, because it is
time for the most expensive
challenge in RuPaul's Drag Race
her-story!
This week we are throwing
a make-dat-money ball,
and each of you will have to
come up with a portfolio
of three different looks
that you could take to the bank,
honey.
First category--Swimsuit Body
Beautiful.
You need to create a bathing
suit hot enough to attract
a billionaire.
Second category--
Cocktail Attire After 5:00.
You need to create a flirty,
short dress where all that
glitters is gold.
Third category--Evening Gown
Eleganza.
- Work.
- Using 2 1/2 million Ru paper
dollars,
you need to create a dress that
literally screams money.
Yara, because you won the mini
challenge,
you have an extra million
dollars to play with.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- We have three challenges
in a row that have multiple
looks for the runway.
Like, are you exhausted?
'Cause I'm exhausted.
- I feel like I'm a glamorous
sweatshop worker, if you will.
- That's just 'cause you're
Asian.
- [laughs]
- [sighs] Have you ever made a
swimsuit before?
- No, I haven't--
I've never made one.
- What're you gonna do
for a swimsuit?
- A gold swimsuit.
All I hear from the judges
all the time is that my body's
not right, that my walk is not
right, that my hair is not
right.
I cannot please all the judges,
but that doesn't define
who I am.
I mean, there's nothing wrong
with my body at all.
Probably something wrong with
Michelle's and Santino's body,
but it's not--nothing wrong
with my body.
I'm just the girl that wears
the pads and the titties
in the show.
- Alexis mentions her
insecurity coming in,
and it's all in her head,
I think.
- But they're not, like,
sleeping on you, Alexis.
Like, they love you.
You have a great personality.
- It's just bullshit.
I don't know.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
- Why are you saying that
the judges are against you?
You have win three challenges,
girl.
- Now because of that,
I'm gonna get all fucked up.
- Fuck glue gun.
- Did you burn yourself?
- Fuck, fuck.
- Today's main challenge
is to make three distinct
money looks--uh, a swimsuit,
a cocktail dress, and an evening
gown--for Ru's make-dat-money
ball.
- Where's the only
fucking glue gun?
- We're stressed out, 'cause
it's gonna be a long day, honey.
- Some craziness.
I know there's a lot of people
that think that I'm gonna do
wrong in this challenge.
I don't have a clue
how this is gonna turn out.
I have never worked with this
kind of material, and every time
I try hard, I get shit.
- Girl! That--oh, maybe you
wanna start over.
- Um, I hate it.
I think we're all in a great
panic at this point.
There's very, very little time,
and I can feel the stress
in the room.
Oh, I hate starting over.
I can't stand this anymore.
- Hello, hello, hello!
- Hola!
- Are you ready for the
make-dat-money ball?
- Yes.
- Not yet.
- Hi, Alexis.
- Hi, Ru!
- Does this challenge frighten
you at all?
- Yeah, I am worried about it.
Like, it's so difficult.
I'm not a pro.
I'm not a designer.
- Okay, all right.
So, are you gonna do a whole
gold storyline here?
- You know what, Ru,
I have no clue what I want
to show on the stage.
I'm talking to Ru,
and it was not going well.
That scares me a lot.
- Who's your biggest
competition?
- It is Yara.
Yara have everything that I love
in a drag queen.
Her mind is very high-fashion,
and her personality is so,
so big.
Plus she's Puerto Rican.
- Uh-huh.
- So, if I don't win this
competition, another
Puerto Rican should be crowned.
- [laughs]
All right, get back to work.
- Thank you, Ru!
- All right.
Yara Sofia.
- Hi!
- Tell me about money.
Are you free-spending,
or are you very frugal?
- I'm very free-spending.
- [laughs]
- I'm broke, but I'm still
fabulous.
- If you win the $75,000,
are you just gonna spend it?
- I am gonna move probably
to the states.
Puerto Rico, it's hard to find a
job.
- It's hard to find a job here
too.
- Yes, I know, but it--
in Puerto Rico, it's more hard.
- Do you make a living
making dresses?
- Yes. My inspiration
is Bob Mackie.
- You could be the next
Bob Mackie.
We need another Bob Mackie.
We need more wearable art.
- Mm-hmm.
I want to risk the American
dream.
I want to make my own line
of clothes.
And that's why I'm here, I'm--
because I love drag,
I love to make dresses.
This is my life.
- Ooh!
Look how delicious.
All this money.
You've been in the competition
for a long time.
Are you surprised that you've
lasted so long?
- Well, no, I knew that, like,
I was gonna be in for the long
haul.
I just didn't know you were
gonna bring all these girls and
have all these extra challenges.
- So, is it safe to say you
didn't come to the competition
to make friends, you came
to win?
- Uh, well, both.
I love meeting new people,
so I'm gonna make a lot of
friends, but if I have to stab
them in the back, I mean,
whatever.
- [laughs]
Well, hello, Raja.
- Hi, sexy lady.
- What are you working on now?
- Well, I'm basically making
an armature for a top hat made
out of coins and cash.
- Oh, wow.
Do you have enough time
to do something like that?
- I think so.
- All right. Now, tell me
something about the swimsuit.
- I wanna show my skinny body
and do just a bikini.
- How do you stay so skinny?
- I work out. I do Pilates and
yoga.
And with my, uh, $75,000 that
I win, I'll finally get
my gastric bypass.
both: [laugh]
- All right, ladies,
gather around.
All right, there's one more
thing that will make this week's
main challenge even richer.
- Ah, no!
- I want you to choreograph
a group number that will kick
off the make-dat-money ball.
- On top of all this?
Oh, my god, I'm gonna die.
- Now, Yara, since you won
the mini challenge,
you're in charge.
Oh, and you'll be shaking
your moneymakers to the song
Just Wanna Dance
by Miss La Toya Jackson,
because tomorrow on the main
stage, back again at my personal
request, we'll be joined by
Miss La Toya herself.
all: Yay.
- And our extra-special guest
judge will be the New York Times
best-selling author
Gigi Levangie Grazer.
- Cool. Yay.
- All right, ladies,
time is money, so get to work.
And, remember, don't fuck it up.
- Oh, my god!
- You have to measure your--
your size, and you have to make
the mannequin for you,
'cause it will take your shape.
- Alexis, is your fit gonna be
immaculate?
- You know what, I'm looking
like the way I want it to look.
If they like it, they like it.
If they don't like it, oh, well.
I'm completely freaking out
right now.
I was feeling stressed out,
and I cannot do the challenge,
and it's horrible.
You get to a point when you
cannot control your feelings
anymore.
I just want this to be over.
I just wanna go home.
- When I see Alexis packing,
what the fuck are you doing?
What are you doing?
both: [speaking Spanish]
- I am tired, I'm exhausted,
and to see Alexis packing,
it makes me feel angry.
- What's going on with, um,
Alexis?
- She's trying to give up.
I don't know.
- She's over it?
- She's trying to leave
the competition.
- Alexis gave up and left this
competition.
It's a very, very dark moment.
- I don't know where--
where is she? Where is she?
- I don't know.
I have had, like, meltdowns
and freak-outs, and I'm trying
to hold myself together, because
at any moment, it could happen.
Like, the pressure is so intense
right now.
- She told me, like, she gained
weight, and sometimes it's so
hard to make clothes for her.
- We have no time.
- No time!
- We have to do three outfits.
- It's frustrating for me,
'cause I don't want to be
uncomfortable.
- Anyway, well, guess I'm
gonna start putting shit
on my dress.
[sewing machine whirs]
I decided to, like, whip out
Sahara's picture because
it's like seeing my boyfriend is
a really great reminder
of why I'm here.
- Girl, what's going on with
that picture?
- Oh, It's Sahara Davenport.
The most beautiful drag queen
after RuPaul.
- Do you miss her?
- Fuck yeah, I miss the bitch.
- Cute.
- You know, I think I've tried
sewing a dress before,
with a slit in the side, and it
didn't work out.
So I don't know why I'm trying
this again.
Bitch man is not the tea.
- [sighs]
Stress, stress, stress.
[door squeaks open]
- [exhales]
- Ay!
You're scaring me.
You're a psycho bitch.
- It was just--I don't know.
I decided to stay in this
competition all the way
till the end.
I'm here, bitches. I am here.
I didn't came here to just
give up in the top four.
I came here to be America's
next drag superstar.
- Drama, girl.
- [chuckles]
- So, girls,
let's get--dance, girl!
It's time to go to rehearsal.
- Just 'cause RuPaul put you
in charge doesn't mean you have
to yell at us.
- I decide to split the
choreography between Alexis
and me, 'cause we have a great
connection and Alexis is
a good dancer.
- Here we go.
- Whoo! The coins!
- Get your coins, girl.
- Um, let's begin.
- What are we gonna do?
- Manila seems a little bit
terrified,
but so am I, so we're in this
together.
- First step.
Step with the right...
Shoulder, out.
Boom, bam.
Five, six, seven, eight, we do
this in line.
And we get out of the line.
We go back in line,
and we gonna repeat that again.
- Perfect.
- Whoo! Okay.
- Good job, darling.
Outsides all yours.
I told you, she's good.
- Here we go! And step.
Again, we got it, we got it, we
got it.
- I'm lost, I'm so lost.
Oh, what happened?
Oh, wait, what am I doing?
- Wait a minute.
[laughs]
- Wait, sorry.
What am I doing? Am I following
you?
I'm doing the opposite of you
now, right?
- [laughs]
- I'm still doing that?
I haven't done a choreographed
routine in such a long time.
I'm terrified.
- It's easy.
- Once I get this, you guys
better watch out.
- Okay.
- Oh, girl, you're gonna have to
catch up,
because it's not that difficult
to understand, so get it
together, bitch.
Hands up.
Then we going to the left,
to the right,
and go all the way to your ass.
Shakin' my ass.
- Yeah, darling!
- Shake your ass.
- Yeah!
- Manila, Manila, just shake
your back.
- [laughs]
- Yeah, we just shake the ass.
- How are you doing that?
- I'm moving, I'm moving.
- I don't know how to do this.
- The cha-cha is inside all of
you.
Hey, I want to do this.
It's like...
We supposed to be touching each
other's back.
- Oh, hey, girls.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
Boom!
Don't leave the back.
No, no, what are you doing,
Manila?
- Again.
- Can we do this?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Can we just not put it in
front of our faces?
'Cause I don't want to block
this mug.
- Hey, hey, watch out!
- [exclaims in Spanish]
- I'm not really a dancer,
and so picking up choreography
is like not the easiest thing
for me to do.
We're down to the final four.
I don't want to fuck this up,
so...
Awesome, guys.
Go team.
- This is gonna be a mess.
- [laughs]
[alarm beeps]
- Money morning!
- Money, money, money,
money, money, money.
- Oh, my god.
Feel like I should've just had a
bed here.
- I know. Like, what was the
point of even going back home?
- We haven't sleep or nothing.
- There's a lot of pressure,
and it's really important for me
to do a great job on this
challenge, because it's one of
our last challenges.
And if I don't do a good job,
I'm gonna be in the bottom two
again.
[sighs] All right.
- You guys, did we use every
single glue stick there is?
- Yes.
- Yes, we did. See?
- Did you use the extra
million dollars?
- Yes, except for--
- Everything?
- Except for this one.
- Wow.
- 'Cause I wanted a big one.
- That's a lot of dress, honey.
- Yara's is way too
complicated.
And I understand avant-garde,
but it's just really crazy.
If she were to sit down in it,
it would look like a pile of
garbage.
Yara, it's like a tropical
garden.
It's really huge.
- I don't care if
the other girls will like it.
I'm focused on my stuff.
RuPaul is gonna love it.
- Who's top three?
- I would like to be me,
Yara, and Alexis.
- Manila, you think it's gonna
be easier for you to win
the competition if Raja's gone?
- If it all goes correctly,
then I should be in the top
three.
- If you don't make the top
three,
the decision is incorrect.
- Sure.
I put so much energy into this
competition from day one,
and I feel like I really worked
my hands to the bone,
and I need to be in the top
three.
It's just so close.
- The top three gonna be me,
Raja, and Yara.
- Never, never, never
in a million years.
Where's Manila going?
- Home. After tonight.
- Hey.
- I deserve it.
I want Alexis in the top three.
And the other one, I don't know.
- Since Manila and I had a--
had a pretty close relationship
throughout this competition,
I would like to see her there.
- I deserve it, motherfuckers.
I'm gonna make the top three,
because I worked very hard
for this, and I'm gonna let them
have it!
[laughter]
- And what?
Hey, guys!
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Hey, Michelle, you like?
- I love.
- Mike Ruiz, you look like
a million dollars.
- Oh, so do you.
- Well, you know, as Dolly
says, "it takes a lot of money
to look this cheap."
- [laughs]
- Gigi Levangie Grazer,
how does a Hollywood wife make
her money?
- Well, we earn it the
old-fashioned way, RuPaul--
through divorce.
- [laughs]
- L.A. Toya, you're back by my
request.
- And I will do anything for
you, Ru, you know that.
- Oh, honey, that's big money,
La Toya, if you ask me.
both: [laugh]
- This week our queens
were challenged to create
three million-dollar looks
for the make-dat-money ball.
To kick things off,
they're gonna make it rain
to La Toya Jackson's
Just Wanna Dance.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Category is Swimsuit Body
Beautiful, and they will be
performing to La Toya's song
Just Wanna Dance.
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
- [laughs]
- Wow!
- Whoo!
- Amazing!
The gold-diggers of 2011.
Category is Cocktail Attire
after 5:00.
Yara Sofia.
- She's the merry widow,
ready for her next husband.
- Yes.
- It's like she's getting ready
for Liberace's funeral.
- Uh-huh.
- My cocktail dress is inspired
by Nina Ricci, like,
very Evita Peron,
very sophisticated, very dark.
- And I love the gloves on her.
- It's very film noir.
- The widow wore gold.
Up next, Alexis Mateo.
- Ooh!
- Goldfinger.
- With my cocktail dress,
I think about myself.
Alexis always cha-cha.
That's what the dress is.
I'm not gonna change myself
for nobody else.
I'm just gonna walk the dress,
and I know it looks sickening
on me.
- The Golden Globes.
- It's like two canned hams
under a blanket, fighting it
out.
- Really, yes. Ooh, I love ham.
Manila.
- Hey, girl, hey!
- All right!
- Lots of attitude.
This reminds me of a disco.
- Well, I don't know about Ru,
but I take my disco nap
at 5:00 P.M., so this is going
to be an after-5:00-A.M. Look,
yes, and, honey, I am still
partying, and I'm about to go
to the after-party, honey.
- New year's eve 1984.
- Oh, my god.
'80s in the San Fernando Valley.
- For the love of money.
Up next, Raja.
Ooh, Raja and the gold rush.
- The look for my cocktail
dress is a little bit heiress,
and it's a little eccentric.
- I own everything, and I
bought it on my American Express
Gold card, darling.
Category is million-dollar
Evening Gown Eleganza.
Yara Sofia.
- She blew her cash wad.
- Yes.
It's Marie Antoinette.
- Cha-ching.
- I'm doing my runway,
and I feel like a queen,
and it feels so great.
I feel so powerful.
The avant-garde for me
is everything.
- She's got the credit cards
in there too.
- Her whole safety deposit box.
- Suze Orman called.
She wants her Fico score back.
- [laughs]
- Up next, Alexis Mateo.
- Goddess of the sea.
- Yes. Yes, like scales.
- They're like fish scales.
- I wanted to look like a
mermaid.
I wanted to look like tropical,
flowers, colors.
I wanted to look very pageant
as well.
- It's like the Little Mermaid
meets Lil' Kim.
- Yes, it is!
Mo' money, mo' problems.
You can bet your bottom dollar,
and I do mean bottom.
Manila.
- Imelda markup.
- Imelda markup, that's right.
- It's better than a markdown.
- For my evening gown made of
money, the judges are really
liking my look.
I think my hair is just so big
that they have to love it.
I mean, come on, who doesn't
love a drag queen with gigantic
hair?
- She looks like a Texas
tycoon's wife.
- Yes!
Black gold.
both: Texas tea!
- [laughs]
- I think her economy
just double-dipped.
Up next, Raja.
- Wow.
- Ow!
- Ultimately I had this idea
of this 1930s sort of starlet,
and she is going on a train
to the Hearst castle to meet up
with all of her fancy buddies,
and I think it looks fantastic.
I think I look like an exotic
bird.
- She owns the world.
- If I had the dollars...
- Very Linda Evangelista.
- All the honeys making money.
Welcome, ladies.
It's time for the judges'
critiques.
Yara Sofia.
- Yes?
- Penny for your thoughts.
- [chuckles]
This is my inspiration,
from Alexander McQueen.
- Yes.
- And the hair is my trademark.
My pop-it-ons.
- Your pop-it-ons.
- But this time covered
in money.
- Yara, you are absolutely
gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- I do think that it's
a bit busy.
All the gold necklace and then
the gold going into the bustier,
with the hair and the necklace,
it's almost like that.
- Your cocktail dress
presentation was a little
morose, and I would've hoped
that you would've been a little
more effervescent, you know,
on every level.
- Up next, Alexis Mateo.
- I love what you've done
to this dress.
This is why I know you could've
done something much better
with the bathing suit than
what I saw.
- And it's pretty much the same
for your cocktail dress.
I think it was just a little
too simple for me.
- When you came out in
the bathing suit, I thought,
I'm so glad she got rid of Ike.
- [laughs]
- That Tina Turner wig was
fabulous. I loved it.
- The problem with the swimsuit
for me was that it was too
abuelita.
It was too grandma.
And because it was cut low,
it made you look bulky.
- All right, up next, Manila.
- Hi, judges.
- Now, tell us about this dress.
It looks like Beverly Hills
shrubbery.
- You know, at the end of
the night when you open your
drag bag to see all your tips...
- Yes.
- They're all crumpled
and sweaty, and so I thought
that it would be kind of
interesting to, like, tear up
money and crumple them,
and then, um, glue them on here.
- When I look at the pink
flower in your hair,
it's absolutely gorgeous.
It enhances your color tones.
I did feel and think your hair
was a little bit too big.
- How dare you!
all: [laugh]
- I'm a drag queen!
both: [laugh]
- Well, I loved your swimsuit
presentation.
It was very Saint-Tropez,
French Riviera.
It was very Samantha Jones,
you know, goes to the Hamptons.
I loved it.
- It all worked.
It was thought out, and it was
executed beautifully.
- The cocktail attire,
very Mahogany, very Diana Ross.
I wanna go to that cocktail
party.
- All right, up next, Raja.
- Hi.
- When you walk out,
you act as if you own the stage,
and I wanna focus on you,
because you give me, you demand
that attention from me.
And that's what I love about
you.
But your after-5:00 to me
was so plain.
It was so simple.
It was so ordinary.
The entire outfit, to be quite
frank with you, reminded me of
a Pointer sister.
- All right, ladies,
here's the $75,000 question--
why do you deserve to be crowned
America's next drag superstar?
Let's start with Yara.
- I'm so broke.
all: [laugh]
- Uh, I don't have anything in
my bank.
My credit card is over--
is overdrawn, and I need money
to--to move to the states,
and I would like to live
the American dream.
I have charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
I have everything.
I'm the full package.
- All right, Alexis,
same question.
- I think I deserve to be
America's next drag superstar
because inside of me, like every
American and every real person,
I am not perfect, but I have
the desire to continue.
And if I can move forward
in the competition and become
America's next drag superstar,
I would do it with honor,
respect, and proud.
- Manila, why do you deserve
to be crowned America's next
drag superstar?
- I came to this competition
blessed.
I feel like I represent
the product of a loving
and supportive family.
I'm not a Cinderella story.
My parents didn't kick me out.
My parents have been very loving
and very supportive.
And I have a beautiful family.
And I think that I carry
a message of--to love and be
really supportive of--of all
your friends and your family,
because we all have, like,
the power inside of us.
We just need that extra push,
and I'm here to--
to speak that.
- Raja, same question.
- In winning this competition,
I would love to leave a legacy
for all those little boys...
[sighs]
All the little boys who are
teased, who are afraid,
who don't know how to express
themselves creatively yet,
you know, and they don't even
know that they're allowed to go
against the grain.
It's okay to say fuck you,
and do what you love to do,
and express yourself thoroughly.
I wanna be an example of someone
who is proud, someone who is
accomplished, and someone who
loves--loves what they do.
- The power of Fuck You.
all: [laugh]
- Well, girls, I think we've
heard enough.
Now, while you go and untuck
in the interior illusions
lounge, the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, just between us
gargoyles, what do ya think?
Let's start with Yara Sofia.
- To me, it looked like she got
run over by a Brink's truck.
- It was a miss.
It was too much.
- Her speech, I'm sorry,
but I felt for her.
- You're a softie.
- Oh, my god, this poor thing.
She doesn't have any money.
- I really felt for her,
but, you know, I don't think
we can pick a drag superstar
based on the fact that we feel
sorry for them.
- Right. All right,
let's move on to Alexis.
- She's not utilizing her body
the way she should and could.
Just the bathing suit alone.
- It was like a middle-aged
woman trying to get laid
at Jones beach.
- If you're gonna pick a
proportion like an hourglass
in that dress, why are you gonna
pull all of your hair back
into this teeny-tiny--
she looked like Beetlejuice.
both: [laugh]
- All right, let's move on
to Manila.
- The swimsuit was beautiful.
It was feminine. It was elegant.
Totally nailed the challenge as
far as that goes.
- She has incredible stage
presence.
She's always on when she's up
here.
She's the queen of that coy
kind of thing, and you have to
take that into consideration...
- Sure.
- When these people have your
name attached to them as
America's next drag superstar.
- Let's move on to Raja.
Now, I've just gotta start with
that gown...
- Crazy good.
- Which was just breathtaking.
- Two words about the cocktail
dress, Ru.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oil can.
- [laughs]
- I'm probably gonna lose it
again, but listening to Raja's
speech, I was one of those
little boys.
I was one of those little boys
who wanted a beacon of hope,
who wanted somebody to look up
to, to say, "you know what,
it's gonna be okay.
Be yourself, and be creative,
and be inspired, and think
outside of the box, and don't
let anyone ever tell you
that you can't."
You know, so, to me, I don't
even care what Raja was wearing
tonight.
- [claps]
Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Now, based on your performance
in the make-dat-money ball,
I've made some decisions.
Manila, this week you looked
like a high roller,
but did you hit the jackpot?
Raja, your Evening Gown Eleganza
was top dollar, but were you
outspent on the runway?
Manila, condragulations,
you are the winner of this
week's challenge.
- Oh, my god.
- You will receive a collection
of fine jewelry from
Kathy Ireland Jewelry.
- Thank you, guys.
I won, I won!
Two weeks in a row, bitches.
- Raja...
You're safe.
Alexis Mateo, Yara Sofia,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you are up for elimination.
- For me, being in the bottom
two is like losing.
I feel horrible.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-synch for your life.
- Yara is my sister,
and I know what the competition
means to Yara.
She wants this so bad,
but I want it too.
- Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ When I feel like loving ♪
♪ Kissing and hugging ♪
♪ I think about you ♪
♪ When my heart starts
to burn ♪
♪ And then I get ♪
♪ That crazy yearning ♪
♪ I think about you ♪
♪ When I need satisfying ♪
♪ Without even trying ♪
♪ I think about you ♪
♪ I think about you, you, you ♪
♪ Oh, I think about you ♪
- I cannot even think.
I cannot perform.
I have to lip-synch to convince
the judges that I'm good.
I don't know if I can.
- ♪ Oh, I think about you ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
- I'm crying because there's
a lot of emotions.
I was thinking too much.
I'm so angry,
and I'm so disappointed.
I'm a mess.
- ♪ Ooh, I think about you ♪
♪ Said I, said I, said I ♪
♪ Said that I ♪
♪ I think about you ♪
♪ You, you, you... ♪
- [sniffles]
- All right, ladies,
I have made my decision.
- [sniffles]
[sobs]
- Yara...
[speaks Spanish]
- Alexis Mateo,
Shante, you stay.
- I told you.
Don't worry about it.
- [speaking indistinctly]
[sobs]
I'm so sorry.
- Don't be sorry.
It's emotional.
We've all been there.
- [sobs]
- Yara Sofia, listen to me.
The sparkle you have,
the sparkle you brought to
this competition, no one can
wash off.
It's there, it's yours.
You are a star.
Remember this--
Echa, echa, echa pa'lante.
Now, sashay away.
- [kisses]
The lip-synch was so awful
for me, 'cause I didn't expect
to be in the bottom two,
but it's not my decision.
And this is for Puerto Rico.
So, I'm gonna echa pa'lante,
darling.
I'm fine. I'm--I'm so happy.
Um, I did my best, and this is
me.
I don't know.
I have too much to offer.
- All right, ladies.
You're the top three.
Let me tell you something.
Everyone on this panel can
attest that show business
is a tough business.
It can be very painful,
but we go on.
If you cannot love yourself...
Say it with me.
How in the hell...
- How in the hell...
- You gonna love somebody else?
- Does that make sense?
- Yes.
- Amen.
- All right.
Now, let the music play.
Let's celebrate.
Grand prize contributed
in part by ALandCHUCK.travel.