- You know the law.
13 glamazons enter,
one drag superstar leaves.
Let the Thunderdome begin!
- ♪ Welcome to the... ♪
- Tonight on RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited!
Our 13 drag warriors return
to battle it out...
- I'm the Charlie Sheen
of drag.
Duh, winning.
- Set the record straight...
- I was never trying
to sabotage you.
- You could have simply rolled
some marbles out there
and just called it a day.
- Bam.
- And let each other have it.
- Did I talk shit?
Absolutely.
We know our names
aren't Heather,
even though they're
right here on our neck.
- If this is the face
of Booger,
I think it's sickening.
- Plus, the queens turn
the tables on Michelle Visage.
- You're a bitch, Michelle.
You bought your titties too.
- And we announce
the fans' choice
for this season's
Miss Congeniality.
The drag race may be over,
but the real drama
is just getting started.
- ♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
- Welcome to RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited!
You've watched it,
they've lived it,
and now the whole family's
back together
to work it out.
Release the kraken.
These first two fierce queens
came to win, but sadly,
they were gone too soon.
Please welcome back
Venus D-Lite and Phoenix.
Pose. Now vogue.
Rising from the ashes.
The last time we saw
these two queens together,
one was head and shoulders
above the other.
Please welcome back Mimi Imfurst
and India Ferrah.
Pose.
Pose, I said.
Up next,
the belle of the ballroom.
From Hotlanta, GA,
and we call this queen Mariah.
Don't be throwing no shade.
She just wants to get paid.
- ♪ Glamazon-on-on-on ♪
♪ ♪
- Well, hello, ladies.
- Hello.
- Hey, Ru.
- Now I've dedicated the song
you've just heard
to you and all my girls,
and it just so happens to be
the title track
off my new album, Glamazon,
available on iTunes.
Now speaking of glamazons,
how are you,
Miss Venus D-Lite?
- I'm great.
How are you?
- Fantastic.
It's great to see you.
- It's great to see you too.
- Now, being the first girl
to go...
- Uh-huh.
- Must really suck.
- To be honest, it's actually
been a mixed blessing
because, um,
since after the show, um,
it made people
even more interested in me
because they really did get
to see a lot of me.
- Now, it was revealed
during the show
that you had some work done
to look like Madonna.
- Yes. Uh-huh.
- Would you go further with it?
- I've had some
since I've been gone.
- Really?
- I have.
- What'd you have done?
- Um, just a little more
facial work.
Just a little here and there.
- Injections?
- Injections.
- Would you consider having
a little mini Lourdes created?
- You know what?
When Madonna fades out
and Lourdes becomes famous,
I think that's gonna be
my next solution,
and, um, I naturally
have brown eyes, so...
- Oh, really?
I naturally have
a brown eye too.
- Ooh!
- Well.
- Well, well, well.
- Now, having watched
the rest of the season at home,
which one of the challenges
would you have rocked?
- The Snatch Game.
- So can I put you on the spot
and give you
a Snatch Game question?
- Okay.
- For Madonna?
- It's my turn.
- Okay.
Dumb Dora is so dumb,
she thinks a Kardashian
is a blank.
- She thinks a Kardashian
is my next deejay boyfriend.
Deejay Kardashian.
- [laughs]
Fabulous, Madonna.
Lady Phoenix.
- Yes, Ru.
- Now, watching at home,
were you shocked
by your performance
as Lady Ta-Ta in the
drag queens from outer space?
- Well, you know, I've never
claimed to try to win an Oscar,
so, you know, I mean--
- How about a Golden Globe?
- I mean, possibly.
- NAACP Image Award?
So what did you think
when you saw yourself?
- Because I've never been in
front of the camera like this,
you know, they kept screaming
at me to cheat the camera,
cheat the camera,
and I'm like,
"What the fuck?
I don't cheat on anybody."
I'm like, "what is going on?"
So, you know, it was really
like--really confusion.
- All right.
Mimi Imfurst.
- Hey, Ru.
- In the now legendary
lip-synch for your life...
- Oh, yes.
- When you threw India
over your shoulders...
What was going through your head
at the time?
- Well, I had been doing it
in my show for ten years.
You know, I've probably picked
up over 1,000 people.
Uh, I've never dropped anyone.
It's just something I do.
Like, some girls do splits
or death drops,
and that's what I do.
The stakes there seemed so high.
It's not you're lip-synching
for Mariah Carey's
Glitter album, you know?
You're lip-synching
for your life,
and it feels like
if you fail at this, you know,
you're gonna reach over
from behind your table,
reach in your Prada purse,
and pull out a gun,
and that's the end.
- Well, thank God you didn't
have a Prada purse.
- No, no.
- How did it feel?
What was going
through your head?
- [scoffs]
Craziness.
Like, it was just so out
of the blue, like, unexpected.
I was trying to perform,
and she would just,
like, move in front of me,
and I said,
"Okay, I want the judges
to see me."
Only way that y'all could see me
was to go down to the judges,
and in a split second,
I was seeing
the whole rest of the girls
in the back of the thing,
and I didn't know
what was going on.
Get her off of me!
I said, "Okay, I'm up
on this bitch's shoulder.
Like, what just happened?"
- I understand
it was over the top,
and it--it--you know,
and people--
there were people
who thought it was
the worst thing in the world,
there are people
who thought it was entertaining.
- Right, well, I want to ask
the other queens,
do you think it was entertaining
or was it over the line?
- In a show in New York,
you know, that's--that's okay.
You know, it's fun,
it's part of--
but, you know,
this is my chance.
- I can't say that I probably
wouldn't have bopped you, girl.
- Yeah, I think that also.
- 'Cause there's no screaming,
"Get me down, honey."
I'm gonna get myself down.
- And, India, what would you
have done differently?
- Actually, there was nothing
that I could have done
differently,
'cause I think
if I was anywhere else,
she still
would have done that.
Me as an entertainer,
I was there,
performing for you all.
Like, I paid no attention
to her,
other than her blocking me.
So I think
she should have done the same,
and she should have just gave it
her all at that moment.
- I respect that,
and I totally think--
I totally think
if I was in your position,
I would feel the same way.
Just to be clear, I was never
trying to sabotage you.
Like, it was for me,
it was like,
"What can I do to shake this up?
What can I do to make it
different?"
- In lip-synch for your life,
there is a certain
sort of fairness.
You're up to perform,
and if your focus
is to just get in the way
of the other girl...
- Right.
- It's not really
that professional.
- Isn't it a competition?
- You could have simply rolled
some marbles out there
and just called it a day.
- Yeah.
- No.
- So let's move on.
- Actually, I have
a little gift for India.
- Oh.
- Oh!
- Oh, goodness.
- Is it ticking?
- Does it have bullets in it?
- It's not ticking at all.
I got India Ferrah
this lovely shirt that says,
"I got picked up
by Mimi Imfurst,
and all I got
was this lousy T-shirt!"
- All right, now, India.
- Hi.
- Were you surprised when you
sashayed away when you did?
- I thought my time
was cut short.
I think two of the challenges,
I wasn't able to show
who I was as a person
or entertainer
due to the, um, duties
that I was given
from Carmen Carrera.
- By the way,
you did say duty.
- Oh, duty.
I'm sorry, duty.
- So what do you mean?
- The workout challenge.
- Right.
- Um, with the rubber band.
We're gonna lower it down,
ladies.
One, two, three, four.
- So the rubber thingamajiggie
prevented us
from seeing
your real personality?
- Absolutely, yeah.
- [laughs]
- Like...
[both laughing]
- Really?
- Yeah.
Like, where could I go
with a rubber thingamajiggie?
- Well, if you know,
the other girl won the challenge
with the thingamajiggie.
- Yeah, with the lip gloss.
Yeah, that's very true.
I just wasn't clever enough
at that moment
to pull out a thing
of lip gloss or eat chicken.
- [laughing]
Now, I gotta say,
I'm hearing a lot
of excuses right now.
- Well, that's what I do, Ru.
- [laughing]
- I laid 'em out,
card by card.
- So had there been a challenge
about excuses,
you would have...
- Well, like, every challenge
after I got kicked off,
I would have succeeded in.
Like, I'm not even lying.
Like the cake challenge,
because I sew,
sew all my costumes
and gowns and stuff,
so I would have definitely
succeeded in that.
- You would have ate that.
- Yeah, I would have ate it up.
- Well, that's the thing.
That's the thing
about this competition.
It's almost like
a roll of the dice.
- Right.
- You've basically got to be
a jack of all trades.
- Exactly.
- Mariah aka Mariah Paris
aka Mariah Balenciaga
aka Mariah Successful.
Now, before you came here--
of course, you did balls,
uh, and the ballroom scene
down in Atlanta.
- Yes, I do balls.
- We've all done balls.
- Now, do you think
being a ballroom queen and,
uh, and not being
a nightclub girl,
uh, put you at a disadvantage
in the competition?
- Um, yeah, it did,
a little bit,
because I don't do it
every week.
The changing, the transition.
I also don't have to learn
lyrics.
- Oh, you're talking about
your lip sync now, aren't you?
- Well, yes.
That was my disadvantage.
- [laughs]
Because you saw the lip sync,
there wasn't a lot
of lip-syncing to the--
- No.
- But you--
- But I-I-I will mug
the shit out of you, though.
- She was.
- Baby.
- Plugs for days, girl.
- Okay?
I will mug the shit
out of you.
- Well, what do you do
when you don't know the lyrics?
- You know what?
I just study BeBe Zahara Benet.
- [laughs]
- You move your lips enough,
and they'll think
that you are turning it.
- [laughing]
What kind of fan mail
have you gotten?
- I've gotten
so many touching letters
about people who were inspired
by my confidence.
They know drag queens,
we go through a lot
of adverse experiences in life
and we still walk around
with our heads held high.
There was this one young girl,
she went through
a tragic experience,
and she felt the need
to reach out
and just tell me her story
and get it out.
Just the fact that me just being
who I am impacted somebody,
it was very touching.
There's no words.
- These next two queens
supersize our love of drag.
Give it up
for Miss Stacy Layne Matthews
and Miss Delta Work!
Uh-oh!
Work!
Be a lady!
- ♪ Jungle ♪
♪ She's so... ♪
- In a year of firsts,
this queen returned to take
the competition by storm.
Please welcome
Shangela Laquifa Wadley!
Ooh, child!
Hallelu!
- ♪ She's like a female... ♪
- Now, when these two queens
lip-synched for their lives,
neither one of them
sashayed away.
Please welcome back
Carmen Carerra
and Yara Sofia.
Echa pa'lante!
Yo, Jersey!
Sickness.
- ♪ Glamazon-on-on-on ♪
- Well, hey, girls.
Let's kick it.
Stacy Layne Matthews.
- Hello.
- From Back Swamp,
North Carolina.
Now, how has doing Drag Race
changed your life?
- Oh, I'm like the local,
um, Oprah Winfrey
of Back Swamp now, so...
- Really?
- I go outside, you know,
walk out my door,
and, like, my cousins,
and like, "Oh, my God, hey!
Hey, girl, oh, my God!
It's Stacy!"
I'm like, "Honey,
it's still me, honey."
- [laughs]
Do you have any beef
with any of the other queens?
- Um, when I first watched
a show,
I was pretty upset
with a lot of things
a lot of people had to say,
especially Delta.
I love her,
but there was one point
where you said I shouldn't
have been in the competition
from the beginning.
- I want to be here with people
that I think are the fiercest
in competition
so that when I win,
I can feel like I had a victory
over people who were
just as strong as me.
And I don't think
you're just as strong as me.
- You barely knew
anything about me,
and those things,
you know, really hurt
when you said that.
- I apologize if they hurt,
I really do.
Did I read?
Absolutely.
Did I talk shit?
But my intention wasn't
to hurt someone's feelings.
This is a sorority
and a fraternity
at the same time.
Part of drag is sitting back
and talking shit.
"Girl, you got that big old wig
on again?"
But did I think
I was more cut out
for the competition
from the outset?
I did think so.
Obviously I was wrong,
because you were winning
before I was.
- Did you find out
anything new about yourself
that you didn't know?
- I did.
I found out that maybe I,
on some level,
I could have been more
of a "lady" like Stacy.
I mean, I could learn a lot
from Stacy.
Sometimes when I answer
people's questions,
it's probably better
to tell them
what they want to hear,
not what I really think.
Because honestly,
at the end of the day,
maybe the high road
would have been to just say,
"Yes, I think
you look beautiful.
Yes, I think you're
my fiercest competition."
Because it really--
the answer either way
wouldn't have mattered
and would have been easier
to stomach.
- Was it a positive experience
for you
or a negative experience?
- There were negative aspects,
but as a whole, it was positive.
I mean, I've been given so much
that was never promised to me.
Nothing was promised to me
from this,
and I've been able to travel.
I mean, I'm 35 years old.
I've never been to New York.
I got to go to New York
and walk red carpets,
and I just have been
afforded so much.
I'm so lucky.
- Stacy Layne, do you think
you're forever changed
from having done this show?
- Oh, Lord, yes, honey.
I've even had marriage proposals
from Africa.
- Oh.
- So I might have to take
myself up on the offer.
- Kamaru.
[laughter]
- Shangela, you're back again.
I can't seem to get rid of ya.
- I'm back, Ru.
I'm back.
- Now, how'd it feel
to be given a second chance?
- You know, I feel like I had
a lot of pressure,
I had a lot to prove,
but I really feel
like I belonged
in this competition,
and I was thrilled to be back.
- Do you feel like
you redeemed yourself?
- Well, hallelu, I hope I did.
- [laughing]
Now, you seem to be one
of the most strategic queens
that have ever been
on RuPaul's Drag Race.
- Well, thank you.
- Do you think it helped you
or hurt you in the end?
- I mean, top five.
I definitely feel
like it helped me.
- Entertainment Weekly reports
that you were just cast
in the new TV show
with Don Johnson.
Tell me about that.
- I recently was cast in a pilot
called A Mann's World.
It's being directed, created,
and written
by Michael Patrick King.
I play a male hairstylist
on the show,
so I'm really excited
about that.
But I'm also excited
about continuing Shangela.
So I'm dual pathing it,
kind of like Beyoncé
and Sasha Fierce.
- Oh, okay.
- Indeed.
- Hey, Carmen.
- Hi, Ru.
- Now, did your stepdaughter
watch the show?
- She did.
- What'd she think?
- Well, I mean, she is--
she's six years old,
so she doesn't
really get the whole,
like, competition.
She wants me to put her in drag.
She wants me to--
you know, she's like,
"I want the same eye shadow
as Carmen,"
and "I want the same lipstick
as Carmen."
She'd ask my husband, like,
"Why is Chris wearing makeup?"
And once you, you know,
answer the question,
it's like she's cool with it.
You know,
she's really smart, so...
- Yeah.
Now, were you surprised
when the judges
brought you back?
- I was.
I was really surprised
and grateful,
more than anything.
- Now, in the music challenge,
Shangela manipulated it
so that you would get reggae.
What do you think about that?
- I don't think so.
Honestly,
when it came down to it,
I was not gonna go
with country, period.
- But, Shangela,
you did have a strategy.
- With us being
the last two left,
I didn't want reggae,
so my strategy
was to make her feel
like I wanted reggae.
I set that up.
Can I have that deal
on the reggae?
I love reggae music,
like, buh, buh, buh.
Ba-da, buh, buh.
- I really like reggae.
So I'm gonna go with reggae.
- Okay.
- If there was a competitive
spirit within her,
where she didn't want me
to have what I wanted--
- Regardless of whatever
Shangela was saying,
I wasn't gonna think
in my mind, "Okay,
"well, she wants reggae,
so I'm gonna pick reggae
so I can mess her up,"
you know what I mean?
That's not the way I think.
You know, competition or not,
I don't purposely try
to sabotage anyone.
If it came down--
let's say if it was me
and, you know,
if I was in the top three,
that's a different story,
you know what I'm saying?
'Cause it's already--
you--fine.
- But how do you get to the top
three without competing?
- No, but you don't have
to throw people under the bus.
You don't have to, you know,
think like that.
You can just be the best.
You can just be the best,
and then you can win.
- Could you just push them
in front of the subway train?
- [laughs]
- No.
- Now, Shangela,
it seems like you have
a different point of view
in terms of strategizing.
Care to elaborate on that?
- Well, I think everyone
has their own--
their own objective
in this competition.
I was here, fighting to win,
because it meant a lot more
than just the check.
It meant security;
it meant being able
to provide for my family
and to pursue my dreams,
'cause that's why
I'm really here.
- Yara Sofia, echa pa'lante.
- Yes.
- Are you feeling
the echa pa'lante
down in Puerto Rico?
- Of course, darling.
- You're still serving it up?
- Yes, I do.
- Yes, darling.
- Very sad
to see your elimination.
- I know.
- You gave up during
the middle of the number.
- I'm crying because there's
a lot of emotions.
I was thinking too much.
I'm so angry,
and I'm so disappointed.
During the competition,
I was, like,
holding in a lot of emotions.
Challenge after challenge
every week,
it's so challenging,
you know what I mean?
I kind of disagrees
with some of the judgment.
The judges, like, sometimes
putting other one on top of me,
like, over.
Like, "Oh, my God,
I love you,
"the way you fart,
the way you fall,
the way you walk,
the way you wear everything."
And then I was like,
"Oh, okay."
I don't think I agreed,
you know what I mean?
- Right.
Who were they praising over you
that made you feel that way?
- Well, it depends.
- Names, darling, I want names.
- Raja.
She's a great makeup artist.
And she could do a better job.
If you choose this kind of drag,
be the best.
- Do you feel that you could
have gone a little bit further?
- Where's further?
- Could you have pushed more,
echa pa'lante?
- Yeah, probably.
But, um, after you--
um, the judges
asked us the question, like,
"Why you deserve to be
the next drag superstar
and win 75 fucking dollars?"
- [laughs]
- Thousand.
- Yeah. [laughs]
It was a lot of pressure.
- Yeah.
- And uh, it--
probably in another moment--
- That's a perfect point,
because it does come down
to how you react in that moment.
- Yes.
- And a lot of this competition
emulates what real life is
in show business,
and sometimes,
it comes down to that moment
where I cannot go on
any further,
but somewhere,
that energy's gotta come.
- It's out of--
it's out of my hands.
- Yeah, I understand.
I understand.
All right.
Let's see what
the top three queens have to say
when RuPaul's Drag Race:
Reunited! continues.
Are you ready
for the final three?
First, let's welcome
a true pageant princess,
honey.
- ♪ Oh ♪
- Alexis Mateo!
- ♪ Sashay, shante ♪
♪ Panther on the runway ♪
- Sickening.
The jig is up.
Bam!
- ♪ All the boys say ♪
- Next,
a multi-talented queen
who's a real thriller.
- ♪ She's so wild,
so animal ♪
- Manila Luzon!
Imelda Marcos!
Big Bird!
Give it.
- ♪ Phenomenon ♪
♪ Glamazon-on-on-on ♪
[drumroll]
- And now, the one queen
who, week after week,
had us gagging
on her charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent,
America's next drag superstar,
- ♪ Gonna love you ♪
- The one, the only Raja.
♪ You're a superstar ♪
- Pose!
Lift!
Tan, tan, tan.
- ♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ You're a superstar ♪
♪ ♪
- Alexis Mateo, honey.
- Hi, Ru.
Bam!
- Bam!
Is your family proud,
how well you did?
- My family has been
very supportive.
My mom became
one of my biggest fans.
It actually helped me
to understand
my family point of view
about the situation,
because I grew up in a very
Catholic, Pentecostal family.
- Ooh, child.
- And now--yes.
We have been mediating
between what was
the homosexuality
and, like, the whole drag
experience in my family.
But now they see me as an actor,
more than just a wannabe woman.
That it was the point
that I really wanted
to put across in my family.
- Yeah.
Now, this was your third
audition for the show.
- Yes.
- Uh, what do you--
how do you think
it would have turned out
had you been chosen
the first go-round?
- Oh, child, if I was chosen
the first season
or the second one,
I probably went home
the first two episodes.
- Really?
- Think about it that way.
- Exactly,
and I would have come back,
in the third one in a box.
[laughter]
- What would you say to queens
who have auditioned
in previous seasons,
like yourself,
and didn't get chosen.
- Keep trying.
When the fire is there
and when you wake up
in the morning,
that's what you want to do,
go for it.
Never, never give up.
- Now in the Life, Liberty,
and Pursuit of Style challenge,
you revealed you had
a relationship
with an active duty marine.
- Papi, I want you
to come back home, baby.
- Have you heard from him
since the show's aired?
- [laughs]
Not at all, Ru.
And I wish him the best.
I already closed that chapter
in my life.
- What would you say
if I told you
we have him backstage
right now?
[laughter]
In drag.
- In drag?
[laughs]
- Can you bring him out now?
- Yes, immediately,
please!
- We are not that kind of show.
We can't afford the airfare.
But we could afford
a DNA result,
and the result is...
[laughter]
Manila Luzon.
- Hi, Ru.
Hey, girls.
- Hey, girlfriend.
- [laughs]
- Now, let's get
into the real story here
that's been
on everybody's mind.
Your characterizations
of Asian-Americans
or just Asians in general
came under a lot of heat.
Have you heard
from groups or people
who say you were wrong
or you were right?
- When the episode
of the news challenge aired...
Klistin, "terr" us,
what's next?
I got a lot
of, um, negative feedback
saying people thought
it was offensive,
but they were always,
like, not Asian.
Comment after comment
left on my Facebook page.
"Um, I'm Asian.
"I didn't find that offensive.
I thought it was hilarious."
It's also the whole thing
of humor.
If it's not kind of--
if it doesn't push any buttons,
it's not funny.
- Now, there were a lot
of emotions
for you on this show.
Uh, your father,
did he get to see the show?
- After I got back home,
I called him up,
I sent him a letter,
and he wrote me back,
and he said,
"Okay, I understand that's--
"this is what you're doing,
but it's still
a little strange for me."
So it was just like
an open discussion
that I'm just trying
to keep, like--
let him, like,
marinate in a while.
- Did your mother
watch the show?
- My mom watches the show,
and she's always
calling me back, like,
"Oh, my God,
Carmen's so pretty."
I'm like,
"Mom, what about me?"
[laughter]
- And, Miss Raja,
how's it feel to be
America's next drag superstar?
- Surreal.
Surreal, abstract.
Sometimes invasive a little bit,
'cause there's a lot of haters
out there,
which is kind of
a new thing for me.
- Now, your win is
actually very controversial,
and, you know,
uh, some people have--
saw you as the fiercest thing
ever to walk a runway,
and other critics have said
you're just a man in a dress.
- You mean her?
I'm just kidding.
- Well, actually,
that was Alexis Mateo's quote.
[laughter]
- If it were said to me
ten years ago
and I was at a different place
in my head and in my life,
I would have been
completely offended,
and I would have told everyone
to fuck off,
but, you know,
now I'm in my early 30s.
- Uhh!
[laughter]
- My mid--mid-30s,
and you know what?
I've just come to a place
in my life
that I don't really mind
embracing the fact
that there's a masculine
and a feminine.
And why not join
the two together
and morph it into
one amazing creature, right?
- Well, it worked
for Bea Arthur.
- Absolutely.
[laughter]
- Now, you kids all have
Twitter and Facebook and all.
Do you read the comments
from the people out there?
- Um, I do,
and I don't.
On Twitter, you're only allowed
a certain amount of characters
to cuss someone out.
And on Facebook, it takes
a little bit more effort
'cause you have
to like the bitch first
and then leave her
a mean comment.
- Well, a lot of people
have said that Raja
was too, uh, experienced
for the competition.
Do you feel that way?
- As far as me being seasoned,
yes, I am seasoned.
And, yes, I have been doing it
a long time.
And, yes,
people do know who I am.
But there was nothing said that
America's next drag superstar
should be a beginner who's never
been known or seen, you know?
- Or maybe she could have been.
- She could have been,
you know?
There's still a long line
and legacy
of RuPaul's Drag Race
still yet to happen,
I hope, you know?
And I think
there's a lot of room
for different styles,
different points of view
in drag and what--
how we perceive
our own personal art.
I think there's still
tons of room for that.
Now I want to talk
about something
that was touched on earlier.
Delta said that
we were like a sorority
and a fraternity mixed together.
And there's a lot of comments
that sometimes backstage,
we are harsh with one another.
But the truth is,
if we were in a locker room,
some of the things
that wives would hear from men--
and we are men--
could be harsh too.
We call it, what's the T?
And the T being the truth.
I want to open the floor
about that.
Now, Raja, you came under
a lot of criticism
because you could be seen
as harsh
with your backstage speak.
- It was like watching
a sports event.
You know, no one wants
to go to the soccer game
and, like, hope that
the two teams love each other.
"Oh, my God.
"I hope he gives the ball
to that guy.
Oh, my God.
I hope that he makes the goal."
Nobody does that.
There's a battle that happens.
Reading is fundamental,
and I think
it's definitely part
of drag culture,
and it's fun.
It's our way of like,
you know,
straight guys
come up to each other,
and they punch each other
on their shoulder.
That's what we're doing.
- To me, I think it's a way
of sharpening your wit
and getting quicker
and thinking quicker,
and you have to be on your game.
And it's like practicing
before a baseball game.
You have to throw
that ball hard,
and you have to do it quick,
and you have to catch it hard
and throw it right back.
- Shangela, do you agree?
- Some of the things that I saw
throughout the season,
just, they didn't sit well
with me,
and I hate to keep even
giving it attention,
but this whole
Heathers/Boogers thing,
that's ridiculous.
But if you want
to put someone down
to build yourself up,
then, you know,
that's what you have
to do for yourself.
I mean, if this is
the face of Booger,
I think it's sickening,
so ta-da.
Hell, minus the lawsuits
and the prostitutes
and the drugs
and the tiger blood,
I'm the Charlie Sheen of drag.
Duh, winning.
- Alexis,
did you feel put down
by being called a Booger?
- No, I think
it was stupid as hell.
It was hilarious to listen
to a person
believing on that
to make herself feel better.
- Honestly, 'cause I heard it,
like, three times today,
you guys were saying, "Oh, well,
we're calling you Boogers
so that we can feel better
about ourselves."
I don't think that's
what it was at all.
- Well, why did you call us
a Booger?
- Because it's not shady.
It's funny.
It's just for fun.
- To you.
- But if you take it
that personal,
that's your insecurity.
- No, baby,
it's not insecurity.
It's clockin' it how it is.
Let's get it real.
If you want to bring it,
let's do it.
- Who else didn't think
that Heathers versus Boogers
was funny or tongue-in-cheek?
- When I first started drag,
I was a Booger down.
You know,
I was a Booger for years.
- Explain what that is.
- Well, a Booger
is just a term that, in drag,
of just being, like, a busted,
like, unpolished mess.
- When you call us Boogers,
you're calling us not polished.
- A mess.
- A mess, a beginner.
- I think what--
what's happening here
is that people are taking
everything so damn literal.
It wasn't a reference point of,
you look physically
like a booger.
It was a state of mind.
And that fact was
that we're grown men.
We know our names
aren't Heather,
even though they're
right here on our necks.
We know that
that's not the case.
And we kept doing it
over and over
because it was
the audacity of that.
The audacity that
this farting Mexican man up here
in a blond wig
is really Heather.
- Why did you call
this particular group of girls
Boogers?
- Because it's extreme,
it's funny,
it's exaggerated,
as much of what drag is.
And it's not that we were being,
you know, literal,
and we're not really
putting you down.
It was just like,
at some point,
the whole idea of Heathers
and Boogers
just kind of dissipated for me
and Heathers just meant
my three little friends
that I felt safe around.
- Who would you consider
the queen of the Boogers?
- Personally, I had my most,
biggest frustrations
with Shangela,
so in my mind,
I think it would be Shangela
'cause that was my, like...
- Nemesis.
- My nemesis at the time.
- Now, Stacy, when I asked
who was offended
by the word "booger,"
you raised your hand.
What's going on?
- Just listening
to the comments,
I just felt like it was
a little bit different
than what I saw in person,
because I felt this nice,
kind people in front of me,
and then to watch it,
the behind the scenes,
and to see what people
"really" thought about me,
it was very difficult for me,
and it took a toll on me.
- What specifically?
I want to know
what specifically?
Who offended you the most?
- Raja, basically, you know,
just saying
that I shouldn't be here anyway,
I shouldn't be here at all.
The whole bullfrogs thing,
it bothered me so much.
- Looking at the episodes,
I'm like,
"Some of the things that I said
were quite harsh," you know?
And I was just kind of
blurting them out
and just being a badass
about it,
but I don't think
I really meant it
to hurt anyone's feelings.
The Heathers
and the Boogers thing
was all meant to be fun
and light,
and it still should be
sort of that,
but it really shouldn't be taken
literal,
and if I could actually
just sort of just squash it
and not really perpetuate it
any further--
I mean, I feel like Stacy
was probably
the most vulnerable
out of the group.
And apparently the things
that were said
have really hurt her,
and if I could just sort of
reach out to you,
and I don't know if it means
anything to you at all,
but I would like to present you
with my Heathers necklace,
which really means a lot to me.
Wait, just hold on.
I want you to have this, so...
- Yay, I'm a Heather.
[laughter]
- I love you.
- Aw!
- Yay.
- That's very nice.
[applause]
That's very nice.
I tell you what,
from this moment on,
there will be no more Heathers;
there will be no more Boogers.
We will all be referred to
as Hoogers.
[laughter]
- Hoogers!
- Queens, get your questions
ready for Michelle Visage,
as RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited!
continues.
Now, this season,
my best squirrel friend,
Michelle Visage,
joined the judges' panel,
and the main stage
will never be the same.
Hey, Michelle.
- Hey, baby.
- [laughs]
Now, this season,
you had a chance
to bring back
one of the eliminated queens,
and you chose
Miss Carmen Carrera.
- I did.
- Now, let me ask
what's on America's mind.
Why?
- Look at her.
No, really--
- Is it because
you're from New Jersey?
- Yes,
that's exactly why, Ru.
- [laughing]
- Repping the Garden State.
No.
Billy Santino and I
felt that--
Delta came up,
Mariah came up.
We were all back and forth,
trying to figure out
who to bring back,
and in the end,
we all agreed unanimously
that Carmen
was fresh on the mind,
fresh on the lips,
and we knew
that she had more tricks
up her sleeve,
or so we thought.
- Now, Alexis, you almost
left the competition
because of comments
that you felt Michelle made
about you.
- Yeah.
I think you're a bitch,
Michelle.
[laughter]
- It's frustrating
'cause we're dealing
with so much pressure,
and, like, I mean, you think
you're killing
the hip-hop moment.
You a little came down,
and she got--
she bring you back in
120 degrees.
She's like,
"You're not giving me hip-hop.
"You're Hannah Montana,
a hooker version
of Hannah Montana."
- This is like Hannah Montana
does hip-hop.
- Hannah Montana?
- Yeah.
- And I was like,
"Really, bitch?"
- Pero una pregunta.
Okay?
Would you rather me
sit there and go,
"Oh, honey,
you're fabulous."
- Like, I'm gonna say it,
and I'm gonna say it one time.
- Okay.
- It's so easy to talk
about a drag queen,
but it's so difficult
to be one.
- Honey, I know.
- It's amazing.
It's amazing.
I mean, for me,
drag is a female illusion,
and to make comments
about a plate
that I just bought
that actually helped me
reach the point
of female illusion is stupid,
because you bought
your titties too.
- Yes, I did, absolutely.
- So it's completely--
it's completely pointless,
because that's what we are.
And then to see that I'm getting
picked in the little details,
where Raja doesn't even
wear titties, is--
- She is tonight.
She's got something going on.
- Yeah, it's complicated.
- Okay, now let me explain
where I was coming from
so you understand.
I think you are
an amazingly talented queen.
I think you're gorgeous.
With all of you,
my job was to help you
get to the next level.
Tonight, your body
looks perfect to me.
Like, I would have no critique
of this, Alexis.
I know I have my issues,
and I try to dress accordingly,
so I kind of hide those flaws.
Why would you do something
that makes you
30 pounds heavier looking
when you don't need to?
That was my only issue.
I'm just here to be as real
as I can be,
minus my boobs.
And you want to rock
a breastplate, that's fine.
I grew up in New York City,
where drag queens don't do that.
So I do get your pageant drag.
I get it.
It's not that I don't get
anybody's drags.
I know regional drags
are different.
But I just wanted to see things
switched up every now and then.
Tonight, you don't have it,
and you look beautiful.
- But I do--wearing--
I'm wearing titties.
- That's fine.
That's different.
- I love my titties,
and I work it out all the time.
- And you should.
- Bam, yes.
- Bam.
- I'm wearing a body pad, so...
[laughter]
- Now, this is an opportunity
for all the girls.
If you have something to say
to Michelle Visage,
now is your time.
- I thought you were mean.
I mean, that eyebrow
just kind of goes up,
and those cheekbones
are all up here.
When God painted
the Michelle doll,
he painted her fiercely,
so I just think you have
that look on your face.
- I was always the girl
at the club
where somebody would come up
and say,
"Why you look like that?
Why don't you smile?"
And I'd be like,
"Why don't you get away?"
- Actually, I just wanted
to commend her.
I did enjoy
the consistent judging,
and it seemed like
she wasn't temperamental,
and then I really did get
a good vibe.
There's a term called
"Stone Cold Carter"
in the ballroom scene,
and it's for those,
the mugs that don't smile.
- Uh-huh.
The judges who--
who don't give any--
- Well, her.
- Uh-huh.
- It's not every judge
had a mug.
- Well, Michelle Visage
is from the ballroom scene.
- Yes, she is,
and I definitely related to her.
- All right, now,
RuPaul's Drag Race fans
are the best fans
in the whole wide worldwide net.
- [laughs]
[snaps]
- So here's some questions
that you've shemail, tweeted,
or posted on our
Face-face-facebook fan page.
The first question is
from David in New Hampshire,
and it is for Mimi Imfurst.
Why do you always look
so scared?
[laughter]
[person speaks indistinctly]
- I don't know.
Do I look--
do I look so scared
all the time?
- She's painted that way.
- I'm surprised.
I think it--
probably it relates back
to during the competition.
I think I definitely had
a lot of insecurities.
- Did the competition scare you?
- I scared--
I think I scared myself
more than anything.
I--I got lost in my own world
of not trusting
that I have good ideas,
and I let it be my demise.
- All right, this next question
is for India Farrah
from Anonymous
in northwest Indiana.
Says, "I'm a 13-year-old
aspiring drag queen.
What is your biggest piece
of advice you could give?"
- Oh, wow.
- You started at 12.
- Yes, I started
at the age of 12.
- So basically you were
the Miley Cyrus of drag.
[laughter]
- Absolutely.
Luckily my brother
is gay as well,
so it was kind of easier,
and with my family
being so supportive,
that was really easy
for me to do it.
So try to feel comfortable
in your own skin.
Don't pay attention to, like,
the negative, like, comments,
the bullshit.
Let it go in one ear
and out the other.
- All right, next we have
a question for Shangela.
It's from Kayla G.
who wants to know,
"While watching the show,
did you ever get sick
of hearing yourself
say hallelu?"
[laughter]
- Actually no, because I like
to say, "I live in the lu,"
because "hallelu" is more
than just a word to me.
It's kind of the way
that I live.
It's joyous.
- It's an attitude.
- It's happy.
It's an attitude.
It's a way of life...
- Yeah, it's a way of life.
- To me, hallelu.
- Okay. Right on, right on.
Joseph G. in Los Angeles
asks,
"Carmen, have you seen J. Lo
since the taping?"
- So I've been around
Jennifer Lopez in person,
I mean, movie sets, concerts,
like...
I went to her birthday party
impersonating her.
Like, Marc asked me to come,
whatever.
No.
Mm-mm.
I usually get to see her
when she's, like, on tour
or when she's doing, like,
a movie.
If she's filming a movie,
it's like...
I can be with her
for, like, a week
because she's
at the same location.
Like, you know what I mean?
But I haven't seen her.
I'll see you soon, Jennifer.
We're gonna do a video together,
and we'll put it out there
and post it on Facebook
to clear all the rumors.
- Gorge.
All right.
Now, the next question
is for Raja,
and it is from Tommy
in Salt Lake.
"Have you heard from Tyra Banks
since your parody of her
on the Snatch Game?"
Girl, I saw you smiling
with your eyes.
What do they call that?
- Smissing.
- [laughs]
Tyra,
is there anything going on
that you want
to tell us about?
- What?
- Are you smissing too hard?
- I think I smissed so hard,
my eyes bled, girl.
- Oh, my goodness!
- Mm-mm.
Nope, haven't heard from her
at all.
But, you know, I do hear
from Miss J all the time.
He's like, "Walk back,
you fucking crazy...
blah, blah, blah,"
just all through texts.
Tyra did tweet me,
but that was when the season
first started.
- Okay.
- When the season--
She hadn't seen me
do her parody yet.
- Ooh.
- Hope she has a sense of humor.
- She does.
I know Tyra well enough,
even though we're not
the bestest friends
by any means,
but I do know her well enough
that she would have
a great sense of humor about it.
And, you know, she's funny.
She's crazy just like us.
She's a big ol' drag queen,
so she gets it...
I hope.
- [laughs]
- Now, Yara, I do have
a question for you.
It's from Michael H.
in Los Angeles.
"What did
your little person friend
think of Yara Sofia?"
- He love it.
You know what?
I haven't received,
like, a bad comment
or a bad feedback
about the little person
performance.
- Good. good.
It's been a year of
unprecedented twists and turns,
and if I could live
this season all over again,
I wouldn't change a thing.
Now, to those of you
out there watching,
don't fuck it up.
Continue to support my girls
live and in person,
on Facebook, Twitter,
and wherever fine sequins
are sold.
Now, here to announce the winner
of Miss Congeniality,
as voted by you,
the superfans,
welcome back Santino
and Billy B.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah.
- ♪ She's so wild ♪
- Whoo!
- ♪ So animal ♪
- Mwah, mwah.
- My darling, mwah, mwah.
Lovely.
So, Santino,
what do you got for us here?
- All season long...
- Yeah?
- We've expressed our opinions,
and now it's time
for the viewers
to have their say.
- Thousands of fans voted.
- Well...
- And we have a winner.
- And we have a winner?
- We have a winner.
- OMG.
The one queen
America loves to like is...
[drum beating]
Yara Sofia.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Gonna love you ♪
- Oh, my God.
- ♪ You're a superstar ♪
- Yara Sofia,
you are Miss Congeniality.
Here is your sash.
[applause]
- Work, mami.
- Condragulations, mami.
- Thank you.
both: Mwah, mwah.
- Yara, you've won a trip
for two
to the luxury Our Lucaya Resort
on Grand Bahama Island.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah, baby.
- Courtesy
of AlandChuck.travel,
America's number one
gay vacation specialist.
And lucky for you,
you only have one island
over from where you live.
[laughter]
You could swim there.
Yara, what do you have to say
to your fans?
- I love you all.
Thank you, thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you,
thank you.
Mwah.
Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
- Now to all you future
drag superstars out there,
if you want to compete
next season,
go to our Facebook fan page
for information.
And for all the T
on the new season
of RuPaul's Drag U,
premiering June 20th,
check out Facebook
and logotv.com.
And if you still
can't get enough,
follow me on Twitter,
and we will become
lifelong friends.
Hashtag, friends forever.
And from the bottom of my heart,
I want to thank my queens,
my judges,
and especially you
for making RuPaul's Drag Race
the craziest damn show
on television.
Now remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen!
- All right, ladies,
the time has come
for you to lip-synch
for your lives
to my new single, Glamazon,
available where?
all: On iTunes, bitch.
- [laughs]
Let the music play!
- ♪ She's so wild,
so animal ♪
♪ She's gonna work
that sexy body so sexual ♪
♪ She's like a female
phenomenon ♪
♪ She's a glamazon ♪
♪ Female phenomenon ♪
♪ A glamazon-on-on-on ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Sashay, shante ♪
♪ Panther on the runway ♪
♪ Do it, do it, oh ♪
♪ All the girls say ♪
♪ Sashay, shante ♪
♪ Panther on the runway ♪
♪ Do it, do it, oh ♪
♪ All the boys say ♪
♪ She's so wild,
so animal ♪
♪ She's gonna work
that sexy body so sexual ♪
♪ She's like a female
phenomenon ♪
♪ She's a glamazon ♪
♪ Female phenomenon ♪
♪ A glamazon-on-on-on ♪
♪ She's so wild,
so animal ♪
♪ She's gonna work
that sexy body so sexual ♪
♪ She's like a... ♪