- Previously on RuPaul's
Drag Race...
Snatch game!
- Yay!
- Okay.
- Hi, how are you?
- Ooh, ooh!
- Naomi Campbell is
a cum-guzzling whore!
- Hold up.
- Yeah, baby.
- Mm-hmm.
- Stacy.
- Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
- To see Stacy win,
and I'm in the bottom two?
W.T.F.?
- Delta Work.
Shantay, you stay.
This is the emancipation
of Mariah.
Now sashay away.
And tonight...
It's time to bare your souls.
The queens have their cake...
- Aw, thanks.
- And eat it too.
- I took a bite of it
and I swallowed.
- Oh, dear.
With extra special
guest judges,
Sara Rue and Eliza Dushku.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag
Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut,
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win!
- Morning.
- We're walking
into the workroom today.
And the whole entire room
is empty.
And at this point,
we're eight left,
and I need to step up my game.
- There's a message.
Aww.
- Cheers to Mariah.
- Mariah!
- Mug for days.
- I'm gonna erase it.
- The more people leave,
the happier I'll be.
It's just less noise in my ear.
I'm just an old granny,
and I just can't handle all
the yip-yap, chitter-chatter.
- So are you excited you won?
- I am.
Pulled that shit out
at the last minute, girl.
- I actually, like,
wasn't expecting it.
I don't know if Stacy's amazing
job last week was a fluke.
She's like the underdog that
people aren't paying
attention to.
- I'm proud of myself because,
you know, I had doubted myself
a few days ago.
There's people
in this competition
who feel like I'm not talented.
But I feel confident now.
So, you know, fuck these
other bitches, honey.
I feel like I'm gonna win
this shit.
- Heather.
- Heather wants to talk to us.
- Come hither, Heather.
- Heather, what are you making?
- I'm making my skirt, Heather.
Carmen, Manila, Delta and myself
have decided to call each
other "Heather."
Because we formed this clique
which looks a lot
like the movie Heathers.
- We're basically
the pretty girls,
the top four.
And then there's
the other girls.
- Ooh, she left--
what did she leave?
Earrings, these are cute.
- We take a lot of pride
in what we do.
And, um, I think that's where
we find a common ground.
So, so be it.
We're Heathers.
[laughter]
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl!
You've got shemail.
Hey, ladies.
all: Hey.
- I've got a little secret
I want to share with you.
I like cake.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
- Big, German chocolate cake.
- Ooh.
- If I could, I'd have a hot
cake in my mouth
first thing every morning.
- Me too.
- If you love cock the way
I do, just be careful.
Don't bite off more
than you can chew.
all: Oh, my God.
- I don't want
to eat anything crazy.
- It's cake.
- Oh, it's not cock?
- [laughing]
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi!
- My girls.
Now, a drag superstar needs
to be able to serve womana,
even when she's stripped of her
wigs and padding and things
of that nature.
Now, I posed undraped
for a photograph in my book,
Working It.
And I did it without
compromising my Christianity.
I found the experience
so liberating,
I wanted to share it with you.
- Thank you.
- Now, for today's
mini-challenge,
you'll be posing for a tasteful,
intimate, feminine portrait.
And you'll be doing it
in the nude.
- Oh!
- Ooh!
- My heart just drops.
You know, I don't even like
to have sex naked.
- Now, in a moment you'll meet
celebrity photographer
Deborah Anderson,
who's renowned for
her artful nude portraits.
You have ten minutes to prepare.
You may use light makeup,
then it's time
to bare your souls.
Bye.
Let the games begin.
- Are you fucking serious?
My fat ass has got to take off
these clothes?
Y'all bitches is crazy.
- Oh, Jesus, take the wheel.
I just really don't want
to do this.
I have been single for a reason,
and now America is going
to find out why.
- Where is my bathrobe?
Oh, shit.
- Hi, Stacy.
This is Deborah.
- I have a piece of fabric
that you can use a little.
There's no pressure;
you do whatever feels
most comfortable to you.
- Let's get naked.
- Serving womana.
- All of a sudden I had
this spiritual awakening
that happened to me.
And I fell into it.
- Ooh, fabulous, fabulous.
Let's discuss the socks.
- Oh, right.
Gotta have these off.
- [laughing]
There you go, perfect.
Beautiful.
- You cannot knock the modeling
powers of Raja.
Put me in front of a camera,
and I will pose you down.
- Beautiful, right there.
There you go, there you go.
Beautiful.
Careful now,
not too much backside.
- Too much ass.
- I can't see anything.
- Yeah.
I wonder if you straighten
that top leg.
- There you go, there you go.
There.
- Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
A work of art.
- Bring that leg up, bring
that--beautiful, right there.
Gorgeous.
Beautiful.
Fabulous.
That body?
You kidding me?
Keep moving that face,
my darling.
It's like we've got
the same face in every frame.
I want choice, darling.
- Okay, I can do that.
- Otherwise, we're stuck
with one picture.
Love.
Just watch where your light is.
- You feel like you're
a little tentative here.
- It's horrible, the feeling
is just horrible.
I just want it to be over.
- Alexis, Alexis.
Look at me.
You're not there.
All I see is your nervousness.
Focus, focus.
Give me drama, okay?
We want the confidence,
we want the beauty.
And find that light.
- Ooh, loving that.
Loving, loving.
Hi, Delta.
- Hi, how are you?
I'm so scared.
All I can think is
that this lady's
gonna freakin' laugh at me.
Deborah, nice to meet you.
- Oh, the joy.
I get a kiss, I love that.
- But I realize, this is it.
If I want to be the next drag
superstar, I have to do it
at all costs.
- If you indeed want to use it.
- I want to use every yard
of it.
[both laughing]
- Yeah, feel that light.
- There we go, there we go.
Beautiful.
Yes, loving that.
Loving that.
- Gorgeous.
A new dawn for Delta.
- And darling, we are done.
- Oh, cool.
- Awesome.
- [laughing]
- My biggest fear was met today.
I met it head-on.
I felt so liberated.
I would love to do it again.
- We won't be able to get you
to put clothes on anymore.
- No, I don't think so.
Carmen Carrera better watch out.
- [laughing]
Ladies, all I can say is
you give good flesh.
But one of your nude portraits
stood head and shoulders
above the rest.
Carmen Carrera.
- Thank you.
[applause]
Yay, I won.
Piece of cake.
- Now that we've all gagged on
Carmen's cheesecake photo,
I hope you've left room
for dessert.
For this week's main challenge,
each of you will be designing a
couture designer dress inspired
by one of these mouth-watering
cakes.
There's angel food,
red velvet, pineapple upside
down, chocolate lava,
cheesecake, princess cake,
carrot cake,
and my favorite,
strawberry shortcake.
[giggles]
Now, Carmen.
Because you won
the mini-challenge,
you will assign each queen
a cake.
I'm gonna start off
with this cheesecake.
- Aw.
- Thank you.
Carmen's gonna give me the one
with the boring colors.
I knew exactly
what she was doing.
- We'll go with
the pineapple upside down.
- One of my favorites.
- Mm...
We'll give it to Shangela.
- Aw, thanks.
Would you be happy with
a pineapple upside down cake?
- Who's got some shortcakes
here?
Yara.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Red velvet.
Mmm.
Stacy.
- My favorite.
- Angel food cake is next.
For the cool kids, I want to
make sure that they're taken
care of.
Delta Work.
- Aw.
- Carrot cake, Manila.
- Oh, yay!
- Chocolate lava,
that leaves one person.
- Thank you.
- And that leaves the princess
cake for the princess herself.
- Princess cake is the prettiest
one, so it's mine.
- Now to create
your perfect face, face,
face of cakes outfit,
you can use materials provided
by Michael Levine fabrics.
Your couture confection should
look good enough to eat.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
See you later.
- Whoo!
Got a cake, got a cake.
Got a cake, cake, cake.
- I kind of need to be inspired
by my cake.
I need to taste it first.
Mm.
I'm getting an idea.
There's nothing I love more
than chocolate.
I could drip it
all over my naked,
lithe body over and over again
and just lick it off myself.
- Is anyone nervous?
Shangela?
- Evil bitch.
- Ha.
- The sewing challenges
in this competition
continue to be my downfall.
- When you put this together,
they create these barriers.
- Oh!
But what about the bottom?
- The fabric is not enough.
- Oh, no.
- No, this is the front.
This is just the front.
And where's the back?
You know what I mean?
- Right.
Now the question is, am I going
to fall in the hole,
or am I going to be able
to jump over that hole?
- So, Shangela,
what are you making?
- A dress.
Today's challenge is that we
have to create a high-fashion
couture outfit,
based on the type of cake
that we were assigned.
There are tons of girls left in
this competition that sew.
And here I am, still over there
trying to get the one-two
stitch down.
- Cuteness.
Heather, can you help me?
- Yes, Heather.
- I think it's hilarious we're
calling each other Heather now.
- Well, I mean, aren't we?
Those are our names.
- Like, didn't they all kill
each other?
- Well, yeah.
Only one Heather stands.
Right, Manila?
- Hello, my sweets.
all: Hi, Ru!
- Can I borrow a cup of sugar?
- Sure, darling.
- How you doing?
- I'm good, how are you?
- This cake is almost all gone.
- Well, not really.
It's just a few slices.
Part of the description
of this competition
was to do cake couture.
- Mm-hmm.
- You understand
what couture is?
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Pretty much.
- Yeah.
- One-of-a-kind,
special details.
- Honestly, I'm not a
high-fashion kind of drag queen.
So I think that's one of the
biggest obstacles I have
to overcome.
- All right,
I want to see fashion.
So I will see you
on the main stage.
- All right. Thanks, Ru.
- All right.
Hey, Manila.
- Hi.
- So tell me about
your carrot cake couture dress.
- I'm kind of drawing from
Givenchy meets Jessica Rabbit
meets Playboy bunny.
- Oh, that's a lot of ideas
going on there.
Are you sure you can incorporate
all of this?
- Well, I'm gonna try.
- Okay.
I can't wait to see it.
- Thank you.
- I'll see you later.
- Hey, Alexis.
- Hi, Ru.
- Now, of course this outfit
looks like cheesecake.
- I'm going for it.
- You're gonna go for it.
- That's the idea.
- Now, how are you gonna make
this more high-fashion couture?
- I will work with the style
of it.
It's not going to be
evening-gown Cinderella.
It's just gonna be
a high-fashion model.
- All right, kiddo.
I'm gonna let you get back
to work.
- Yes, thank you for visiting
me, Ru.
- All right, kiddo.
Yara Sofia.
- Yes.
- You're doing the strawberry
shortcake.
- Yes.
- Now, you sew for a living.
- I love to sew, I love it.
I'm gonna give the judges
a couture high-fashion dress,
but well-done.
I'm a strong, wicked bitch.
- All right, kiddo.
- Bye.
Raja.
- Hi, Ru.
- Chocolate lava cake.
- Hold me, Ru.
- [laughing]
- I took a bite of it,
and I swallowed.
- Oh, dear.
Oh, my goodness.
- I swallowed it.
I'm a terrible model.
- But you had to bite it to get
your inspiration, right?
- Sure, sure.
- I've always been really
obsessed with different, like,
historical silhouettes.
So I just happened to have
these, like, French peignoirs,
and I was, like, maybe I can
kind of play with that with,
like, a little bit of an exotic,
Indian, spicy kind of thing.
- All right, get back to work.
- Okay, see you later.
- All right.
Delta Work.
- Hi, Ru.
- Angel food cake.
- Yes.
- Are you a fan?
- I am.
Of all the cakes
that you could go get,
it's the lowest in fat.
So I can eat the most of it.
- [laughing]
- I think I need to bring
something youthful.
- Yeah.
- And I think I need
to bring something fresh.
Because the characters that I've
been doing have always been
older than who I am.
- Right.
I think it's about making
something that's contemporary.
I know that that's what
the judges are looking for.
- I like that.
- Yeah.
I look forward to seeing
some fresh cake on the runway.
- I'm excited.
- All right, go for it.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Carmen.
- Hey, hey.
- Why did you choose
a princess cake?
- 'Cause I was just drawn
to the color.
- This is, like,
green and pink and white.
- But you're going
with just the pink here.
It's the Barbie interpretation
of a princess, isn't it?
- When I hear Barbie from Ru,
I'm like, "This is wrong."
I'm not trying
to be princess Barbie.
- Well, listen, I'm gonna let
you get back to creating
your Jersey couture.
- My Jersey couture, yes.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- All right.
Hey, Miss Shangela.
- Hi, Ru.
- How you doing?
- [deep breath]
I'm okay.
- On season two,
you had problems sewing.
- Yes.
- And it's what ultimately
got you eliminated.
How's it going this time?
- I don't know.
You know--
- You're nervous.
- I am.
- Has anyone offered to help you
out at all?
No?
Do you feel like the other girls
are not supporting you?
- I know this is a competition,
and everyone's out
for themselves.
- But you have helped
other girls.
Do you expect them to help you?
- I would--I would like that.
- Well, I think it starts
with you asking.
- What?
Seriously?
Like, Ru has been asking,
"Has anyone helped you today?"
And, bitch, she's made
the other girls her puppets.
- It's sometimes hard for me
to ask for help.
- Well--
- But I will, I will.
- Get in there
and make this happen.
Okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
Gather around, ladies.
Every time I watch one of those
cake decorating shows,
I say to myself,
"My queens could do a better job
in their sleep."
So in addition to finishing
your cake couture dresses,
you need to turn a real cake
into the ultimate edible
accessory.
- We have no time to make
these fucking dresses,
and now we gotta make a cake.
I don't want to see no more
motherfucking cake!
- Starting with a naked cake
and a look-alike doll,
the icing on the cake will be
your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
The end result should look
a little something like this.
You'll be debuting your
cake-stravaganza ensemble
tomorrow on the main stage.
And our guest judges will be two
sweet and stylish actresses.
The ever popular Sara Rue.
- Oh, my gosh!
- Ooh!
- And Eliza Dushku.
all: Ooh!
- Ladies, good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
All right,
I'll see you tomorrow.
all: Bye, Ru.
- Oh!
- I need to figure out
how the frick
I'm gonna decorate a cake.
- Now I got a cake to do too?
- I feel sick.
- This is gonna be a challenge
that we're gonna remember.
We have to not only create an
outfit for the runway look,
we have to create a cake that
represents who we are.
I don't even cook nothing
at home.
- Here we have our guest chef
from North Carolina.
What are you doing, girl?
- Uh, first I'm gonna ice
this motherfucker.
- Oh, really?
Ooh.
- You got to whip it good.
- Whippin' it, whippin' it,
whippin' it.
- No, no, whippin' is like this.
- No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm the chef.
- [laughing]
- Ew, that's not me.
That's some booger.
Who the fuck is that?
Yara's is beautiful.
- Yes, Yara, yours is hot.
Bitch, they retouched hers.
- Word of advice, do not leave
your cakes out in the rain.
- [laughing]
- Look at my Native American
[indistinct].
- What tribe are you from?
I don't really know.
- Lumbee Indian.
This is the traditional pinecone
circle.
- What's on the arm?
- Fancied-out shawl.
Being the only Native American
in this competition,
I thought it would be different,
you know,
not just to decorate the cake
in my own style,
but, you know,
to represent my heritage.
- I offered Shangela to help her
with her garment,
because, for me,
it's nice to see
that somebody actually takes
advice and trusts you.
Because in a competition
like this one,
it does tell me a lot
about Shangela.
It amazes me how you trust me.
- Yeah.
- When you know I don't know
what the hell I'm doing.
- Oh, that's great.
That makes me feel real good
right about now.
Oh, I go on the outside
of your stitch?
- Even if you're going on top
of it, it doesn't matter.
You're just going to reinforce.
- It's okay,
I'm just reinforcing it.
Okay, cool.
Ooh.
Oh, crazy.
Oh, come on.
Work with mama, work with mama.
- Shangela gets the most
of her help from Alexis.
She gets makeup help,
now she's getting sewing help.
And if Alexis would have left
last challenge,
then maybe Shangela would have
just been sitting there,
confused.
- This machine,
this bitch's name is Bertha.
Work, Bertha!
Oh, fuck.
- Ugh, annoying.
- Now you know.
- Hey, Raja.
What does your family think
about you getting in drag
and stuff?
- Oh, they like it.
They know that I enjoy doing it.
So...
- That's all that matters, huh?
- Yeah, that's it.
What about you?
- My mom was, like,
really cool about it.
- And what about your dad,
where's he at?
- My father passed away
when I was two, in the '80s.
- Oh, babe.
- I met his family, like,
a year ago.
- Really?
- I didn't know them.
I didn't have any type
of relationship with them.
But, yeah,
it's just really weird.
Like, I'm trying to, like, find
out little by little as much
as I can about him.
Growing up, I had my mom,
I had my grandmother.
And it was enough for me.
But I always wondered, how would
my personality have changed,
having my father in my life?
But I'm very happy
for who I am now.
- What was the reaction,like,
when you met your dad's family?
- I wasn't going to keep it from
them that I was gay.
They kind of gagged
a little bit.
So after that shocker,
I was like,
"Oh, and I do drag
on top of that."
- Oh, awesome.
- And then they gagged again.
And after that,
everything's cool.
- Manila, ven aqui.
- Yes, mama.
How can I help you?
- When you won your challenge,
did you feel a little bit of
extra pressure after winning?
- Oh, for sure.
No, they're looking at you
even harder.
- Judging, and--
- 'Cause you were, like, you
were the best of the best.
And, like,
once you're at the top...
- Mm-hmm.
- The only way to go is down.
So, like, you have to prove it
to everyone.
And be, like, I'm gonna be
on the top again.
- I'm just trying to figure out
couture,
'cause I don't wear couture.
I don't know.
I felt very confident
at the beginning.
You know, Ru comes over.
And I went from maybe
a nine to, like, a three
in, like, ten minutes.
So I don't know
what to do anymore.
I mean, what do I do?
- What is this?
They're, like, strawberries?
- No, I don't know what the fuck
that was, girl.
I just designed it.
It doesn't even look couture.
- Huh?
- How would it look in here?
- Uh, like a football player.
- I don't know;
it was just an idea.
- I mean, I like
the asymmetrical look of it.
Yeah, do, like, one side.
Make it asymmetrical.
That's always more couture.
But I ain't gonna tell you how
to design your damn thing.
- [laughing]
- 'Cause, honey,
I'm gonna win this one.
Check.
- Okay.
[alarm clock ringing]
- Oh, my God.
- Ooh la la!
- Look at the mess.
- Look at this mess.
- Cake time.
- We're back in the workroom
this morning.
We have to decorate the cake.
And we have to finish our
costumes for today's runway.
- So this morning, I'm looking
at my sequined dress.
And I'm, like,
"Listen, these judges are gonna
read me down."
This dress isn't my style
of cake.
- Hey, Carmen.
- What are you doing?
What do you think
about the dress?
Tell me.
- About my dress?
- Yes.
- I found some really nice green
fabric today, thank God.
And I just whipped something up
real quick.
- Oh, so you sew.
- Well, I guess I do now.
- Yeah!
[laughing]
- Let me do your braid.
Oh, here you have...
It's pretty?
- Yeah, it's pretty.
Maybe, can we start it higher?
- Yes, it could be.
- Yara was helping Shangela
style her wig.
Yet again, help.
She needs a lot of help.
- She's like fucking doing
her hair.
- I know.
- It just really upsets me.
I'm representing myself here,
not the work of other people.
- Bless her helpless
little heart.
- For today's main challenge,
we actually have to design
a high-fashion cake look.
And we actually have
to decorate a cake.
- Oh, I've always wanted to put
safety pins on a child's cake.
- Oh, well.
Hallelu.
Can I make a suggestion,
just an artistic one?
- Yeah, most definitely.
- Just bring the corn up higher.
Right now it looks like corn
straight out of the can.
- Is that a read?
I didn't say anything about
that graffiti mess
that she had going on
on her cake.
- Ooh, work.
- But I decided
to take her advice
and add a couple more kernels.
Hallelu.
- What a beautiful corn
you've made.
- Yeah.
- Shangela.
- I need iridescent.
- Yara, do you think it's cute?
It looks like a cheesecake.
- Ooh, Alexis' costume.
She might be in trouble.
I mean, there's nothing more
unflattering
than to, you know, strap
a blanket around your waist.
- I'm freaking out.
I still have a lot
of finishing touches
on my runway look.
I really don't know how
I'm gonna finish this cake
and finish my outfit
before the runway time.
- Raja.
- What--
Oh!
- Is there any way to get
a little bit more height here?
- Let me see, Stacy.
- Not with these.
- [laughing]
I was about to say.
- It looks like comfy couture.
Stacy's couture,
runway worthy outfit,
inspired by tights.
Hmm... bold move.
- I have the colors,
I have the white shoes.
I have capris.
I feel like it's couture.
[laughter]
- Hello!
- Hey!
- Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
- RuPaul!
- Billy B.
Why, you old geezer.
- I'm hungry.
- Sara Rue.
- Hello.
- Love the name.
- Ooh, yeah.
I love yours.
- Eliza Dushku.
- That's right.
- Welcome to my dollhouse.
- I'm Susie stalker fan
right now.
I love you, Ru.
- Security.
- [laughing]
- This week,
we challenged our queens
to create cake-inspired
couture dresses
and then to decorate a doll cake
that expresses
their true drag persona.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Yara Sofia, serving
strawberry shortcake.
- Look at those stems.
- Uh-huh.
- Ooh.
- I'm bringing a Puerto Rican
strawberry shortcake.
- Now, I see her berries.
But where's her twig?
- It's hiding in the vine.
- Serving carrot cake, Manila.
Ooh, as a blonde.
- What up, doc?
- Where's she hiding
that carrot?
- I have my Madonna Louis
Vuitton rabbit ears.
I got my cute little
Samantha Jones belt on.
And I'm just going to pump down
that runway
like a starving model.
- Trix are not for kids
with this one.
- Mm.
- That's right.
Alexis Mateo,
serving cheesecake.
- She's a high-end cheesecake.
- I'm going down the runway,
and I'm feeling high-fashion.
I just want to serve drama
at this point.
- Designer cheesecake.
- A little bit
Bed, Bath &amp; Beyond.
- [laughing]
- That's there, too.
Princess cake,
from Carmen Carrera.
- Of course.
- I'm serving something
really different:
a different hairstyle.
I have the shaved side thing,
that, like, Cassie, and other
celebrities are doing.
- Paris Hilton.
- Paris Hilton, that's right.
- Heatherette.
- Yes.
- Oh, here's one hot piece
of cake.
- Mm-hmm.
- Red velvet cake.
From Stacy Layne Bryant Matthews
Lattisaw.
- I have my puffiness going on.
I have my white
and my red velvet.
I know I look delicious, honey.
- This would make me get
off my diet.
- Shangela,
pineapple upside down cake.
- It's like Barbra Streisand
meets pineapple cake
with a touch of Rapunzel.
- I'm serving "pineapple upside
down keep turnin' me" cake.
I'm serving cake
on my shoulder,
and I'm definitely serving
cakes in the rear.
- She's all pretty
with a cherry on top.
- Always gotta have the cherry.
It's the first thing to go.
- Yes, it is.
Delta Work,
angel food cake!
- [gasps] Look, it's the teen
angel food cake.
- It is teen angel.
- I hit the stage today, and
I think it's undeniable that
I'm doing angel food cake.
I feel confident.
I know that there's no way
that I can land in the bottom.
- Heaven must be missing
an angel food cake.
- Uh-huh.
Peggy Lee stole it.
- That is Raja,
serving chocolate lava cake.
- I step out onto the runway,
and I am completely aware that
there's a possibility
of my undergarment showing.
But the rest of it
is pretty awesome.
And so what if a little bit
is showing underneath.
- It's bubbling lava, honey.
You need a 12-step program
to deal with that lava.
- And a glass of milk.
- Ooh!
- Welcome, ladies.
It's time
for the judges' critique.
Yara Sofia.
Tell us about your doll cake.
- This is mini-me.
She's wearing a national costume
with the Puerto Rican flag.
- Echa pa'lante!
- Yes!
- Now let's hear
from our judges.
- Did you have a run-in with
the police this morning?
Because someone beat the hell
out of your face.
- Thank you, thank you.
- I love the dress.
I knew instantly you were
strawberry shortcake.
- When you're wearing white,
wearing a darker undergarment
might not be the best.
Just 'cause it pulled me out
of the fantasy.
- Sara, a little inside
information.
There's a lot more than
a dark underwear going on
underneath there.
- [laughing]
- Let's move on to Stacy Layne
Bryant Matthews Lattisaw Q.
- As everybody knows,
I'm Native American.
I actually decorated
in a traditional regalia
for a female.
- You definitely pulled off
the red velvet.
And it made me hungry.
- Would you like to taste?
- You and I have this thing.
You know I do.
- [laughing]
- It's too simple.
- All of the interest
is up here.
It sort of looks like you had
a skid and have a strawberry
and then some glitter got in it.
- The outfit's not couture
in my eyes.
- All right.
Up next, it's Manila.
- This is little baby Manila,
and she took a little trip down
to Chinatown,
and she got a whole buttload
of fake designer purses
shoved up underneath this dress.
- When you first came out,
the belt, I loved it.
And then I hated it.
And then I loved it.
- Yeah, and you know.
Loving something and hating
something
at the same time
is very couture.
I mean, you've got
a lot going on.
- Yeah.
- Right, right.
- Your makeup here looks like
that you had an accident with
the flour when you
were making the cake.
- Next up, Alexis Mateo.
Now tell me
about your doll cake.
- It screams Latina.
It screams passionate.
This doll is actually who I am.
Just in a cake.
- One thing that I think
about the skirt.
It's not particularly
flattering.
You have to admit.
I mean, there are bedspreads
made out of that.
- We girls are trying
to maintain a figure.
And, to me, that adds
unnecessary bulk.
- What is the material that you
used to wrap around your hair?
- It's just fabric.
- I feel like if you're gonna do
that,
like, really show that fabric
and make it precise,
so that it's really sleek.
- Is it plain?
Yes, but maybe that's how you
wanted to represent yourself.
- Up next, Raja.
- I wanted it to feel really
edgy and very straight
and punk and fun.
Sort of like me.
- You reminded me how much
I love chocolate.
For sure.
- Your makeup went a little bit
more spooky
than I think you meant for it.
It's too Goth, I think.
- I wanted to yell out when you
were walking, like,
"Oh, no, honey!
We see your white bloomers."
- I know.
- Now, Sara.
- Yes, Ru.
- Would you put that cake
in your mouth?
- No, I would rub it
all over my body.
- [laughing]
- I think that cake's amazing.
- All right.
Carmen Carrera.
- Thinking about my cake,
I just wanted to put a lot
of that, like, queen,
like, pageant girl,
that I have in me.
I just wanted it to be pretty
and sparkly.
- And you're very diamond
princess, like Trina.
And how'd you go from turning
your dress from pink to green?
- When me and you had spoke,
the minute you mentioned Barbie,
I was like, "I don't want to be
Barbie princess on the runway."
- The dress and the belt, and
I think your hair and all of
that--I'm not sure how it
becomes a princess,
except maybe the princess
of New Jersey.
- Being a Jersey girl,
I'm very proud to say
that you look
like the princess of New Jersey.
But here's the thing.
You're way sexier
than that doll.
You should have done her sexier.
- Can we just talk
about from the neck up?
This sort of, like, mohawk off
to the side
with those jewels,
it's gorgeous.
- Next up, Delta Work.
- I really like
what I'm wearing.
I thought I would sort of do
an inspiration of that
in, like, a little ball gown.
So I made sure that I had,
like, pearls.
And then there's rosettes on
here that mimic the rosettes
that are at the bottom--
- Oh, yes.
- Trim of, um, here.
- Delta, I loved
your look tonight.
I think it's glorious.
- Thank you so much.
- And your cake is on fire.
- It reminds me of that scene
in Grease,
where she's a beauty-school
dropout.
- Oh, yes!
- Frenchie.
- It just, like--yeah!
I just think it's great.
It made me happy
when you walked out.
I was, like, "Oh!"
- Up next, Shangela.
- The doll cake
is very Shangela.
Of course, corn has always
haunted me and I've embraced it.
As you can see,
the Shangela has a hand up.
She's saying hallelu.
- The dress, it's cute.
It didn't totally blow me away.
But I mean,
it makes sense for your cake.
- With the makeup, something
is freaking me out today.
You're much friendlier
and prettier of a person
than the way you're painted.
- All right, this is my question
for you, Shangela.
- Yes.
- All these queens
that I see in front of me,
I can tell that being a queen
is their life.
I question that about you.
Is being a drag queen
what you really want to do?
- Yes.
You know, some people have 20
years doing drag,
and I only have
a little over one.
- Understood.
- But I'm here
because I want to be here.
And I'm here because I want
to be the Next Drag Superstar.
100%.
- Okay.
- Shangela, one last question.
- Yes.
- Who do you think should go
home tonight?
- Carmen Carrera.
- Clearly I have to disagree
with Shangela.
I mean, I think that my outfit
is a little bit more
high-fashion than hers.
- I'll present the
same question to Stacy.
- Carmen.
There's high-fashion looks here,
but just don't feel
like she executed that.
- Same question.
Delta Work.
- Stacy.
You know, I think maybe Stacy
thinks, like,
sometimes, "Well, I'm big, so
there should be
some accommodation made."
And I don't allow
any accommodation for myself.
- Manila, I want a serious
answer from you.
- I would like to see
Shangela go.
She's just a loudmouth,
and she's always talking
and hallelu-ing.
- Raja.
- Stacy and Shangela,
get the fuck out.
- Tell me why.
- Oh, Stacy.
I--you know, I'm not sure
if she's ready.
And Shangela, although
your personality shines,
I think you should be
on season five or six.
That's where you should be.
- That's interesting, Ru,
because Raja's been in the game
for 20-plus years doing drag,
and I've been only for one.
And we're in the same
competition here.
- Well, girls.
I think we've heard enough.
While you go and untuck in
the Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
Just between us girls.
Let's start with Yara Sofia.
The dress.
Would you wear that dress?
- No.
- She was supposed to recreate
a couture creation
of her cake that she was given,
which is a strawberry shortcake.
And I thought
that was interpreted
and executed flawlessly.
- She keeps building
in this competition
in ways that we really
didn't anticipate.
- She's the dark horse.
- The pro is her personality.
- Her cake was hysterical.
- It was.
Here, I'm gonna take a little
taste of her cake right now.
- Mm.
- Good?
- It's moist.
Stacy Layne Bryant Matthews
Lattisaw Q.
- I am a sucker
for people's backstory.
And I think the fact
that she's from Swampville.
- Back Swamp, yeah.
- I don't want to fall in love
with somebody's backstory.
I want to fall in love with
what's on the stage.
- The reality of it tonight
is that she looked awful.
- Manila.
Now, Manila's dress
I thought was fantastic.
I wasn't crazy
about all the accessories.
- It was just kind of strange
and cartoony in a way.
- I was so obsessed with
that gray, cadaver makeup.
- I loved Manila.
I would have worn that dress.
Again, yes, I would have taken
off the carrot belt.
- Yeah.
- But, you know,
we all would've.
- Next up, Alexis Mateo.
I understand the silhouette.
I know what she was going for.
But the execution of it
wasn't fierce.
- The skirt looked like
the polyester bedspreads.
- Motel 6.
If you put a black light on it,
you'd run.
- Let's talk about Raja.
I was surprised about the
pantaloon storyline, you know.
- It happens.
I've been on red carpets.
And sometimes, you know,
you just--it happens.
I just think she is not to be
played with, and I like her.
- Now, Sara, do you think
that her Depends...
- Yeah?
- Cost her the top spot?
- It didn't bother me,
'cause it was such a--
it was so clearly, like,
"Whoops," you know,
she made a mistake.
- The reason why I said that the
makeup went a little bit spooky
is because I couldn't find
anything wrong with her.
Her cake was a piece of art.
- Carmen Carrera.
- Like, if we could pick
"from the neck up winner,"
she would be my winner.
- When somebody gets their
16-year-old a car at Christmas,
that's the bow that goes
on the top.
- Her face looked pretty.
Her hair looked pretty.
I loved the little tiara
that was on her head.
But was it lower-level
than the other ones?
Yes.
- Delta Work.
- She looked amazing
when she rounded the corner.
And then, as she stood there,
I saw more and more wrong
with the outfit.
- I thought, quite honestly,
she looked gorgeous tonight.
- Miss Shangela.
- If you still don't know how
to beat your face,
which is a huge part
of being a drag superstar,
then you're not ready.
- The other ones live
to be drag queens.
She stands out as one who does
not live to be a drag queen.
- It seemed to me tonight,
that there was, like, a lot
of raw talent there.
She just didn't quite know
what to do
'cause she doesn't quite have
the training.
- Well, then,
she shouldn't be here.
- Right.
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your face of cakes
presentation on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Yara Sofia.
Your strawberry shortcake
was sweet as pie.
Echa pa'lante.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Delta Work.
Your angel cake couture had
one too many layers.
But the overall effect
was heavenly.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
Your red velvet cake
was hard to swallow
and not couture.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- It just pisses me off
that a lot of these bitches
look like shit.
But, you know, I wanted to do
something different.
Everybody's wearing
fucking dresses.
I should have made a dress
and called it a day
and been the fiercest bitch
onstage.
- Manila.
You doll cake was moist.
And I want another piece.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Raja.
Even though you flashed
your knickers,
the judges couldn't stop
gushing over
your chocolate lava couture.
Condragulations.
You're the winner
of this challenge.
You've won a glamorous
shopping spree
at the legendary house
of L.A. Eyeworks.
- Thank you so much.
This is my second time winning
a challenge.
And I think I deserved it.
Because I have a master's degree
in fierce.
I should be a professor.
- Carmen Carrera.
Your Jersey princess cake
couture did not hit the spot.
Alexis Mateo.
You're a sweet talker,
but your cheesecake couture
struck a sour note
with the judges.
Shangela.
You and a sewing machine
are a recipe for disaster.
Shangela, you're safe.
Is there anything you'd like
to say?
- I'm here
because I want to be here.
And I appreciate
what you see in me.
And I'm gonna continue
to show you
that not only
am I an entertainer,
but I am a drag queen.
And I'm meant to be here.
- Carmen Carrera.
Bada-bing, you're safe.
- Thank you, guys.
- Alexis Mateo.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I consider Stacy my friend
in this competition.
But if you give me the choice
between me and her leaving,
of course I'm gonna choose her.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-synch for your life.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
-  I don't want to lose you
This good thing
That I got
'Cause if I do
I will surely
Surely lose a lot
'Cause your love is better
Than any love I know
It's like thunder
Lightning
The way you love me is
Frightening
You better knock
Knock
On wood
- I didn't know what the judges
wanted to see.
I went to the high-energy road.
'Cause that's who I am.
-  You better knock, knock
Knock on wood
Think I better knock, knock
- I'm not that great
of a dancer.
But this is a competition.
I do have a name, a reputation.
And I'm not just gonna stand
there
and just give up in a song.
-  It's like thunder
Bursting lightning
- Now, I'm no stranger to being
bald on the runway,
but Stacy is taking out track
by track by track.
It looks like a poodle just shed
all over the runway.
-  You better knock, knock
Knock on wood
Babe, you better
Knock, knock, knock on wood
[applause]
- [laughing]
Ladies.
I've made my decision.
Alexis Mateo.
Shantay, you stay.
Stacy Layne Matthews.
You've come a long way
from Back Swamp.
But from this moment on,
the world is watching.
Be proud, be a star.
But most of all, be a lady.
Now sashay away.
Thank you.
[applause]
- Love you.
- Stacy.
- I never thought that,
coming from a small town
in North Carolina,
that I would even be
in a place like this.
So, you know, it's amazing.
I'm just glad to have made it
this far.
I'm very proud of myself.
I'm happy with what I've done
and what I brought
to the competition.
Condragulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen!
- All right.
Let the music play!
male announcer: RuPaul's
menswear provided
by Moods of Norway.
Grand prize contributed in part
by ALandCHUCK.travel.