- Oh, but, baby, you know how
I feel.
I mean, you really want me to
say it?
[laughing] This is silly.
Okay, here goes.
[imitating Cher]
Wagon wheel watusi!
[laughs]
You so crazy.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hey, Chaz.
I got that song, Superstar.
You know, the one you wanted to
rehearse for the show tonight.
- Oh, Chaz, I been so busy
selling the air rights to
RuPaul's Drag Race, I
completely forgot it.
- Cool.
I-I can come in tomorrow.
- Well, no, no.
Let's just get it over with.
Okay, you want a spot?
- [imitating Cher]
Snap out of it!
What do you think, Chaz?
Tonight, it's the superstar
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
- Oh oh!
- Get ready to gag, as we flash
back on this season's most
unforgettable moments.
Watch as this year's
queens bare
more than just their latex
boobies in never-before-seen,
up-close, and personal moments.
Join our extra-special guests,
Jujubee, Raven, and queen Tyra
as we count down the top ten
most sickening fits and
fashions.
Plus, outrageous outtakes
of our celebrity judges.
- It's gonna be a bitch fight!
- [giggles]
- With just one week until we
crown our new queen.
We salute our final three.
Alexis Mateo, Raja,
and Manila Luzon.
Welcome to the superstar edition
of RuPaul's Drag Race, chock
full of never-before-seen
footage for added freshness.
This season, none of our
showgirls threw marbles on the
runway, but they did have a few
catty things to say about each
other.
Let's take a look.
- What did you think about
Shangela's Tina?
- Shangela's Tina was okay.
You know.
- Are you serious?
She looked like Tina Turner
after Ike beat her down.
- Was that my name?
- Yeah, we're talking about
Tina Turner, girl.
- This hair is not soundproof.
- When people are talking about
you, that means you're doing
something right.
What's more American than
Marilyn Monroe?
- Oh, my gosh, you don't look
anything like Marilyn Monroe.
You probably look like Marilyn
Manson.
[laughter]
- But not Marilyn Monroe.
- If, but--I'm not in drag, I'm
so quiet.
- You say you're quiet?
You're not quiet, bitch.
- You're not quiet.
- Who would you say is the
funniest person here?
- Like, who cracks me up the
most?
- Mm-hmm.
- I do.
I crack myself up all the time.
- No one ever gets your jokes
except for you.
- First of all, she look like a
fat ass, cheap Barbie doll from
the dollar store.
- [laughing] Damn.
- If you have nothing nice to
say, don't say anything at all.
But if you nothing nice to say,
come sit next to me.
- I like your shoes.
They're cute.
- [deep voice]
Thanks, Heather.
You guys have the most
a-softest voices for men.
- Well, that's because you sound
like James Earl Jones, honey.
- Oh, fuck off,
sprepper bitch.
- What do you think of Alexis'?
- Wow.
That's just gonna make her look
really thick in the middle.
- That is so ugly.
- I don't want to look like I've
been eating the cake.
- Raja, girl, listen, I'm gonna
give you a little bit of advice.
Don't ever walk into an antique
store.
They just might keep you, girl.
[laughter]
- I mean, even her skin is
rejecting the makeup.
It's like, some people are just
not meant to do it,
and if your skin is rejecting
the makeup...
- Your body is telling you
something.
- Your face looks so much
better; so much better.
- Uck, I know, 'cause before I
was painted like Carmen Carrera.
- No, before, bitch, you was
painted like a motherfucking
ghost, honey.
- Okay, the library's closed!
- Me-ow!
Speaking of mean girls, the
self-proclaimed popular queens,
led by Raja and Manila, formed
a secret clique called
the Heathers.
- She was fetch.
- Heather!
Stop trying to make "fetch"
work; it's not happening.
- They pitted themselves
against the rest of the girls,
who they lovingly referred to as
the boogers.
["valley girl" voice] Oh, my
god, don't you, like, totally
miss high school?
- Heather.
- Heather wants to talk to us.
- Come hither, Heather.
- Heather, what are you making?
- Carmen, Manila, Delta, and
myself have decided to call each
other Heather because we formed
this clique which looks a lot
like the movie Heathers.
- There's just Heathers and
boogers.
- Does anyone know why the
other girls are calling each
other Heather?
- I don't know.
- It's just retarded.
These dumb bitches.
- I love calling you Heather.
It's so much fun.
- How's your outfit going,
Heather?
- It's going gorgeous.
- So, Yara, are you still
friends with Shangela?
- Yes.
- We can make you a Heather,
but you can't talk to the other
boogaronis.
- No, I don't want to.
- I'm just kidding.
- Everybody's just playing a
game.
But I think they're going
overboard.
No, I would have never worked
with the Heathers.
- If anyone looks at us as being
a clique, it's just
because they're insecure.
- I don't know what they put in
the breakfast.
- Boogers.
- Relax.
- I'm so over them.
- We got this.
We're the Heathers.
- Thank you.
- Here at RuPaul's Drag Race,
we don't just entertain.
We "edjumacate."
And this season, our queens
taught us more new words than
Sarah Palin, although she may
refudiate that.
The first Drag Race word is...
"busted."
- Everybody should have the
right to do drag, even if they
look busted.
- When it's not polished and
it's not there, it's just like,
bitch, it looks busted, and you
need to fix it.
- And you have to not be busted
like miss Raja over here.
- Crusted and busted.
- Busted people, they don't
know they're busted.
- Busted, party of one.
- [laughs]
- These other girls are busted.
- If you want to know the
truth, you need just one letter.
T.
- Ugh, I have so much T for you.
- What is the T?
- Here's the T.
- Just give me the T.
- There's the T.
- What's the T?
- She knows the T.
- You spilled your T to your
mom?
- How do you say, "that's the
T in Spanish?"
- [speaks Spanish]
- What?
- Oh, that is not the T.
- Some queens invented
their own catchphrases.
- Hallelu, ladies!
Hallelu!
He said hallelu.
- Hallelu!
- Hallelu.
- Is that a read?
- Hallelu, lelu.
- To quote Alexis Mateo, it
should say...
- Bam!
- Bam.
- Love the bam in all that
stuff.
- Bam!
- It was bam.
- Ah, thank you.
- Echa, echa, echa pa'lante!
- Help me say it.
- Echa pa'lante.
- Darling, I have one thing to
say to you.
- ♪ Echa pa'lante ♪
- And there were certain
expressions that seemed to get
stuck in all our heads.
Be a lady.
- Be a lady.
- "Don't be shady, be a lady."
- That bitch dances the house
down.
- He is going to ream me the
house down.
The house down is a drawn-out
version
of the exclamation point.
She is fierce, the house down.
- She is painted the house down.
- I'm padding the house down.
- I'm a diva, because a diva
delivers.
- Oh, so now you're delivering.
- Cannot walk.
- Oh, so, now you injured.
- It's really just the shoes.
- So now you're a drag queen?
- I can walk on water.
- Oh, so now you Jesus?
- [laughs]
- And then there's every drag
queen's favorite.
The f-word.
- Ooh, girl, you look fierce.
- I am fat, I am fierce.
- The reason you're here is
because you are fierce.
- It's like, "bitch, you look
fierce."
- Your Joan Crawford was not
Mildred fierce.
- You know there are some fierce
bitches here.
- She's one fierce mothertucker.
- But I think I did a fierce job
today.
- We're not here to be shady,
just fierce.
And what do you call something
that's fiercer than fierce?
You call it sickening.
- I am what? Sickening.
- Sickening.
- It was sickening to break him
in, honey.
- And by sickening, she means
sending people to the hospital.
- That's when it's, like,
sickening, girl.
- My thing is glamour and being
sickening.
- Thank you.
- One day, Alexis Mateo, I will
be as sickening as you.
- Sickening, no?
- Hi, and welcome back to the
superstar edition of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Now, here to help me count down
the most sickening fits and
fashions, I've invited three
legendary children.
Yes, legendary.
Welcome back the tasty Jujubee.
The mistress Raven.
And America's reigning drag
superstar, miss Tyra Sanchez.
Well, hello, my queens.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hey, mama.
- Welcome back.
- Thank you for having us.
- [laughs]
- Now, ladies...
let's count down the most
sickening fits and fashions on
the runway.
Coming in at number ten,
Manila Luzon
and her fluffy Christmas muff.
- Ooh.
- Look at the size of that muff.
I think she looks like this
exotic Russian model.
She looks absolutely
breathtaking.
- Manila Luzon, you have a muff
to die for.
- I think she looks fabulous.
I mean, I want that outfit for
myself.
It might be the only muff I put
my hands in.
It's cute.
- Coming at number nine
is Yara Sofia's
twisted follicle fantasy.
- I loved it.
The purse is my favorite.
It was, like, very hot.
- Yeah, she puts it together.
- This thing, though, I don't
know how that stayed on her
head.
- I think she looked like
a couture poodle.
Giving you hair body.
Ruff.
[laughter]
- All right, girls, coming in
at number eight, the ambush of
Shangela.
Who do you think should go home
tonight?
- I would like to see Shangela
go.
She's just a loudmouth, and
she's always talking, and
halleluing.
- Shangela, although your
personality shines, I think you
should be on season five or six.
That's where you should be.
- You know, you three have all
been in the workroom with
Shangela before.
- Yes.
- Is she annoying, Jujubee?
- I don't think she's annoying
at all.
She cracked me up.
- Yeah?
- I was mad when she left.
I wanted to see more of her.
So I think it was great that
she's back.
- Do you think that was fair
what Manila and Raja said to
Shangela?
- Well, I think everyone's
entitled to their own opinion,
but it just reminded me of the
wedding episode.
So I felt like how Shangela
felt.
They're entitled to say what
they want to say.
I think they could have said it
in a more polite way.
- In your case or in Shangela's
case?
- In both cases.
- [laughs]
- I'm sorry.
- In our number seven spot,
it's our cheerleading jocks in
frocks.
They've got spirit, yes they do.
They've got spirit.
How 'bout you?
- Whoo!
- Baby!
- Wrap your dick!
Wrap up your dick!
- No bareback! No bareback!
- Abstinence is for boogers,
but we love our diaphragm!
- Protection is the key!
Safe sex!
- These are some ladies.
- Well, one of 'em looked like
Juju.
- Okay, she was giving you body.
- Yeah.
- She was giving shoulders,
girl.
- Whatever.
- Raja was my favorite.
It reminded me so much
of White Chicks
when they started dancing.
It was just hilarious.
- I love Yara Sofia trying to
spell out the word "wrap," and
every letter, it sounds like
she's gonna say a different
letter.
- Give me the A!
- A!
- Give me the ah-a!
- Their performance was one of
the funniest things I've seen on
national television in a long,
long time.
- Safe sex, motherfuckers!
- Wrap that dick!
- Coming in at number six is
Raja from the lost tribe of
supermodels.
- Fabulous fierce.
I wish I had her body, for real.
There needs to be a time when
you can go, "okay, I'm gonna
rough it up and make this a
little edgy."
I wanna see that bitch do
Avatar.
- Dragatar.
- Yes.
- At number five, Alexis
Mateo's eye-popping,
jaw-dropping outfit from
the drag queens of comedy.
- I'm a Latina girl, and I only
have two options in this
country.
And you all know I didn't came
here to clean toilets, baby, so
I became a stripper, baby!
- I love big titties.
[laughter]
- Actually, last season,
I think you were the only queen
who had a breast plate.
- Mm-hmm.
- This season, several of the
girls were pumping breast
plates.
Is that a trend that's happening
around the world right now?
- Um, I've noticed that,
wherever I go now, there are
a lot of queens with it now.
It comes to the point where,
like, I don't even wear it as
much anymore because--
- Are you pumping the breast
plate now?
- No. No.
- Just natural.
- [laughs]
Making the number four spot
on our countdown is the gift
that keeps on giving...
Carmen Carrera's ass.
- I think clothing repels off of
her.
You know?
I'm like, "girl, did you get
that half off?"
- My dick would be really mad
as--
I don't know where she put it.
- Pissed off.
- She's got some skills.
- Yeah.
- In your group, Raven, were
there any girls who were naked
like that?
- I think the only one that
came close to that was Mystique.
- Yeah.
I'm kidding.
[laughter]
- Coming in at number three is
Shangela, serving some
post-modern pimp realness.
- Well, you know I had a dumbass
girlfriend.
She came screaming at me last
week, talkin' about, "Laquifa!"
I said, "what?!"
"Where your hoes at?"
I said, "bitch, don't you see
I'm wearin' four pair of hose
right here
holding back my dick!"
- That bitch is hilarious.
I can watch that over and over
again.
- It was very well thought out.
Everything that she did.
The way she puts her hand on
her, "I'm also my own ho."
I absolutely loved it.
- Coming in at number two on
the most sickening fits and
fashions involves miss India
Ferrah getting a bit carried
away.
- If that were me, if that was
me carried away...
Mimi would have been
drop-kicked.
- Uh-oh.
- I would have got kung fu on
her.
- Okay.
- Yes, ma'am.
It crosses a line, and it shows
your desperation.
- First and foremost,
be a lady.
- Keep it cute.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Now, what would you have done
in that situation?
- Well, it's $75,000 that
you're giving away, and you
don't want to go home.
You want to be there and you
want to win.
So, in her mind, she's thinking,
"I can't go home.
I cannot go home."
- But I will say India handled
it very well.
When she was finally put down,
she did her thing.
I will say props to India.
And I love India's mug.
- And now, the moment we've all
been waiting for, the coveted
number one spot on our
countdown.
The most sickening of them all
goes to...
Who could it be?
Isn't anybody gonna interrupt
me?
- Hold on, now, Ru.
The top spot belongs to...
- Ahggh...
- You!
- Me?! What?
What are you talking about?
Are you telling me that I'm
number one three years in a row?
- Three years in a row.
- Is that a record?
Susan Lucci, eat your heart out.
- My favorite was
your Barbie look.
You came out and you were like,
"okay."
- Valley girl.
- Oh, yes.
- Where I was going as a black
woman for the first time in my
life.
I was portraying a black woman.
- You nailed it.
- Do you think so?
- Did a really good job.
- Oh, good, thank you.
Thank you.
Raven, what was your favorite
look?
- The one where you're in the
black and yellow dress.
- That's the glamazon with the
Mohawk story going.
- Yes.
- It was gorgeous.
- And, Tyra, what about me?
What about RuPaul?
What I want to know is what
dress would you want to mock?
- It's like a peach color.
- Yeah, it's got the dandelion
big--
- All over, I think I'd want to
mock that one.
- Very ra-cha-cha.
[laughter]
Well, thank you, ladies.
I know you'll be watching next
week to find out who gets
crowned America's next drag
superstar.
Thank you for chiming in.
Lots of luck.
Welcome back to the superstar
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Now, to reach the final three,
Alexis, Manila, and Raja had to
really pump up the volume.
Because the ten queens who left
before them did not go quietly.
- Hello.
all: Hi!
- Now, we barely got to
know Venus D-Lite.
A fierce Madonna
impersonator...
Venus found her holiday was cut
short, and quicker than a ray
of light, she was gone.
The next queen to fly the coop
was Phoenix.
After an awkward first
impression, her psychic ability
made her team captain.
- Action!
- You've arrived in a
hermaphrodite spaceship.
Prepare to trannyport in three,
two, one.
- Phoenix, you're delivering
all your lines away from the
camera.
We need to see your gorgeous
face.
- Okay.
- I think you could have been a
little zanier, especially with a
name like Lady Tata.
- But even Phoenix couldn't
predict that her performance as
Lady Tata would make her the
second queen to leave the race.
Mimi Imfurst...
- Welcome to my party!
I brought cookies.
- Got off to a rocky start.
Her confidence was shaken when
she tried to put the "merry"
back in Christmas.
- [crying] I don't know what I
was thinking.
And if I have to lip-synch,
I'll
motherfucking lip-synch my life
off.
- But her lively personality
soon came busting out all over.
Much to the annoyance of some of
the other girls.
- Action.
- Aah!
- Miss Mimi, there's a
difference in being talented...
and being a showboat.
- Her performance from
Queens from Uranus received
some stellar reviews.
But her workout video proved to
be more pain than gain.
- You gotta get higher!
Chase after your man!
You're gonna grab him!
- Oh!
- Hold him up!
- Cut! It's just feeling a
little disorganized.
- It was hokey.
It was not good.
- And her lip-synch with India
Ferrah got way too physical.
- Get her off of me!
- And Mimi Imfurst was the
third queen to go home.
India Ferrah arrived from Ohio
with an all-star reputation.
- Girl...prison, honey.
I look over to Phoenix copying
my style, so I actually had to
go up to her and be a little
cunt to her.
I love your hair.
- India's rubber boobies became
stars in their own right.
- I thought they were just
completely believable.
- But the judges wanted to see
more than just jiggle.
- Give me more face.
- Okay.
- Give me more of that.
- There is a hell no storm.
Okay?
- Her performance as the QNN
weather girl was met with an
arctic blast, and India was the
fourth to sashay away.
This next lady boy served fish
like she was working at Red
Lobster, and we call this queen
Mariah.
- Prepare to gag on my eleganza.
- One of the most flawless
beauties to ever grace the
runaway.
Mariah's poise and
self-confidence seemed like it
would carry her far.
- When we find out that we have
to go out during the daytime and
go shopping in drag, I'm good,
'cause, baby, if it's right,
it's right.
- And in the snatch game, her
impression of Joan Crawford did
not earn her the respect she
felt entitled to.
- Now, that is not a wire
hanger.
- It's not.
- What is it?
- It's a wooden hanger.
[all groan]
- And that led to the
emancipation of Mariah.
It's safe to say that Stacy
Layne Matthews has put
Back Swamp, North Carolina, on
the map.
Her clone does not sleep alone.
- You look so much
like my relatives.
Is she related and I don't know
it?
- The back swamp Jacksons.
- Shake it! Ohh!
- Excellent.
- Yes! Mmm!
- But Stacy's personality,
humor,
and star quality soon emerged.
- Okay.
- Monique?
- Precious!
- Uh-oh.
Is Precious back there?
- Mm-hmm.
Bitch knows I'm hungry as hell.
- Eventually, the pressure of
competition started to get to
Stacy.
And even her red velvet cake
ensemble wasn't sweet enough to
keep her in the competition.
Delta work arrived here as one
of the girls to beat.
- Delta, you better...
♪ Work ♪
- And I'm Delta Work.
Pour yourself another cup of
ambition
because this is the Morning
After News.
- Looking sexy.
- So do you. I love you in pink.
- Thanks.
- And, darling, we're done.
- Oh! Cool!
- [laughs]
- We won't be able to get you
to put clothes on anymore.
- No, I don't think so.
Carmen Carrera better watch out.
- [laughs]
Her ability to make us laugh
kept her in the competition week
after week.
- One, two, three. Like that!
You see how that feels?
Do it like that!
You've got enough, you can stick
it right down inside there.
And you can jump up and down.
- But in the end, it was her
stand-up comedy routine
that got
her eliminated.
Jersey princess Carmen Carrera
flaunted a figure
that wouldn't quit.
- Hey, hey.
- Carmen Carrera is like the
flyest girl you're ever gonna
meet in your life.
- She's an ass-tronaut.
- I make sure that her body is
flawless.
If you find the flaw, let me
know.
- Hey.
No foam here.
- 100% made in the USA.
- Ohh!
- Her reggae version of
Superstar
didn't make the sun splash
she wanted it to.
- ♪ Gonna remember my name ♪
- But in a Drag Race first,
the judges later overruled
my decision.
- I can't.
I don't wanna look.
Ohh!
[cheers and jeers]
- I'm back, bitches.
both: Uh-oh, she said
my pussy's turning red.
- Ooh!
both: No burn, limpy.
Protection is the key!
- Unable to turn her jock into
a convincing drag sister,
Carmen
was sent home...again.
This time for good.
This season started with a big
surprise.
- Hallelu, ladies!
[cheers and applause]
- What the fuck?
- Ohh!
- But it turns out the surprise
was on Shangela when her snowman
couture put her in the bottom
two in the first week.
both: Stop flirting!
You stop flirting!
Ohh!
- She rocketed back, winning
the next challenge with her
twin bot, Alexis Mateo.
[imitating Cher] Shangela.
It's the drive I saw in Shangela
that kept her fighting when her
back was up against the wall.
- I said, "bitch, better have
my money!"
You pick up the hallelula hoop
and you put it back around your
waist!
And you work the hallehula hoop.
One, two, three, four.
I don't want that whore no more.
Five, six, seven, eight.
I am gonna find a date.
- But even her irrepressible
hallelu spirit couldn't carry
Shangela into the final three.
Yara Sofia arrived from
Puerto Rico as a dark horse
in this competition.
- Oh oh!
Oh, almost burned my ass.
Oh, my god.
Cha! Cha!
Echa pa'lante!
- But her sense of humor and
her
joy for life proved to be
contagious in challenge...
- Ohh!
- After challenge.
- Hyuh! [raspberry]
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Get out, get out, get out!
- Let me hear some of your
English accent.
[laughter]
- Can I have some whater?
How'd it sound?
- By George, I think you've got
it!
- Ohh, rheally?
- Yes!
But, forced to lip-synch for
her life against her good
friend
Alexis Mateo, Yara seemed to
throw in the towel too early.
- I'm so angry, and I'm so
disappointed.
I'm a mess.
- Sadly, we had to say adios.
I'm so proud of each of these
incredible queens.
They made this competition the
stiffest one yet and really
forced our final three to earn
their place at the top.
Welcome back to the superstar
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
This year, the judge's panel
was star-studded.
- [laughs]
- But you didn't get to see
half of what goes on behind that
table until now.
Like when my best girlfriend
Michelle Visage and I start
kicking, things can get real
stupid.
- Seeing India tonight on the
runway was like walking into the
mall,
and Claire's exploded all over
her.
- Well, I want to see you do me;
how would you do me?
[laughs]
Michelle, sashay away.
- Ohh.
- You know, my personal mantra
is, it's not a party until
someone gets a bucket of pig
blood dumped on her head.
- Oh, that's mine too.
Mm, it smells like freedom
in here.
- Ooh, I thought I washed.
- [laughs]
The boy judges had their manic
moments too between Santino,
Billy B., and Mike Ruiz--
child, nobody was safe.
- She always looks beautiful,
but she looks like a beautiful
special needs child.
[laughter]
- And we love special needs
children.
- Some of you who do have very
feminine features still contour
the crap out of it, and you look
like Lil Kim before she went to
the doctor.
- Oh! Oh, oh!
- I'm just saying.
- You need to get
a refrigerator,
because you're going sour.
- Am I wilting?
- There's some fruit flies
buzzing around your head.
- Now, Billy, is it possible
that you are pregnant right now
and you don't know it?
- My shoes are wet.
I think my water just broke.
[laughter]
- You did this funny thing with
your lips when you were doing
the runway, this puckering
thing.
It looks like you were--
suck the
paint off a Cadillac
with those lips.
- Your...pie looked delicious.
And not the one you were
holding, heh heh!
In a whole constellation of
asses,
she's got the brightest ass.
- Thank you very much, Albert
Einstein.
Santa Claus, please, keep it
quiet.
Thank you, Phil Donahue.
Now, my favorite part of the
show is watching our celebrity
guest judges, who are really
just big fans, get caught up in
the spirit of drag race.
And nobody goes home until
they've strutted their stuff on
the runway.
Don't be jealous of their
boogie.
- Not only can the judges walk
the walk,
they talk the talk too.
Here is some never-before-seen
footage to show you just what I
mean.
- I think it's extraordinary.
You look like Paris Hilton if
she was the Motel 6 heiress.
[laughter]
- I think Santa has Venus envy.
- It looks like ladies' night at
the Star Wars cantina.
Are you feeling intergalactic?
- Very intergalactic.
- That's so funny, because I'm
interga-lactating right now.
- Are you?
- Because that is the real T,
this girl, okay?
If you could put a pair of
trousers and a blazer and look
feminine, hon'ty, you deserve to
snatch several daytime Emmys,
okay?
- The walk, however.
It's like you do have a horse
between your legs.
- Apparently, he does.
- Your smile is absolutely
lovely.
- 15 years since I've been to
the dentist.
I just brush and floss.
- What?
- But you just take 'em out and
put 'em in a glass at night,
right?
- The biggest career move I ever
did was
to have my teeth removed.
- Exactly.
- Choking on chicken in an
exercise video is not good.
- It's not cute.
It's not cute for her.
- But choking on chicken in
private or choking your chicken.
- Choking anybody's chicken is
not cute
if it's on camera.
- I think your dress goes with
the whole India theme.
Sari.
- Sorry seems to be the
hardest...dress to wear.
- Yeah.
It is, it is.
- Smizing got out of control.
The smizing was--it's like gonna
be the next version of Saw.
Like, Saw 10: The Smize.
- Smize 5.
- Oh, I'm gettin' daggers!
I'm gonna cut you and she's
gonna cut me.
It's gonna be a bitch fight!
- You know, there's something
about RuPaul's Drag Race that
frees up our judges to let it
all hang out.
Maybe a little too far out.
- If you haven't noticed, I'm
like a bald-headed ho.
I don't have any hair at all.
- That's the cake I would've
wanted
when I was like eight and having
my princess birthday party,
so I guess when I was eight, I
wanted a gay wedding cake.
Which makes sense.
- I want that shrug so bad.
- This one?
- I want to roll around in it.
I want to see it first thing in
the morning.
I want to nuzzle it.
- The thing that I didn't like
was, like, I felt like she had a
bouquet of flowers in her hair.
- What's wrong with flowers in
her hair?
- And it was really distracting.
- Will you look at Ru?
- Yeah, I've got a bouquet of
flowers here.
- Ru's got a damn florist,
not a bouquet.
- I got a lot going on.
- You're more fresh than a
hibiscus bush.
- I got some birds.
I had some snakes.
- I'm gonna have an apple in a
minute.
[laughter]
- Did you bake that cake in your
lovin' oven?
- What? I'm sorry?
[laughter]
Never mind.
Judges, you have not been a help
at all.
- Sorry.
- Two-time guest judge, the
luminous La Toya Jackson, has a
giggle that is both magical and
infectious.
Before long, she had everybody
doing the toy-toy titter.
Hee hee hee hee!
- [giggling]
[laughter]
[giggling]
Am I wrong for saying that?
- How about that La Toya
Jackson?
- Hee hee hee hee hee!
- Are you recording this?
[giggling]
[all mocking La Toya's laugh]
- I'm drinking champagne!
Hee hee hee hee!
- [giggles]
Stop it.
- Welcome back to the superstar
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Now, there's more to drag
queens than meets the eye.
Beneath all the padding,
glitter, and false eyelashes,
lady boys need love too.
- I've had a boyfriend
for ten years.
- I want to be with my husband
It's been more than three years.
- The thing about a
relationship, and plus, you're
a drag queen; I mean, you gotta
just be ready for anything,
you know?
- Well, the thing is that he
gets a two-for-one with Carmen,
you know what I mean, so...
there's no complaints.
- Are you missing your husband
at all?
- Yes, I miss him, girl.
- Are you?
- And I know he's missing me.
Like, I guess that's the hardest
part of--that I know, like, what
he's going through.
You know, he loves me to death.
He would do anything for me.
He goes to all my shows.
Helps me, dresses me.
- Oh, how cool.
- It's so difficult for us in
this business to actually meet
somebody.
- Oh, yes.
- That's why you have to date
another drag queen.
- Yes!
- It's nice, because, like, you
understand each other.
And you double your wardrobe.
[laughter]
- When it comes to seeing their
son in high heels and a dress,
some parents just don't
understand.
But our brave and talented
queens have learned to carry on.
- Yara, has your family ever
come to see you perform?
- My mother, the thing she
doesn't get it is she thinks
that I'm a stripper.
- Well, you kind of are.
- She doesn't get that
we lip-sync and we do
[indistinct],
you know what I mean?
She doesn't get it.
- I think Yara's a stripper.
[laughs]
- Hey, Shangela, has your
grandmother ever seen you
perform?
- She loved it, she was like,
"I couldn't believe it.
You look like a woman.
I said, 'That's not DJ.
That's a white woman.'"
- Home is where the love is.
And some of our queens have
created new families, with drag
mothers and drag sisters that
make the world a more fabulous
place to live.
- You guys have houses.
- Mm-hmm, houses.
- What does that mean?
Like a family?
- It's kind of like
fraternities and sororities.
But with gay culture.
Most of our house names are
after designers.
- Okay.
- So it's like you have the
house of Balenciaga, the house
of Chanel, the house of...
so many others.
- What house are you in?
- Balenciaga.
- The Balenciaga.
- Balenciaga. Okay.
- I miss my drag family.
I mean, I see my family...
I call them my family 'cause
they really are my drag family.
But more than that, they're my
friends.
And I see them and talk to them
every day, all day long.
Even if we're not working.
- Exactly.
So really just family.
- Let's do this; let's do that.
- Before I did drag, I used to
go watch Raja's shows.
So she's like my unofficial
drag mother.
- Okay.
- Amen and hallelu.
Now, coming out is different for
everybody.
Some queens don't put it
together until later in life.
And others, well...they just
seem to be born that way.
- When I came out of the womb,
I came out.
So it was just a matter of my
parents having to learn
and deal with it, you know?
- I grew up in a very ignorant
place.
We got, like, one gay kid a
year.
- Were you that one gay kid in
your class?
- I was the one gay kid that
everyone probably suspected.
I can remember, like, in
kindergarten, I was in catholic
school...and I would just like
go up to boys and kiss them.
- Believe me, if we were in
kindergarten together, I would
let you kiss me.
- [laughs]
- So, miss Phoenix, girl, we
both are from Georgia.
Was it as unpleasant for you as
it was for me?
- I remember, like, in high
school, somebody getting pegged
in the head with a Coke can,
'cause he was gay.
- Girl, shut up.
- And...
- They, ooh, they were--
- Yeah, I was like, "absolutely
not."
I'm like, "whatever is going on
with me..."
- Is gonna be with me.
- It's gonna be with me.
I'm not telling another
motherfucker.
One of my best friends, he kind
of like helped me come out, and
he actually is the one that
helped me get started in drag,
so...
- Oh, word.
- Yeah, I mean, he, like, kind
of showed me there is, like,
another world out there.
- Thank god.
- I'd take my friends to lunch
and be like, "um, okay.
So I have something to tell you.
And, as you know, I've gone on
dates with girls, but also I
have gone on dates with guys."
And then I'd just pause and wait
for the reaction.
And every time, everyone went,
"oh, I knew."
And I was like, "oh."
- I didn't come out.
My mom caught me.
- What do you mean she caught
you?
- Wait, wait, wait.
Your mom caught you doing what?
- I called my neighbor, and I
was doing my thing, and then my
mom opened the door, heh.
And I was there...
- Alexis, what's your coming out
story?
- It was horrible.
- How?
- I decided to have an
experience with a man.
He used to pick me up at school.
I got really scared, 'cause
everybody started saying that I
was gay and all this bullshit.
So I cut off relationship
thingy,
and he wrote a letter to my mom.
- [gasps]
- I walk in my house, and my
mom was sitting at the table,
and she said to me, "put your
backpack in your room.
I need to talk to you."
The jig was up.
- Welcome back to the superstar
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
In just one week, one of these
queens--Manila Luzon, Raja, or
Alexis Mateo--will be crowned
America's next drag superstar
and walk away with a lifetime
supply
of Kryolan professional
makeup...
headline logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut,
and win a cash prize of 75,000.
Let's take a look back at the
special blend of charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent
that make these three queens the
cream of the crop.
Manila Luzon had a unique
insight coming
into this competition.
- My drag persona Manila is my
personal muse, because I inspire
myself.
During the day as a boy, I'm a
graphic designer.
And my job does affect my drag
because it really helps me put
together a visual story that I
want to communicate to the
audience.
- Her comedic abilities made
the judges laugh in challenge
after challenge after challenge.
- Manila, you're all ears, girl.
[laughter]
- Manila proved that there's
more to her than just comedy.
She brought originality and
served up high glamour.
- Drag, to me, is creatively
bringing together an entire
story and costumes and
character
and putting them
into one living being.
That's the best part.
- A world-class queen
with beauty, brains,
and a bright persona,
Manila just might have what it
takes to be
America's next drag superstar.
Christmas came early for
Southern California native Raja,
winning both challenges her
first week here.
- Oh, no stranger to the runway.
- I've always been a drag
queen.
To me, it's just like
breathing.
I've always loved fashion and I
do drag because I don't believe
that only women are allowed to
wear beautiful, fashionable
things.
- Her high fashion
sensibilities, unexpected
choices, and incredible makeup
artistry kept Raja at the top
of the class.
- I love iconic people
within fashion.
A little coo coo, a little
berserk, a little funny,
a little eccentric--that's my
style; that's my fashion
reference that I look to.
I don't care to look like
a Kardashian.
Raja is cultural.
She's smart.
She's adventurous.
She definitely thinks
outside of the box.
And she's genderless.
She's raceless
and she's ageless.
- Raja isn't just fierce.
She proved that she's versatile,
intelligent,
and isn't afraid to act the
fool.
- No one can hear your
lip-synching in space.
Prepare to die!
- Raja is definitely at the top
of her game.
But will her many talents take
her to the top of the heap?
Straight out of central Florida
comes Alexis Mateo.
Bam.
- Hi, my name is Alexis Mateo
Rodriguez Rivera Elizabeth
y todos los demas.
[laughter]
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
Bam! Bam!
- Cha-cha.
- A Puerto Rican pageant queen
whose beauty and positive
attitude are captivating.
- I grew up doing pageants.
And it's always about how
flawless
and how perfect you are.
So I guess, in the back of my
mind, I'm always trying to be
completely pageant-ready.
- Behind her big smile,
we learned a story of pain
and loss.
Do you know anybody
in the military?
- [sighs]
Three years ago, I met somebody
very special in my life.
We get our relationship very
secretly.
And, like, the best moments of
my life was with him.
And he got called to go to
service,
and I don't know nothing
about him
since like a year and a half.
So I really don't know
if he's okay.
- What would you say to him
right now?
- I want to say I'm sorry and
that I love him so much
and that I am very proud of him.
- Alexis Mateo, you turned
sadness into gladness
and made us proud.
Condragulations, you are
the winner of this challenge.
- Thank you.
- Is there anything
you'd like to say?
- I know some things
happen in life.
It teaches you a lot of valuable
lessons.
And this one helped me to grow,
'cause I normally depend a lot
from people.
And I want to say thank you to
that special person that showed
me that I needed to love myself
first.
The best part of being a drag
queen--have the chance to be
a star and be the center of
attention for a second.
When I'm Alexis Mateo,
I think I'm perfect.
In my eyes, Alexis Mateo is the
most beautiful drag queen
in the world.
[cheers and applause]
Bam!
- Alexis proves the winning
power of perseverance.
And that is a quality of
a champion, honey.
So there you have it.
Are you team Manila?
Team Raja?
Or team Alexis?
All three are fierce
competitors.
But only one can be
the champion.
Tune in next week, when we crown
America's next drag superstar
on the grand finale of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get a amen in here?
- Amen!
- Let the music play!
Grand prize contributed
in part by ALandCHUCK.travel.