- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
May the funniest bitch win.
- It's like our workroom is now
divided into two groups.
We got team talent
and team look.
I will see each one of them
go home.
- Whoo!
- Anybody else on their period?
- Mm-hmm, I said bitch better
have my money!
- Pfffft!
Get out, get out, get out,
get out!
- That bitch was crazy.
Shangela, you bitch-slapped
the competition.
Con-drag-ulations.
You are the winner of this
challenge.
[cheers and applause]
That is what a lip sync for your
life is all about.
Manila...
shante, you stay.
Delta...
sashay away.
- I'm just glad to have lost
to a Heather,
not to one of the boogers.
- And tonight...
I'm so excited,
I'm lactating.
Fierce flies.
- [imitates gunfire]
- And a star-spangled salute...
- Bam!
- With extra special guest
judges
Cheryl Tiegs
and Johnny Weir.
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut,
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win.
- ♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ Ru--Ru--RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
- Yoo-hoo!
Toughest queens coming through.
- So we're back in the workroom,
and there's Delta's message,
and it's pretty
heartbreaking for me, because
Delta and I are so close.
- I can't believe I sent
Heather home.
Delta's gone.
We're missing one Heather.
It's sad, but I haven't had
such a rush in my life before.
When I was lip-syncing
last week,
I was living onstage.
It's really put in a new energy
into how I'm playing this
competition.
- Delta was so fetch.
- She was fetch.
- Heather, stop trying to make
"fetch" work.
It's not happening.
- What is the hell with this
"Heathers" group?
I think Carmen is fake.
I think Raja is fake.
I think Manila is fake.
Bam.
- Oh, I love you, Delta.
- You sent her home.
- Well, bitch, it was her or me,
honey.
- See you at the bathhouse,
girl.
- What'd you think about how,
you know, everyone was so sad
when Delta left and went up and
gave that big old hug
and that teary good-bye
and that production?
- It was exactly that,
a production.
It was a "we are the world,
we are the children" moment
on the stage.
- Let's stay strong in this
competition, okay?
- All right.
[siren wails]
- Oh!
- Ooh, girl!
You got she mail.
Hey, racers.
all: Hello.
- I have dragged my ass all
around this world,
and I've learned one thing--
the U.S.A. is still the best
damn country on earth.
- Yes.
- Whoo!
- My fellow drag Americans,
ask not what RuPaul's Drag Race
can do for you.
Ask what you can do for
RuPaul's Drag Race.
[laughs]
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Whoa!
- Well, howdy, partners.
This week, we're gonna focus on
two of my favorite things--
"t" and "a."
You want to know what the "t"
is?
all: Yes!
- All right.
For today's mini challenge,
I want you to turn these plain
brassieres
into something
truly glamorific.
I want you to bedazzle a healthy
pair of hooters.
- Ooh! Yes!
- Yes!
- The queen with the most
bedazzling bra wins.
Now, you have 30 minutes,
so ready, set...
Go!
[frantic percussion]
- Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Yes!
- Oh, fuck that asshole!
[humming]
- Really? Is that, like,
actually part of the challenge?
Deal with you?
- Aah!
Oh, girl, look.
The bra--that's the wrong side.
- No, you didn't.
- My initial idea is to do kind
of a modern replica
of RuPaul's face on the bra.
Now, that is couture.
- All right, ladies,
time's up.
Gather round.
Wow.
I'm so excited, I'm lactating.
First up, Alexis Mateo.
Careful, girl.
You could put somebody's eyes
out with those things.
Bam!
- [laughs]
- Beautiful.
Thank you, Alexis.
- Thank you.
- Next up, Yara Sofia.
Wow.
- This is my ze-bra collection.
- Ah, your ze-bra.
- By Yara Sofia's Secret.
- Hunty.
Next up, Shangela.
- [humming sultry music]
- Ooh.
Now, is that corn?
- Actually, this is supposed to
be a model of you.
- Uh-huh.
- With the big blond hair here,
and then it's the signature
RuPaul line.
I'm hoping to pitch it to you.
- I didn't see RuPaul's head
in there at all.
I just saw, like,
popcorn kernels.
- And you're using the glitter,
which is really interesting.
Next up, Raja.
- I kind of wanted to go for,
like, rocker chick Samantha Fox
meets Burlesque, so I tried to
concentrate a few of the...
- Well, I think that they're
perfect for motor-boating.
Bbbbbbb!
- Pfffft!
- Thank you, Raja.
Carmen Carrera.
Ooh, there's rhinestones in them
there hills.
- Mm-hmm.
- Did you breast-feed
with those?
- I don't breast-feed.
I pump.
- Oh, you pump.
Very Latoya.
For those of you who didn't
believe, roll up your sleeves.
Next up, Manila.
Now, is that a nursing bra?
- Well, I thought they looked
like rivets,
so I went for, like, a submarine
look for my torpedoes.
[imitates torpedoes firing]
[imitating gunfire]
- Better luck next time, Manila.
To kill RuPaul, you gotta be
faster than that.
- Uhh!
- Ladies, all of your designs
were truly bodacious.
But I can only choose one.
So cross my heart,
the winner is...
[suspenseful music]
Manila.
- Whoo!
Yes!
- Why, those are the fastest
tits in the west.
- [exhales sharply]
- Now, I told you this week was
all about my two favorite
things--"t" and "a."
The "t" was for ta-tas,
but the "a" is for...
America.
- Ohh!
- Yes.
There is no place like
the U.S. of A.
For this week's main challenge,
you'll each create a public
service announcement
entitled
"Why I love the U.S.A."
So the message should be
entertaining and from the heart,
because we'll be sending your
P.S.A.s
to the brave men and women
who are serving our
country overseas.
You'll each have ten minutes
in front of the camera,
and, Manila, since you won
the mini challenge,
you'll get an extra
five minutes.
Gentlemen...
start your engines.
And may the best American woman
win.
- It just kind of needs to be a
few words, right?
- Yeah, I'm doing, like,
snippets.
- Yeah, that's what I'm thinking
of.
When it came time for me
to write my P.S.A.,
I had to think about what
American values
do I cherish the most?
If it's too speech-y...
it's only supposed to be 30
to 60 seconds long,
so you have to kind of fill it
in
with just a few words, you know.
I always want it to feel
inspired,
and I definitely want to be
connected to it emotionally.
- Uh!
- Ew!
- Did you really seriously fart?
- [laughing]
- Sick.
- I'm having a hard time
with it.
- You are?
- Yes, I have so many things
that are personal.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I really don't want to
make it personal and sad,
'cause I know it's gonna be sad
for me.
It's just too much, too much.
I hope I don't cry.
- Why would you cry?
- It's a lot of things.
It's a lot of things.
- Like what?
- There's a lot of things
personal that I...
I wish I could say, but I can't.
- Made in the U.S.A.
Our main challenge today is to
shoot,
like, a 30-second public
service announcement
for our troops.
- Hey.
Can you hear my--
- Go ahead.
- "Right now I'm wearing no
clothes,
"because I don't want any brand,
any stereotypes to cover
who I am."
I don't want any brand to cover
my identify--my identity.
You like it?
- I didn't get it.
At the competition, Yara is a
very original girl,
and her personality help
her a lot.
But when it comes to talent
and performing,
I think Yara's still behind.
- Do you like that idea?
I'm gonna be naked.
- Yeah, but, baby, you gotta
let me write.
- Oh.
- You gotta let me write.
- I taught Shangela a few things
about makeup.
And today she doesn't want
to help me.
- If I thought Yara needed
the help,
I would help her,
but she doesn't.
Girl, you can do it.
- Shangela and Alexis are like,
"Do your job."
I know you're doing your job,
but before, I was doing my job,
and I helped you.
- So did you guys grow up
really, like, patriotic
and, like, "We love America"?
- I was born here, but I lived
in Indonesia
when I was a little boy,
and I remember thinking
of America as, like, the land
of candy bars and M&amp;Ms,
so it was kind of a dreamland
for me.
- I know, it's kind of like
my mom,
you know, coming from
a different country
where you're just like,
"America is the dream.
That's where I need to go."
- Being an American wasn't
something that was hard for me.
I was born into it.
It was easy, but being
Carmen Carrera wasn't,
and being married to my husband
wasn't.
I had to fight for all those
things,
so those are the things
that I'm really proud of.
[door opens]
- Well, hello, my star-spangled
ladies.
- Hi!
- I'm gonna check in and see
what you all are up to.
Hi, Raja.
What do you love about America?
- I love freedoms that I'm
allowed to have here.
I'm allowed to get in drag and
parade around the streets
and make money doing it.
- This needs to be uplifting,
entertaining,
and from the heart.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay? All right.
Carry on.
- All right.
- Hello, Manila.
- Hi.
- Why do you love America?
- There's just so many different
kinds of food here.
- So America to you means
a variety of different foods.
- Yes.
- What else does America mean
to you?
- Well, I think that is a symbol
of the diversity of America.
Different ethnicities and
cultures--they're all just
out here for the tasting.
Try something new.
Do it with an Indian guy.
- Now, of course, you are gonna
be talking
to the troops who are serving
this great nation of ours,
so we want you to express
yourself,
but just know that we want it to
come from the heart,
not come from between your legs.
I'm gonna let you get back
to work.
- Okay, thank you.
- I can't wait.
Carmen Carrera.
You, as you flutter your false
eyelashes--
is that what being an American
means to you?
- Yes.
I'm free, honey.
- Hello.
- No restrictions,
you know what I mean?
- Now, tell me what you have
planned for your P.S.A.
- My aunt has six boys,
and most of them are all
in the Army, the Navy.
I'm keeping in my mind that my
video's gonna get to them.
- That's a great idea.
- Thank you.
- Yara Sofia.
- Yes.
- Now, you're working on
your P.S.A.,
and you understand
where this will go.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- My dad is Army Reserve.
- Has he ever been shipped
overseas?
- Yes, to Iraq.
- Really?
- And you have no communication
with him.
I don't think I'm going
to mention
my father in that P.S.A.,
'cause it's too emotional
for me.
It was a very hard time
in my life.
- You have dialogue that you
will say.
Just give me a synopsis.
- If you don't love America,
how the hell you gonna love
yourself?
- [laughing]
- 'Cause you are America.
- It sounds so familiar.
- Yes.
- And you're just gonna stand
there.
You're not gonna do any of
the sensual Puerto Rican...
- I could be quiet.
- Yes.
- And I will express my cha-cha
inside.
- [laughing]
All right, Yara, I'll let you
get back to work.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- ♪ Oh, shan-ge-la, girl ♪
- Yes, Ru.
- Now, why are you proud to be
an American?
- Well, you know, my mom was in
Desert Storm twice,
and then she also fought
in Bosnia,
and she would call home, and she
would be like, "Make me laugh.
Tell me something funny."
so that's kind of the spirit of
what I want my P.S.A. to be.
All the way, wherever the
troops are,
I want to make them smile too.
- I'm excited.
- Yay. Me too.
- All right, get back to work.
- Thank you, Ru.
- All right.
Hey, Alexis.
- Hi, Ru.
- America.
- What's it mean to you?
- It's love. It's freedom.
- Do you know anybody
in the military?
- [sighs]
Three years ago, I met somebody
very special in my life.
We get our relationship
very secretly,
and, like, the best moments
of my life was with him.
And he got called to go to
service,
and I don't know nothing about
him since, like,
a year and a half, so I really
don't know if he's okay.
- During the P.S.A.,
are you going to be speaking
directly to him?
- I would love to.
- What would you say to him
right now?
- I would say I'm sorry,
because I took us
in a wrong way.
Like, I felt abandoned,
and I didn't say anything before
he left.
I was really upset.
I want to say I'm sorry and that
I love him so much
and that I am very proud of him.
- Your story is shared by
thousands of others
who have had people they love go
overseas to serve their country.
I have a feeling yours is gonna
be very heartfelt.
But keep it entertaining, okay?
All right, kiddo, get to work.
- Thank you.
- All right.
All right, dolls, this one's
for Lady Liberty,
so do me proud and don't fuck
it up.
I'll see you in a moment.
[fanfare]
- This week, for our main
challenge,
we're filming a public service
announcement,
basically, to the troops
and to share about
loving being an American.
- Hello!
- All right, you can use any
of the props you'd like,
including the pit crew.
- Mmm.
- Your ten minutes starts now.
- You know what?
Here we go,
'cause nothing says "I love
America" like a dog.
Not only are you protecting
we humans,
but also the furrier kind.
- Cut.
Shangela, do you think you're
getting your message across
as to why you love America?
- It's because of the freedom
that we have here, the freedom
that you're out there
protecting.
- I wish you'd be saying this
right now to the camera.
- Okay, we'll do that.
- Every moment counts.
[The Star-Spangled Banner tune]
- ♪ From the heart ♪
♪ Of all the gays ♪
Oh, no, baby, I'm a solo act.
Y'all can go off now.
Thank you.
♪ And the home ♪
♪ Of the ♪
♪ Of the g-a-a-a-a-ays ♪
- Carmen, are you ready to do
your P.S.A.?
- Um...
- That's a yes or no answer.
- All right, well, let's just
start.
- Carmen, if I were you,
I would squat all the way down
and then come up.
Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
- But don't do that.
- Okay, okay, okay.
All right,
the Statue of Liberty.
Hey!
No foam here!
- Uh-huh, it's all real--
100% American,
made in the U.S.A.
- All right, so I'm gonna be
in the mirror,
and then I'm gonna be doubting
myself.
I'm gonna be like, "Oh!"
you know, like, "Mm!
Maybe I'm not that pretty."
- Carmen, look at me.
Don't explain it, just do it.
30 seconds.
- The American dream for me is
to have, like, wigs
and jewelry and hot dogs
and balloons.
Ooh!
- I'm Yara Sofia.
I'm puertorriqueña.
I'm American girl!
Right now I'm not wearing
no clothes.
- Betsy Ross,
eat your heart out.
- Oh, definitely.
- This is where--
Oh, I'm sorry, and go.
I love America 'cause I'm --
ah, fuck.
I love America.
I le--ah, ah, fahh!
- Take a deep breath,
and you got it.
- It's okay.
- I love America
'cause America let me be...
[strumming guitar]
a musician.
I want to make the troops laugh.
It's a hard time for them,
and they need to laugh,
'cause laugh cures everything.
[shouting]
[Mexican Hat Dance]
Hey!
- Only in America will you
find the diversity of different
backgrounds and ethnicities,
and each of them offer a
different kind of food to eat.
And I love to eat food.
[imitating flatulence]
- We got that.
Let's see what else you have.
- Okay.
Ooh, sweet cherry pie.
Hold it like this so people can
see the length of it, honey.
Oh! Yes!
That was good.
Mmm!
- Manila, just bring it back
to America
and why you love America.
- Boys out there serving our
country,
when you come back,
there is going to be
all the food you can eat.
- [laughing]
- Oh, my God.
- My name is Raja.
I'm proud to be an American.
America, the land--
sorry.
The land where it--sorry.
- Can we get some of the joy
of what you're saying?
I can see you reading
your script in your head.
- So far, all I've been able
to do
is just present this funny side
of me
or a very serious kind
of runway look.
You think I could fit my giraffe
ass in there?
- [laughing]
- This is my opportunity
to just be pretty this time
and pinup-y.
- Anything you want to say
to our troops?
- Um...
- Look at the camera.
- Speak from the heart.
- Oh.
God bless the troops.
- Mm, nice.
- Oh!
- Alexis Mateo!
- Hello!
- Wow!
- Hi, Michelle. Hi, Ru.
I am very nervous about what
I have to say,
because there's a lot of things
going in my mind right now
that are not that happy.
But at this point, I just want
to go
and do my best in front
of the camera.
- Action!
- It's time for a party.
It's a U.S.A. American
celebration!
I met the love of my life.
Now he serve in the U.S.
Military corps.
Papi, I want you to come back
home, baby!
- Ooh, yeah.
- That's right, just pick it up.
- Yeah, keep it going.
- And even if I was born on
the moon,
I would still be in America.
Sexy, no?
- What?
What did she say?
- Sexy, no?
This is so corny, I love it.
- [laughing]
- I think the troops are gonna
say,
"Who the hell is this crazy-ass
drag queen?"
Bam!
Get it, baby.
Only in America can a woman like
me have a freakin' chorizo!
- [laughing]
- Yes, baby!
Bam!
Oh!
- Yeah, catch your breath.
- You got a cramp, girl?
- I'm trying to feel where's
my genitals right now.
- Yes, yes, yes.
Ladies, thank you for serving
your country.
Now, tomorrow I want you to
wear
your most patriotic outfits
to the main stage,
where we will be joined by two
American icons.
Swimsuit supermodel,
the legendary Cheryl Tiegs
will be here...
all: Ooh!
- And Olympic figure skater
Johnny Weir.
- Word!
Oh, my God, Johnny Weir.
Love her!
I'm gonna lick her if she gets
anywhere near me.
- Good-bye for now,
and God bless America.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- Yoo-hoo!
Show must go on.
- Good mornin'.
- We're back in the workroom
this morning,
and we are getting ready
for our patriotic runway.
- Do you guys think that it was
a little difficult
to be entertaining and heartfelt
at the same time?
- When you're not putting on an
act and you're being yourself,
it's not difficult to put your
feelings in front of everybody
at the same time being yourself.
- The way that I did mine was
that the spoken word
was heartfelt, and the visual
was entertaining.
- Did you speak in English
and Spanish?
- No, girl.
- But you speak Spanish,
don't you?
- No, I don't.
I understand Spanish.
- No, you speak Spanish.
- I speak broken Spanish.
- She does.
- You're Puerto Rican, right?
- Uh-huh.
But my mom is very Americanized.
- I would love to see Carmen
embrace Puerto Rican things.
- I know Puerto Rican culture.
It's always been part of my life
since I was little, but I think
that Yara and Alexis don't think
that I'm Puerto Rican enough,
which I don't care.
[upbeat music]
- Work, Marine Corps.
I'm gonna wear
the military jacket,
because no matter
what I'm wearing
and no matter
if I'm a drag queen
I wanted to show respect
for the militaries
and the Army,
and I hope I look great.
- Ooh, you're so
Michael Jackson.
"Hee-hee!"
- That's a man.
- This challenge
was kind of hard to me,
'cause I will like to entertain
and do happy things.
I don't want to remember
the year
that my father went to Iraq.
I miss my mom and my dad
so bad.
This challenge remembered me
my dad, of course.
He is Army Reserve.
- I'm sure they miss you too.
- Yes.
A few years ago
we didn't have my father, like,
on year,
and it was so, so hard.
Guys, I'm so loud.
Without me, the house sounds
really empty.
Sometimes when I'm next
to my father,
like, I drop things and--
"Oh!"
Like, watch out, girl!
Watch out, girl!
Don't be so gay here.
[laughs]
- And you get along with him
well?
- Yes.
- Yes. [laughs]
[RuPaul laughing]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl]
Hey, guys.
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage?
- Yes, baby?
- God bless America.
And one of our forefathers,
Santino, is here.
Hi, honey.
I am so proud to be a part of
the Wig Party.
- I pledge my allegiance to you,
Ru.
- Good.
And Cheryl Tiegs,
the all-American girl, is here.
So glad you're here tonight.
- Thank you, sugar.
- And Johnny Weir is here
with us tonight.
Hi, Johnny.
- Hey, Ru, thanks for having me.
I am tucked in anticipation.
- Good. And keep it that way.
This week our queens were
challenged
to create patriotic
public service announcements
to send to our troops overseas.
Now, wearing their best
Yankee Doodle drag,
we salute them.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Manila...
for the love of money.
- Great Gatsby, look at her.
- My patriotic look is a 1920s
flapper silhouette,
but instead of fringe,
it's hundreds,
because there's nothing more
American
than the American U.S. "d."
- In God we trust.
- Carmen Carrera...
look at that pinup.
- The look for today's runway
is Carmen Carrera meets
Dita Von Teese in the 1950s.
- I love the stones accenting
the money bits in the back.
- Yes, the moneymaker.
Exactly.
- Star-spangled bang her.
[laughter]
- Alexis Mateo, giving you
military drag.
- An officer and a lady.
- I turned out a U.S. Official
uniform into a evening gown.
- I want to see where
the pistol's hidden.
- Yes.
Who are you wearing?
Oh, wait.
Don't ask, don't tell.
- Exactly.
[laughter]
- Yara Sofia...
Now, this is a traditional
Puerto Rican costume, isn't it?
- Is it?
- Yeah, I saw it on a J.Lo
special.
- [laughing]
- This is the national costume
from Puerto Rico.
It's very patriotic,
but there is a surprise.
- Oh, what's happening?
- Oh!
- This is a traditional
Puerto Rican outfit.
- We see her rice
and her beans.
- Yes, we do.
- Mm.
- Yara, did you double-park
your invisible plane?
This is Shangela.
A bouquet?
Wow.
- What I have to wear is simple,
but it's still patriotic.
It's like classic '50s,
Marilyn Monroe-esque,
but I'm gonna turn it
Shangie style.
- She's serving a little
Eva Longoria.
- A little bit of Marilyn Monroe
there for a second.
- Happy birthday, Mr. President.
- Oh, wow!
- Nava-ho.
- How!
- That's all I ever heard.
- I've chosen tonight to do
a look
that's a little bit
Native American
and a lot of rock and roll.
- "Dances with drag queens."
- Yes.
"Legend of the Walks Far
Woman."
Welcome, my fellow
drag Americans.
- Yes.
- All right, let's get to it.
Let's start with Shangela.
Cheryl, what'd you think of
Shangela's runway presentation?
- The outfit is very, uh,
simple.
You see the others--there's
a lot more going on.
- The lame is coming off
a little lame for me.
You know, it's not quite
banging enough.
- Thank you, Amadeus.
- [laughing]
- Let's take a look at your
P.S.A.
- Hey, all you fierce-ass
freedom fighters, it's me,
Shangela, and let me tell you,
I appreciate you out there.
We miss you, and we want you
home safely...
[The Star-Spangled Banner tune]
♪ From the heart ♪
♪ Of all the gays ♪
Ooh!
♪ And the troops ♪
♪ I love yo-o-o-u ♪
Hallelu.
- [laughing]
- I thought you did a really
good job on your P.S.A.
You knew exactly what you were
gonna do.
- Hallelu.
[laughter]
- I felt like the costume,
the singing, everything was
so fun and vibrant.
- All right, next up,
Carmen Carrera.
- The Statue of Liberty--
ever since I was a child,
it has been a symbol of freedom,
acceptance, and diversity
for everyone to be able to live
the American dream.
Our forefathers have made it
possible for us,
and now it's you who's ensuring
the future of our children.
- Yes.
- Carmen, you have to stay
in character.
You have a tendency to,
dare I say, look bored.
- That was my biggest thing.
I wanted you to excite me
and make me want to sign up,
but it was just very, very
soft.
I just wanted a little bit more
command of the voice,
especially with this attitude
and this look that you've got.
- Carmen, when you first
came out, I gasped.
It was very sultry.
Standing here, you've lost that
a little bit.
- You're standing there like
you could really give two shits
about what we think.
- No, I don't want you
to think that.
- But that's how it's coming
across.
All right, ladies, next up,
Alexis Mateo.
Now, you told me in
the workroom
that you had a lover who went
to war.
Did you direct your P.S.A.
toward him?
- I tried to make my P.S.A.
a little bit underground message
for him.
Oh, my gosh, if he was watching
right now,
I would've loved to say that
I miss him a lot.
Inside my heart,
I'm still waiting for you.
- Well, let's take a look
at your patriotic P.S.A..
- It's Alexis Mateo con sabor
from Puerto Rico!
This is the only land
where you can grow up and become
whoever you want to be.
I'm a fucking drag queen!
Ha ha ha!
Bam!
Papi, I want you to come back
home, baby!
Celebrate life.
Celebrate love.
Celebrate freedom.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Ooh-ee.
- Bam, Michelle Visage.
- Bam!
Alexis, you came out with one
thing you wanted to do.
That was dance and be happy with
a piece of lame,
and it worked.
We couldn't breathe,
we were laughing so hard.
- Your P.S.A. was so much fun.
"I'm a fucking drag queen!"
That sums it up.
That's right, mama.
- Thank you, Beethoven.
Is this the jacket of
your ex-boyfriend?
- Yes, he left me this
as a memory.
So today I decide to wear it.
- If you're all covered up
in the high neck on the jacket,
show us a little something.
You know, you don't have
to show us everything.
I don't want to see your
honey basket.
- [laughs]
- I love a queen in uniform.
And you respected this,
and by "respect,"
I mean definitely put
Swarovskis all over it.
[laughter]
- All right, next up,
Yara Sofia.
Yes, ma'am.
- This is the national costume
for dancing.
It's called bomba.
This is also part
of their religion.
It's called Santeria.
- You're not gonna kill
a chicken, are you?
- No, no!
- 'Cause I'm hungry, girl.
Let's take a look and see
what happened.
- I'm Yara Sofia,
and I love America.
America let me be the Latina!
I feel free, darling!
Hey!
If you don't love America,
how the hell you gonna love
yourself?
- Okay, guapa, this is the deal.
Your P.S.A.,
don't just be crazy.
If you're gonna be crazy,
be crazy with a purpose.
I expect more from you now,
Yara.
- It was a little bit crazy.
I'm not gonna lie.
There wasn't a lot of class
and integrity in it.
I just thought it was kind of
jumping all over the place.
- All right, next up,
our flapper, Manila.
Tell us about your look.
- Well, I'm trying to go for
a thoroughly modern millionaire.
- Oh, I love it.
Well, let's take a look
at your P.S.A.
- I'm an American,
and I love to eat out at
different kinds of restaurants.
Only in America will you find
the diversity
of different backgrounds
and ethnicities,
and each of them offer a
different kind of food to eat--
hot dogs, sushi, Italian,
kielbasa.
[imitating flatulence]
Oh, America, you taste so good.
- Being a lady, I am not quite
so sure
about when you emit some gas.
[laughs]
- Relying on a fart joke
in the P.S.A.,
the message of having freedom
of choice
just got completely lost
for me.
- Thank you, Mr. Lagerfeld.
- [laughing]
- Manila, I am so in love
with you tonight.
I love everything about this
look on you.
It's absolutely stunning to me.
I just gotta be honest, I can't
stand you as a blonde girl.
- The blond wig and the outfit,
I just felt I saw
Jessica Simpson,
and I feel like I wouldn't want
to look like Jessica Simpson.
- All right, next up, Raja.
Can you get more American than
Native American?
- How.
- [laughing]
- Let's take a look at your
patriotic P.S.A.
- I'm Raja, and I'm proud to be
am American.
Growing up in Indonesia,
my parents taught me that I
could be
whatever I wanted to be.
America--where the son
of immigrants
can wear her freedom proudly.
- Raja, I thought you were
amazing on the runway.
The P.S.A. was a little stiff.
- Take me to your tepee.
- Okay.
- I saw Cher, like Half Breed,
Janis Joplin, and it's awesome.
- Thank you, Gandalf.
- [laughing]
- It's kind of like there are
two versions of being cold.
The runway walk,
it's cold in a way
that is so scorching and so hot
that you can freeze anyone
that's watching you.
And then when the video came up,
it was just a wet, dead fish.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Now, while you go and untuck
in the Interior Illusions
lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
[engine turning]
Now, just between us girls,
what do you think?
Let's start with Shangela.
- The fit on that dress
is horrid.
It's slightly American,
patriotic--slightly.
- I really feel that a polished
drag queen
would never come in that outfit
tonight.
- Right.
- The performance on the runway
tonight--it was just kind of...
♪ Wah wah ♪
- I thought her P.S.A. was kind
of canned.
Felt that it was kind of like
part of her shtick.
Carmen Carrera...
- The P.S.A.
was personality-less.
- Yeah.
- She was a stink-ball.
- She did her beautiful walk.
She looked lovely,
and then she stood there,
and she may as well have been
chewing on a piece of wheat,
taking a dump, doing her nails.
This girl, if she ever wants
to be a huge success--
people will not buy tickets,
she will not be able to pay
her rent,
and she will be flipping
burgers.
- She will die penniless.
- Yes.
- Alexis Mateo...
She seemed very somber
on the runway.
- I liked the somberness,
because she was being
a respectable
marine woman to me.
I felt like it was part
of the persona.
- I laughed hard at her P.S.A.
I thought it was very funny.
And her jumpsuit--
it was just amazing.
It was like the ugliest fabric,
but--and the silhouette was
so on point and so fun,
I couldn't take my eyes off
of her.
- Yara...
- I was really thrown when
I first saw her in that curly,
frizzy hair.
I didn't like that, because she
was quite stunning,
I thought, on the runway.
- This P.S.A. that's wild
and over-the-top,
it very shrill for me.
You're constantly
going, going, going.
When is it going to stop?
- Her P.S.A. Fell flat for me.
Yara has to rein it in.
- Right.
- It doesn't...
[blurting gibberish]
All the time have to be out
there like that.
- Let's move on to Manila.
- Manila lost me within the
first five seconds,
uh, because of going in the
direction of bathroom humor.
- It's comedy, people.
Why does everything have to be
so serious?
I appreciate a good crass video.
There's a lot of people like me
out there,
and I loved her runway look
tonight.
- Raja...
- I like Raja.
That costume, which was so
outrageous--
she just carried it,
and I really like that.
- As the pinup girl in her
P.S.A.,
really stunning, beautiful.
But when she starts to speak,
there's a disconnect.
- The message was beautiful,
but it was as flat as I was
before Dr. 90210.
- Hello.
- Okay?
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your performance
in the patriotic challenge
and your presentation
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Shangela, your runway
presentation
was underwhelming.
And compared to the others,
your P.S.A. Was just okay.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Manila...
you made a meal out
of this challenge.
But it left a bad taste in some
of the judges' mouths.
You...
are safe.
- Thank you.
- Carmen Carrera.
You're pretty.
But your patriotic P.S.A.
lacked pizzazz and personality.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- I'm in the bottom,
and I'm a little surprised.
I'm not a mediocre bitch.
- Alexis Mateo,
you turned sadness
into gladness
and made us proud.
Con-drag-ulations, you are the
winner of this challenge.
[applause]
You've won a three-piece,
super-lightweight,
luxury-luggage set from Antler.
Yes, Antler.
- Thank you.
- Is there anything you'd like
to say?
- [sighs]
I know some things that happen
in life--
it teach you a lot of, like,
valuable lessons.
And this one helped me to grow,
'cause I normally depend a lot
from people.
And I want to say thank you
to that special person
that's shown me
that I needed to love myself
first.
- Alexis, you may join
the other girls.
- Thank you.
- Raja...
You pummeled the runway.
But when it came to the
challenge,
you stumbled.
Yara Sofia...
Your performance in the P.S.A.
was entertaining,
but are you resting on wacky?
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- I am very in shock.
I cannot breathe.
I cannot cry.
I cannot laugh.
I don't know why I am
in the bottom two.
- Raja, you are safe.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight, you were
asked
to prepare a lip-synced
performance
of Mickey by Toni Basil...
in Spanish.
- Yara doesn't have an advantage
over me
just 'cause she speaks Spanish.
I want to make this one one
for the history books.
- Ladies, this is your
last chance
to impress me
and save yourselves from
elimination.
The time has come for you to
lip-sync...
para tu vida!
Good luck.
And do not...
fuck it up.
[Toni basil singing in Spanish]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Hey, Mickey ♪
- Oh, my god, Carmen--
she knows every single word,
and she is just pooching
the song.
She better work, Heather.
- [laughing]
♪ ♪
- Yara was very patriotic,
and she's doing Puerto Rico
very proud.
- We are doing our lip sync,
and Carmen is kissing Johnny.
It's not kissing for your life.
♪ ♪
[applause]
- Work, Carmen! Work!
Work, Yara!
- Ladies...
I have made my decision.
Carmen Carerra...
shante, you stay.
- Thank you.
- Yara Sofia...
shante, you stay.
- [softly] What?
Are you joking, Ru?
No, no, do not joke that way,
please.
- For the first time in
Drag Race history,
no one is going home tonight.
This is the land of opportunity.
And I've decided you both
deserve
to stay and fight another day.
Now, remember, if you can't love
America,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
[laughing]
Can I get a "amen" in here?
all: Amen!
- All right, let the music play.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Grand prize contributed
in part
by AlandChuck.travel.