- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
It's Christmastime
at RuPaul's Drag Race.
[cheers and applause]
[dramatic music]
- Hallelu, ladies!
[people cheering]
- What the fuck?
- Hi!
- I don't know
what I was thinking.
And if I have to lip synch,
I'll motherfucking lip-sync
my life off.
- Oh, it's Venus D-Lite.
Mimi Imfurst.
Shangela.
Raja.
Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
Two queens stand before me.
- I'm in disbelief.
A year later,
and here I am again
in the bottom two.
- Shangela, shantay, you stay.
Venus D-Lite, sashay away.
- Thank you.
- And tonight...
are you ready to have
some psychic fun?
The dolls gaze into the future.
- ♪ Ah ♪
- And it's out of this world.
Prepare to gag on my eleganza.
- With extra special
guest judges
Caprica's Alessandra Torresani
and the legendary Lily Tomlin.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup;
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails
perfected by Absolut;
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen,
start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ R-R-RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen,
start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman,
best woman win ♪
[tires screech]
- Oh.
- Here we go, ladies.
- Oh, hallelujah.
No more snow.
- Oh, thank god.
- Oh, she left a message.
- "Don't be shady.
Be a lady."
- We had our first elimination.
I see Venus' message
on the mirror,
and it's just a finalization
that one of my sisters from home
is now gone,
and I'm feeling
completely vulnerable.
- I've never done this before,
'cause I was the first one to go
last time.
It's what happens
when you push Shangela.
[laughter]
I survived.
But I don't even feel like
the same Shangela.
I'm battered, bruised.
My spirit is beat down.
- Well, glad you're still here,
Curly.
- Oh, thank you.
- Just stay here longer,
and don't wear none of them
crazy-ass outfits.
- Okay, well...
Manila's coming over
to talk to me,
and all I hear really is,
"Blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah."
I just don't want to be
bothered.
- I know you have some cute
drag up in here, so...
- I do.
I actually do have a lot
of good stuff in here.
- Do you think Venus
should have gone home?
- Yes.
It's all about a line of
professionalism.
You know, we all want this,
like, really bad,
but you guys will never have to
deal with that with me.
The competition part
has really kicked in.
You're like, "People really do
go home."
Everything we've worked for
and wanted for so long
is over like that.
- Venus is gone.
The jig is up.
Let's see what's next.
I'm pushing myself 100% forward
and harder to stay here.
I think Shangela, she need to be
very careful,
'cause the queens in this season
are really fierce,
including me first.
- If I was to go home at that
moment, I would have...
[sighs]
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl!
You've got she-mail.
Drag, the final frontier.
These are the voyages
of the starship Drag Race,
a one-year mission
to boldly tuck
where no man has tucked before.
[men exclaiming]
Set a corset for warp speed,
because this mothership is
about to blast off.
[laughter]
Hello, hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and applause]
Look at you all.
For today's mini challenge,
I'm looking for two ladies
with a little something extra.
I'm talking about ESP,
extrasensory perception.
I need you to pair up
with the queen
you feel the strongest
psychic connection with.
The one team that gets the most
correct matches wins.
Raja, you'll be giving
mental vibrations,
and, Delta, you'll be receiving.
- Delta and I are very
psychically connected,
or at least I hope we are,
because Delta knows a lot
about me.
Delta knows how many cab drivers
I've slept with.
Delta knows all kinds of shit.
- Delta, what wig
is Raja wearing?
- It's brunette.
- What color ring?
- The white diamond.
Last question.
What color is the pussycat?
[cat meows]
- Pink.
- So, Phoenix, what color boa
is Mariah wearing?
- Day-Glo green.
- What color is the pussycat?
- This is definitely
a black pussycat.
- I don't know where she got the
lime green boa from,
but everybody needs a black
pussycat in their life.
- All right, Carmen,
please send it hard.
[whip cracks]
Ow--ow.
Oh, okay.
Girl's wearing a purple boa.
- Okay.
Stacy Layne Matthews,
what color pussycat?
- I'll say a pink pussycat.
- ♪ Ah ♪
- I'm gonna say pink.
- Okay, a pink wig.
- Yes.
- All right.
- Let me find it.
Let me find it.
- Find it, honey.
- It's coming through.
It's coming through.
And she's wearing the green one.
- The green one.
- Yes.
- All right.
Now, I've tested your ESP.
And the winning team
is Phoenix and Mariah.
[cheers and applause]
How about that?
The next drag superstar
has to prove
that her charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
is truly out of this world.
Now, for today's main challenge,
you'll be shooting scenes for
the new sci-fi movie saga...
[voice echoing]
Drag Queens in Outer Space.
You'll be splitting up
into two teams.
Phoenix and Mariah, together
you won the mini challenge,
but now you are
competing captains.
men: Ooh!
- I see Phoenix,
she's my rival now,
and I think I'm gonna
wear her out.
- I definitely have leadership
experience.
I could totally win
this competition, yeah.
- Now, Phoenix,
go ahead and choose
the first member of your team.
- Raja.
- Mariah.
- Arianna.
- Delta.
- Alexis.
- Ooh!
- They all fools, 'cause I have
an acting company.
So their loss
if they don't pick me.
- India.
- Shangela.
- Manila.
- High-five, team.
- Stacy.
Of course had to get with
big girl Miss Stacy, honey.
- Phoenix, two are left,
Carmen and Mimi.
Who are you choosing?
- Carmen.
- Carmen's coming on over,
which of course means that Mimi
is going to Mariah's side.
- By not picking me, the other
team is gonna be sorry.
[people cheering]
- I'm on Phoenix's team,
and I feel amazing.
I feel like that's,
like, the dream team.
We have, like, the most talent.
I'm looking across the room,
and I'm like, "Ugh.
A bunch of boogers."
- In these two envelopes, I have
two scripts,
Drag Queens in Outer Space:
From Earth to Uranus,
and the sequel,
Return to Uranus.
- Thank you.
- Now, your sci-fi movie
trailers
will make their world debut
on the main stage tomorrow.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
- All right.
Let's go scandalous.
I want to be Boobarella.
Hermaphrodite, which is this
genderfuck evil queen,
mannish and womanly
at the same time,
and is absolutely jealous
of Boobarella's beauty.
- The villainess,
Hermaphrodite, is Mimi.
Fitting.
You better get your Oscar,
bitch.
- I'm gonna give you
Meryl Streep realness.
You got to get ugly
to win the prize.
- And, Tweaker,
this is perfect for you,
an alien space monkey.
The twinbots,
sexy robot twins.
Okay.
- Yes.
- I didn't want to pair up
with Shangela.
I mean, I haven't seen
no improvement.
She said she had worked
the whole entire year.
Where?
- We're filming
our sci-fi trailer today,
and we have to learn lines.
We got to make costumes.
- Yay, we have a great cast.
- Our cast is great, yes.
- We're gonna really win this.
- All right,
let's go over our lines.
- I feel like...
- Everybody, okay.
Let's start--start just going
over this.
- [clears throat]
- Phoenix's leadership skills
are a little questionable.
- All right, y'all ready?
- If you go to Mexico.
- It's actually a lot to
memorize.
- I think she was afraid and
really didn't assert herself.
Let's do our table reading.
- Okay.
- Bimborella,
looking for these?
- [high-pitched babbling]
- That's right, Tweaker.
- We've arrived at
Hermaphrodite's spaceship.
Prepare to tranny-port aboard.
- Twinbots, stay
on the lookout.
both: We are on the lookout.
- Y'all need to, like, come up
with a voice.
I don't want you to just use
your normal voice.
You're, like, robots.
- Rosie the robot, she wasn't
really that robot-y.
Her voice was kind of normal,
and...
- Yeah, we can be like,
"Oh, wait a minute."
- And in unison together.
- Yeah.
- Maybe I should have been
team leader.
- Lady Tata's been kidnapped?
- Prepare to gag
on my eleganza.
- The ship is surrounded
by a force field...
[laughs]
- We're trying to rehearsal,
and Mimi's being loud.
She's acting like
we're not there.
- I am...your father.
And your mother!
- Back off, Hermaphrodite.
- Your weapons are no good
here.
- That's not the line, baby.
"Your weapons won't work here."
- "Your weapons won't work
here."
- Read it.
- I got it, girl.
You get the punctuation
in your line.
I'll get my lines, all right?
- But just read the script.
You're doing your thing.
No tea.
Just read the scripts.
- Let's refocus.
Let's refocus.
- Mimi already is trying to show
that she is the star
of this group,
that she's standing out.
Miss Mimi, we know
you're talented, honey.
We know you have
the theater background.
Can we get through
one read-through, please?
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hey, Ru!
- Now, I'm just checking in
on my budding starlets.
all: Hey, Ru.
- Let's start with Team Phoenix,
From Earth to Uranus.
- That's right.
- Now who's playing what role?
- We've got Delta playing
Boobarella.
- Okay.
Pleasure to meet you.
Phoenix, I'm surprised
you didn't take the lead,
Boobarella, for yourself.
- I think she will make
an amazing Boobarella.
She's got this one.
Look--hello!
She's got it.
- And what is Manila playing?
- This is the Tweaker.
- Tweaker the she-monkey?
- Yes.
- That's hot.
You do have to create
your own language.
- Yes.
- Can you give us a little
taste of what that sounds like?
- I'm gonna be like...
[high-pitched babbling]
- That's beautiful.
- She ordered the Cobb salad.
- Yeah, she...
[laughter]
Now, I want to hear the twins do
a line together.
- Twinbots,
stay on the lookout.
both: We are on the lookout...
for single guys.
[both giggle]
- [laughs]
Oscar!
All right, ladies, work hard.
I don't want to see drag queens;
I want to see movie stars.
All right, get to work.
all: Thank you.
- Team Mariah.
- Hey, Ru, what's happening?
- The cast of Return to Uranus.
This is an epic.
Now, Mariah, what role
are you playing?
- Uh, the milkmaid.
[laughter]
No, I'm playing Boobarella.
- You assigned yourself
the lead role.
- Actually, I think it was
slightly unanimous.
- [laughs]
Now, you all picked the sequel.
As you well know, most of
the time, sequels suck.
So you have your work cut out
for you.
Make sure
that it's a hit picture.
- Yes.
- All right,
I'm gonna leave you ladies
to get camera ready.
- Cool.
- Good luck.
all: Thank you.
- Ladies, on the set, you'll be
visited by Michelle Visage
and our extra-special
guest judge,
the star of the sci-fi series
Caprica,
my favorite Cylon,
Alessandra Torresani.
- Oh, awesome.
[applause]
- Alessandra Torresani.
She is fierce.
- Now, they'll be here
to give you some pointers.
This is your chance to shine.
So lights, camera,
and don't fuck it up.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Good luck, bitches.
- Good luck.
- Thanks, baby.
- I want to know why was I
fucking picked last.
- I don't know.
Why do you think?
- Do you think Phoenix
didn't pick me on purpose?
- I don't know.
- I heard she was--I heard that
she was threatened by me.
- She's threatened by you?
- Or she thought I was
her competition.
- I mean, if she's threatened
by you,
then she would think
that you were good,
and then that would be a benefit
to her
to have you on her team.
- Yeah.
- If she was strategizing
the way you think
she's strategizing.
- I just don't know.
- I didn't think that Phoenix
was threatened by her.
Phoenix hasn't mentioned that.
And I don't know what she could
possibly be threatened by.
Her name is Mimi Imfurst,
but she's not first,
and I don't even think
she's second.
I don't think anyone's placing
any bets on her.
- Hey, hey.
- Team Phoenix is on the set
of Drag Queens in Space:
From Earth to Uranus.
- Greetings, ladies.
all: Hi.
- I'd like to introduce you to
our guest judge today.
This is Alessandra.
- Hi, guys.
How are you?
- We will be directing
your performances today.
Let's get this show on the road.
- Let's do it.
- Bring it.
- Okay.
- Take one.
- Tata, twinbots,
we must intercept
the queen's spaceship,
or the balls will be held
in Uranus...
forever.
- Cut!
Delta.
- Yes.
- The line is "the queen's balls
will be stuck
in Uranus forever."
"Stuck" is the punch.
- Okay.
We must intercept
Hermaphrodite's spaceship,
or the queen's balls will be
stuck in her anus.
- That would be "Uranus."
Just so we're clear,
it's "Uranus."
It's a planet.
Family show, honey.
- At this point, I realize
I should have probably spent
more time
memorizing my lines
than primping my hair.
- Action.
- We've arrived on
Hermaphrodite's spaceship.
Prepare to tranny-port
in three, two, one.
all: Dragonauts away!
- Phoenix, you're delivering
all your lines
away from the camera.
We need to see
your gorgeous face.
- Okay.
- Tata, twinbots,
stay on the lookout.
both: We are on the lookout...
for single guys.
- We've arrived at
Hermaphrodite's spaceship.
Prepare to tranny-port aboard
in three, two, and one.
- Phoenix.
- Yes?
- You keep looking away, girl.
You're giving somebody else
your time.
- Okay.
- I'm like, "Bitch,
just get it together."
- Phoenix, what's your
character feeling right now?
- I think I'm kind of...
I don't really know.
- Exactly.
- Phoenix, let's say that you
are super scared.
- Okay.
- But you're trying
not to show it,
because you're trying to
impress Boobarella.
- Let's give you one more shot,
Phoenix.
Full of emotion, baby.
We know you got it.
- Okay.
- Twinbots, be on the lookout.
- Prepare to tranny-port aboard
in three, two, and one.
all: Dragonauts, away!
- Cut.
Okay, Raja and Manila.
- The idea of having
Michelle Visage sitting there
terrifies me a little bit,
because that woman scares me.
- And action.
- [chitters]
[laughter]
- I'm wearing the smallest
little leotard,
and I'm getting
a huge cameltoe.
Tweaker got pipe.
- Manila, you're all ears,
girl.
- Hmm?
[laughter]
- Action.
- The most gorgeous woman
in the universe?
Don't you need to be a woman
first?
- Kill 'em, Tweaker!
- Whaaa!
[imitating lasers firing]
- Manila, do not make fake
sound effect gun noises.
It's not your backyard.
It's a movie, darlings.
- I don't know.
- Just look gorgeous
and do your lines.
Action!
- Say what?
- Action?
- Oh.
[laughter]
- Lady Tata is to become...
my bride.
- Lady Tata would never marry
a Martian like you.
- Cut. Tata, you're giving us
Maya Angelou.
Give us just a little bit more
- Okay.
[laughter]
- I am from Crab Nebula, bitch!
- Yeah, Mimi, take it back
a little bit.
- Okay.
- Lower the energy
a little bit.
- Okay.
- Action!
- [screams]
- Miss Mimi.
There's a difference
in being talented
and being a showboat.
- Boobarella, I see you've
increased your war chest.
- Can I get the line?
- "Prepare to gag on my"...
- Thank you.
Prepare to gag on my eleganza!
[shrieks]
both: Get her, Boobarella!
- Shut the fuck up.
- No!
"Go fuck yourself."
- Go fuck yourself.
My lines have to be fed to me
a little bit,
and I'm like, "Oh, my god.
Please do not let me lead
these ladies off a cliff."
- [high-pitched babbling]
both: Has anyone ever told you
you look like an Ewok?
- The hardest part of my role
is to have to share it
with Shangela.
I wanted my spotlight.
both: Stop flirting!
You stop flirting!
Shut up!
No, you shut up!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, ho, ho, ho!
- Alexis and I,
as the twinbots,
we delivered when
we hit that set.
both: Dragonauts, away!
- And cut.
Nicely done.
Okay, that's a wrap, ladies.
Congratulations.
[cheers and applause]
Your sci-fi trailers will make
their world premiere
on the main stage tomorrow.
[cheers and applause]
Very exciting.
And Ru has asked you all to come
decked out in your finest
space-age couture.
[people gasp]
And we will be joined
by our extra-special, far-out
guest judge,
the legendary Lily Tomlin.
[cheers and applause]
- Lily motherfucking Tomlin.
You--you really--you don't get
better than that.
- All right, so until then,
live long and prosper.
[cheering]
[alarm beeps]
- Just as we left it.
- We're back in the work room.
Today we're getting ready for
the runway,
and we're all gonna get
decked up
in our shiny, metallic,
futuristic realness.
Miss Manila?
- Yeah?
- My hair is sticking through
in that wig.
Can you trim it?
- What, shave your hair?
- No, I just need you
to just trim the back.
- Can't you get someone else,
like the Delta or someone,
that does hair to do it?
- Mimi starts asking
the other queens,
"Will someone come over
and shave my head?"
Girl, what if I shave my head?
- And maybe have, like,
a little piece of hair
hanging down on the side?
That would be cute.
And have, like, a little
spit curl in the front.
- Do you want
to shave it real quick?
- Oh, uh-uh.
I don't have time, babe.
- I understand going
the extra mile,
but this is nothing but Mimi
pulling another production.
Her name should be
Cimi Imfurst,
because every time
we turn around,
she's doing something
for someone
to "see me, see me, see me."
- I feel so vulnerable.
I didn't hit the mark
in the challenge.
I wish I would have spent
a little more time
memorizing my lines,
because I expected more
from myself.
I hate how this thing, like--
you know what I mean?
Like, how is that even
a tight bobbin?
Like, that is not even
gonna work.
Now my job is to amp up
what it is that I wear,
how I conduct myself
on the runway.
I need to basically give 300%,
not 100%,
'cause it's just not enough.
Forget it. I'm using
somebody else's machine.
- [gasps]
How cyborg.
- Yeah, right.
- Yeah, your look is gonna be
on point.
- We will see.
I am team leader.
You know, I want to make sure
everything's perfect.
I need it to be on point.
I'm, like, a fucking nerv--
I, like, never get nervous.
- Why was I the villain?
Do you think of me as a villain?
- Yeah.
- How so?
- You could be antagonistic
if you--
- [laughs]
- Mimi, do you feel
that you worked well
with everyone in the group?
- I think so.
I think we had definitely
some clashing, but--
- Who clashed?
- I think you and I clashed,
girl.
- I think it's because
we both have
very strong personalities.
We both had an idea
of how we wanted the production
and our role to go.
But in the end,
you have to release
and trust each actor to be able
to take the role on
and put their own self into it.
- I'm really proud
of my performance
in the trailer.
I really think I hit it
out of the park.
- Shangela underestimated me,
but I know what I can do,
and now she does too.
So you're cool?
Me and you cool?
- Girl, we're always cool.
Listen, you can take nothing
personal in this life.
- Indeed.
- It has to be really severe.
- I look over, and Mimi puts on
this headpiece,
and I think she looks like
Uncle Fester
from Addams Family, honestly.
- Mimi looks ridiculous.
If that's what the future has
in hold for me
or for my kids
or for my grandkids,
I'm--I'm scared.
- [laughing]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl]
♪ ♪
- Hey, guys.
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
So what do you think
of my dress?
both: Whoo-hoo!
- Are those pussy willows?
- They sure are.
Santino, you've got it
every time.
Michelle Visage.
- Yes, my darlin'.
- Are you ready to have a close
encounter of the drag kind?
- I am tweaking my knobs
and setting a course direct
for the Milky Way.
- [laughs]
- Bring it.
- Alessandra Torresani.
My favorite Cylon.
You look gorgeous.
- You do as well.
- And the great Lily Tomlin
is here.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Now, this week, our girls made
their film debut
in the sci-fi saga
Drag Queens From Outer Space.
Now, decked out in their best
futurama glamorama,
they're ready for a blastoff.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win!
Space age.
- When I dress up, I'm always
looking for perfection
and a complete look,
and that's my strength.
- Does that outfit come
with solar panels?
Get ready for Raja.
- Whoo!
- All right, Miss Raja.
- C-3PO's girlfriend.
- Yes.
- Any time I'm on the runway,
I'm sparkling.
I'm having a blast up there, and
I'm doing my robot runway.
- The queen who fell to Earth.
Up next...
Wow, look at those.
- Oh.
- You're gonna put
somebody's eyes out
with those things.
- I'm feeling 100% diva
in my whole space costume.
Very Gaga,
very Christina Aguilera,
very Britney
all mixed into one.
- She's a galaxy girl.
- Yes, she is.
Up next...
Oh, wow!
Flash Gordon does drag.
- I'm just trying to show
in the runway
that I'm a little Power Ranger,
and I am feeling on fire.
- Wonder Woman
from outer space.
Her clone does not sleep alone.
- I'm in a body suit,
for god's sakes.
Just having curves
and just being able to walk
down the runway
and have the judges look at you
made me feel really good.
- Danger, Will Robinson.
Stacy Layne Matthews
is on the run.
Next, Shangela.
- Ooh.
- Shangela's
a real bubble head.
- Captain Shangela.
- She's a Starship Trooper.
- So I'm on the runway,
and I'm, like, "Ooh,
this is super hot."
I feel so much more confident
hitting it the second time back.
- The queen
of the space cadets.
Beam me up.
Up next, Mimi Imfurst.
Supersonic.
- My headpiece is inspired by
the planet Krypton.
I'm just going
to make my look be
as out of this world
as possible.
- Oh!
- Oh, my god, those eyes.
- She's serving satellite TV.
Oh, my stars.
That's some kind of futuristic
chastity belt.
- So I'm on the runway, praying
I don't trip over these shoes,
'cause they are a bitch
to walk in,
praying they like it.
But I'm feeling good.
- Kiss me. I dare ya.
From planet New Jersey...
She's blinding me with science.
- I'm walking that runway,
and I'm thinking,
"This hair better not come off,
"and I'm gonna keep my neck as
perched as I can,
"and I'll just shake my ass
a little bit
and just hope for the best."
- She's an astronaut.
- She's got a mind
for rocket science
but a body for sin.
Look who we have here.
Representing Atlanta, Mariah.
- Our hair looks very similar,
doesn't it?
- Yes, it does.
- I truly feel like supermodel
of the universe.
I am stomping that runway.
- She's not having any trouble
with her Tribbles.
All right, Delta Work.
She's giving us a total eclipse
of the heart.
- I'm hoping the judges are
going to love the difference
between what I'm wearing
and the sort of
metal-colored-inspired costumes
that they're seeing.
- She's a real Judy Jetsetter.
Next up, Manila Luzon.
That ensemble is just rocking
my universe.
- I'm coming down the runway,
and I'm giving evil henchwoman
realness.
I kind of wanted to separate
myself from the other girls,
because I think a lot of girls
kind of had, like,
a similar look.
- She's got a big dipper too.
- She sure do.
- Welcome, dolls.
Now it's blockbuster time.
Team Phoenix, let's take a look
at your trailer.
Help me, Boobarella.
You're my only hope.
- Whoo!
- Delta Work as Boobarella.
- I have a hunch things are
about to get a little ugly.
Twinbots, be on the lookout.
both: We are on the lookout...
for single guys.
[laughter]
- Carmen Carrera and
India Ferrah as the twinbots.
both: Resetting course.
- Prepare to tranny-port aboard
in three...
- Phoenix as Lady Tata.
- Two, and one.
- [laughs]
[warbling]
Bimborella.
You looking for these?
both: Give us back those balls.
- Sarlaccs!
- Raja as Hermaphrodite.
- No one can hear you
lip-synching in space.
Prepare to die.
- [high-pitched babbling]
- That's right, Tweaker.
- And Manila Luzon as Tweaker.
- Whoo!
Shama-la-la-la-la bing bong.
[weapons whooshing]
[laughter]
- Cute.
Wonderful.
- The other group
was all over the map.
I'm feeling really confident.
I think we could win this thing.
- Next up, Team Mariah.
Let's take a look at the sequel.
- [cackling]
- Prepare to gag
on my eleganza.
- Mariah as Boobarella.
- [shrieks]
There's something
I want you to know!
I am...your father.
- Mimi Imfurst as
Hermaphrodite.
- And your mother!
- Go fuck yourself.
- I did!
That's why I'm your father
and your mother!
- Ew!
- Stacy Layne Matthews
as Lady Tata.
- The gas levels indicate
that Uranus is burning.
both: Hey, Tweaker.
Stop flirting.
You stop flirting.
Shut up!
No, you shut up.
- Shangela and Alexis Mateo
as the twinbots.
- [screeching]
- Tweaker, no!
- Yara Sofia as Tweaker.
all: Dragonauts, away!
- Damn you, Boobarella...
Ella--ella--ay--ay--ay.
[screams]
[laughter]
- I am so happy, 'cause I was
so worried about my accent.
But it actually came out
very cute.
I'm so proud of myself
right now.
- Ladies, the reviews are in.
And based on your Drag Queens
in Outer Space movie trailers,
we've made some decisions.
The winning team is...
[dramatic music]
Team Mariah, Return to Uranus.
[people cheering]
Condragulations.
You are all safe.
- Thank you.
- Yes!
- But three of you emerged as
breakout stars.
Shangela.
Alexis.
The twinbots.
Mimi Imfurst.
- I'm feeling super confident.
Comparing myself
to everyone else in my group,
I think that I stand a good
chance of winning this one.
- I can only choose one.
Oh, damn the rules.
Let's call it a tie.
Shangela, Alexis,
condragulations.
You have won this challenge.
Each of you will receive a set
of hand-sculpted silicone
breastplates
courtesy of boobsforqueens.com.
[cheering and laughing]
Did you hear that, Lily?
Boobsforqueens.com.
- Yes, I did.
[laughter]
- However, neither one of you
will be granted immunity
next week.
Team Mariah.
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
Team Phoenix.
Each of you is up for
elimination
except, of course, for Raja.
You have immunity.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
Let's start with Phoenix.
What'd you think of Lady Tata?
- I think you could have been
a little zanier,
especially with a name like
Lady Tata.
- I do believe that you were
the weakest link in this cast.
- You just didn't commit.
Because you had fewer lines,
you should have committed 150%
just to show up everyone else.
- India Ferrah.
- I was very taken
with your bosoms.
I thought they were just
completely believable--
from this distance, anyway.
- I love, love, love this look.
- Thank you.
- This is Judy Jetson
does Vegas.
- Thank you, India.
All right, up next,
Carmen Carrera.
Now, Carmen, you're having some
trouble with your headpiece.
- This is, like, kind of
a mixture of super glue
and spray adhesive to my head.
It's literally pulling the hairs
out of my scalp.
- It's such an extraordinary
waistline.
It's just incredible.
You must have had a rib removed.
- I think your outfit today
is poorly conceived
and poorly designed.
- Carmen, stop relying
on that body.
- All right.
Thank you, Carmen.
Manila,
tell us about your outfit.
- I wanted to do, like, a
really sexy, like, Grace Jones,
Thierry Mugler-inspired,
like, catsuit.
- Well, you failed.
- [laughs]
- No, just joking.
- I thought your character
was great.
- Thank you.
- Very original and unexpected
and totally committed.
- Thanks, Manila.
Delta Work!
- You could've gone way out
with that Boobarella character.
You seemed more like a
combination of divine and Dali.
And I liked that.
- What is futuristic
about this look?
It looks a little dated, and
other than it being shiny,
I don't see space.
I don't see sci-fi.
I don't see the future.
- I sort of was inspired
by the look of that 1950s
and '60s feeling
of what space-age would be.
- Now, what about
her performance as Boobarella?
- In the performance aspect,
you had to do
a million things at once.
I think for your first time
on film,
I think that was a very hard
character for you to play,
but you did listen to us.
- All right, ladies.
I want a piece of advice
from you.
Who should be going home
tonight?
Manila.
- I think...
Phoenix.
She was our leader,
and I think that the leader
has to take responsibility.
Carmen.
- I kind of agree with Manila.
She was our leader.
- India.
- Phoenix,
one of the first things
she actually told us to do
was, you know, change our voices
for our characters,
so that's one of the things that
I expected from her as well.
- All right, Phoenix.
- I think for you to come out
in just a catsuit
that I have 15 of,
I don't really think
that's worth $75,000.
- But you're wearing
a catsuit.
- I think that I've got
so much more of a $75,000 look.
- Manila, is there something
you want to say
about your $75,000 catsuit?
- [laughs]
- I got this made for $100,
so I guess I could make
75...uh, hundred.
- Do the math, honey.
- I'm Asian,
but I don't do math.
[laughter]
Sorry.
- All right.
All right, Delta,
it's your turn.
Who do you think should go home
tonight?
- Based on the runway
presentation,
I would say myself.
- All right, Raja.
- I just don't like the idea of
the possibility
of my friend leaving,
'cause Delta and I--
I was so excited to see my
very good friend here with me
in this process.
I hope that if she has to
lip-synch for her life,
that she fucking lip-syncs
for her mother[bleep] life.
You know what I'm saying?
- Amen.
- Thank you, Raja.
Thank you, ladies.
Now, while you untuck in
The Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
All right, ladies, ladies.
Just between us girls,
let's start with Phoenix.
- I was gagging.
She was horrible, and she didn't
look very good either.
- She was definitely nervous
the whole time.
- But her runway ensemble today
looked really futuristic
and great.
- India Ferrah.
- Well, I liked her costume.
It was nicely pulled together
and interesting.
- I was saying, are we gonna
see the boobs every time?
- I have a feeling, yes.
- Yeah?
- [laughs]
- On to Carmen.
- I didn't think her costume
was well designed.
- It's a bikini with a corset.
- She came out, and she had
her sort of head pulled down
so that the thing--I thought
she had osteoporosis.
- You wanted to give her
some calcium.
- Yes!
Is she out of her league?
- She needs to step up
her game.
- Now Manila.
She took what could have been
a disaster of a role,
and she ran with it.
- Oh, yeah.
She was great.
- Delta Work.
When she described what she was
doing, a retro look,
I understood it.
It's just the execution of it
wasn't well done.
Did she have trouble
with her dialog?
- She did indeed.
We had to go over that
quite a few times.
But she really wanted to get it
right, bless her heart.
She wasn't like...
[scoffs]
Like, she really was listening
and really took the direction.
I thought we were happy
with some of the decisions
she made as an actress.
- Now, the decisions she made
as a stylist
on the runway tonight,
not so much?
- She's contacting
a different person in her head.
- Yeah.
- It didn't look Judy Jetson.
- I felt like when she was
standing next to everybody else,
she felt, like, almost sheepish.
- Silence!
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Raja, you have immunity.
- Yes, I do.
- You're safe.
- Thanks.
- Manila, you had us at...
[high-pitched babbling]
Condragulations.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Phoenix, now, as team leader
and Lady Tata,
you let us down.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- I do not want to go home
up against people that are
not as good as I am.
- India Ferrah.
Condragulations, you are safe.
Carmen.
Your runway presentation was
weak and lacked vision.
Delta,
your Boobarella was curvaceous,
but your look on the main stage
left us flat.
Carmen...
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Delta, my dear, I'm sorry,
but you are up for elimination.
- I knew that Ru was gonna
announce me
to lip-sync for my life.
I don't know that I should have
been there,
but I didn't think our entire
team should have been there.
I mean, I thought it was a load
of crap.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourselves
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-sync
for your life.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Ra ra, ah ah ah ♪
♪ Rom-a, rom-ma-ma ♪
♪ Gaga, ooh la la ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ Ra ra, ah ah ah ♪
♪ Rom-a, rom-ma-ma ♪
♪ Gaga, ooh la la ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ I want your ugly ♪
♪ I want your disease ♪
♪ I want your everything ♪
♪ As long as it's free ♪
♪ I want your love ♪
♪ Love, love, love ♪
- Get it, bitch.
I want them to see the fire
that is in my eyes right now.
- ♪ I want your love
and I want your revenge ♪
♪ You and me could write
a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- I see Phoenix, you know,
copying a few of Gaga's moves,
and I think that's just poor
entertainment, honestly.
Don't copy anyone else.
And Delta was being herself,
and, you know, not trying to be
Lady Gaga.
- ♪ Caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
- I'm not trying to be shady
in any way,
but Phoenix is a man
doing movements.
- ♪ Walk, walk, fashion, baby ♪
♪ Work it,
move that bitch crazy ♪
♪ Walk, walk, fashion, baby ♪
♪ Work it,
move that bitch crazy ♪
♪ I want your love,
and I want your revenge ♪
♪ You and me could write
a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh,
oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ Caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ Ra ra, ah ah ah ♪
♪ Rom-a, rom-ma-ma ♪
♪ Gaga, ooh la la ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
[applause]
- Wow.
- Phoenix.
Delta.
I have made my decision.
Delta Work.
Shantay, you stay.
- [exhales]
Thank you very much.
[applause]
- [whispers] I'm so happy.
- Phoenix.
Rising from the ashes.
For a great queen like you,
this is just the beginning.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you.
[applause]
- We love you.
- For me to go home and some of
these people remain
is very crazy to me,
especially when I look
at certain people
in this competition
that definitely are not the best
that America has to offer.
- Ladies, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" in here?
all: Amen!
- Now let the music play.
Grand prize contributed in part
by AlAndChuck.travel.