- Previously
on RuPaul's drag race...
Escandalo!
- Oh!
- Kristin, what's next?
- Manila Luzon,
you've perpetuated stereotypes.
Condragulations, you're the
winner of this challenge.
- I'm ready to show you
who Stacy is.
- Well, you said that
last week.
Stacy Layne Matthews.
Shantay, you stay.
And tonight...
Oh, my goodness!
The competition heats up.
- Word.
- And the dolls get shady.
- I hate her!
I hate her!
- With extra special
guest judges
Aisha Tyler and Amber Rose.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup;
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut;
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win!
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen,
start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ R-R-RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen,
start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman,
best woman win ♪
[tires screech]
- Oh, my goodness.
- [laughs]
- ♪ Another day has come ♪
- "Never give up.
You're all stars."
- I am so glad I am not the one
that went home.
Bye, girl.
- Stacy, put your back into it.
- Girl...
- [laughing]
- When I was on stage
for the elimination,
I was so mad at myself.
Girl, I felt like I was about to
walk the plank, honey.
- Yeah.
- It does.
- You know how Shangela said
you feel like you about to die?
- Yeah.
- Girl...
I feel like I could be doing
a whole lot better
in this competition.
I just feel like stuff keeps
coming back
and just knocking me down.
- God, Manila won
the challenge.
- Yeah.
- How sad is that?
- I thought she did
really good.
- You don't think it was, like,
a little bit risky
that she was making fun of
some--
- She was making fun
of a culture
that she looks to be a part of,
but she's not.
You know, it just made me
uncomfortable,
but the judges seemed
to enjoy that.
So hallelu.
- Girls, it's just like
Margaret Cho.
That's what I was going for.
You know, she makes fun of her
Asian mom all the time.
- But she is of that culture.
That's her mom.
- It's really no different than
you doing black, Southern lady.
- Well, but I'm black,
and I'm from the South.
- She is not acting.
She is.
- I think that the whole
conversation is bullshit.
If a black girl was asked to be
funny,
the first thing they
immediately do is get ghetto,
get country, and I love it.
What's the difference, really?
- Some of us were doing it
as drag queens.
- Well, no, I think
that everybody on that set was
doing drag.
It was just a different
interpretation.
- It's your interpretation
of it.
- Yeah.
No reason to get mad.
- I just don't want to talk
about it.
- What's going on?
- They're just making it all,
like, a race thing,
and it's not.
- It's so not.
I don't mean this to be
offensive,
but do you have nail polish?
- [laughing]
- No, I'm serious.
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl!
You've got shemail!
Hey, hey, racers.
all: Hey!
- In the cosmos, there are
billions and billions of stars.
But the brightest ones are
right here in Hollywood.
Now, when it's your turn
in the spotlight,
will you sparkle, Neely,
sparkle...
or will you fall deep into
the Valley of the Dulls?
[laughing]
- [giggles]
She's so good.
- Hello, hello, hello!
all: Hey!
- Hi, ladies. Wow.
For today's mini challenge,
we're gonna play
the new gaming sensation
that's sweeping the nation,
and it's called...
Shit RuPaul Says.
- Okay.
- Say it with me.
all: Shit RuPaul Says.
- [laughing]
One by one, letters will pop
onto the screen.
Now, if you think you know
the answer, hit your buzzer.
But be careful, because if
you're wrong, you're out.
The last queen standing will win
a phone call home.
- Oh!
- I almost started to tear up,
because I immediately think,
"Oh, my god, I have the
opportunity to call my grandma."
- Are you ready to play?
all: Yes!
- When I call your names,
swish on down.
Yara Sofia, swish on down!
[laughing]
- I would love to call my mom.
She's gonna be so excited.
She's gonna be like,
"Are you eating?"
- Delta Work, swish on down!
[laughing]
Carmen Carrera, swish on down!
All right, so let's go
to the puzzle.
This puzzle is Shit RuPaul Eats.
[laughter]
Let's go.
[clock ticking]
[bell rings]
Delta.
- Two piece and a biscuit.
- Oh, my goodness!
[cheers and applause]
Condragulations, Delta Work!
This next puzzle
is Shit RuPaul Says.
[clock ticking]
Buzz in when you know.
[bell rings]
Raja, what is your answer?
- Eleganza extravaganza!
- Oh!
- Raja is right!
All right, the last three queens
to play.
This round
is Shit RuPaul Plugs.
- Oh.
- Oh, dear.
[clock ticking]
Buzz in when you think you know
the answer.
[bell rings]
All right, Shangela.
What is your answer?
- Available on...iTunes.
- That is correct!
Condragulations, Shangela.
- Word!
- All right, Delta and Raja,
whoever wins this round
will be the winner
of the mini challenge.
This puzzle is
Ghetto Shit RuPaul Says.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay?
[clock ticking]
Buzz in when you think you know
the answer.
No answers yet.
[bell rings]
All right.
Delta Work,
what do you have?
- She done already done had
herses.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Whoo!
- Yeah, she done already done
had herses!
Delta, you win!
[cheers and applause]
You've won yourself
a phone call home.
Ladies, I hope your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent
are all warmed up,
because for this week's
main challenge,
you're going to be guest stars
on a game show
we like to call...
Snatch Game!
[cheers and applause]
This is your chance to bring
to life
your best celebrity
impersonations.
Bottom line, you need to be
an entertainer
who really entertains.
I'll be back a little later to
check on your progress.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best Cher win,
okay?
- I remember Shangela saying,
"Oh, I would call
my grandmother,
and I would love
to just check up on her."
And I thought to myself,
"I don't need the phone call
right now."
Well, listen, the more I hear
about your grandmother
and, like, how she's kind of
on her own,
the phone call would be
better used by you, I think.
- Oh, my god!
- You want it?
- It was a really sincere gift
that was so unselfish of her.
It touched me.
- So what you doing?
- Child, miss,
I'm Joan Crawford.
- Oh, work.
Do you ever do, like,
impersonations?
- Oh, bitch, I got this nailed.
I am Joan Crawford.
Yes.
- I'm debating between
Anna Nicole and Fran Drescher.
- I don't even know.
Who is that?
- Fran Drescher.
♪ The nanny ♪
- You are doing Tina?
- Nico-Tina Turner.
She's doing Nico-Tina.
I'm doing Alicia Keys.
- Okay, I think I've decided
on it.
- What have you decided on?
- Anna Nicole.
- Girl, you're being
a bit flip-floppy.
- I've decided
I'm gonna do Anna Nicole
because she loves pink;
I love pink myself.
Should I make
a silver and pink dress?
- W-w-a-n-d.
What would Anna Nicole do?
I love my girl Stacy.
But I don't feel that she's
completely confident
in what she's saying.
So I'm wondering, "Is she gonna
be able to pull this off?"
- Today we're doing
the Snatch Game,
celebrity impersonation.
- I'm a little concerned
about my character,
'cause I don't think
Alicia Keys is funny.
- So how are you gonna
combat that?
- I'll do my best, honey.
- So, um, what are you
gonna do?
- Um, I'm gonna do
Imelda Marcos.
- Yay!
- After all this, like, Asian
accent talk this morning,
I think that I'm gonna go out
on a limb
and do another Asian accent.
I'm going to be showing a lot of
my Filipino pride.
[door squeaking open]
- Hello, lady-kins!
- Hi!
- Hi, Ru!
- Hey, Delta.
What you have here?
- I am doing Cher.
- What?
- I know.
- I happen to know she's a fan
of this show.
- Oh, wow.
- You know
she'll be watching this.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Yeah, no pressure.
Every queen in the world is
gonna be watching this,
and everyone
who's ever done Cher
is gonna be watching this.
- Sure.
- So you have to represent.
- I can certainly try.
- Hey, Raja.
- Hi, Ru.
- Who do we have here?
- I'm doing Tyra.
- Now, didn't she win the last
RuPaul Drag Race?
- No, not the other Tyra,
the actual Tyra.
- [giggles]
- I wanted to do her
'cause this is someone
that I know firsthand,
and I've been in the same room
with all of her Tyra-isms.
Sometimes she's, like,
quite proper
and she seems really educated,
and then she'll just like,
"Hey!"
You know, "Mm-hmm!"
- Tyra-ize them, hunty.
- Honey, word!
Uh!
- [laughs]
Yara Sofia.
- Hi.
- Hola, mami.
- Hola.
- Who do we have here?
- Amy Winehouse.
- You're from Puerto Rico.
- Yes.
- She's from England.
- England.
- How are you gonna do that?
[laughs]
- Well, I've been watching
Hatty Potter, so probably--
- Harry Potter?
- Hatty Potter, yeah.
- Let me hear some of your
English accent.
[both laughing]
- [with not an English accent]
Can I have some water?
- [laughs]
- How'd it sound?
- By George,
I think you've got it!
- Really?
- Yes.
All right, darling,
I'm gonna go this way.
Carmen Carrera.
- Hi, my love.
- Look at that face.
It's beat down.
Now, I see that you have padded
your already fat ass even more.
Stand up.
Let me take a look.
Are you doing J.Lo?
- I am.
- You are doing J.Lo?
- Yeah.
- You know that you are sitting
behind a desk?
- Well, I asked for a throne,
so I'm just hoping that
I have that when I get there,
'cause I'm gonna be
really upset,
and I'm gonna have to call
somebody.
- Yes, thank you very much,
Jennifer.
And I will see you on the set.
- Yes.
- All right, see you
in a minute.
- Thank you.
- Alexis Mateo.
- Hi, Ru.
- I know exactly who this is.
- Who is it?
- It's Alicia Keys.
- Oh, you got it right.
- How are you gonna make
Alicia Keys funny?
- I'm gonna be a pregnant, butch
Alicia Keys.
- [giggles]
Well,
Miss Stacy Layne Matthews.
I see a blonde wig.
Dolly Parton?
- Anna Nicole.
- How are you gonna convey
Anna Nicole Smith?
- The fabulous shoes
with the pink on them.
- Oh, okay.
- With my purse.
- So you're gonna rely on your
purse and your shoes?
Listen, I gotta tell you,
I'm not sold.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, because you know
you were in the bottom two
last week.
- Yes.
- What are you gonna do to
ensure
you won't be there again
this week?
- I'm gonna give everything
I have, because--
- Well, you said that last time,
giving everything.
It's got to be more than just,
"I'm gonna give
everything I have."
- I'm gonna bring
something new.
- You got to bring it, baby.
- I will.
- I'm rooting for you,
Stacy Matthews.
- Thank you, Ru.
- All right, baby.
And they call this queen Mariah.
- Howdy do?
- Oh, my go--am I feeling
a little Joan Crawford here?
- Yes.
- I love it!
- Okay, she was such a bitch,
and I love her.
- Well, it's funny you're doing
Joan Crawford,
because a lot of the criticism
you've gotten
on the main stage
are all the things
that Joan Crawford is not.
She's strong. She's powerful.
She's concise.
- I'm very much Joan Crawford.
I don't think that on the runway
I've never given anything
but confidence and strength
and poise and elegance.
- Mariah, will you walk me
to my car?
[giggles]
All right, ladies,
gather around.
Today's Snatch Game contestants
are sexy celebrities
in their own right.
Model and red carpet phenomenon
Amber Rose is here.
[applause]
- Oh, my god, what?
Amber Rose?
I love Amber Rose.
- And one of my favorites,
actress and comedienne
Aisha Tyler will be here.
- Oh, wow.
- Amber and Aisha are also
your guest judges this week.
all: Ooh.
- Yes.
Ladies, the game is on.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
All right, see you later.
- Bye, Ru.
- I just want to punch a wall.
Why am I here?
I feel like this is the lowest
point in the whole competition.
Whatever.
- What are you over?
- Well, she keeps bringing
the god damn bullshit up.
I can't...
- What do you mean?
- "Well, you said that
last week."
Don't keep bringing that up.
That's not helping me.
- Stacy, maybe that is trying
to help you.
- But it's not.
- But that's what I'm saying,
is maybe she's trying
to give you a heads-up.
I know how you feel.
But if she gave you
that recommendation
of she's not feeling it,
I would come up
with something else.
Who else--who else
is pop culture right now
that you can do?
- What about Mo'nique?
- Mo'nique.
Do fucking Mo'nique.
- [sighs]
- Don't get frustrated.
Let's do this.
- I don't want to give up,
because this is a dream for me.
I don't want to go
the fuck home.
- Hello, and welcome
to the new Snatch Game.
I'm your host, RuPaul.
Now let's meet our first
contestant.
She's a model from South Philly.
Please welcome Amber Rose.
- Hi.
- Up next, she's a talented
actress and comedienne.
Please welcome Aisha Tyler.
Hello, Aisha.
- Hello.
- And let's give
a Hollywood hello
to our star-studded celebrity
panel.
Well, hello, Cher.
- Hi, Ru.
- So happy you're here.
- Well, you know, I don't know
what the hell I'm doing here.
I'm a fucking Oscar winner.
- [laughing]
And next to her, we have
the former first lady
of the Philippines.
Imelda Marcos is with us.
- Mabuhay, mabuhay!
- At least this time, she picked
a Filipino.
- Of course, next to her, we
have media mogul and supermodel
Tyra Banks is in the house.
Hello, Tyra.
- Hey, Ru.
- Girl, I saw you smiling
with your eyes.
What do they call that?
- Smizing.
- [laughing]
- Next to her, we have Academy
Award winner Mo'nique.
Mo'nique, is everything...
- Precious!
- Uh-oh, is Precious
back there?
- Mm-hmm, she better be
cooking me something to eat.
- [laughing]
All right, ladies and gentlemen.
With us
is the fantastic Tina Turner.
Hello, Tina.
- All right, RuPaul.
- Are you gonna be nice or
rough on the Snatch Game?
- I always do it rough.
- [laughing]
- Next to her is the late, great
Joan Crawford.
Now, that is not a wire hanger.
- It's not.
- What is it?
- It's a wooden hanger.
- Mariah's Joan Crawford,
I think it's a little crunchy,
and I don't think Joan
would ever allow herself
to look that bad.
- Next to her, of course, is
Grammy winner Alicia Keys.
- Ooh, ooh!
New York!
Now, Alicia, a little birdie
tells me
that you got a secret
to tell us.
- Yo, I am pregnant,
and I am fierce, ah!
- All right, next to her
is the incomparable--
Jennifer Lopez is with us.
And, honey, I got your rider.
- Yeah, compliment, compliment,
question.
- Yes, yes.
- Thank you.
- Next to her is England's
gorgeous rock superstar
Amy Winehouse.
Hey, Amy.
- Hi, how are you?
- [laughing]
- I think this is your first
game show in America.
Have you done game shows
in England?
- Yes, yes.
[garbled speech] Once.
Um, I have...
- Yes.
All right, Amber, Aisha, I will
ask a series of questions,
and our celebrities will fill in
the blanks.
You give an answer you think
will match theirs.
Are you ready to snatch
the stars?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes.
- Starting with Aisha.
Crazy Daisy is so crazy, she
thinks a Kardashian is a...
- Country in Africa.
- That's a very good answer.
Let's see if you got any matches
up here.
Oh, you've got more shoes,
Imelda.
- These ones have sparkles
on here.
It match your outfit.
- Did you write down
your answer? Good, good.
- Designer shoe?
- Not a match
but a very good answer.
All right, Tyra.
- I only have one answer
in my hand.
And this answer
is the only answer.
Naomi Campbell
is a come-guzzling whore!
I hate her. I hate her.
I hate her!
She ruined my life!
- [laughing]
- Smizing.
- All right, Mo'nique.
- Yeah?
- No, it's cool. It's cool.
We cool, Mo'nique.
- Hold up.
- Yeah, baby.
All right, let's go to the great
Joan Crawford.
- My eyebrows.
- "My eyebrows."
- That was almost...
nothing like what I put down,
but...
- All right, let's go
to Amy Winehouse.
Crazy Daisy thinks a Kardashian
is a...
- Lubricant remover.
- That's a great answer,
actually.
- It is a great answer.
Unfortunately, Aisha,
it's not a match.
Up next, Amber Rose.
Psycho Sally is so psycho,
instead of kissing her dates
good night, she blanks them.
- She stabs them.
- Let's start with Cher.
Instead of kissing her dates
good night...
- She buys them tickets
to my never-ending tour.
- Not a match.
All right, Tyra Banks.
- That answer is "smizes."
- She smizes them.
- And Naomi Campbell
is a come-guzzling whore!
- [laughing]
Tita Turter, what do you have?
- She sends them rollin' down
the river.
All right.
- All right, Joan Crawford,
Psycho Sally...
- She cuts their rose bushes.
- No, unfortunately, that is
not a match.
- Mariah could've given us
a little bit more drama.
You always remember
the shrieking kind of--
you know, that intensity
from Joan Crawford
and especially
in Mommie Dearest.
It would've been nice to see
a little bit more
of that extremity.
- Alicia Keys, let's see
if you match Amber Rose.
- I match you, Amber.
- Yes.
- Completely.
- Psycho Sally, what does she
do with her dates?
- She give them the number.
Call me, baby.
I'm just waiting for you.
- [laughing]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jennifer Lopez.
Now, Psycho Sally is so psycho,
instead of kissing her dates
good night...
- She actually marries them to
promote her next album.
- Oh, that's what she does.
Now, Aisha, Freaky Fanny
is so freaky,
instead of shaking hands,
she shakes...
- Schlongs.
- Trips off the tongue.
- What'd you got, Cher?
- It's not a match.
- Not a match.
- She shakes with age.
- See, that would never happen
to you, doll.
- Never.
- Never, never, never.
Mo'nique.
Freaky Fanny is so freaky,
instead of shaking hands,
she shakes...
- A chicken leg in my face,
'cause the bitch know
I'm hungry.
Bitch know it.
I'm hungry as hell.
- We'll see you about
getting you some food
over here, all right.
Let's go to the great
Joan Crawford.
- Since I lost Barbara,
could we get Mo'nique to come
and be my new housekeeper?
- Well, you're both
Academy Award winners.
- Fuck that skinny bitch.
- Okay, all right, all right.
Now, Joan, what do you have,
darling?
- Shake the shit
out of Christina.
- Aw.
Not a match.
Tyra, is there anything going on
that you want to tell us about?
- What?
- Are you smizing too hard?
- I think I've smized so hard,
my eyes bled, girl.
- Oh, my goodness!
She's smizing her head off
over there.
But you still look gorgeous.
- Thanks, girl.
Word.
Peeeeeace!
- All right, next round.
Dirty Diana is so dirty,
she washes her weave with...
- Lysol.
- With Lysol.
'Cause she's dirty.
- Yeah.
- All right, we'll go directly
to the Philippines
and Imelda Marcos.
- Don't cry for me,
Filipinos.
- Yes, darling, yes.
Dirty Diana is so dirty, she
washes her weaves with...
- Sweat from my feet.
- Sweat from your feet.
- Oh, 'cause of wearing
all these shoes!
- Yes, they must sweat
terribly.
- All right, Tita Turter.
- You want to know one thing?
- Yes, I want to know.
- You want to know why?
- I want to know why.
- Love.
- Love. What's love
got to do with it?
- Don't--no, no, no.
Mm-mm, can't do it.
- All right, keep it real,
Tina.
- All right, real.
I'm a long way from Nutbush, Ru.
Hallelu.
- [laughs]
- That is maybe the worst
Tina Turner I have ever seen.
She was like, "I...
"I don't know, like, hallelu.
"What's love got to do with it?
Hallelu."
- All right, Alicia Keys!
- ♪ Amber, Amber, yeah ♪
- She got her number, yeah.
- I'm writing a new song.
It's called Amber.
- Amber, okay.
- Yes.
- I think there should be an
Amber Alert out for Alicia Keys.
All right, Dirty Diana is so
damn dirty, girl.
- Mm-hmm.
- She wash her weaves
with what?
- Dush?
- With douche.
- With a douche.
- With a douch--
- Oh, that's the hood spelling.
- That's the hood, baby.
- She meant to write "douche,"
but she write "dush."
- Oh!
- Yeah.
Unfortunately, we have run
out of time.
Amber, Aisha,
the final score is...
Who cares?
On behalf of all our stars,
thank you for joining us
on the new Snatch Game!
Good-bye, everybody!
See you next time.
[applause]
- I haven't been able to talk
to my grandma
since I came
into this competition.
[phone line rings]
And we talk, like, every day.
- Hi.
- Hey, Grandma, it's me, DJ.
We were raised in a Southern
Baptist lifestyle.
And I know that it was
a big shift to go,
"Oh, my god, my grandson's
a drag queen now."
But my gram loves me.
She's been one of my biggest
supporters.
- Just have to keep going.
Just don't give up.
- No, I'm not gonna give up.
I promise that.
- Okay.
- Today when I'm talking
with her on the phone,
it just reinspires me
for this competition.
I don't want to let her down.
- Good morning.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- So we're back in the workroom,
and the look for today
on the runaway
is to look fabulous
in our favorite drag.
But not everyone is at the most
confident right now.
- Is this what you wear usually?
- Uh-huh.
- God, I'm swimming in it.
It's so huge.
Squeezing the gas out of me.
- Well, imagine
this is what I wear.
- This is why you fart so much.
- This is, like, what?
A twenty--
Oh, this is a 34.
- Oh! No.
A 34 in where?
This better be 34 in Europe.
- Yeah, this is my
best friend right here.
And my mom's on the other wall
over there.
- What about your dad?
- Passed away.
- When?
- About two years ago.
I was mad at him
most of my life.
Just being on drugs so much
and, like, stealing.
And he was on crack, basically.
- Right.
I'm starting to understand
a lot more
of why Stacy
is the way Stacy is.
- The way I was raised
and the way I grew up,
having to deal with my dad,
I feel like it made me nervous.
Like, I have panic attacks.
But, you know, I've learned
to control 'em.
I feel like me and Shangela
have grown so close
in this competition.
I can open up to her and share
pretty much anything.
And we fall out.
- Oh!
She's like my sister.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Mariah?
- Help.
Look, look, look, look,
look, look, look.
Help.
- Come on, barbershop.
- It's just the story
of Shangela.
She's got all personality,
but how much skill
does she have
as someone who can, you know,
put herself together?
She always has somebody
helping her out.
She's got her little minions
over there.
- Clearly, there's two cliques
going on,
and one of the cliques
is Shangela's handmaidens.
She look like Tina Turner
after Ike beat her down.
- These conniving bitches are
talking about my sister, honey.
And so of course I'm gonna go
tell her, honey.
- Who?
- The clique.
- Initially, I thought,
"Well, I'm gonna go over
and find out what they're saying
about me."
But, honestly,
what will that change?
When people are talking
about you,
that means
you're doing something right.
This hair is not soundproof.
- If she hears it,
then she hears it.
I don't have to scream it
out loud,
but I will use my normal tone
of voice,
and I will let her know that
"you know what?
Do it yourself."
- Just so you know, Cousin It
can still hear you.
- What makes a good
impersonator,
and what makes a good female
illusionist?
- Carmen, you should've asked
this question yesterday.
- Right.
Maybe I should've thought of
y'all answers yesterday.
- Don't be a jerk!
Such a jerk.
- Sorry.
- I remember my elementary
school teacher
called me a jerk one time.
- Really?
- I called her a heifer.
I grew up in Gainesville,
Georgia.
It was not the easiest
experience.
No, I pretty much was picked on
for one reason or another.
Either I sounded too white
or I wasn't black enough.
I just didn't fit in.
I just knew I needed to get
where I had a lot more
opportunity.
And I stumbled into the world
of drag.
Girl, I'm gonna get my life.
And if the arrow goes real high,
hooray for you.
- [laughing]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl]
♪ ♪
And what?
[applause]
Hey, guys.
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Hey, Michelle.
- Hey, baby!
- Santino.
- Hey, Ru, I missed you.
- I wrote you letters.
Did you not get them?
- [chuckles]
- Amber Rose.
- Hi, Ru.
- So happy you're here.
- Thank you for having me.
- Aisha Tyler.
- Ru, Ru, yoo-hoo.
- This week,
we challenged our girls
to do their best celebrity
impressions.
Tonight they've come
to the main stage
wearing their favorite
drag looks.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win!
It looks like she's going back
to her roots.
- I love the dark, wicked
bitch look.
I feel so powerful.
- Very Gaultier.
- It is Gaga Gaultier.
- Shangela.
- Oh, and the reveal.
What?
- I picked out this beautiful,
cream-colored structure gown--
design couture.
- First time
you see a black woman
whose hair can provide shelter
from the rain.
- Can you save me a slice of
that hair pie?
They call this queen Mariah.
- Her legs are amazing.
- Gorgeous legs.
- I am a wild animal
on the runway.
I stalk my prey, I hunt,
and I pounce.
- Let me just say,
as a black woman,
I have a very flat ass.
And now I know
where it all went.
- It all went to Mariah.
She took it all.
Raja.
- Two tribes go to war.
- That's right.
Shaka Zulu, honey.
- The look I've chosen
is quite global,
just kind of
National Geographic drag.
Apocalypto Amazon gal.
- She served you up
on the Serengeti.
- Girl, the natives are
restless.
Alexis Mateo.
- Quinceañera.
- This, by the way,
is one of the real housewives
of Puerto Rico.
- I am wearing a creation from
one of my friends,
and I just feel like a princess.
- It makes me hungry
for some sherbet.
Carmen Carrera.
She's at the cabana by the pool
serving glamour.
- I'm feeling like a supermodel
on the runway right now.
My head held high
and just kind of, like,
letting the chiffon blow
behind me.
- Look at that chassis.
- And look at the
undercarriage.
- She's one fierce
mother tucker.
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
Formerly Stacy Layne Bryant,
but she got married.
- This gold coat is my
signature piece.
I'm feeling very confident
in what I'm wearing.
Stacy Matthews has arrived.
- This face is just popping.
- See, now, Mo'nique should have
worn this to the Oscars.
Delta Work.
- Got to love a pantsuit.
- Ann-Margret.
- Ann-Margret...
after the buffet.
- On the runway, I'm feeling
confident today.
I feel great.
I love my outfit.
- That red hair is so gorgeous
on her.
- Delta, you better wooooork!
- Manila.
- Very Twiggy.
- That must be
the Filipino flag.
- I'm getting pinay fish
in this really, really, really
cute Filipino flag dress.
- Filipino couture.
- From the house of Imelda.
- All right, ladies.
Fun and games are over.
When I call your name,
step forward.
Raja.
Stacy.
Alexis.
You are the top three.
Yara.
Delta.
Mariah.
You...
are the bottom three.
Carmen. Shangela. Manila.
You three are safe.
And "safe" is a word
that I have come to loathe
in this competition.
Moving forward, I want you to
make bold choices
worthy of America's next
drag superstar.
You three may leave the stage.
Ladies, you represent the
best and the worst of the week.
It's time
for the judges' critiques.
Let's start with Raja.
- All I have to say is...
[clicking tongue]
- Well, fuck you too.
[laughter]
- You bring it to the runway
every time.
And I love this global warrior
princess you've got going on.
And as far as your Tyra Banks, I
laughed out loud several times.
- I thought because
you know her so well,
you could've done so much more,
because she is a human
caricature.
- I loved
your runway look today.
I thought that it was bold,
drama.
You know, it really felt
editorial.
It really felt high fashion.
And that was really exciting
to see.
- Thank you, Raja.
Up next, Alexis Mateo.
- I loved your Alicia Keys.
You killed that.
It was so, so funny.
- I love the color,
and I love the bling on it.
You look like a real housewife
of Dubai.
- I love gaudy things,
and that's very gaudy
and sparkly and glamorous.
And I think you look great.
And the fact that you were
flirting with me was a plus.
And I was like, "Damn, I'm gonna
get some Alicia tonight."
[laughter]
- Stacy.
You told me that you were going
to be Anna Nicole Smith.
What had happened?
- I feel like I'm relating more
to Mo'nique,
so that's why I switched.
- You stayed physically
in that character.
Your facial expression
was completely different.
You know, you had the--
yeah, and you held it, mama.
You never fell out.
Look at--
[laughter]
- You're so beautiful.
I mean, you're representing
the big girls,
and you're doing a great job.
I mean, you have, like, breasts,
and it looks amazing.
You look so good.
Like, wow.
- I'm so proud of you tonight,
Stacy.
You stepped it up this week.
You need to now realize
that you can't go back.
- Yep.
- All right, thank you, Stacy.
Raja, Alexis, Stacy...
you may leave the stage.
Yara Sofia.
Let's start with you.
Aisha?
- I loved your look today.
I thought it was really
original.
It was really exciting.
That being said, I struggled
a little bit
with your Amy Winehouse.
I could not understand the
accent that you were doing.
I was like, "Is she German?"
- I'm totally into your
dark, wicked bitch look
that you got going on.
I like your own brand
of what you're bringing
to this competition.
- Because Amy is such a big
character, we want more.
You have it.
Give it all.
- I will. I will.
- Next up, Mariah.
How'd you feel
walking the runway?
- Frankly, I'm surprised to be
down here.
I definitely believe that
there's someone more qualified
to be in my position right now.
- Who?
- Carmen Carrera.
She played a bitchy version of
herself.
If I wanted to be offensive,
I could play a knock-off
Filipino.
But I'm not a judge, so--
- I'll speak for myself.
You know,
being a Joan Crawford fan,
I was so happy that you chose
to do that role.
I was disappointed, though,
that there were a lot of missed
opportunities with punch lines.
Were you happy with your
performance?
- I was--I was--I was pleased
with my performance, yes, ma'am.
- All right.
Next up, Delta.
- If you're gonna be a queen
and you're gonna deliver Cher,
bitch, you better deliver Cher.
You were shy Cher.
- There are so many Cher-isms,
and I didn't want to rely
on what you've seen.
And I thought what I would do
was amp it up,
and I didn't turn the knob
completely.
- Delta, what's going on?
Why are you holding back?
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
Okay, just between us girls,
what do you think?
Let's start with Raja.
- Raja on the runway was,
for me,
far and away, the top dog today.
- Being that she has worked
with Tyra,
she could have made it
a little more irreverent.
- But then Tyra would have sued
the shit out of us.
[laughter]
Let's talk about Alexis.
- Her Alicia
was fully realized,
not just the voice
but the look, the physicality,
the jokes.
It was like
your granddaddy's boat;
it was tightened up.
- I'm kind of stuck with Alexis.
- Really?
- 'Cause I feel like
she's stuck.
I feel like we're seeing the
same thing in different colors.
- But she killed Alicia Keys,
in a good way.
- Well, let's move on
to Mo'nique.
- She was funny even when
she didn't speak.
She really was in that character
at all times.
- As far as the runway goes,
really?
Your favorite drag look are
those pants,
which happen to be--
you know, she's hanging
with her besties,
Poly and Esther.
- Yara Sofia.
- Obviously, the accent
did not work.
- In the beginning,
it was funny.
Then it got, like, really dry
and not in a good way.
- But she made brave choices
on the runway.
The dreads were off the hook.
That face makeup was what-what.
- Miss Mariah.
- I don't understand
the black cheeks.
- It was Lily Munster.
- It was!
That wasn't Joan Crawford.
She would never go out without
blending all that in.
- It was a really bad
Joan Crawford.
There was just so much
that she didn't do.
- Well, it's been her criticism
before
that she sort of fakes her way
to the middle.
- She could sleep her way to
the top.
- Even when you get to the top,
you're gonna have to have
something to deliver.
Delta Work.
- It's Cher. You learn that
in Drag School 101.
- You need to have
that confidence.
When you walk into a room,
it's like, "Honey, I'm here,
and I'm Cher."
She didn't do that.
- I just want to say to Delta,
"Schnap out of it!"
Silence!
I've made my decision.
Tina!
Bring me the axe.
Welcome back, ladies.
Now, based on your performance
in the Snatch Game
and your presentation
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Raja...
your impersonation of Tyra Banks
smizing
brought tears to my eyes.
You're safe.
Alexis Mateo.
No one, no one, no one
can do Alicia Keys like you.
You're safe.
- Stacy, I had all but given up
on you.
But you played
to your strengths,
and you came out on top.
Isn't that precious?
- Yes.
- Condragulations, you are the
winner of this challenge.
[applause]
And you've won a cruise for two
to the Bahamas
from ALandCHUCK.travel.
- After being in the bottom
and all these bitches
talking shit,
saying, "Stacy Matthews,
why are you here?"
Fuck those bitches, honey.
- However,
you will not be immune
from elimination next week.
From this point forward, no one
will receive immunity.
Ladies, make every moment count.
Mariah...
your impersonation
of Joan Crawford
was not Mildred Fierce.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- Being bottom two,
I didn't realize
how emotional it could be.
It's definitely intense.
- Yara Sofia.
Playing a mess does not give you
permission to be messy.
Delta Work,
your impersonation of Cher
didn't make any of us believe.
I'm sorry, Delta, but you are up
for elimination.
- To see Stacy win
and I'm in the bottom two
was, just, like, the travesty
that's gonna go down
in, like, history as WTF.
- Yara, you may join
the other girls.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
for you to lip-sync
for your life.
Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Gave you love ♪
♪ You did me wrong ♪
♪ Didn't know what to do ♪
♪ Now other guys will have me ♪
♪ They'll appreciate my love ♪
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ How does it feel ♪
- Even though Mariah's really
serving it,
Mariah doesn't know her words
too well.
But Delta's hitting, like,
every word.
Mariah's just, like, there,
like...
- ♪ Other guys will have me ♪
- I knew most of the words to
the lip-sync song,
but there was some gaps, so
I'm gonna make up something.
Fill in the gaps, bitch, with
"elephant shoe," honey,
"cantaloupe,"
and "sha-laba-laba-tuna."
- ♪ I'm looking for
a new love, baby ♪
♪ A new love ♪
♪ ♪
- Yes!
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies...
I have made my decision.
Delta Work...
shantay, you stay.
- Thank you
for the second chance.
- My beautiful queen.
This is not the end.
This is the emancipation
of Mariah.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you.
[applause]
I'm feeling entertained.
Their judgment was interesting.
It wouldn't have mattered if I'd
have done anything differently.
You play the game and then go.
It's gonna be hell
getting the bags back home.
- Condragulations, ladies.
You are all one step closer
to becoming America's next
drag superstar.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen!
- All right,
let the music play!
[RuPaul's Main Event]
- RuPaul's menswear provided
by Moods of Norway.
Grand prize contributed
in part by ALandCHUCK.travel.