- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
It's time to get totally
leotarded!
- Sha! Sha!
[speaking Spanish]
- Stretch...
- [exhaling rhythmically]
- Alexis, you are the winner.
Stacy, we feel
you are holding back.
But you're safe for now.
- I'll bring it.
- Ladies, this is your last
chance to impress me.
- Bitch, step it up.
You gotta make sure
that you're always
the one that's in front.
- Mimi Imfurst.
Drag is not a contact sport.
India Ferrah, shantay, you stay.
- Whoo!
- And tonight...
Escandalo!
The dolls hit the red carpet.
- Ohh! Ha ha!
- And things get steamy.
- Oh! Ohh!
- With extra-special
guest judges
Chloe Sevigny
and Debbie Matenopoulos.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive
a lifetime supply
of Kryolan Professional makeup;
headline Logo's Drag Race Tour,
featuring cocktails
perfected by Absolut;
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win!
[car engines racing]
- Another day.
- Good morning.
- Life is too short to lift
someone else.
- Girl, y'all gonna lift me.
[laughter]
- Being in the bottom two,
it's a very serious thing.
It kind of like lit a light bulb
in my head.
I have to, like, fight harder
now, so...
- Speaking of fighting.
[laughs]
When Mimi lifted you up,
I was like,
y'all didn't have to grab me.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause you know I was ready
to come out there.
I was coming out in my ponytail
and everything.
- I know everyone expected me
to, like,
punch her or something,
when she did that.
No, I'm not a violent person.
I just gotta go on,
focus on the competition
and what I have to do.
- Oh, so now you competin'.
- Now I'm gonna kick you--
- Oh, so now I gotta go home.
Alliances in this competition
are very important.
India is someone that
I can share some tea with
and not think it's gonna
come back around to me
from another mouth.
- Girl, I'm just, you know,
hoping I can wear something that
I don't have to wear
my breast plate with.
- And that we don't have to sew.
- Thank god I don't have big
flower patterns anymore.
- Listen,
be strong in your opinions.
Say you don't have another
chance,
so you better bring it
every time you get out there.
- They wanna see who I am.
Miss Visage said she didn't know
if I'm a bitch,
if I'm a sweetheart.
- She doesn't know
your personality.
- Mm-hmm.
- What is your personality?
Do I need to know?
[laughs]
[siren blares]
- Ooh, girl!
You've got shemail.
Today's drag queen on the go
needs to stay abreast
of current events,
whether she tweets, blogs,
or just talks smack
behind some t-girl's back.
Remember, an informed queen
is a winning queen,
and that's the way it is.
Good night, and good tuck.
[laughing]
[all groan]
Hello, hello, hello.
[all cheer]
To make it today, young stars
have to be in control
of their public image.
For this week's mini-challenge,
you need to create
a quick drag look
for an outrageous photo op
on the red carpet.
You have ten minutes
to pull it together
before the photographers from
Polite in Public arrive.
The two queens that create
the most sensational
paparazzi photo
will win this mini-challenge.
Ready, set...
Escandalo!
[laughing]
- Drag, girls!
- Ooh, scandal!
- The first thing I think about
is, like, the crotch shot.
In order to create a fake vag,
it's all about the way that you
tuck and fold your skin.
I noticed Shangela was kind of
doing something similar.
I could put on a pair of
pantyhose and put on some fuzz,
you know, but this is,
like, real.
It's like a double take.
- All right, here we go.
- Oh!
- You're gonna get
three pictures.
- Okay.
- Make them count.
Are you ready?
- Yes!
- Okay, one, two, three.
Doggie-style.
All right.
Yes.
- I'm just so pandalicious.
- Oh, you're a panda!
- Oh, wow.
That's a Carrera
I'd like to drive.
- So is it okay that my face
is not gonna be in the frame?
I mean, 'cause it's about here.
- Yeah, whatever you wanna do.
And I appreciate you sharing
your inner dialogue,
but we're gonna take that
picture right now.
- Okay.
- One, two, three!
Girl, you put the junk
in junket.
- India Ferrah is here.
Yes, Miss Jackson
if you're nasty,
you better
put that nipple away.
Scandal!
Yes, take that, Harvey Levin.
Wow, look at the size
of that rock.
And that ring's not bad, either.
Ooh, that was scandalous.
- Kind of basing this off
real life, a little bit.
- You have a similar story?
- We won't--
we'll talk about it later.
- Fantastic.
- Hey, Shakira.
Uno, dos, tres!
Escandalo.
The red bow tie really dresses
that outfit up.
Something tells me your tuck's
gonna come undone.
- Let's just make sure that
doesn't happen.
We need a plug.
[laughter]
- Oh, my goodness.
Did you forget something?
- Yes, my bra.
- [laughing]
- Yabba dabba don't.
Oh, girl.
- Can we like--bloob is out?
- Yes, I love it. I love it.
Fantastic.
Nobody said you can't do that.
[southern accent]
One, two, three.
It's nipple-gate!
- Ohh!
- [laughing]
- I'm giving him hairy coochie
and toilet tissue shoe.
You don't think you would
double-click?
Aah!
- Now, I reviewed
your scandalous photos,
and I'm proud to say
you all are whores!
[laughter]
Now, news travels fast.
So to see which two queens
have hit the blogs,
let's go to the WOW Report.
Carmen Carrera
is one of our winners.
- Oh, my god.
[laughing]
I look crazy.
- For the next winner,
let's go to newnownext.com.
[all whoop]
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
- Oh, my god, you know,
finally my fat ass
has won something.
So these bitches better
watch the fuck out.
- Condragulations.
You are the queens
of morning television.
all: Ooh.
- For today's main challenge,
you'll split into two teams
to broadcast
a morning news show.
Each team consists of
two co-anchors,
a weather girl, a gossip gal,
and a roving reporter,
who'll be interviewing
celebrity guest
Kristin Cavallari.
all: Ohh.
- Carmen and Stacy,
you are our team captains.
Stacy, you get to pick first.
- I just hope Stacy
don't pick me.
Because that team is going to
crash and burn.
- Alexis.
- Manila.
- Ooh!
- Shangela.
- Ooh.
- Mm, Raja.
- Come on, girl, that's it.
- Yara Sofia.
- Delta Work.
- India and Mariah are
the two girls left standing.
- Mariah Carey.
- Me?
- Is she here?
- India Ferrah,
you are on Carmen's team.
- I end up with India.
She was in the bottom
last challenge,
and I don't want to
have to baby anybody.
- These are your news teams.
You will broadcasting live.
- What?
- Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best newswoman win.
- I would like to be...glossy.
Just serious but funny
at the same time.
- Okay.
- You know what I mean?
- Are we gonna take this, like,
more on a serious note?
- I don't know--what,
you're the team leader.
You tell me.
Is it gonna be like fun-serious
or fun, like spoof?
- We gonna have to figure out
this as a team.
Right now,
Stacy is actually clueless.
- I'm gonna be
the gossip reporter,
because I love to
fuckin' gossip.
- News anchor one
is gonna be Raja.
News anchor two
is going to be...
Delta.
Who wants to do weather girl?
No one wants to be weather girl.
But I don't really see it
for India to be interviewer,
because India can get boring
sometimes.
You're gonna be
the roving reporter.
- Okay, work.
I'll do the interview.
- Weather girl
is gonna be India.
- So I end up with weather girl,
and, honestly, I'm hating it.
But what kind of weather girl?
What should I wear?
- Let's just do a quickie,
just so we get used to it.
- Live from the QNN news center,
I'm Raja Fantaja.
- I'm Carmen Carrera,
and I've got all the tea
in my kiki report.
- Weather girl.
- Oh, is it me now?
- I'm worried for India
a little bit.
- Hey, uh, does anyone know
how much time we have?
- We have like
an hour and a half or so.
- Our main challenge
is to split into two teams
and create a morning news show.
- Remember this?
- Oh, with a bow on it.
- Yeah, this is
my newscaster look.
- Yeah, mine's kind of
muted too,
so that'll look good.
Delta and I have
a great dynamic together
and a chemistry.
So we knew that the banter
was going to be great.
- So what do you think?
What do you got?
- Yeah, I have no clue.
- I've got this.
It's a little skirt and jacket.
- Oh, yeah, that'll work.
Right?
- Is that, like, too bright?
- No, we're drag queens, honey.
- I feel that India
is a little bit
more concerned about her outfit
rather than her character
and knowing her lines.
Last time
she didn't do so good,
so it's like now I want her
to really prove herself.
I really want her to do well.
- I-I don't understand this one.
Like, just how nippy--
can you say this for me?
- Nippy, it's like cold.
- No, I know, I know.
But it's--
- It's getting a bit nippy
out there.
- I asked Stacy if
I could be the weather girl.
Even though speaking English
is kind of difficult.
- Hell, no, storm brewing
deep in the heart of Texas.
- Um, um, Shangela, could you...
- I can say it in Spanish.
- I'm listening to Yara
actually deliver her lines,
and I'm getting a little
worried, you know.
I picked this bitch
for a reason.
She better deliver.
- Hello, hello, hello!
all: Hi.
- So, Carmen,
you're a team captain again.
- Yeah.
- So what roles did you assign?
- Well, I'm gonna be
the gossip girl.
- Okay.
- We're gonna have Manila
interview.
- What is your interview style?
- I'm kind of channeling, like,
the best queens of interview.
- Like who?
- Like Mario Lopez
or Ryan Seacrest.
- Ah, okay, I love it.
[laughter]
- Raja is anchor one.
- Have you ever done
any anchoring before?
Any teleprompter?
- No, but I've pretended
quite a bit when I'm alone.
[laughter]
- And then we have Delta's
anch--uh, anchor two.
- From the desert to the sea,
to wherever there's tea.
- [laughing]
Is that your tagline?
- That's our tagline.
- I love it!
That's perfect.
- [singsong]
Bo-ring.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um, we're gonna have India
as the weather girl.
That may be the hardest part.
- Yes, it might be.
But, you know, I'm kind of going
with a little ghetto twist.
- Uh-huh.
- You know,
because you gotta be like,
"Girl, you know, it's gettin'
sunny outside, so..."
- That's you being ghetto?
- Yeah.
- [laughing] Oh, that's...
Well, I can't wait.
I know you all
have a lot of work to do,
a lot of makeup to put on.
I'm gonna let you get to work.
- The opening, the opening.
I love the opening.
- Okay.
- Well, hello,
team Stacy Layne Matthews.
all: Hi.
- How's it going?
- It's going great, honey.
- So who's who?
- Yara is our, um, weather girl.
- Okay.
- You know miss Shangela,
honey, she's our own
gossip columnist.
- Okay.
- This is my sidekick,
reporter number two.
And this is our roving reporter.
- How are you faring
as a team leader?
- I think I'm doing good, and,
you know, we all just organizing
things, you know, and it's--
- You said we all organizing.
You're organizing,
or we all organizing?
- We're working as a group.
- So now, you've made yourself
one of the anchors, right?
- Yes.
- You got some criticism
from the judge panel
that you weren't, you know,
you're not really the most
outrageous person on the planet.
- I can be.
- I'm...we wanna see that.
- Being from a small town,
it just sets me apart
from the other competition,
because I'm a little rough
around the edges.
I'm not as polished
as the other girls,
but, you know, I represent.
- Now, Yara, you're gonna be
working on a green screen.
Practice with me.
If the map of the United States
was behind you,
where is Florida?
- Florida's right here.
- Yeah.
Where's Maine?
- Maine?
- Maine.
- Where is Maine?
- Uh, now, where's New York?
- Um, right there.
- Yes.
And where's the North Pole?
- Ah, over there.
[laughter]
- Now, Alexis, you're gonna be
reading off of a teleprompter.
Do you feel comfortable
with that?
- I just gonna hope
that I do very well.
This is gonna be
a learning experience.
- Now, Mariah, you're gonna be
the roving reporter.
- Yes, I get to interview
Kristin.
I'm going to first start out
with where she's from.
Touch base on, you know,
her achievements
on film and television,
and then I also
want to touch base
on some of her charitable works.
- How much time do you have?
- Three minutes.
- Three minutes
is not a lot of time.
- I have an outline,
and I have base points
to touch on,
and I'm gonna get to
every single one of those,
and they lead to
the next question.
- Right, this is really about
your own personality.
That's really
what we want to see.
Ladies, to help you get your
charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
ready for morning television,
you'll be receiving
a crash course in media training
by veteran broadcaster
Debbie Matenopoulos.
[all gasp]
You know her from The View.
- Bitch, we find out
that miss Debbie,
honey, from The View
is gonna be giving us feedback
about our performances.
I mean, this shit is, like,
serious and exciting, honey.
And I cannot wait to hear
what this bitch has got to say.
- All right, news flash:
Don't fuck it up.
- Okay.
- I'll see you all later.
All right.
all: Thank you.
- Thanks for the tip.
[upbeat music]
- Team Stacy Layne Matthews
has entered the news room.
Say hello to
Debbie Matenopoulos.
all: Hi, Debbie, how are you?
- Hi, you gorgeous creatures.
- Now, Debbie's here
to walk you through
some of the technical aspects
of being in a news room.
And then we are going
all the way live.
Three, two, one.
- This just in:
Scientists have announced a cure
for hetosexural--
heterosexuality.
I've never, you know,
been in front of a teleprompter.
Slow that shit down.
I got to read.
- Side effects include diarrhea,
sudden baldness,
and an uncro--
uncontrollable urge
to dress age inappropriately.
- Wow, that's a great discovery,
girl.
- Yes, honey.
- Yes.
- You two are the main anchors.
You have to set the tone.
So at the top of a show,
be up, up, up.
- Hey, Yara Sofia,
how are things looking
out there today?
- Down here, there is a--
hurricane carnage.
Oh!
It's just right there.
There's a barometric dropping.
Oh! Ohh!
Almost burned my ass.
Oh, my god.
- Girl!
You forced me to believe
everything you said,
although I didn't
understand a word.
Slow down or don't even speak
a word of English.
- Now
it's Shangela Laquifa Wadley.
- Now, listen, the next
drag superstar wannabes
Carmen Carrera
and Stacy Layne Matthews
were the talk of the town
after creating a huge scene
last night on the red carpet.
Honey, it was escandalo!
Yara Sofia, escandalo?
Honey chile, yes.
That's right.
- You were giving me
the attitude
that you knew exactly
what you were doing.
You were sailing the ship.
I could take a note
or two from you.
- I'm here with
Kristin Cavallari.
So...so...
all the scandal.
Around the town
with Justin Brody,
and you have Shawn--
- Justin Bobby.
But you've been spotted
with Nick as well.
- Who?
- Uh, Corzone.
Am I saying his name wrong?
- Nick Carzone.
- I had some facts that I didn't
have completely together.
- There are times where I have
had my facts completely wrong.
And it's okay,
as long as you can recover.
- Okay.
- Oh, my god, look at the time.
We're almost on the air!
places, people!
Places!
- It's time to go live,
and I was so scared
about my English.
And how I can deliver
my personality.
- Count it down in three, two...
- Live from the QNN news center,
Stacy Layne Matthews...
Alexis Mateo...
Yara Sofia...
Shangela Laquifa Wadley...
and Mariah.
The QNN Morning After News
starts now.
- Live from the QNN news center,
I'm Stacy Matthews.
Just in, scientists
have announced a cure
for heterosexuality.
- I am so glad that pill
just came out.
- Yes, girl.
- We're suffering
here in United States.
- Honey.
- It's time to check in
with our Drag-U-weather.
- What's going on?
Ohh!
It is raining men down there!
[speaking Spanish]
Okay! Rainbow right here!
Oh, my god, that's so gay.
But it's so good.
That's a wrap on the weather,
I'm Yara Sofia.
- Let me just say, I do think
"It's so good, but it's so gay"
is my new favorite phrase.
I love that, Yara.
Listen, honey, let me tell you.
Which A-list action hunk
is finally
coming out of the closet?
I'll just tell you this:
He's so gay, and he's so good.
Listen, it's
Shangela Laquifa Wadley,
and that's your daily
kiki report.
Back to you, Stacy and Alexis.
- Mariah, over to you, honey.
- Hi, ladies.
Good morning.
I'm here, Mariah,
with Kristin Cavallari.
So are you working
on any new projects?
- I'm working on
a shoe line right now,
which I'm really excited about.
- Oh, perfect.
I'm excited about that too.
So, were you really born
a genetic woman?
- [laughs]
I was, yes.
- Oh, darn, girls.
We can't claim her for our team.
So, back to you
in the news room, QNN.
- Well, that's all
for the Morning After News.
Stay tuned for the same news,
different anchors.
- All right, that's a wrap.
- Welcome, team Carmen!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
It's time for the morning news!
- Pour yourself
another cup of ambition,
because this is
the Morning After News.
- Today's breaking story:
We'll have the latest on
that horrific freak accident
that killed so many innocent
little people last night.
- Loosen up some.
You two are the anchors,
and you have to drive the ship,
but you also wanna be likable.
- It's Carmen Carrera.
- Next drag superstar wannabes
Carmen Carrera
and Stacy Layne Matthews
were the talk of the town
after creating a huge scene
on the red carpet last night.
I didn't even know I was there!
- Performance is a little bit
flat.
- In Provincetown...
Massachusetts...
I'm like, "Girl, just like,
pictures what, like,
Al Roker would do."
There is the barometric
pressure.
It's dropping.
- The weather people
are the personality.
They have carte blanche to be,
"Girl!"
I'm still waiting for your
personality to come through.
India, this is the time.
- Manila, over to you.
- [Asian accent]
Thank you, Delta.
So...Kristin...
you were on two hit TV show!
Tell us, how has that
changed your life?
- It just made me move
up to L.A. and pursue acting.
- What year you born?
- Uh, '87.
- Oh! Me too.
You are the cock.
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Rooster, rooster.
- [laughing]
- When you weren't pronouncing
your Ls and your Rs,
I thought
it was a terrible decision.
But, you know what?
That never hurt Barbara Walters.
It's time for the morning news.
We are going live.
- I'm very nervous
before the broadcast,
because this team
is depending on me to do good.
So I'm just like, "Ugh."
- I'm gonna count it down...
in three, two, one.
- Live from the QNN news center,
Raja...
Delta Work...
India Ferrah...
Carmen Carrera...
and Manila Luzon.
The QNN Morning After News
starts now.
- Live from the QNN news center,
I am Raja.
- And I'm Delta Work.
- Lookin' sexy.
- So do you.
I love you in pink.
- Thanks.
- [gasps]
- Now let's go to the gal
with all the gossip,
it's Carmen Carrera.
- Ugh, I have so much tea
for you.
Which A-list action hunk
is finally
coming out of the closet?
Well, let's just say
he was at my house last night.
both: Ooh!
- Well, it's time to check in
with our Drag-U-weather girl.
Hey, India, how are things
looking out there today?
- Now...deep in the heart
of Texas, y'all--
y'all feelin' me?
There is a hell no storm.
Okay?
In the heartland,
a rainbow has appeared
in the Gayville
of South Dakota.
This is India Ferrah
with Drag-U-weather.
Back to you, Raja and Delta.
- Thanks, weather grr.
Manila, over to you.
- [Asian accent]
Kristin!
Now that the final episode
of The Hills has aired,
what's next?
- Right now,
I'm really focusing
on my shoe line
that I'm designing.
- Oh, shoes.
I love shoes.
- I think every girl
loves shoes.
- You don't have boyfriend?
- I don't, I'm single.
- Ooh, I have brother.
You should hook up with him.
You should marry.
Immigration.
Lots of money.
- [laughing]
- Back to you in the studio,
Raja and Delta.
- From the desert to the sea
to wherever there's tea,
I'm Delta Work.
We hope the rest of your day
is a big ol' drag.
- Ladies, your newscasts
will be played for the judges
tomorrow night
on the main stage,
where we will be joined
by our guest judge,
Academy-Award-nominated actress,
from HBO's Big Love,
Chloe Sevigny.
[all gasp]
- I love Chloe.
Not only is she
an amazing actress,
but she's a fashion icon
at this point.
- So come decked out in your
most fabulous drag looks.
On behalf
of Debbie Matenopoulos,
I'm RuPaul,
and we'll see you tomorrow.
- Can I come in?
- No.
- We're back
in the workroom today,
and we have to put together
our fiercest drag look.
- How do you think our team did?
- I think our team is great.
I think we're not gonna
have a problem with that.
- I'm a little nervous.
I mean, if our news piece comes
out really shitty,
it's gonna be on me.
- I feel confident that we all,
on our team, did a good job.
- Change the subject.
I don't want to talk about this
anymore.
[laughter]
- India.
- What's up?
What went down on y'all's team
yesterday?
Everything went good
except for
the run-through with me
with the weather girl.
- Who else was on your team?
- Carmen.
- She's your team captain,
though, right?
Well, if you want to call it
that.
I'm just calling it like it is.
Carmen's only strategy was just
for her to pick her part.
I think she should be more like,
"Bitch, we need to win
this challenge.
Like, let's practice.
Let's get our roles down."
But you know, she just went on
about her business.
Bitch, I got stuck
with the weather girl.
Looking, trying
to read cue cards,
pushing this button,
trying to point at the map.
My performance yesterday
was horrible, you know.
I feel like I'm gonna be in
the bottom two again, honestly.
Like, I don't think
I stepped up my game,
and I'll see what happens.
Never again, bitch.
I'm not cut out
to be weather girl.
- For today's
runway presentation,
we actually have to bring
our most fabulous
drag-tastic outfits.
I need to get to my glue gun.
Ugh!
I have so much to do.
I do not want to be the one
lipsynching for my life.
Okay--Stacy.
- I actually overheard her
saying that I fucked it up.
- Do you think you did good
in this challenge?
- I think I did all right.
Let's be honest.
I fucked it up.
I did.
I'm very nervous that I'm
going to be in the bottom two
and have to lip-synch
for my life
and probably go home.
- My home girl, Miss Stacy.
Now, you know we're two
country girls.
But Alexis and I were both
engaged in pageant life,
and more so than pageants,
we're performers.
Would you ever compete
in a pageant, Raja?
- It's not my thing.
My name is Raja, so--
I can't do that.
I'm way too rock and roll.
- First thing
out of her mouth was,
"I don't do all that
'do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.'"
That's a stereotype.
- We don't smile
like Miss America.
Like, it's all about personality
and what you--who you are.
- The whole pageant thing
is really new to me.
We don't have that
in California.
- We do.
I'm the current California
Entertainer of the Year.
- Shangela is California
Miss EOY, honey,
and she is really passionate
about that.
She definitely let us all know.
- I've been in California
working it longer than you have.
- I adore Shangela,
but when I see
that little glimpse of,
like, entitlement, when you've
only been doing drag for...
minutes,
I don't think it's cool.
I think you have to be
an artist.
- It sounds to me
like you're saying
that people
who compete in pageants
aren't performance artists.
- Oh, stop it, Shangela.
I didn't say that.
- I'm listening.
- How is it your art form
if you're doing the art
under somebody else's rules?
- Thank you.
- You can defend her
'cause it's your best friend.
- I'm defending her
because she's right.
Shangela decided that
when you start talking
about a pageant,
you're attacking her.
- Girl, it's like
the West Side Story.
Bitches is like, "Ha, ha, ha!"
- It's not part of
our drag culture, though.
I think this is
a really new thing.
- Well, then y'all
defeated yourself already.
- No, I don't want to be
in a pageant.
No, but what if--
- Wait, time out.
Yeah, you're right, Raja.
- That's the performance
I wanted to do, what if--
- You're getting real
confrontational with me,
but I'm just saying other people
could do unique forms of art,
and they could also win.
- That was kind of heated.
- [laughing]
[upbeat music]
- Hi, gorgeous lady.
- Hey, guys.
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Hey, Michelle.
How you doing?
- Good, gorgeous.
How are you?
- I'm doing wonderful.
It's gonna be a great show.
Makeup superstar Billy B
is here.
Hi, Billy.
- Hey, Ru.
- Debbie Matenopoulos.
- Hey, girl.
- Chloe Sevigny.
Hey, Scorpio sister.
- Hello.
- I'm feeling very Scorpio
tonight.
- Good.
I'm a double Scorpio.
So watch out.
[laughter]
- Now, for this week's
challenge,
our queens went live,
serving up morning newscast
realness.
Are you ready to take a little
time to enjoy this view?
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
First up, Delta Work.
[all gasp]
- Look out, Darryl Hannah.
She's makin' a splash.
- I think today
I'm just channeling,
like, Mae West or something.
Like, maybe it's like
Sally Kirkland,
like that, on the red carpet.
- We found Nemo.
- Yes!
Up next, Shangela.
Donatella would approve.
- As I'm coming down the runway,
I feel "wind" with me.
It's like that Beyonc feel,
where everywhere you go
you've got wind.
- Sell the garment.
- Go 'head, go 'head, girl.
- Fly, butterfly.
Carmen Carrera.
What could she be reading about?
- I handmade that whole thing.
So I'm just hoping
nothing falls off.
There's no strap to my top,
so if that comes off,
then it's like you guys
are gonna see my titties.
- Who says the newspaper
industry is dead?
Mariah.
- She wore blue velvet.
- Feel like
I have a fabulous look.
It's clean, it's elegant.
- I love that gown.
- I'm getting Vanessa Williams
from this too.
- Oh, yes.
- Alexis Mateo.
Wow!
- Cha-cha.
- I'm just giving RuPaul
a lot of personality,
and being very cha-cha,
very Latina.
- Turn the--
- Charo!
- Go ahead, Charo.
- All we need is a trapeze.
- Ohh! Whoo!
Ooh.
- India Ferrah.
This is her more tasteful
sister.
I'm giving a little glamorous
India, you know?
Kind of old Hollywood.
I don't have my breastplate on,
because, you know,
I'm showing them
a versatile side of me.
- She's a lady.
- She's giving
a little bit of Ginger
from Gilligan's island.
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
all: Wow.
- It's very Mad Max.
- I'm in this lovely dress, and
the first thing I think about
is, "Smile, bitch."
They're really enjoying it,
because they haven't seen
this side of me before.
- I feel like she has
a puppy on her head.
- Is that a puppy on her head?
- Manila Luzon.
all: Ohh!
- Is that a bomb?
Everybody down!
- I'm just swaying my hips
and smiling
and showing off my purse
and having a gay old time.
- Did you, Tina Knowles,
a real pineapple?
- Honey, it's a T.K.O.
- You better work.
- Tina Knowles original.
- Yara Sofia!
- Oh, my goodness.
- Qu'est que c'est?
- Something wicked
this way comes.
- I'm bringing hairy horns,
the cape, and I take it off.
- [gasps]
Look at the body.
- She says, "Carmen Carrera,
you're not the only one."
- Yes.
- Hunty.
- Drive this.
Last but not least, Raja.
all: Ohh...
- It's fashion week.
- There's your Westwood,
right there.
- I'm really, really inspired
by things rococo
and Marie Antoinette.
All things sort of French.
- Let them eat cake!
- Anna Wintour will run that
in the spring issue.
- Gaultier,
remember who did that?
- We've got our cover.
- For sure.
- Yeah.
- Ladies,
I asked you to dazzle us,
and dazzle you did.
After this week's
main challenge,
morning television
will never be the same.
You hear that, Kathie Lee?
Earlier, the judges screened
your full live newscasts.
Now, ladies, I have
a little news for you.
Alexis Mateo,
you have immunity this week.
Raja, Yara Sofia,
Carmen Carrera, Delta Work.
You're all safe.
You may leave the stage.
- Thank you.
- Ladies, the five of you
represent the best and the worst
of this week.
It's time
for the judges' critiques.
Let's start with Manila.
- As over-the-top
as the performance was,
I really enjoyed it.
- Kristin Cavallari,
my brother, ho fun.
- I literally cried.
I mean, I thought that it was
brilliant on so many levels.
- Manila was a star tonight.
- Thank you.
- With that type of thing,
it cannot be half-assed.
And you went completely there,
did not break character.
It was fantastic.
But as far as the look goes,
it's absolutely flawless.
- It was so wrong...
that it was so right.
And truthfully, if you're
gonna be groundbreaking,
some eggs have gotta be broken
to make an omelet.
- If someone watching tonight
were offended by what you did,
how would you answer to that?
- I don't think we have enough
Asian people in pop culture.
So I'm here to entertain.
I'm here to be farcical.
And just trying to do my job.
- All right, next up, Shangela.
- The accessories
might have been
a little over-the-top
for my taste.
Maybe one of the bracelets
would have worked better.
- I think that it could be
a little bit less eye makeup.
- I loved this look tonight
for you.
I thought it was very pretty,
very sassy.
Not so much stuff lighting up
and lanterns
and this, that,
and the other thing.
You know, gossip on the radio
is my thing,
and you served it.
You did a great, great job.
- You could tomorrow
go to any local show
in this market in los Angeles
and say, "I wanna do your
entertainment news on a Friday;
take a shot on me,"
and I think they'd have
a hard time telling you no.
- What I saw in that broadcast
is what--the potential I saw
in your audition.
And I'm very proud of you, mama.
India Ferrah.
What was it like broadcasting
live as our weather girl?
- I had so much confusion
going on.
I didn't know where to go.
Cue cards were on the sides.
Like, I was lost, definitely.
- When India came out, I was
very impressed with her grace
and posture.
But the dress not so much.
- It was you reciting
what they told you to say.
And I think it did fall flat.
- What I wanted to see
was more of you.
- I wanna know what's keeping
you from bustin' out?
- Honestly, I don't know.
I don't know
if it's nervousness...
- I don't know what to tell you,
but the time to jump on it
is yesterday.
Next up,
the queen we call Mariah.
- I think she's stunning.
I mean, absolutely beautiful.
I think if I saw you, I'd think
you were a real woman.
I mean, you could give Naomi
a run for her money,
you know, on any catwalk.
- But Naomi would probably
throw a phone at her.
- I would catch it
and throw it back.
- Thank you.
- When the interviewing process
started,
I was getting
a little concerned,
and then it turned
for the better.
- So you're better known
for The Hills.
- Mm-hmm.
- But you're becoming
quite the man-eater.
- Mariah, you are what we call
a grower, not a shower.
When the interviewing process
started,
I was getting
a little concerned,
and then it turned
for the better.
But I thought
you looked stunning.
- I agree with
what Michelle said.
However, they don't give you
a second shot.
Three, two, one,
the camera's on--
it's sink or swim, right now,
'cause nobody cares--it's live.
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
- When she first came out,
I thought maybe she had a little
Yorkie on her head.
The hair was very confusing
to me.
- So, now, Chloe, are you saying
you're a Yorkie lover?
Is that what you're saying?
- I actually don't like animals.
[laughter]
- I love the way you look.
Know what I loved most of all?
Your smile, honey.
You lit up tonight.
- On the broadcast,
you did put a lot of thought
into it.
Almost too much.
You got so into
trying so hard
to memorize and memorize
that you forgot to be you.
- There seems to be something
blocking you
from completely blooming
in this competition.
- After thinking everything over
last night,
I feel like I lifted something
from myself.
And I'm ready to work.
I'm ready to show you
who Stacy is.
- Well, you said that last week,
Stacy.
Thank you, ladies.
While you untuck in the
Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
All right, just between us
gar-girls,
what do you think?
Let's start with Manila.
- The makeup to me
was a little heavy.
- Yes, the makeup was heavy,
but I don't know.
There's just something
about Manila tonight
that was a win-win situation
for me.
- I love Manila,
because I agree she's fearless,
and she's an equal opportunity
offender.
That doesn't mean you're racist.
You hate everybody,
including your own race.
Then it's funny.
- 'Cause if you can't
hate yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
hate anybody else?
- I say it all the time.
- All right, up next...
Shangela.
This is a tough one, 'cause she
did a really good job too.
- She impressed me, you know,
in all aspects.
And I think her personality
really showed through.
- I wasn't 100% sold
on the dress this evening,
but I loved the character.
She did a great job with it.
- Her personality
jumped through the television
and just tugged at your heart.
I just--I really--I wanted to go
have lunch with her.
- India Ferrah.
- It was hard to watch.
- Yeah. I feel for the girl,
but I wasn't impressed.
- She has the gift of us telling
her exactly what to do.
And she's still not doing it.
- Good point.
- I thought the dress
was horrible.
I thought the performance
I thought the makeup
was horrible.
This is $75,000
and a huge title.
- Yes, absolutely.
Mariah.
Listen, I gotta admit,
her performances do leave me
a little flat.
- She looked like
a professional journalist,
but acted like it was
a school project in ATL.
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
Every time she gets up here,
she's saying, "I'm gonna start
bein' me tomorrow!"
Chloe, do you believe her?
- Not if she keeps saying it.
- And she keeps saying it.
- Watching the newscaster,
I did not see anything
spectacular brought to it.
Did not see a character.
- Maybe that's her idea
of how bland newscasters are.
- It could be.
- And how boring a job
that would be.
Because she did look like a
woman walking at the mall.
- She looked like just a lady
on the number 110 bus uptown,
to me.
- The first thing I thought was,
"That looks like the newscaster
in Tupelo, Mississippi."
- It's true.
- All right, silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back the girls.
- Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your live
morning newscast
and your presentation
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Manila Luzon.
This week,
you broke all the rules.
You crossed the line
of good taste.
And you perpetuated stereotypes.
Congratulations,
you're the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
Not only are you safe
from next week's elimination,
but you also win a $2,000
gift certificate from Wig USA.
- I'm really excited
that I won this challenge.
I'm proud of myself.
- Shangela,
keep up the good work.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- India Ferrah...
as Khloe Kardashian once said,
"You can lead a horse to water,
but a pencil must be lead."
India, I'm sorry, but you are up
for elimination.
- I am disappointed that I'm
in the bottom two again.
But, you know,
I came here to do a job,
and that was to prove to
everyone that told me
that I couldn't do it
that I can do it.
- Mariah, listen to me, girl.
You are resting on pretty.
And while you rest,
the other girls are gonna
race right past you.
You're safe.
- [whispering]
Thank you.
Good luck.
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
Your brilliance
comes in flashes,
but those moments
are too few and far between.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I do not want to go home.
There ain't shit
in North Carolina
but cornfields, honey.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and to save yourself...
from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lipsync...
for your life.
Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
I had to leave my condo
To come to this
Well, I'm back
But this time, with my man
And these women are putting
Their hands all over
His Yamamoto Kansai sweater
That I bought
And I'm much, much unhappy
About that
I'd hate to come down to
Their level and become a BW
A basic woman
But if it don't stop
It's gonna get scandalous
Uh-oh
- I had this mentality,
you know,
just be fierce, be a bitch,
give attitude.
Give everything that they need
to keep me in this competition.
-  You wanna be sure
You best go powder your nose
-  Go on and
Powder your nose
'Cause you wanna look good
When you step on the floor
- I've worked so hard
to get here.
The only thing standing
between me and the finish line
is Stacy Layne Matthews,
and I've gotta
take this bitch down.
-  He looks good
Good enough to eat
But believe me, lady
He belongs to me, yeah
-  Got a meeting
In the ladies room
I'll be back real soon
- Don't slap me.
- [laughing]
- 'Cause I'm not in the mood.
-  Got a meeting
In the ladies room
I'll be back real soon
- [laughing]
[applause]
- Ladies...
that was a close one.
Stacy Layne Matthews.
Shantay, you stay.
- Thank you.
- India Ferrah,
your time at RuPaul's Drag Race
has reached its climax.
But your legendary journey
has just begun.
Now...sashay...away.
- Thank you all.
- Thank you.
[applause]
- I'm definitely disappointed.
Apparently, I'm not
what the judges want.
I'm not comedy.
I'm not camp.
So I'm me, and I'm not gonna
change myself
to fit someone else's standards.
I can't reach it.
[grunting]
Yeah, anyway...
mwah!
- Condragulations, ladies.
I see a lot of incredible talent
on this stage.
But America's next
drag superstar
has yet to emerge.
Remember...
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get a amen in here?
all: Amen.
- All right,
now let the music play!
- Yeah.
- RuPaul's menswear provided by
Moods of Norway.
Grand prize contributed in part
by AlandChuck.travel.