- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
There is no place like
the U.S. of A...
- ♪ From the heart ♪
♪ Of all the gays ♪
- No foam here.
100% American, made in the USA.
- Wah!
- Papi, I want you to come back
home, baby!
- Alexis Mateo,
you made us proud.
Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
- I wanna say thank you to that
special person
that's shown me that I needed
to love myself first.
- Ladies...I have made
my decision.
For the first time
in Drag Race history,
no one is going home tonight.
- What?
- And tonight, Rupaulapalooza!
- Ooh!
- The dolls hit a high note.
- ♪ Oh ♪
- But some fall flat.
- ♪ All of the glamour ♪
♪ And all of the ♪
[off-key] ♪ fame ♪
No.
- And extra-special guest judges
Jody Watley and Carmen Electra.
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut,
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win.
- ♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ Ru--ru--RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
- Buon giorno, buon giorno.
- Back again, new day.
- We're all still here.
It's a new day, and there's
still six of us...
because no one went home, so...
we'll see what's gonna happen.
- Why do you think Ru gave us
another opportunity?
- Honestly, I think that Ru
feels like
she says--like we're both really
fierce queens.
Like if I was anyone else in
this competition,
I might feel a little bit like
oh, shit, like...
Ru feels like we're too good
to go.
I would be nervous.
- Can somebody just slap her
and wake her up?
- I wasn't expect to be in
the bottom two.
- You never expected--
- And, yes, I know--and I know.
I know, I know, but...I still
have something to learn.
I appreciate that RuPaul give me
another opportunity.
I cannot fuck it up.
[siren]
- Ooh, girl, you got she mail!
Hey, dragsters.
all: Hey!
- Listen up.
Can you hear that?
It's herstory calling.
Learn to embrace the past.
Make it your own...and you just
might be America's next
drag superstar.
Hello, hello, hello!
Hi...my gorgeous queens.
Now, to kick things off, we're
gonna play a little game
of Rusical chairs.
all: Oh!
- It's a lot like
musical chairs.
When the music stops,
who's ever left standing
has to finish the lyric.
If you get it right, you get
to give a queen the boot.
But if you're wrong, you're out.
Oh, and you have to play
the game wearing high heels.
- Oh, of course!
[laughter]
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
- Let the music play.
♪ ♪
♪ And when they see me ♪
♪ They want to be me ♪
[music stops]
- Oh!
- Ah ha!
- Carmen is left standing.
What lyric comes next?
- Um...
♪ And when they see me ♪
♪ They wanna be me ♪
♪ I am your fan-ta-sy ♪
♪ Cover girl ♪
- Ding ding ding ding ding!
You got it!
- Mm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm!
- You get to give one
of the queens the boot.
- I choose...Shangela.
- I knew it was me.
- Bye!
- Let the music play!
- ♪ Hey, DJ ♪
♪ Love the way ♪
♪ I lose my inhibitions ♪
♪ When you spin ♪
♪ And I don't care ♪
♪ If people stare ♪
[music stops]
- Ha ha ha ha!
- Carmen, dear, are you on
a five-second delay
or something?
What lyric comes next?
- I got to think about this one.
[laughter]
I'd rather something than try to
fit in.
Damn, these bitches got me.
- I'm sorry, Carmen,
but you are out.
You may join Shangela.
Let the music play.
- ♪ Is some tranny chasers ♪
♪ Up in here? ♪
♪ Welcome to my stratosphere ♪
♪ Fierce, fierce, fierce ♪
♪ Make a move ♪
♪ What you wanna do? ♪
[music stops]
- Oh!
- Ha ha!
- ♪ I ain't got no time ♪
♪ For no looky-loo, boos ♪
- That is right.
Ha ha ha ha!
- Get out, girl!
all: Oh!
- There are two chairs left
and three queens.
- ♪ This is the main event ♪
♪ Are you ready ♪
♪ Just let the music ♪
♪ Dance into your soul ♪
♪ Faster, faster ♪
♪ Exhilarating ♪
[music stops]
- Ha ha ha ha!
All right, Yara.
- Can't wait to hear this.
- ♪ Accerleratin' ♪
I don't know!
- Time is up, Yara, I'm sorry.
But go ahead and join
the other girls.
Okay, we have two girls
and one chair.
Sounds like a video you can
watch online.
[laughter]
Okay. Let the music play.
- ♪ Nobody rocks ♪
♪ Like the girls ♪
♪ I'm running with ♪
♪ Hit me up ♪
♪ I'm that chick you know ♪
[music stops]
both: Aah!
- Ah ha ha!
- All right, Raja.
Do you know the lyric?
- Mm...
- We have a winner!
- Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop!
Ow!
- Now, it is time to pump up
the volume.
For this week's main challenge,
you'll need to find inspiration
from the vast herstory of music
to perform in a ladyboy music
festival
we're calling...
Rupaulapalooza...
sponsored by Absolut vodka.
Please welcome Jeffrey Moran.
[applause]
all: Hi!
- Hi, guys.
There are a couple of things
I think you need to know as you
go through the competition.
You need to let your personality
show through.
We really wanna see that you
know who you are.
Show us what it means to be
part of this family and part
of Absolut.
- Now, ladies, this week
each of you will record
the brand-new RuPaul song
Super Star.
all: Ooh!
- But each of you will be
interpreting it in a totally
different
and timeless musical style.
Your options are hip-hop...
country...
disco...
reggae...
punk, or pop.
Now, Manila, since you won
the mini-challenge,
you get to choose first.
And then one at a time,
you decide who chooses next.
- I'm gonna go with...
bloo, bloo, bloo, bloo, bloo...
disco!
- Ooh-ah, ooh-ah, ooh-ah!
- Now, Manila, who gets
to choose next?
- We'll go with Raja.
- I want punk.
- Who gets to go next?
- Yara.
- Yara gets to go next.
Come on over, Yara.
- Manila picks Yara, not Carmen.
What happened to Team Heather?
- I'm gonna take pop.
- All right, Manila,
who goes next?
- Alexis.
- Thank you, Manila.
- I get what you're trying to
do, Manila,
but girl, just pick
the Heathers.
Who cares about those boogers?
Girl, stop being fair.
- I'm gonna take the hip-hop.
- All right, mami.
- Next is Carmen.
- Finally.
- Carmen, are you feeling
coun-try?
Or are you feeling reg...gae?
- I really like reggae.
So I'm gonna go with reggae.
- Okay!
And of course, that means,
Shangela, you are our
country queen.
- I'm straight out
of Paris, Texas,
and I'm going to hold onto
the country.
- All right, ladies, before
your recording session,
you'll have time to rehearse
and put together
an appropriate performance
outfit.
Until then, gentlemen...
start your engines...
and may the best woman win!
- Carmen Carrera.
Join us here on
Alexis Mateo Show.
You have any questions
for our comedy queen?
- No, I thought you--I thought
you was gonna ask--
I thought this was your show.
- I'm giving you the free option
to say something to her before
we continue
just criticizing you.
[laughter]
Manila just took me by surprise.
- I wasn't expecting her
to pick me first.
I know her.
She would have said okay.
Now, who do I think's gonna try
to turn this competition?
I don't want them to have
the music they want.
- I don't really read into
those things.
I think that some people might
want to, you know, stir up
some drama because of that, but
I think that's why she did it.
- Oh, I don't think nobody's
trying to stir up drama.
But you can be stupid all day
long,
pretend to be aloof,
but I know better, honey.
You go play that one with
somebody else.
- I think Alexis and Shangela
wanna start drama.
Fuck those hos.
Who cares?
Maybe she did and maybe
she didn't.
I don't know.
I'm gonna ask that bitch.
Gonna ask her now.
They're trying to say that
you're trying to sabotage me
because I only had two options
instead of four,
and I should have been called up
there after this bitch.
- You know what, honey,
it's not shade.
I'm not strategizing
besides myself.
- Oh, so you're being selfish.
- Going down the line was like
the easiest and fairest
way to do it, 'cause I don't
wanna start drama
being like picking you guys
first and then having
all the other girls being like,
"Oh, Manila's just picking
the Heathers."
- I actually wanted the reggae
one, actually, so...
- Well, then it worked out,
so what are you fucking
complaining about, bitch?
- I'm not complaining about
anything.
Don't get me twisted, honey.
- You know what? No.
Carmen's trying to start up
some motherfucking drama!
She's turning into Shangela.
- ♪ What you were meant to be ♪
♪ Oh, all the glamour ♪
♪ And all the fame ♪
The main challenge this week
is we have to record
our own version
of RuPaul's new single
Super Star,
and we have to perform it in
front of a live audience.
- [laughing]
- ♪ Oh oh oh ♪
- ♪ All of the glamour ♪
♪ and all of the fame ♪
- ♪ People are gonna ♪
♪ Remember your name ♪
- It is battle of the vocals
right now.
Everyone is doing their song.
- ♪ Gather your broken dreams ♪
♪ All the pieces together ♪
♪ And everyone will see ♪
- Girl, I thought I was at
the audition for Glee.
- ♪ Bam ♪
- [off-key]
♪ Meant to be ♪
♪ They're gonna love you ♪
♪ Whatever you do ♪
- Yara sounds horrible.
- [off-key] ♪ Oh ♪
- Maybe tone is lost in
translation.
- ♪ People are gonna ♪
♪ Remember your name ♪
- She don't sing it in Spanish.
She doesn't sing in English.
[laughing] She doesn't sing in
any language.
- Bah!
- Hello, hello, hello,
my superstars.
all: Hello.
- Hey, Carmen.
- Hey, hey.
- Lady reggae.
- Yes.
- Does this challenge
frighten you at all?
- No, this excites me.
- Because you were
in the bottom two...
- Maybe I might have a little
bit more to prove,
but I like a challenge.
I'm not gonna try to fake it,
you know?
I'm just gonna sing like I do
and gonna go with something that
I can pull off.
- Irie, man.
One love.
- Okay.
- Well, hello, Raja.
- Hi, gorgeous lady
of wrestling.
- [laughs] Yes!
So why'd you choose punk?
- As much as I wanted to be a
punk rocker as a teenager,
I was way too glamorous up here.
- Ha ha ha ha!
- Like I could not stick
a safety pin in my nose.
I might bleed, it might hurt.
- You've been criticized for
over-thinking your challenges.
You're very cerebral.
What is your strategy to sort of
break out of that?
- Well, you know, this is
a perfect one for me
because I can finally go balls
to the wall.
- Something that's always worked
for me is to remember
that what other people think
of you...
- Right.
- Is none of your business.
- Yeah.
- That--that's their--
that's them.
All right, Raja.
- Thanks, Ru.
- Get back to work.
- Right. See ya later!
- Hey, Manila.
- Hi.
- Do you have your disco moves
together?
Can you do the bump?
- Yes.
♪ Boom boom ♪
- Can you do the double bump?
Uh-uh.
You got it, kiddo.
- ♪ Ooh ooh ♪
- Yara Sofia!
The new princess of pop.
- Yes.
- Do you know how to sing
at all?
- Um...yes.
- You do? [laughs]
There was a little hesitation
there.
- Yes.
I'm not the best singer.
I'm an actress.
You have to believe it.
And in front of the mirror,
I'm gonna practice--
"I'm a singer, I'm a singer,
I'm a singer,"
and I'm gonna sell it.
- I'm very glad I kept you
around,
because I'm very excited to see
your pop princess.
- You're gonna love it, darling.
- Hey, Shangela.
- Hi, Ru.
- Now, you got stuck with
country.
Would you have chosen it?
- It's not about the song.
- Yeah.
- It's the look.
There's the traditional,
you know,
Jessica Simpson, these boots are
made for walkin' kinda look.
- Yeah.
- And then there's
Carrie Underwood concert.
- That is quite a conundrum
because a lot of people are
gonna expect...
- Jean skirts and plaid tops.
- You're just gonna have to
follow your heart on this.
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
- [laughing] Hey, Ru.
- Whassup?
- I got the hip-hop.
- And you chose this.
- Yes.
I'm modeling myself after
Lil' Kim.
- Uh-oh!
- [laughing] Yes!
- Uh-oh, the queen bee?
- I love Lil' Kim.
Ru knows I am hip-hop.
[pops tongue]
- Keep it hood and, um...
- Peace.
Bam!
- Bam!
[pop]
- All right, ladies,
in a few moments,
you'll be headed to
a professional recording studio.
♪ Field trip ♪
- [whooping]
- Now, tomorrow on the main
stage,
you'll be debuting your version
of super star in front
of a live audience.
We'll be joined by our
extra-special guest judges,
Grammy-award winning artist
Jody Watley...
- Ooh!
- Hey!
- Jody Watley is an amazing
performer.
So I'm excited that someone on
that judge's panel
is gonna finally be looking at
performance over look.
- And the sizzling hot
Carmen Electra.
- Wow!
- Whoo!
- So whatever you do...
don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Super star ♪
- [snickers] Shangela.
She looks like Mystique's
country realness.
- Poor Shangela.
I mean, she's got country and...
ugh!
It's tragic.
How's Shangela gonna do
in country?
- I think she's gonna rely what
she's been relying on this
whole time--
being a loud mess.
I don't know what the hell
Shangela's wearing right now.
Like she just cut a piece
of fabric,
and it's all uneven
and it just--
it's not making any sense to me.
- I hope that I don't get ragged
for not coming out there
in a cowboy hat, you know,
in a denim skirt, but...
it's not that.
It's more this.
This is Carrie Underwood
concert.
You know what--you know what
I mean?
- She's somehow got her way
through
with fucked-up outfits before,
so, you know, we'll see
what happens with her.
Bless her little heart.
- Hey.
- Hi. I'm Shangela.
- I'm Lucian.
- Today our main challenge is
to record RuPaul's song
super star
in a specific musical genre.
- Have you been in the studio
before?
- No. I have not.
- This is your microphone.
Steve is in the booth.
He's gonna help us out.
- Lucian produced RuPaul's CD
Champion.
This is real!
It makes me feel like
I'm already
a musical recording artist.
♪ Now that the time has come ♪
♪ Waiting what seems like ♪
♪ Forever ♪
- The melody that you're singing
there seems a little different.
- Okay.
- Are you changing it on
purpose?
- I may have taken it too high
with the "oh."
- What I would say is that--
- But I'll do it...
and then I'll take your feedback
on it.
I'd love to record one more
time,
and then that way I can get
the timing down for the intro,
so you guys may not have to do
any editing,
which would be nice.
Okay. Thank you.
- It seems like Shangela might
benefit
from being less confident.
[laughs]
- Anything else that I can do to
make it better?
No is okay too.
[laughing]
- It's gonna be my first
experience as a singer okay?
So...easy on me.
- Oh, okay. All right.
It's really scary, though.
- It is?
It's been a while since we have
seen a hot, gorgeous guy.
Bam!
I cannot concentrate.
♪ Whoa, all of the glamour ♪
♪ And all of the fame ♪
♪ People are gonna ♪
♪ Remember your name ♪
- Okay...
There's a lot to go over here.
- What you didn't like?
- You sound terrified.
- I am terrified.
- Your vocals are like...
oh...oh...
- Shaking?
I know! I'm nervous.
- I know.
What would make you not nervous?
- We cannot say that on TV.
[pop]
- ♪ All of the glamour ♪
♪ All of the fame ♪
♪ People are gonna ♪
♪ Remember your name ♪
[music ends]
- Yeah, it's those upper notes
that are a little like...
- So I'll just like push harder.
- Well, don't think push.
Just think power.
- Okay.
- Here we go.
- ♪ Gonna love you as you are ♪
[stronger]
♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ You're a super star ♪
[music ends]
Okay, if you can run some
auto-tune on that,
that'd be great.
[laughter]
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Now that the time has come ♪
♪ Waiting, it seems like ♪
♪ Forever ♪
- Just enunciate the words
a little bit more and make it
a little more prettier
in that girl punk way.
- ♪ We are super stars ♪
♪ Ha ah oh ♪
[laughs]
What does that mean?
- Sounds like you have a deeper
voice
than the key of this song.
- I'm kind of a more edgy gal.
I don't wanna compromise
my voice
and fuck it up by doing
something
that's out of my range.
- We gotta figure out how to
make you sound less
"I can't find the right..."
- The right tune.
Right.
I can't wait to perform in
front of a live audience,
and I just hope that
the recording...
the look, all of it goes well
so that the audience
can love it.
Yeah, there is definitely
pressure.
- Maybe we should play it back
so you can hear...
and then maybe we can figure out
a game plan.
- I'm doing reggae.
- Okay.
- But I don't wanna be like...
old-school,
like with the accent...
- You don't wanna play up any
comedy here or anything.
- Yeah, I think that's--that's
not really my thing.
- Well, this is the microphone.
- Okay.
This is to catch my spit,
I guess?
- It's actually to block
the air from...
- Oh!
- ♪ Now that the time ♪
♪ Has come ♪
[off-key]
♪ Waiting will seem ♪
♪ Like forever ♪
♪ They're gonna love me ♪
♪ Whatever I do ♪
[laughing]
I'm sorry.
Hearing my voice
is freaking me out.
- Do you think that you're
performing right now?
- Well, I don't sing,
so it's like is there a way that
you can throw in
some extra things in the beat?
The beat is so like...
da da da.
- Reggae is laid-back.
You have to perform it.
If you were in a club
and you were singing this
and there was a crowd of people
around you,
what would you do?
- I would sound like a mess.
But let's go, let's do it.
[music starts]
♪ And everyone will see ♪
♪ What I was meant to be ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ All of the glamour ♪
♪ And all of the ♪
[off-key] ♪ Fame ♪
No.
- It's just not interesting
at all.
It's just like...just so flat.
If you don't give me something
more entertaining,
it's gonna be like...
[snaps] Just do it.
- I'm a little frustrated.
Lucian just wants me to keep
going, give more.
But this is not my thing.
- I think we're done.
- Oh! That was crazy.
- ♪ Now that the time ♪
♪ Has come ♪
♪ Waiting will seem-- ♪
Ah! Fuck.
I'm sorry.
♪ Now that the time has come ♪
Fuck.
- Okay, here we go.
From the beginning.
- ♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ You're a super star ♪
Fuck.
Sounds bad, right?
- It's still not great, no.
- Okay, uh, let's try--
keep trying, 'cause...
- Okay. Here we go.
- I'm sorry.
♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ You're a super star ♪
Is bad too?
- We should figure out the
best way
to make you...sound good.
- I'm doing my best.
I don't have the best...voice.
But after being in the bottom
two last week,
I'm gonna be a professional and
I'm gonna be more serious.
- You know, I have to give you
props, because you're workin'.
[laughs]
- Thank you, Lucian.
Appreciate it.
- I felt like Yara was always
trying hard, even,
to make something happen.
But I don't know that anything
ever really did.
- ♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ You're a super star ♪
♪ ♪
[music ends]
[hip-hop]
- Recording artist Manila Luzon
is in the house!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yaaah!
- Oh, are those our music?
We walk into the workroom,
and and there are mp3 players
just waiting there
with our songs on them.
Today we have to lip sync the
song we had just recorded...
super star!
- Oh!
I gotta be alone.
Hearing my voice
with the track and the lyrics,
I mean, it was a full-on song,
and it was me singing it.
And I had never heard that
in my life.
I love it!
I love it, I love it!
I wanna do more.
It's good to have that feeling,
'cause I'm an old jaded queen,
and I just--I was, like, beside
myself.
- Whoo-hoo! I love it!
I'm so excited to hear my song!
I cannot believe it!
I can understand me!
- Wow, Yara!
- What?
- I love it--I can actually
understand you.
- Oh, shit!
I sound sickening!
I sound ten times better
than what I was expecting to
sound like.
- It's awesome!
- It sounds great!
Bam!
- So I got my track.
I'm listening to it.
But I'm like, oh...my...God.
I don't like the way it sounds
right now.
- I wanna hear yours.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I need to learn mine.
I don't like the song
personally,
so I'm not gonna go around
and like spreading my bad song
to everyone.
I wanna keep it to myself and be
like, all right,
let me think of a plan in order
to make this work.
- So, Heather, what did you
think of your recording session?
How'd it go yesterday?
- It went well.
I like it.
- Now that we have our music,
I was like, "Oh, dang,
I don't know about this."
It's kind of weird to hear
my own voice.
Trust me; it sounds a lot
better in my head,
but there was really nothing
left to do
except to perform
the hell out of it.
This is gonna be interesting.
- Oh...making a cowboy hat?
- Mm-hmm.
- Did you rhinestone the trim?
- Uh-huh.
- That's cute.
Do you need more rhinestones?
I have some more.
- Mm-mm. I have some more.
Oh, you sure you don't wanna put
some more rhinestones on that?
That was not her trying to help
me.
That was her trying to get into
my head.
- Well, these are pretty
rhinestones, gir.
- Thank you.
[dramatic music]
[RuPaul laughing]
[music plays]
♪ ♪
Well, hello there!
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, a name
that's music to my ears.
- Aw, go on.
- Jeffrey Moran...
Absolut brand czar.
Baby, we gotta stop meetin'
like this.
- Yes, honey, but in that dress,
we're gonna meet a lot more
often.
- [laughs]
Jody Watley.
Not only are you one of my
favorite singers,
you're my favorite Soul Train
dancer.
- Thank you!
- Carmen Electra, welcome!
I feel so Paisley Park tonight.
- Yes, very!
- This week, each of our queens
was challenged to record my song
Super Star
in a different style.
Now they're here to perform in
front of a live audience
at Rupaulapalooza,
sponsored by Absolut.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[music plays, applause]
[whooping]
- ♪ Super star, super star ♪
- ♪ Now that the time ♪
♪ Has come ♪
♪ Waiting what seems like ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ You gather ♪
♪ Your broken dreams ♪
♪ And put all the pieces ♪
♪ Together ♪
♪ And everyone will see ♪
♪ What you were meant to be ♪
♪ Oh ♪
I just unfold my wings.
I'm giving you Soul Train
realness, honey.
♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ As you are ♪
♪ You're a super star ♪
- ♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ All of the glamour ♪
♪ And all of the fame ♪
♪ Yeah, people are gonna ♪
♪ Remember your name ♪
♪ Hah hah ♪
I know I look good.
I'm feelin' fabulous.
Whoo-whoo!
Alexis is serving hip-hop.
♪ Seriously, mama ♪
♪ Please don't look back ♪
♪ 'Cause I have been drivin'
in from far ♪
♪ for Puerto Rico ♪
♪ I'm about to attack ♪
♪ 'Cause this is my time ♪
♪ And I'm a star ♪
- [whooping]
- Bam!
- Can I get a hallelu?
♪ ♪
♪ Now that the time has come ♪
♪ Waiting what seems like ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
Everyone looks wired.
They might as well be in
a country hoe-down,
and I love that.
So I just start boot-scootin'
my way
right on across that stage.
♪ Now and forever ♪
♪ Your dream's comin' true ♪
♪ They're gonna love you ♪
♪ Whatever you do ♪
♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ As you are ♪
♪ Yee-haw ♪
♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ You're a super star ♪
♪ Super star ♪
♪ That's what you are,
whoo ♪
- ♪ Now that the time has come ♪
♪ Waiting what seems like ♪
♪ Forever ♪
I'm a little worried
about the audience...
how they are gonna take this
ballad.
But at the end...people like
receiving me with open arms.
I love it.
♪ What you were meant to be ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ All of the glamour ♪
♪ And all of the fame ♪
♪ People are gonna ♪
♪ Remember your name ♪
♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ As you are ♪
[singing in native language]
- ♪ Now that the time ♪
♪ Has time ♪
- ♪ Ooh ooh ♪
- ♪ waitin' will seem like
forever ♪
♪ And everyone will see ♪
- ♪ Everyone ♪
- ♪ What I was meant to be ♪
♪ Oh ♪
It's hard to get into character
and be, you know,
the sexy person
performing to, like, the cats
in the alley.
So I'm just trying to like do
something that's gonna
compensate
for the horrible vocal.
♪ Gonna love me ♪
♪ Yes, they are ♪
♪ They're gonna love me ♪
♪ I'm a super star ♪
♪ ♪
[punk rock music begins]
- [whooping]
- ♪ Now that the time
has come ♪
♪ Waiting what seems like
forever ♪
♪ Gather your broken dreams ♪
♪ And put all the pieces
together ♪
I go out there, and I'm really
feeling my look.
I want it to embody punk as a
philosophy and as a movement,
and I just wanted to have
a great time out there.
♪ Now and forever ♪
♪ The dreams come true ♪
♪ They're gonna love you ♪
♪ Whatever you do ♪
♪ Gonna love you as you are ♪
♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ You're a super ♪
♪ ♪
♪ A super star ♪
- [whooping]
- Ladies...
it's time for the judges'
critique.
Let's start with Manila.
- Ooh!
- [laughing]
- I thought the lip sync
could've
been a little more on point.
I wanted to feel like you were
singing it a little bit more.
- I was surprised that you went
directly to the audience,
as soon as you came onto
the stage.
I felt you grabbing
at the audience too early.
- Okay.
- Your moves were great.
You had really super moves,
and I pray to god there's a
bottle of Absolut
hidden in that fro somewhere.
- There's actually a whole case.
- The song was totally late '70s
After School Special
starring Scott Baio theme song,
which I love.
And you look gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- Next up, Alexis Mateo.
Now, tell us about your outfit.
- My outfit was inspired
by Lil' Kim.
- Uh! Bam!
Girl, I think you got Missy
Elliott stuffed up in there!
- Yes. Big ol' titties
and lotsa ass.
- Alexis sold it.
I could tell that you were
enjoying it.
The lip sync was great.
Loved the rap.
- I'm a hip-hop girl,
and this is like Hannah Montana
does hip-hop.
- Hannah Montana?
- All right, up next,
our country queen Shangela.
- Hey, y'all.
- You chose to do today's
country look
like Carrie Underwood
and Taylor Swift.
- To me it was a little more pop
than country.
I would have liked to have seen
something
just a little bit more
unexpected.
- You definitely came out
with the energy.
There's no question.
But I think I almost saw that
energy getting the best of you.
It got a little sloppy
sometimes.
- Your energy is always great.
But I would have liked to have
seen
a little more country stuff
in there.
- But I just--you know, I feel
that it's important that we just
are open-minded with regard
to country.
I know you guys are definitely
open-minded to that,
and so I appreciate all
your comments back.
- When we're sitting here,
we hear that song,
that's what dictated it.
It's not our preconceived notion
of country.
It's that [imitating banjo]
♪ ra-dah-diddle-did-dah ♪
You know?
That's what you heard.
- All right, next up, our
pop princess Yara Sofia.
I love the fact that you put
some Spanish in there.
- Yes.
- That was fantastic.
- Thank you.
- I don't know if I would have
picked that outfit
for that version of the song,
but you do look spectacular.
- I appreciate that sex sells.
I might have maybe covered up
a little skin.
- Had you stood at the back
of the stage back there
for a little longer with
the mic stand,
you could have sold the ballad
a little bit more.
- Yes, you could have worked
the mic stand more,
but you connected
with the audience.
I love the glitter.
It's very Britney MTV
Video Music Awards,
I'm a Slave.
Britney wants her old body back
too, by the way.
- I bet she does.
[laughter]
Up next, our punk queen Raja.
We've been asking you here for
you to tap into that power
that you have when you walk
the runway,
and it looked to me like
you did it.
- I loved it.
I loved the performance;
the lip sync was great.
- You really owned the stage on
this one.
I mean, I was there.
I felt like I could have gotten
in the mosh pit.
- When I was 14, I had the same
hairdo, but it was blue.
Everything was on tonight,
Raja.
Your performance, your look,
your attitude, the emo...
Like, way on.
- Thank you so much.
- Up next...
lady reggae, Carmen Carrera.
Tell me about your outfit.
- Well, my outfit is kind of
like if Bob Marley
had a lovechild
with a Puerto Rican girl
and she grew up in jersey.
- I love the outfit.
There was some problems
in the lip sync.
It was a little off.
- So, now Jeffrey, she pulled
the guy up onstage,
but she left him there.
- Frankly, he diverted
my attention
a little too much from you.
This is about you.
You're going to be
the super star.
It made me feel like quality
impression...
and a little low on the
delivery.
- I sound horrible,
but that's okay--I'm a man.
- You didn't sound horrible.
You didn't--you just--it felt
that you weren't committed
to the vocal.
Ladies, $75,000 is at stake.
And the decisions get harder
and harder to make.
And I need your help.
Who should go home tonight
and why?
Raja.
- Oh, man.
I fucking hate this question.
You know what, I--
oh, God.
I would Shangela,
only because, you know what,
clearly you could go down
the line,
you can tell which genre
of music every one,
for the most part,
and then, you know, it just kind
of gets lost
as far as her look.
- Carmen, same question.
- I have to agree with Raja
because I feel that there's
always a look issue.
You need to look the part
if you're going to be
a drag super star.
- Where look is definitely
important,
you have to be able to perform,
and you need to be able
to connect,
and obviously she didn't do that
tonight,
and she has continuously not
done that
throughout this competition,
and that's truly why I feel
Carmen Carrera
should be the one who goes home
tonight.
- Alexis Mateo.
- I'm going to pick Carmen
Carrera as well,
and I think she's resting
and pretty.
- All right, girls,
I think we've heard enough.
Now while you enjoy an Absolut
cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
All right, just between us
girls...
We'll start with Manila.
Now, I have never enjoyed
a performer
to come out and immediately
attack the audience.
- I loved the fro,
and I love what she delivered,
but I think I'm with you.
I don't want her attacking
that audience.
- I think she looked good;
her costume and the whole
package.
And I love that she attacked
the audience.
Good for her.
- Alexis Mateo.
- The good was she really did
own her performance.
- It's hip-hop.
We don't know you as that kind
of an artist,
and then you come out here.
You got a hip-hop hat on,
you got a girl hip-hop jacket
on,
and then the rest is stripper.
That's not hip-hop.
- I mean, what was she supposed
to wear,
some--she's supposed to sport
a sag and a wife beater?
- If I pick her up, we're going
to an interview
and I see those--you
gotta cover those up!
- Well, a big trend
in queens these days
are those latex boobs.
- Oh! I don't like the way
they look.
Those aren't breasts.
These are breasts!
- Oh! Girl!
- These are breasts!
- You don't have to tell me
twice.
Shangela, now, she made
a bold decision
to do today's country look.
- She didn't do it for me.
And I understand, you know,
the whole "I want it to be
current
and I want it to be now
country,"
like...fine.
But someone's paying you to do
something, sweetie;
you gotta deliver on that.
- I almost don't even remember
it,
it was so middle of the road.
- If you have to explain it,
it's not being projected.
It was a fail.
- Yara Sofia!
- That body is near-perfection.
- But with that said,
that voice is still there.
- [laughs]
- And I don't ever want to hear
her record again, just FYI.
[RuPaul laughing]
- I don't know, I thought she
had guts to get up here.
She sparkled.
I liked her.
- Carmen Carrera.
- The best thing about it for me
was the outfit.
- I saw...some style with
no substance.
- I think she's too
self-conscious
about looking anything other
than sexy.
- Right.
- And I do think she has the
goods,
like she's not moving past this
point of posing.
- That's her crutch.
So she really doesn't have to
bring anything else.
- Raja.
- A lot of performing
is owning it.
Raja just owned it.
- She walked out with those
Doc Martens
and that little plaid number,
and I'm like, she got it!
- She can study a look,
and she can get it,
and she works it on the runway,
but when it comes to emoting,
she's fallen short.
And, Michelle, you've seen this.
Do you think she's broken
through that?
- I think this was so in touch
with the core of who she is
that we can't really judge if
she's broken through or not.
- She represented the strongest
type of woman,
which I find so attractive.
And I wouldn't mind if she,
uh...
well, I guess she wouldn't need
to strap it on.
- No!
[laughter]
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back...my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Now, based on your performance
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Yara Sofia, your performance
was graceful...
but your power ballad ran
out of gas.
You're safe.
Raja, the judges OD'ed on your
punk performance.
God save the queen.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
And you've won an original
custom gown by Marcomarco
from the House
of Infinite Radness.
- I feel fantastic.
Grew up being a little punk kid,
so it was kind of nice to get
to live that look.
And I deserve to win.
- Carmen Carrera...
Your reggae was half-baked,
and your performance went up
in smoke.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- Oh...God!
I was in the bottom two
last time,
so for me, it's do or die.
- Manila.
Your disco look rocked the boat.
You're safe.
Shangela.
Your attempt to explain away
your new country look
fell on deaf ears.
Alexis Mateo, your hip-hop was
just too damn strip hop.
Alexis Mateo...
You are safe.
- Thank you.
- Shangela, my dear, you are up
for elimination.
- When Ru says that I'm in the
bottom two,
my heart is beating so loudly
because it's not time for me
to go home.
It's not.
- Two queens.
Stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last
chance
to impress me and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
for you to lip sync...
for your life!
Good luck and don't...
fuck it up.
[music begins]
♪ ♪
- ♪ No matter how hard I try ♪
♪ You keep pushing me aside ♪
♪ And I can't break through ♪
♪ There's no talkin' to you ♪
♪ So sad that you're leavin'♪
♪ Takes time to believe it ♪
♪ But after all ♪
♪ Is said and done ♪
♪ You're gonna be ♪
♪ The lonely one ♪
♪ Oh, do you believe in life ♪
♪ After love ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I can feel something ♪
♪ Inside me say ♪
♪ I really don't think ♪
♪ You're strong enough, no ♪
♪ Well, I know ♪
♪ That I'll get through this ♪
- It hurts me to say that
Shangela's kind of turning it
out.
I mean, I'm rootin' for my
girl,
but Carmen might be in trouble.
- ♪ I don't need you anymore ♪
♪ No, I don't need you
anymore ♪
♪ ♪
- Ooh!
- ♪ Do you believe in love ♪
♪ After love ♪
♪ ♪
[song ends]
- [whooping, whistling]
- Ladies...
I've made my decision.
Shangela...shante, you stay.
- [exhales]
Thank you.
[whispers]
- Carmen Carrera...
my jersey girl.
You're a fierce queen.
Do you believe in life after
RuPaul's Drag Race?
Because I believe in you.
Now...sashay away.
[applause]
- Ru's decision's Ru's decision,
and I respect her decision.
I think in this competition
it's about doing it
and doing it the best you can,
and if other people do it
better,
then that's...
the reality of it.
But I am the most beautiful one
here,
and honestly, I would have liked
to get sent home by
somebody better.
- Condragulations, girls.
You have been turning it out
week after week, and so don't
even think of letting up now.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get a amen in here?
all: Amen!
- All right,
now let the music play!
♪ ♪
- Grand prize contributed
in part by AlandChuck.travel.