- Sick...
twisted...
unnatural...
you asked for it...
and you got it.
It's a brand-new season
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Let the games begin!
This year's search for
America's Next Drag
Superstar...
- Shake it!
- Goes where no man
has gone before.
- No one can do lip-syncing
in space.
Prepare to die!
- Aah!
- More queens...
more sassy stars...
- Ho ho ho ho!
- What did you just call me?
- Hallelu.
- More tears...
- [sobbing] I don't know
what I was thinking.
- And big, big...
- Can I use that to store some
of my shoes?
- Cash money, honey.
- That's a lotta fucking money.
- We've taken everything you
love...
- Get her off of me!
- And super-sized it.
The time has come...
- ♪ Ah ah ah ah ah ♪
- For you to lip-synch...
- ♪ Ro-ma, ro-ma-la ♪
- For your life.
- ♪ Want your bad romance ♪
- Shot in eye-popping triple D.
Stop the insanity!
RuPaul's Drag Race is about
to spin out of control...
in three...
two...
one.
- My name is Delta Work.
I'm 34 years old, and I'm
from Norwalk, California.
There's gonna be a good half
the people watching
that think that a big girl
can't win this competition.
But if you can't get past that,
then you're not gonna get into
everything I have to offer.
I'm here not just to represent
the big girls.
I wanna follow in RuPaul's
footsteps.
- My name is Christopher Ulman,
also known as Carmen Carrera.
I am 25 years old
from New Jersey.
Titties, titties!
- [laughing]
- Body!
- Carmen Carrera is, like, the
flyest girl
you're gonna ever meet
in your life.
I make sure that her body is
flawless.
If you find a flaw, let me know.
- Hi!
- Hi.
- What's goin' on?
- Oh, look at your shoes.
I love them!
- Oh, those are rad.
- Fierce, honey, fierce.
My name is Phoenix.
I'm 29 years old.
I'm from Atlanta, Georgia.
Yay, craziness.
When I walk in, I want people to
be like, okay...
she could be a handful.
I can play well with others.
My mom raised me well.
But I definitely do have a
bitchy side.
- [falsetto] Hello!
- Well, hel-lo!
- Manila!
- Hi! Oh, my God, look at you!
I'm Manila Luzon.
I am a creative little kid from
the Midwest whose creativity was
too big for Minnesota.
So I moved to New York City.
- Oh, I'm so happy you're here.
I love Manila.
I know her from working
in New York.
- This is the most clothes I
have seen you ever in.
- I know.
- Always buck naked.
My drag persona Manila is my
personal muse because...
I inspire myself.
[laughs]
- Hi!
- Hi.
My name is Stacy Layne Matthews.
I'm 25 years old, and I'm from
Back Swamp, North Carolina.
I'm very much so
a country queen.
I live on a dirt road surrounded
by corn fields.
Can't get more country than
that.
- We got two of y'all tonight.
- Okay.
- Yes, honey.
- Being a plus-size queen living
in a drag community
that's so vicious--
it's so vicious--
it's built me up to be who I am.
- The weather girls are here.
- Say, word.
[door opens]
- Hello!
all: Hi!
- My name is Adam,
AKA Venus D-Lite.
I'm 26 years old, and I live
in Los Angeles.
- Hi, Venus!
- Hey, what's going on?
Hi, baby.
Venus's female role models are
Madonna, of course,
Grace Jones, Barbra Streisand,
and Jean Harlow.
She's just a blond bombshell
ditzy bimbo.
- Hi.
- I'm Yara Sofia.
I'm 26.
I'm from Puerto Rico.
I'm the Puerto Rican one, so...
- So? I'm the Asian.
- And what about you?
- From L.A., I'm Italian.
- I'm from L.A., also.
I'm black.
[laughter]
- Everybody knows who is
Yara Sofia in Puerto Rico.
I mean, if you don't, I'm sorry,
darling, this is not your world.
- Hey!
all: Hey!
- I am Mariah Balenciaga,
AKA Mariah Paris,
AKA Mariah Successful.
I'm from Atlanta, Georgia,
and I am 29 years old.
I know you.
- Good to see you, baby.
- Mariah tends to be the center
of the party.
I mean, you cannot miss her.
A 6'2" glamazon walking through
the middle of the room with legs
like a racehorse.
- Y'all got things worked
in yet?
- No, we're just kinda waiting
around for all the girls to come
so we can judge them.
- Oh. There's more?
I've dominated and conquered
drag's face
for the past 11 years.
There's really nobody who can
touch Mariah.
- Hey, hey, hey!
all: Hi!
- How's everybody doing?
My name is Alexis Mateo.
I'm 30 years old.
Everybody's having fun?
all: Yes.
- [giggles]
- Are you from Texas?
- I'm living in Florida right
now--I'm from Puerto Rico.
- Oh, see, double down!
We got two big girls,
we got two Puerto Ricans.
- What I hate the most is that
people label you
as the Latin queen.
I'm not just a Latin queen.
When I'm in drag, I'm a star.
- Oh!
- Ooh.
Oh, my.
It's embarrassing to walk in
with a room with a whole bunch
of queens,
and you guys are wearing
the same outfit.
- I was like, oh, my gosh.
I know they are gasping
for breath right now.
- I'm India Ferrah.
I'm from Dayton, Ohio.
I'm 23 years old.
Girl, prison, honey.
I look over to Phoenix copying
my style.
So I actually had to go up to
her and,
you know, be a little cunt
to her.
I love your hair.
[laughter]
- I'm definitely wearing the
hair better, the vinyl better.
India's very, like...painted.
She's very, like,
old-school drag.
But it's cool.
It's cool to see, like,
that style of drag still
amongst us, so...
- Have we figured out who's
gonna be the bitch yet?
- Ooh!
[murmuring]
- Welcome to my party!
all: Hi!
- Oh, my gosh!
I brought cookies.
I'm Mimi Imfurst.
I'm 27,
and I'm from New York City.
How y'all doing?
I just want to start off on good
terms with all these bitches
before I start taking them down.
[laughing]
So who's the bitch here?
It's what I need to know
right away.
- You know what...I think we're
gonna appoint you.
You okay with that?
- Girl, no.
- She ain't that slick, honey,
Miss Mimi.
Before there was Mimi,
there was Mariah.
- Oh...
- Yes!
- Oh, my God.
- It's the purple people eater!
- [laughing]
Hi, ladies.
My name's Sutan,
also known as Raja.
I'm 36 years old, and I'm from
Los Angeles, California.
Raja's a model.
She's uber-stylish.
She was doing stuff that Gaga's
doing now
before Gaga even knew about it.
Yay!
- When Raja walked in,
100% pure family walked in.
- Umph, umph, umph!
I love you!
How are you?
What's your name?
- I see you lookin' at me.
[laughter]
Her look is definitely not
polished.
It's definitely not fabulous.
It almost looks as if I went
into my granny's trunk
in the attic.
- I could see the surprised look
on everyone's faces.
It was the exact the reaction
I wanted.
We're drag queens.
We're meant to be pioneers.
So why not wear a funny little
cyclops hat?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Raja.
It's a pleasure to meet you
guys.
- Club kid.
Where's her body, where's her
hair, where's her makeup?
I don't see her on the same
level as the rest of us.
[alarm whoops]
- Whoo, girl!
You got shemail.
Welcome, racers.
[cheers and applause]
You know great things
come in threes--
The Supremes, Destiny's Child,
Mark Wahlberg's nipples.
[laughter]
Now, RuPaul's Drag Race,
season three, hunty, okay?
- Yeah!
- So you think you know what it
takes to become America's Next
Drag Superstar?
Well, think again!
Watch your back, my queens.
'Tis the season when anything
and everything can change in
the blink of an eye.
So strap in, and let's get this
mothertruckin' drag race
on the road, okay?
[all whooping]
- Hello, hello, hello!
[laughing]
Wow!
Look how purdy you are!
How gorgeous!
I think I'm gonna cry!
[laughter]
Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race.
I am so thrilled to be standing
here among such royalty.
You, my dears, are the fiercest
of the fierce!
- Yes!
- This is your chance to show
the world that you've got the
charisma, uniqueness, nerve,
and talent to be America's Next
Drag Superstar.
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup,
headline Logo's Drag Race Tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut.
And America's Next Drag
Superstar will also receive...
$75,000.
- [whooping]
- $75,000!
[cheers and applause]
- Bitch...
- That's a lotta fucking money.
- You know, they say Christmas
comes but once a year.
But around here, we like to deck
the halls all year round.
I declare that it's officially
Christmastime
at RuPaul's Drag Race!
[cheers and applause]
- To kick off the holiday,
I have a little gift from me
to you.
Oh, pit crew!
- Ooh!
- Ow!
[laughter]
- Well, kiss that Christmas!
Baby, I was starting to get
a little sweaty.
These guys are fine.
Maybe there's something bigger
and buffer
coming out of the box.
I was ready for the third one.
It was about to be a party.
- Now, if good things come in
small packages,
then this is gonna be
re-donkulous!
- Hallelu, ladies!
- Oh, my God.
- Whoo!
- And there's Shangela.
Hallelu.
- Hallelu, hallelu!
Oh!
Merry Christmas.
Happy holidays, bitches.
[chortling]
- Everybody's face...gagged.
What the fuck?
Who invite this girl again?
She already got her moment
of glory.
She got eliminated.
- Sahara Davenport...
Shantay. You stay.
Shangela, you have only
just begun.
But I have a feeling...
we haven't seen
the last of you yet.
Now, for the first time
in Drag Race history,
I'm giving one of my girls
a second chance.
Shangela will be joining you
in this competition.
all: Oh...
- Welcome, Shangela.
- It's a nice thing that
Shangela's here,
but she doesn't threaten me
in any way.
- So now that all 13 of my girls
are here...
are you ready for your close-up?
Hey, Carmen.
- Hey, hey.
- Come on, down, mami.
- What's going on?
- This is celebrity photographer
Mike Ruiz.
Mike has set up this gorgeous
Christmas winter wonderland
scenario,
and he's gonna get a few shots
of you.
- Okay.
- Today is the first challenge
of the entire race,
and it's so important
because it's the first
impression that they make.
- This is gonna be a sexy, sexy
cover of your Christmas card.
You are going to be jumping on
that trampoline to do it.
- Oh, God.
[laughing]
I'm not gonna be able to pull
this off.
I'm wearing the wrong dress
to be jumping.
This is gonna be terrible.
Wait, let me just make sure that
all my jewels are locked away.
- Well, you've got several
jewels.
- Okay, all right,
let's do this, yo!
[laughs]
- It's snowin' at the Jersey
Shore!
Blow this, Snooki.
Yes, mama.
You...
- Oh--
[laughter]
- The flying lady
on a Rolls-Royce!
- Don't worry.
We're good, we're good.
I'm sorry.
That photo shoot
was such a mess.
I was not ready for none
of that.
- Okay, we got one.
Uno, dos, tres.
Gorgeous!
- Uh-oh.
- Don't worry, don't worry.
I'm okay.
- Careful, Mimi.
I can see your nutcracker, hon.
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
Yeah...yeah.
Let's start again.
And hit it.
[camera shutter clicks]
Crazy. Okay.
Mimi had a really hard time
maintaining composure.
She wasn't giving us sexy.
She was giving us crazy.
- Pick your feet up.
Whoo--ooh hoo hoo!
- I'm jumping on the trampoline
with my boobs,
which are very heavy.
They weigh about 12 pounds.
I was sweating to death.
They wanted to fall off.
- I think your breasts are
throwing your balance off.
- They're throwing
my balance off.
- [grunting]
- There ya go.
- [laughs]
I was a little nervous
about this challenge.
Me being a plus-size queen
trying to jump around on a
trampoline is not cute.
- You gotta jump
as high as you can.
A little bit higher, if you
can.
One, two, three.
- And he keeps telling me to
jump higher, jump higher.
But my fat ass, I'm sorry...
[laughs] I can't jump that high
on a trampoline.
- One, two, three!
Beautiful.
Okay, do something nasty now
with that candy cane.
Ride that cane!
Beautiful.
Mariah just, like,
radiates sexuality.
- Your eggnog brings
all the boys to the yard.
Send in the clowns!
[laughter]
Hi, Raja.
- Hi, Raja!
- Come on down.
- W.T.F.?
To see a trampoline flanked
by half-nude men...
I mean, what else could
I ask for?
- Gimme sexy face.
- Oh, yes!
- Okay. You know what I want,
Raja.
- Oh, yes, mami!
- Raja is this beautiful,
elegant gazelle.
He really has a good sense
of his body
and how to portray it
in a photograph.
One, two, three.
- Hi.
Ooh!
Look at you guys!
What's up, dudes?
What's up, bros?
Everyone's unpacking, and I got
a chance to kind of look around
the room and see everyone
stripped down
without their makeup,
the wigs are gone,
the paddings are gone.
And I got to see these men and,
you know what?
I've gotta say some of them
are kind of cute.
Yara's kind of a cute boy.
Tattoos.
Oh, my God, kind of hottie
over there.
Oh, my god, that one--is that
even out of drag yet?
Stacy looks like a girl out
of drag.
I was like,
is that somebody's mama?
- For Puerto Rico!
Feliz Navidad!
Gorgeous.
- Alexis, a little Ann-Margret
she was giving me today.
And sexy face.
- Sexy face!
- Gorgeous. We got it.
That was it.
Beautiful.
One, two, three.
Ooh, how phallic.
Manila was actually really great
on the trampoline,
very limber and very capable.
- [gags]
[laughter]
- Okay, we got it!
- [gags]
- Good. And sexy!
- Oh...oh!
- Try and get off the ground
just a little bit more.
One, two, three.
Okay, and hit it.
Not so high with your hands.
Keep your hands down here.
One, two, three.
- Ooh, Merry Christmas!
- Higher, higher!
- You look like a snow leopard.
- Hi!
- Hey, Shangela.
- Hi, Ru!
- Good to see ya.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- One year later, and I'm in
front of Mike Ruiz again.
I have something to prove.
Get out here and turn it out.
Round two, baby.
I am ready.
- All right.
- I look forward to it.
Okay, yea--
oh, yes, mama!
Sex-ual!
Christmas never looked so sexy!
- You have made us proud.
You have done your homework.
- Yay! Thank you.
Whoo!
Girl, got me right on together.
When I step into that room, I
felt like I'd gone back in time.
Well, I remember the spot that
was unlucky in love for me
last season,
so let me go find a new spot.
Hallelu!
Ooh, praise him.
Ah.
Now, some of these new queens
may not be so excited that
Shangela is back
in the building.
- No, I auditioned, just like--
yeah, I auditioned
just like everyone else.
She kept asking me,
"Girl, how'd you get back?"
She seemed a little cunty
about it.
And I feel like over the last
year I've grown,
and also I wanted to come back
and compete
and really compete.
- Shangela, she says she's
gained enough experience.
All I can say, Shangela,
is prove it.
Serve it, girl.
Because you're under
the microscope now, bitch.
- She's probably one I'm gonna
have to watch my back for.
- Ooh!
- Yeah!
[all whooping]
- Over here, baby.
Bring it over here.
Over here, over here.
- Hello, ladies.
Well, who are you?
[all whooping]
- Who are you people?
Now, Mike and I went over all
of your photographs.
One shot in particular really
got our jingle bells ringing.
The winner of the holiday card
photo shoot is...
Raja.
- Yes!
[cheers and applause]
To win the very first challenge
feels good,
feels like I've staked my claim
and put my little mark
on this competition.
I kinda lifted my leg
and pissed on it a little bit.
Cheers, bitches.
[applause]
- Now, tonight I expect you all
to have visions of sugar plums
dancing in your head.
Because the countdown has begun.
Tomorrow, I wanna see you in
your finest daywear drag.
And there's only one shopping
day left until it's Christmas
at RuPaul's Drag Race.
[cheers and applause]
[all speaking at once]
[car horns honk]
[wolf whistles]
- Being in drag in the middle
of the day's kind of weird.
It's like the circus
was in town.
[cars honking]
- I felt a little uncomfortable.
I don't do that.
I don't go out in the daytime
in drag.
- When we find out that we have
to go out during the daytime
and go shopping in drag...
I'm good, 'cause, baby,
if it's right, it's right.
[bell dings]
[overlapping chatter]
- There we are,
standing in daytime drag
in the middle of some
thrift store.
Nobody clocked me.
They thought I was Jada Pinkett
Smith up in there.
- Gather 'round, dolls.
Now, Christmas is a season
for miracles and shopping.
And today, you need to do
a little bit of both.
Using only funky old clothes
and used household materials,
you need to ho ho ho it up...
by creating your jolliest
holiday drag look.
You can use your own wigs,
shoes, and undergarments.
Plus, any holiday chotchkies
you can...
mop.
But the rest of your outfit has
to be 100% thrift store couture,
darlings.
Tomorrow you will debut your
dragtacular holiday look
on the main stage.
Now, you each have $50 and ten
minutes to shop until you drop.
Now, Raja, since you won
the photo shoot,
you get an extra $25 to spend.
- [snaps]
- Gentlemen,
start your engines...
and may the best woman win!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- I had to throw those shoes off
and punch it.
First thing I eyed was that big
lamp in the window.
I knew I'd have to ask, please,
can you give a bitch a bargain?
I just have to have this,
and I don't have $45.
How 'bout $22?
I'm on a budget.
- $23.
- $23! Say hallelu for me.
- Hallelu!
- Hallelu! All right!
You ask, it shall be given.
- Can I see
that gold shiny thing?
- This thing?
- Maybe this could be my skirt.
- You've worn less.
- I'm not sure how much of
an outfit I'm gonna have.
You know, it's gonna have to be
something a little sexy.
- Out of my way, girl.
- It's all ugly.
- Just like some of these
contestants.
- Now, I've shopped in enough
thrift stores in my day to know
that very rarely are you gonna
find my size on a rack.
So I'm just gonna grab
all the fabric I can find.
I need a shopping cart.
- Girl...
- This is the best Christmas
ever.
- Oh! It's so pretty.
- When we walked back
into the workroom,
we have to rush and get any
holiday fixings that we can.
It's a race.
- These ladies are no ladies.
- Don't touch my shit.
This is mine.
- They are runnin' around,
snatching things off the wall.
It is a mad dash.
- Oh, girl,
I found myself a skirt.
Yes!
- Oh...
- Oh, yeah.
I'm ruling this fucking school.
- I just broke my Christian Dior
sunglasses doing this.
I better win this shit.
Ugh!
- I see Shangela.
She is dragging this big-ass
styrofoam snowman
across the room.
Is she gonna wear it?
I don't know
what she's gonna do.
- You always snatching.
What is that?
I'm trying to be sister element
of surprise,
but it's hard when you got
a 5-foot snowman.
She missing a eye and a nose,
but she gonna be all right.
- Ladies, can I just say
something?
I am from Chicago!
[laughter]
- I was waiting
to see the first one
to start screaming at somebody.
I knew it was gonna be
her crazy ass.
Mimi, I think, is one of these
people that, um, really, really
wants to be center
of everything.
- Can I get an amen?
- Amen.
- Can I get
a [speaking gibberish]?
- If that's her way,
that's fine, but it's...
annoying as hell to me, so...
- [speaking gibberish]
- I don't know how I came up
with this idea, but...
it is working to my advantage.
I work great under pressure, and
I was just--I was feeling it.
I was feeling great.
[snapping]
- Does anybody have any red
ornaments they don't want?
- No, I need some too.
- Okay.
- Then I noticed Phoenix was
doing the same thing.
That's shady to me.
- Evidently, I'm "copying"
her amazing idea.
- You can be my friend or you
can be my enemy--
just say it to my face.
I mean, if somebody pisses me
off, I'm gonna tell 'em.
- I see the claws are comin' out
early, honey.
Whatever is in the dark
shall come to the light,
especially with regard
to this experience.
- The runway challenge is to
create a Christmas-inspired
outfit from all the things
that we got at the thrift shop.
- Honey, there was nothing
at that store my size.
I'm using bed sheets.
- Oh, right.
- Girl, if I get in this dress
and it does not fit,
I'm gonna cry.
- Ho, ho, ho, ladies.
- Hey.
- Hey, Ru.
- Shangela Laquifa Wadley.
- This is Laquifa.
Shangela Laquifa
in the Wadley family.
- I see.
- I've made a Shange-replica.
That's how I'm gonna turn it out
on that stage.
I designed this piece myself.
This is actually sewn onto
a bodice--I did that.
So hopefully, we'll all be
hitting the runway tomorrow.
- Well, that's all cute,
but we're talking about $75,000
here.
- But it's gonna work.
I feel like, I'm putting a lot
into my creation,
and I'm confident that it'll
at least go over well.
- Now, Shangela,
I have a lot of faith in you.
That's why I invited you back.
- I really appreciate it.
And I'm trying not
to disappoint you.
- All right, terrific.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Hey, Phoenix.
- Hey, Ru.
- Merry Christmas.
- You too!
- This is pretty amazing.
Now, these are--are what?
- Shattered...
- Oh, shattered glass.
- Mm-hmm. Shattered glass, yes.
- Oh, you're showing a lot
of creativity--we like that.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, Phoenix.
- Thank you, babe.
- Mimi Mimi Mimi Imfurst.
- Ho ho ho, Ru.
- Ho ho ho to you!
Now, I wanna talk about
this amazing...
- [laughs]
- Outfit you have here.
It's very, uh, manger couture.
Would you say you were halfway
done, 3/4 of the way done?
- [laughs] I don't know!
I'm just really nervous,
'cause I don't sew.
Throw me a script, throw me
a song to sing, I can do it.
- Well, you know, those have
been some famous last words
on RuPaul's Drag Race.
- I know, I know, I'm just--
I'm--I'm so nervous.
- But you know,
there are other
girls here who don't know
how to sew,
but they're gluin'
and puttin' things together...
we'll see how it plays
on the runway.
- All right.
I am nervous as hell,
because I
have a raggedy-ass dress, but I
have a big problem on my hands.
- Manila Luzon.
- Hi, Ru!
- So now, I wanna hear
about your outfit.
- So I'm gonna have like a fur
collar, and then with the extra,
I'm gonna make a muff.
- Let's talk about this!
[laughing]
You got this picture of...
- That's Sahara Davenport,
my boyfriend.
- How about that?
- Yeah, she was here last
season, so I brought this.
I have my little sketch pad.
Having my boyfriend being
Sahara,
I don't think it's gonna
have any effect on my chances
of winning this contest.
Besides, Sahara didn't win,
and I'm going to.
- All right, so I'm gonna let
you get back to work.
- Thank you.
Venus D-Lite.
- Ru-Ru!
- Merry Christmas.
Chrissy kiss!
Kissy kiss!
- Now, look what you have here.
Showgirl always, aren't you?
- Yes. This was a jacket.
I took off the collar, got
ornaments, and I crushed them,
gave it a little glitzy color.
- The crushed thing here--
I saw it on a few others.
Who had it first?
- Me.
- You did.
- And the bitches stole it.
- [laughs] All right, Venus.
- All right, Ru-Ru.
- Carry on.
- Till next time.
Kissy kissies!
- [laughing]
Raja.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hello.
Well, look at this.
It's very Christmas pudding
at Vivienne Westwood's
on Boxing Day.
- You're so right!
That's exactly
what I was going for.
But I really wanted to kinda do
the idea of, like, gift wrap
and how under a Christmas tree,
it's all sort of, like,
hodgepodge and mixed up together
and a little
Christmas tree green skirt
'cause, you know,
that's where you keep all the
presents is under the tree.
Yes, ma'am!
- Well, I can't wait to see this
on the runway.
So keep working on it,
turn it out...
- Okay.
- And I'll see you later on.
Good luck.
- All right, Ru.
Thanks a lot.
- Hey, Carmen.
Wow, look, you've got your
Christmas goin' on here.
- Feeling a little spicy
this Christmas.
- Well, something tells me you
feel spicy every Christmas.
- Yes.
- And Easter...
- Uh-huh.
- And Memorial Day.
This is a lotta body showing.
Oh, she has a little booty-booty
back here.
- Yeah, this is the mistletoe
back there.
- Oh, that's the mistletoe!
I'ma let you get back to it.
I can't wait to see you
pull this off on the stage.
All right, get back to work.
- All right, thank you.
- All right.
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
- Well, hello, Ru.
- Are you having fun?
It seems like
you're the shy one.
- I'm not shy.
I'm just focused.
[both laughing]
- Now, have you been
to California before?
- No, this is my first time,
actually.
- First time in Hollywood.
- First time on a plane.
How about--we are just changing
lives over here!
- I know!
I feel like a different person.
- But can you bring
the charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talents?
- I have that,
or I wouldn't be here.
[both laughing]
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Gather 'round, dolls.
All right, ladies.
Tomorrow, on the main stage,
we'll be spending the holidays
with our extra-special guest
judge, the one and only...
Vanessa Williams.
[cheers and applause]
- For some gays and some queens,
they've got Cher and Madonna.
But I'm a big Vanessa Williams
fan.
- 'Tis the season for giving...
so you better be serving up
some holiday realness...
or this could be
your last Christmas.
So don't fuck it up.
I'll see you on the main stage.
Bye.
all: Bye.
- [sobbing]
I fucked it up.
I don't know
what I was thinking!
I don't know how to sew and,
um...
[sniffles] I know it's
my biggest hurdle and...
I'm just a--I've worked so hard
to get here, and I'm just...
I don't wanna fail.
[sniffles]
- Is she okay?
- No.
- Girl, seriously...
come here, babe.
If you have a undergarment,
take it out,
like a full undergarment.
- I don't.
Mariah came over, and she sort
of helped me rethink everything.
- Get your undergarment.
Go get your undergarments.
You need your undergarments.
I knew she had bitten off more
than she could chew so,
you know, when she broke down,
I was like, "Oh, baby."
- What you need to do is pick
out some of your fiercest hair
and, bitch, paint
for filth tomorrow.
I feel bad for her.
I think, you know, she feels
that she's gonna have
to lip-synch for her life
tomorrow night,
and, honestly, I think so too.
- Girl, don't blow your nose
on the fabric, bitch.
- Mimi is freaked out.
Girl! Put yourself together,
darling!
- It's okay, mama.
- No, it's not.
I just have to finish
what I'm working on,
and tomorrow
when I hit the runway,
I wanna sell it like it's
a million-dollar dress.
And if I have to lip-synch,
I'll mother fucking lip-synch
my life off.
[sniffles]
- Hallelu.
- Back to work, ladies.
- We're back in the workroom
this morning, and we only have a
little bit of time to finish up
our Christmas couture.
- The vibe in the workroom felt
very much like
a Santa's workshop,
like, all the elves
were really busy.
- Okay, how come I can't even
sew a fucking jingle bell?
This is just hanging there
like a limp scrotum.
- The emotions are pretty
intense in the room.
Everyone knows that someone's
gotta go home,
and it doesn't matter how
perfect you think you are
or how bad you think
the other person is,
because there's always gonna be
an element of surprise
to these things.
- You feeling a little bit
better today, baby?
- A little bit.
- Okay.
- I had a very long night.
I didn't sleep very well,
but I just need to finish the
garment and sell it
when I go down the runway.
I'm just gonna pray
for a miracle.
- So, Venus, who do you think
is in the bottom?
- I think, um,
Mimi's going home.
Yesterday, Mimi had her
breakdown,
and today, I could just see it
all over her face.
I don't think you can be the
Next Drag Superstar
with no confidence.
- The other queens saw me
at a really vulnerable place,
so they think
that I might be weak.
Whatever.
In this business,
you have to be driven.
I don't think that there's any
drag performers
who are more driven than I am.
I think she might be a dress!
- Mimi had this idea of doing
this Virgin Mary thing.
It just looked like a laundry
bag full of, like, old sheets.
- The last time around I looked
around the room and said,
"Oh, girl, let me get this song
right, 'cause I don't wanna be
in the bottom two."
I don't wanna be lip-synching
for my life again.
It wasn't the best experience
in the world.
But this time around,
I feel really super-confident
about my outfit.
- What was it like to lip-synch
for your life last year, girl?
- Girl.
Girl, have you ever felt like
you were walking the plank
in the pirate ship, okay?
I felt like Pirates
of the Caribbean.
- The time has come...
for you to lip-synch...
for your life.
- It's funny that the phrase is
"lip-synch for your life,"
because it really feels like
you're gonna die.
No one knows that feeling
until you're there.
Being titled America's Next Drag
Superstar is a big deal.
And I'm not taking it lightly
that I'm back.
- How's your outfit comin',
Raja?
- Pretty good, actually.
I'm getting really happy
with it.
- How old are ya?
- I'm 36.
- Are you seriously?
- I started dabbling in drag
when I was 16.
In my teens, I was a pretty
awkward kid.
You know, walking down the
street, it was like, "faggot."
Drag wasn't bad.
Drag was like, "Fierce, honey!
Fabulous, girl, work,"
you know,
and that's what I needed.
As the years start to pass,
you start to, like,
look at drag differently.
- Do you love it more or...
- I love it in a different way.
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
'Cause it's always, like,
changing.
- Yeah.
And I wanna evolve constantly,
you know?
I don't ever wanna be the same
queen for the rest of my life.
- So what do you do, Venus?
- I'm a Madonna impersonator,
mainly.
- Her Madonna is fierce.
She looks just like the bitch.
- I came out at 15, and pretty
much, nobody accepted me.
And all the bullcrap that I went
through growing up,
I think it ended up
making me
a very determined
and driven person.
- Do you do anyone else
besides Madonna?
- I do a lot of characters,
but I had plastic surgery
to look more like Madonna.
[record scratch effect]
- Really? What'd you do?
- I had my cheeks done
and my chin.
- Miss Venus, you're too young,
baby, to have that much work
in your face.
That much wrong work.
- Let me see.
Where is it?
Oh...
- See?
- Is it silicone or--
- It's silicone, yeah.
- I have never had
any plastic surgery.
It's like baseball players
taking steroids.
You're sort of cheating.
- I've had this three times
and this two.
- Well, you better work
that Madonna look, grr.
- All my money and all my time
has gone into drag.
I've dedicated, devoted,
compromised my whole life to be
a drag queen,
and I think that's why I'm here.
Carmen, you always naked.
Naked.
- Sorry. I have to get ready.
- Naked.
- She has been runnin' around
the dressing room all day
completely naked.
Just naked.
I mean, is this
a sex competition,
or is this a holiday couture
competition?
- Miss Carmen,
you gotta be naked.
- Girl, I don't even see it
as naked.
I don't know what these queens
are talkin' about.
I'm sorry, you know, I feel
comfortable with my body.
For me, it's a locker room.
[tape roll stretching]
- I think this hot glue gun
gets way too hot.
It's like a lava gun right here.
- They don't call it
a warm glue gun.
- Oh, fuck.
This hurts.
- Fuck.
- I think everyone
is just really on edge.
We don't have that much time
before we have to be all up in
drag and walkin' out
on that runway.
- How you holding up?
- I wish I had more time.
- You gonna have another
breakdown, girl?
- I hope not.
- Only have a breakdown
if I'm goin' home.
Hey, guys.
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Now, tonight is like a RuPaul
family Christmas special,
and it wouldn't be Christmas
without
our very own Santa Claus!
- Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
[laughter]
- The funniest man on earth,
Bruce Vilanch.
Hi, Bruce.
- Hi, Ru.
- We are so glad you're here.
- It's tough for a Jewish boy
to do this.
- I know.
I know.
But in this economy,
you'll take it where you can.
- Exactly. I'm up-sizing.
[laughter]
- Santino!
- Hey, Ru.
- Hello, my dear.
- Shall we dance?
- Let's.
- [laughs]
- And the return of Michelle
Visage,
my cohost for over 100 episodes
of the RuPaul talk show.
- Couldn't keep us apart.
- [laughs]
And Mike Ruiz.
- Yes!
- We've just gotta stop
meeting like this.
- I know!
- Prissy kissness.
And I saved the best for last.
[laughter]
The lovely and talented
Vanessa Williams is here!
- Darling, you look phenomenal.
- Thank you so much.
I see you glittering
over there too.
- Thank you.
Got some gifts for Santa.
- Yes!
- Thank you!
[laughter]
- This week, our queens were
challenged to make their best
holiday drag looks
using thrift store hand-me-downs
and Christmas decorations.
Gentlemen...start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
Carmen Carrera.
- Hey, hey.
- Look at the size of that box!
- My lips are done,
my hair is done.
I'm feeling hot right now.
The spotlight is on me.
You can see my cheeks from
across the street.
- Uh-uh!
- Oh, the mistletoe.
- Is that mistletoe
or cameltoe?
- Look at that body. Ah!
- Manila Luzon.
- Look at the size
of that muff!
- Both hands fit.
- I am living on the runway.
I'm having so much fun.
The snow is coming, and
I'm just struttin' my stuff.
- A desperate housewife
of the North Pole.
- All right!
- He's giving us
Janice Dickinson.
- It's Yara Sofia,
and she's had her nose fixed!
- What a fabulous
set of antlers.
- I was so nervous,
but I feel great.
I did a good job,
and I give them a surprise.
- Hey!
[chuckles]
- Incredible.
- I love it!
- Oh, who do we have here?
That's Phoenix?
Ahoy!
- I think it was definitely
the best Christmas couture
that I could give.
I think my shit's fierce.
I think I could win.
- Oh, holy night,
that skirt is short.
- I can see her figgy pudding!
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
Representin' Back Swamp,
North Carolina.
- I think it's time
for a plus-size queen.
The skinny girls try
to take over,
so I think it's time
for us big girls to step up.
- Now, that's
the Jingle Bell Rock.
Oh, it's Venus D-Lite!
Merry Christmas.
- I'm just really trying to be
fun and sassy, little flirty.
I'm being me.
- Oh, lick it.
That looks delicious.
- Somebody's gonna get caned.
- India Ferrah.
- Okay, now.
Look at those two treats.
- Santa, would you like some
milk to go with those cookies?
- I'm looking good, bitch.
My hair is done, makeup right,
and I'm just walking
down the runway,
knowing that I look sickening.
- Ooh, the Fahrenheit
is getting higher!
- Delta Work.
And she is giving us
a Kwanzaa celebration.
- As soon as I hit the runway,
I am just--I'm so excited.
It's exhilarating.
It's what I've been waiting
for.
And I'm feeling really good
giving Kwanzaa realness.
- Erykah Badu!
Leontyne Price.
[laughter]
From Puerto Rico...
Alexis.
- Ooh!
- [trilling]
- Feliz Navidad.
Cha, cha, cha!
- I'm feeling fabulous.
The light, the music,
adrenaline comin' through.
I'm just feeling
on the top of the world.
- Oh!
Oh, yes! Okay.
El Barbizono modeling school-o.
- Love the snowflake earrings.
- Next, Mimi Imfurst.
- Oh, little baby Jesus
in her hands?
- Oh, yes,
it's the Madonna!
- It is!
It's the mother.
- Oh, wait a minute, that's--
that's actually a ham
in her arms.
- I hit the runway,
and I just decide in my mind
that I'm going
to deliver this dress
and deliver the character.
- I wanna see baby Jesus.
- I know--is he asleep
right now?
- He's cooking at 350!
- Hotlanta's own,
Mariah.
- In Christmas gray.
- Oh, she's giving a little
Wilhelmina Slater, I'd say.
- Yes, she is!
- I'm not polished as well
as I know I can be,
but I'm not gonna
let the judges see that.
I'm never gonna let them
see me sweat.
- Silver bells!
- Couture Christmas.
- Karl Lagerfeld,
eat your heart out.
Up next is Raja!
Oh, no stranger to the runway.
- Look at the detail
on that skirt.
- Vivienne Westwood!
What?
- Once I get out there,
I feel awesome.
That's my thing.
I am a runway girl.
I am a photography girl.
I'm a model.
- I just can't take my eyes
off of her.
- Gorgeous!
- Yes! Snow angels!
- Was it snow angels or a fit?
[laughter]
- Shangela Laquifa Wadley.
Oh, she's gained weight!
Oh, there she is.
- She made a snowman.
- She's a little frosty.
Oh, and she's got her piece
of corn there.
- All right!
- It's become a tradition here.
Oh, and her skirts light up!
Where is she keeping
the batteries?
- I am feeling so confident.
I love my outfit,
and all I can think is,
"Shangela, work, bitch."
- You know what I say.
Never work with animals,
children, or snowmen.
Welcome, ladies.
Based on your Christmas drag,
your holiday card photo shoot,
and your presentation
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Will the following queens
please step forward?
Mariah.
Delta Work.
Yara Sofia.
India Ferrah.
Phoenix.
Stacy Layne Matthews.
Alexis Mateo.
The seven of you
all stood out...
for not standing out
from the crowd.
You are all safe
from elimination.
But I warn you.
In this competition,
with $75,000 at stake...
"Safe" is a dirty word.
You may leave the stage.
All right, ladies...
you six are the nicest and
the naughtiest of the week.
It is time
for the judges' critiques.
Let's start with Carmen Carrera.
- Well, I think Carmen
used her assets to a T.
- Yes, ma'am!
- All I can think of is bows,
bows, booty.
You used what your maker gave to
you, and you brought the sexy.
- From one Jersey girl to
another, Carmen, you're hot.
You know you're hot.
Here's my one concern:
don't rely on body all the time.
- Y'all, I'd like to hear
from Santa, Bruce Vilanch.
- I'm very concerned
about the mistletoe,
because I think it's bad when
anything takes root there.
[laughter]
- Thank you, Bruce.
Let's take a look
at your holiday photo.
- You didn't really get into,
like, the dancer-ly beauty
of what I was asking
of you guys.
- I've never done
the trampoline before,
and getting on it,
I pulled a muscle.
So I wasn't really ready for
this, and it was kind of like,
the hair wasn't really working
with the--what I had on my arm,
which was getting caught
to the chiffon.
And then my lip gloss was stuck,
you know, and I swallowed
a piece of snow and...
- There's a lot of excuses.
You know, this is a competition.
At the end of the day,
nobody gives a crap.
You just have to bring it.
- Next up, Manila Luzon.
- Being from New York,
you reminded me of a Rockette.
And the second thing was
Marie Osmond, for some reason.
It's very Marie Osmond,
isn't it?
- She has really big hair
these days.
- But very well put together.
- Thank you.
- You are a magical,
fantastical confection.
- Well, this is the second dress
that I've ever sewn in my life.
- Wow. It's great.
It looks like Louis Vuitton.
- Oh!
- I thought more La Toya
Vuitton.
[laughter]
Shangela Laquifa Wadley.
Where'd you get the idea to use
a big prop like that?
- Oh, you talking about
Frostula?
Frostula the Snow Ho.
And if she came to life,
it would be Shangela.
- You kind of have a mild
concept going,
but it's still very kind
of remedial.
The execution is poor.
The back, it's kind
of falling apart.
There just could have been
more attention to detail.
- Now, I did learn to sew.
However, it was a little
difficult in working
with a paper material.
That was new for me.
- Here's the thing--you bring
out a big giant snowman.
The snowman was bigger
than the payoff.
And the thing about props--
you never wanna be upstaged
by a papier-mache snowman,
you know what I'm saying?
You don't!
- Well, I tell you,
on that note,
let's take a look
at your photograph
and see how well you did.
- I see a lot of armpit.
That's the first thing I went
to,
it was like--
armpit, you know.
- But it's fresh.
[laughter]
- All right, Shangela,
thank you very much.
Next up, Venus D-Lite.
How'd it feel for you up
on the runway?
- I was just having a ball.
- Can you turn around
and show me your ponytail?
That is really, I think,
the best part of your outfit.
I think the rest of the outfit
is overdone.
What did Coco Chanel say?
"Before you leave the house,
take one thing off"?
You've got the snowflake
and the beaded shoes
and then the beaded lapel.
I mean, it's a lot goin' on.
- Of the fabrications you
selected,
the whole mix isn't really
working for me.
You look like
a sad Christmas elf.
- The choices that I had
to make an outfit--
it was very limited.
And I'm saving the best
for later.
- Well, Venus, as you know,
in this competition,
with $75,000 at stake,
everything you do counts.
So that's not really an excuse.
Next, Mimi Imfurst.
You've got such a big heart.
- Thank you!
[laughter]
I've got a big everything, girl.
I actually only weigh 98 pounds.
The rest of this is liver.
- Ah!
[laughter]
- It's really a twist on
something that
is very religious,
and you are making it delightful
and campy
and really putting a spin on it.
- You have a great concept.
There's a amateurish quality
about it, but I love it.
I think it all works.
- Santa Claus,
meet the Virgin Mary.
- I think you're show business.
You're what it's about.
And you had a concept,
and you had an execution,
and you've been carrying
that baby longer
than Rose Kennedy
carried 12 children.
[laughter]
- I'm kind of surprised,
in some ways,
that you have
said such kind words.
You guys have sort
of renewed my faith today
in doing what you trust
in your heart.
- Thank you, Mimi.
Raja, you won
the photo challenge.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Flawless.
- It's obvious to me
you have incredible style.
You work this runway
like a supermodel.
- And you're not taking yourself
too seriously,
which kind of embodies, like,
the whole well-rounded,
like, drag superstar kind
of thing that we're going for.
- For me, it's what, like,
drag artistry is all about.
It's just doing something
unexpected
and creating it out of nothing.
- This is what I do, you know?
I'm a runway girl, I'm a model.
I'm Supermodel of the World,
the sequel,
I'd like to say.
[laughter]
- The only thing that I might
suggest is
that you project a little more
in your voice.
- I mean, I can certainly
speak louder,
but she's making me nervous,
so...
[giggles]
- Thank you, ladies.
Thank you, Bruce.
While you enjoy an Absolut
cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges
and I will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
Just between us "goils,"
what do you think?
Let's start with Carmen.
- Carmen brought bo-dy.
I'm still mesmerized
how she tucked all that stuff--
I don't know
where the heck it went,
but it was an amazing tuck.
The one thing I thought might
have lacked was her personality.
- Although, I'm sort of a sucker
for that "Joisey,"
you know, thing like dat,
you know.
- I wanted more Jersey.
I have no idea who Carmen is,
at this point, but a body.
- What about Manila Luzon?
- I think she is gorgeous.
She really embodied the spirit
of a winter wonderland.
- The only thing I might say is
she's funny and engaging
for a cocktail party
but not really
in an entertainment,
kind of showbiz-y kinda way.
- Right.
- Shangela Laquifa Wadley.
- I did think that her outfit
looked a little unfinished.
She could have done better.
- She kind of flubbed it.
- I don't know if Shangela
has the consistency
to make it further
in this competition.
- The personality supersedes
her tailoring skills.
I really wanna see some other
side of Shangela,
and it would be unfortunate
to send her home now.
- Venus D-Lite.
- She was a sad extra in some
kind of, you know, bad--
- It's a Horrible Life.
[laughter]
Her face is beautiful, but you
can't come out on the challenge
and the ponytail be the
highlight of your ensemble.
- That's true.
- Even though the outfit and
everything was very amateurish,
I was hoping she'd redeem
herself with her personality.
But she was inarticulate
and just wasn't engaging.
- Mimi Imfurst!
Her outfit was a little sloppy,
but it was effective.
- I thought it was hilarious
that she used something that's
so iconic and turned it into
something that was flirty
and funny.
- You know I live for camp drag,
but I'm really concerned that
that's her shtick
and that's what she falls on.
I wanna see if she can do
something else.
- Raja.
How 'bout that?
- She brings couture
and a sense of ownership
as soon as she stepped out
on the runway.
- Yes.
- And then the delight was
watching her drop to the ground
and being fun.
And that was
a great combination.
- I did wish she would project
her voice a little more
and kind of be a little more
in your face.
- Right, you not just look like
a supermodel...
- Act like one.
- Silence!
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Let's get down to it.
Mimi Imfurst.
You showed us
that big girls do cry.
Now I'm really gonna give you
something to cry about.
Condragulatons.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I just couldn't believe it.
I was for sure I was
in the bottom two.
I was for sure.
- Manila Luzon.
You have a muff to die for.
You're safe.
Condragulations.
Venus...
you were outshined
on the runway.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- When Ru said I was
in the bottom two, I was...
I was devastated.
- Raja.
With your photo, fashion,
and frolic in the snow...
you are the queen
who stole Christmas.
Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
And Raja, you receive immunity
from elimination next week.
Plus, you'll receive a $2,000
gift certificate from
SequinQueen.com.
That's SequinQueen.com.
- I'm so proud of myself.
I worked really hard, and
I was really focused about this.
And it feels really great.
- Carmen Carrera, you have
the body of death...
but do you have the killer
instinct it takes to win?
Shangela, I've given you
a second chance,
but your holiday presentation
left us a little frosty.
Carmen, you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Shangela, my dear,
you are up for elimination.
- I'm in disbelief.
A year later,
and here I am again,
in the bottom two.
- Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked
to prepare a lip-sync
performance
of Vanessa Williams'
The Right Stuff.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
to save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-synch...
for your life!
Good luck, and don't...
fuck it up.
[telephone rings]
- ♪ I was standin' at 7:15 ♪
♪ Waitin' for my baby's car ♪
♪ Just then out stepped ♪
♪ The driver of the limousine ♪
♪ And asked if I was going far ♪
♪ I said ♪
♪ I've got my mind made up ♪
♪ I don't wanna leave him ♪
♪ Baby, 'cause it's clear ♪
♪ To me ♪
- I really wanna be here.
I'm determined to fight
to be here.
- ♪ With the right stuff ♪
♪ The right stuff, baby ♪
♪ I don't wanna miss out ♪
♪ On the right stuff ♪
♪ You know with Mr. Right ♪
♪ Sing ♪
- Venus gets physical.
But you know what?
Even when pushed,
you can't stop me.
- ♪ The right stuff, baby ♪
♪ I don't wanna miss out ♪
♪ On the right stuff ♪
- Miss Venus throws her ponytail
to the back of the stage.
If she would have hit me
with that hair,
I probably would have
had to sock her.
- ♪ The right stuff ♪
- The lip-synching is starting
to get a little violent.
- ♪ I don't wanna miss out ♪
♪ On the right stuff ♪
- Shangela's lamp shade
has become a weapon.
♪ Na na na na na na oh ♪
♪ Wait a minute, wa-wa-wait ♪
♪ Wait a minute ♪
- Shangela's doing what
she's supposed to be doing.
She's supposed to be
lip-synching and performing,
and Venus is just really
pouncing on her.
- ♪ I don't wanna miss out ♪
♪ On the right stuff ♪
♪ Have you got the stuff ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Hey hey hey ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Wow.
- Ladies...
I must admit, that
made me feel uncomfortable.
I expect my queens to...
outshine each other,
not outgun each other.
But I have made my decision.
Shangela...
Shantay. You stay.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[sniffling]
[crying]
- Venus D-Lite...
tonight you may be leaving
RuPaul's Drag Race ...
but you're returning
to the constellation
of great drag stars.
Shine on, Venus, shine on.
Now, sashay away.
- Thank you for this wonderful
experience
from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you.
I'm happy, I'm sad,
I'm pissed off.
I think I should still be here.
I think I had a lot more
to bring to the table.
And I don't think I was given
that opportunity.
- Ladies,
now, this competition has raised
the bar on drag worldwide.
There's only one way to go,
and that's up.
So take me higher.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen.
- Let the music play.
Grand prize contributed
in part by ALandCHUCK.travel.