- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
Condragulations, ladies.
You are the top three.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Alexis Mateo.
- Stretch and lift.
Are you guys at home getting it?
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
Sickening, no?
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
- Cha-cha-cha!
- Cha-cha!
- Yes. Big ol' titties
and lots of ass.
- Look at those hips.
- The drama.
- Papi, I want you to come
back home, baby.
Bam!
- Hello!
- Manila Luzon.
That ensemb-la from the house of
of Imelda.
- Mabuhay, mabuhay.
What's next?
- Oh!
- Is that a bomb?
For the love of money!
- What you buzzin' about?
- Oh, yes! Okay!
- [chattering]
- That is what a lip sync for
your life is all about.
- Yes! Work!
- Raja.
No stranger to the runway.
- No one can hear you
lip-synching in space.
Prepare to die!
♪ Gonna love you
as you are ♪
♪ Gonna love you ♪
♪ You're a super ♪
- Navajo.
- ♪ A superstar ♪
- And tonight...
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race...
The final countdown...
America's next drag superstar
In this season's stunning
conclusion.
Is...
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup;
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails
perfected by Absolut;
and a cash prize of $75,000.
May the best woman win.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen,
start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ R-R-RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen,
start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman,
best woman win ♪
[tires screech]
- Nice.
- What! Top three, byotches!
- Oh, yeah, that's what
I'm talkin' 'bout.
- We're back into the workroom
today, and Yara Sofia is gone.
- Oh, my god, it's like
a paragraph.
[Manila laughs]
Oh, and there's a flag!
- Yara is my sister, and it's
kind of sad to see her leave.
But it just gonna make me work
harder to reach my goal.
I came here to be America's next
drag superstar.
The top three.
Did you all imagine
that I was gonna be here?
I didn't know
I was ready to be here.
I mean, I always wanted to.
- Yeah.
- But, oh, my gosh, it got
so difficult.
- It got so difficult!
This is so much more difficult
than I ever imagined.
- This has given me
a completely newfound respect
for Alexis.
I've teased about her and called
her a booger, but she's here.
She's part of the top three.
She's worked
just as hard as I have.
I love looking at all these
empty spaces in the room.
Like, I just remember
all the voices and personalities
that were here with us.
- When I first saw Raja, I was
like, "What the fuck?"
Remember you walked in
with that one eye?
[laughter]
I said, "What is this?
The Muppet Show?"
And then Manila was
the other one.
Oh, my gosh, Manila, in the
beginning, you were so annoying.
- I didn't realize how annoying
you were until midway,
and I was like...
[laughter]
- Okay, y'all think
I'm annoying.
Now, imagine what it's like
for me to live my life.
Trust me; I know I'm annoying.
Actually, Raja, I'm really happy
that I got to meet you,
because you've been doing it
for so long,
and it's nice to know that,
like, you can still do it
when you're in your late 40s.
- The library is closed!
[siren]
- Ooh, girl!
You've got shemail.
Mirror, mirror on the wall.
Who's the queeniest of them all?
Who's got the style?
Who's got the grace?
Who's got the balls
to take my place?
Now, if more is more,
then bigger is badder.
And when it comes to your
dreams,
size really do matter.
Mm-hmm.
- What does that mean?
- I think whoever has the
biggest dick, honey.
- I won!
- Yay!
- [laughs]
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Oh!
all: Oh!
- It's me, your favorite judge!
I'm here to deliver
your final challenge.
Ru's often said
that this competition is like
the Olympics of drag.
And now this is your chance to
go for the gold.
This week, you become
Greek goddesses.
all: Oh!
- Living statuary.
- Oh, beautiful.
- Prepare for the clash
of the Xanadu Titans
as you costar in the music video
for RuPaul's single Champion.
[whooping, laughing]
- That's awesome!
- Yeah!
- The brilliant Mathu Andersen
will be your director,
and the super-talented
Ryan Heffington
will teach you
to dance like goddesses.
- Yay!
- And...
to keep up your strength,
you'll each have
a one-on-one luncheon
with Miss RuPaul herself.
- [whooping]
- Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[all cheer]
- Hi.
- Hi, ladies.
- Hi!
- When I first saw Ryan,
I said...
- Today we're gonna work on some
choreography
for RuPaul's new song, Champion.
So let's really try to take it
out on this contemporary mode.
It's about being
a statuesque goddess.
Raja, can I have you take
this box here?
- I'm a little nervous,
because I am a runway girl,
and I don't know about dancing.
That's not my thing.
- You are statues,
but you are gonna morph
into different positions, okay?
So I want to see you guys
hit poses
every four counts.
One, two, three, four,
and then morph.
One, two, three, four.
Hold one, two, three, four.
Pose, one, two, three, four.
Okay?
Here we go.
Five, six, seven, eight.
And hah, two, three, four.
And switch, six, seven, eight.
Hold one, two, three, four.
- Whoo!
I'm gonna fall off the box.
- Raja, let's try to be more...
hieroglyphic,
beautiful statues, yes?
Again, five, six, seven, eight.
And switch.
- Oh.
- Manila, make it a little bit
more grand.
You are a statue.
They've carved you out of stone.
This is not gonna get it.
Now cross over.
Go!
Bah bah bah bah bah.
Bah bah ah-bah bah bah.
And through.
And off camera, yes.
- Oh, I see.
- Yes, yes, yes.
Alexis, her poses are amazing.
She knows how to portray
the character I'm asking for,
and it's instant with her.
The other two girls are really
gonna have to pull up
to match her.
- Hi, Ru.
- Darling!
Have a seat.
- Walking towards Ru
to have my lunch with him
is nerve-wracking.
It's a moment that could define
the whole competition.
- I've taken the liberty
to fix you a plate.
- I'm on a diet.
- Just have half of one.
- [laughing]
- Who is rooting for you
back home?
- Well, my family's rooting
for me.
[tearfully] I am so blessed.
When I walk in my house,
I can be myself with my mom,
with my sister...
with my friends.
And it's completely strange
that people
that I met in United States
that, like,
they always keep me going.
- So they're an extended family
that you've created in America.
I'm sure that they're very proud
of you.
Now that there are three,
what is your strategy?
- Well, I just gonna be myself.
And I am very sure
that I am perfect,
so it doesn't matter
what happens in the competition.
I know I'm a star.
- You already are a star.
Well, we had lunch,
and you didn't touch a thing.
- [laughs]
I told you I was in a diet.
I want to work on my body
so Michelle likes it.
- [laughs]
All right, darling.
You just keep on flying.
- Thank you for lunch.
The bill's on you.
- [laughs]
- Bye, Ru.
- Hi.
- Now it's time for us to
rehearse the part of the routine
where we get to use a pit crew
member as a prop.
- It should look like you've
known each other forever.
Actually, no.
You've known each other
for two nights.
It's always a little bit more
heated after...that point.
Yes. Mm.
Now peeking over
the shoulder.
And in that moment...
ah, we missed that moment.
Come back.
Yes, now get intimate and
closer.
Ah, and down, down, down, down,
down, down, up.
- Ta-da! No?
- Do you have a fear of
intimacy?
- Little bit.
I'm having the hardest time
focusing.
And I understand
where it's coming from.
He is probably seeing me
holding back,
because I fucked up a lot
in my life.
I want to win this contest.
And I really do not want
to fuck this up.
- It's about the intimacy
between you two,
and I think if
it's a little bit more true,
it'll read true on camera.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Raja really needs to let
her guard down.
I think that's what she's gonna
have to break through
in order to make this part
of the video work.
- Well, hello there!
Have a seat.
- Oh, thank you.
- What's been the hardest part
for you?
- Being away from my family,
not being able to call.
Hopefully,
they'll be proud of me,
because this is my medium.
- You're saying hopefully
they'll be proud of you.
Is there a chance that they
won't be proud of you?
- You know, it's a part of me
that my father really doesn't
like to be a part of.
Ever since I was a little boy,
he tried playing catch with me,
and he said, "Oh, well, this is
not gonna work."
- [laughs]
What do you think it would take
for your father to come around?
- Part of it is me.
I feel like my dad's probably
willing to learn
and be part of my lifestyle
as a drag queen.
I came here hoping that I would
be successful at it,
and then I could come back
and be like,
"Dad, Dad, look what I did."
He'd be so proud of me, even if
it's not, like, the ideal thing
that he would want me to do.
- I want you to say to him
what you're feeling,
what you would want him to take
from your being on this show.
- Daddy...
um, I couldn't have been here
without you and Mom.
It feels nice to be blessed,
to have, um...
like, a supportive family,
'cause I know lots of people
don't.
- And you're one of
the lucky ones.
It would be great for your
father to be proud of you,
but the truth is, it's about you
being proud of yourself.
- Well, hello.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Welcome.
- Now it's time to rehearse
the part of the video
when I gonna be joined
by the pit crew guy.
- So we are now gonna work
on the more intimate side
of the video.
- Can we take the clothes off?
- Whatever helps.
- Let's go.
- And rotating in...and...
Beautiful, yes, yes, yes.
Gorgeous. So from here...
I want you guys to improv.
- Oh, Jesus.
- But I don't want you to
separate.
A little closer.
Don't lean away.
Get into it.
Uh-huh. And...
[Alexis giggling]
No laughing.
Stay connected...
and work there for a moment,
improv.
[both laughing]
No laughing!
- It was very nerve-wracking
to have somebody
that you don't know
work with you as so close,
because it's a very intimate
moment.
- It's a simple...
- Touchy-touchy.
- Touchy.
You know, maybe it's here.
Click.
Shabam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
Alexis has dance background.
However, when it comes
to turning off
that stage persona,
I think it's really hard
for Alexis to do that.
Hopefully, she can just be
a little bit more in the moment.
Even though I'm giving you
choreography,
it should not look like
choreography.
It should look like you guys
are in your bedroom,
on your satin sheets,
working it out.
- Hi, Ru.
- Well, hello, Raja.
- What is this, Thanksgiving?
- [laughs]
- I couldn't possibly.
- You're a bit of an introvert.
- Sometimes, yeah.
- When you're on the runway,
you own the room.
How does an introvert live
in the body of an extravert?
- [laughs]
- How does that work?
- Duality comes from me being
a Gemini, I think.
There's a whole other side of me
that's a complete ham and
exhibitionist,
and I really love
being in front of people.
- Who's rooting for you
at home?
- I'm really hoping
that my parents
are going to pay attention
and really see what I do,
maybe for the first time
in their lives.
- Wow.
- You know, they've been
in some of the great moments
in my life,
but never have they seen
how proud I am to do what I do.
This will be a really great way
for them to see how much life
it brings to me.
- Is there anything you want
to tell them?
- Hi, Mom.
Hi, Dad.
Look at me;
I'm sitting with RuPaul!
[laughing]
That's a drag queen,
and so am I.
[both laughing]
- Look, darling,
lunch was fabulous.
Break a leg out there.
- I will.
- All right.
- All right, see you later.
- Thanks, doll.
- Bye, Ru.
- And arms come in
around to his chest.
Yeah. Beautiful.
And...uh, okay, cool.
- Oh, oh, oh, watch yourself.
Watch yourself.
I'm a married woman.
It's kind of awkward.
I have to get all, like, nasty
and grind up on some, like, sexy
greased-up man.
- Look at each other.
- You're so greasy!
What's my boyfriend gonna think?
Sorry, baby.
- Oh, my god,
it's a music video.
I never imagine myself
in one of RuPaul's video.
- I've imagined it before.
I just didn't think
it would actually happen.
We're about to shoot
Ru's video,
and I'm a little scared.
I have put in a lot of blood,
sweat, and tears
into this competition.
Now's the time to put on
the real show.
- Oh! Blond Asian, y'all!
Get used to it.
- It's the final challenge,
and it is bigger than ever,
because this is
some serious shit.
This is the real deal.
The jig is up.
- Wow!
Here comes the bride.
We walk onto set, and there's
Ru, a vision in white.
- ♪ My girls ♪
- She looks like a goddess.
It almost looks like a dream.
- Okay, smoke up!
Action!
- ♪ They try
to keep you down ♪
♪ But there's no denying ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Greatest of them all ♪
- Faces!
- ♪ You're a champion ♪
- Extend those lines!
Go!
- ♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ You're standing tall ♪
- And go!
Go, Alexis, go!
Go!
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- Cut!
Yeah, uh, so try not to leave
too early.
Let the girls pass the end.
You'll be the last one to leave.
So just work the center there.
Don't leave too early.
- Oh, bitch,
I was just called out.
RuPaul's standing right there,
and I'm screwing it all up.
- You'll be the last one,
so just turn, keep posing.
They cross. They cross.
You cross.
- Okay, they cross.
They cross. You cross.
- Yes.
- The first take was a mess.
We don't want Ru thinking, like,
"Oh, these three queens
are gonna fuck
my whole music video up."
We don't want that.
- Long neck, Alexis.
Give face, give bone.
- And...
- ♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ And you'll always be a hero ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- More robust!
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- Quickly, here we go!
- Oh!
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
- Cut!
Thank you.
- I almost fell.
- We are not hitting
what we need to hit.
It has become a circus.
- This is our last thing
with Ru, understand?
So get it right.
- Nip slip, aisle four.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Keep that energy up, ladies.
Here we go.
- Action.
- ♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ You're standing tall ♪
- Go!
- ♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ And you'll always... ♪
- And arms, arms, arms!
Hold!
And exit.
Nice.
Much better!
- ♪ Hey ♪
- Much better, ladies.
- Thank you.
- Moving on?
- Yes, moving on.
- I love how I'm wearing, like,
a bikini
on top of, like, a onesie.
- Fierce.
- The Greek goddesses part of
the video is over,
so now we're gonna be athletes
since we have new, black, sexy,
skimpy-ass costumes.
- ♪ Gorgeous ♪
- Raja, let me use your glue
for a second.
- Alexis is wearing huge hair.
Probably not the smartest thing
to do.
I mean, you're trying to be
fierce athletes.
- Whoo!
Olympi-who?
Yes, mama.
Let's do this.
And action.
- A-one, two, three, four.
A-five, six, seven, eight.
And one, two, three, four.
We have to hit our marks,
ladies.
- Manila, you were off.
- I'm sorry.
- If you're off,
you're just gonna get hidden
behind Alexis's hair.
- It's really hard
to see your mark
that's, like, a little tiny dot
on this big, white stage.
And Alexis's hair is, like,
totally, like, in my way.
- Action!
- A-five, six, seven, eight.
And one!
- Oh, sorry.
- Cut. Try it again.
- Manila fucked it up.
- Sorry, guys. I'm sorry.
- When you hit it, you can do
that, but don't...
because someone's hair is
very large,
and it blocks other people.
But I'm not saying who.
- They trying to blame my hair
because of Manila's mistakes.
Bitch, don't hide behind me.
You got your mark.
The bigger the hair,
the closer to God.
- And one, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
And up and up
and up!
That was the best shot, yes.
- Now we're going to introduce
boys to the mix.
- Manila, let's hit it.
Five, six, take your time.
Seven, eight.
Moving through it.
And ah.
Let this be a moment here.
Ah.
Lift that leg.
[Latin guitar music]
- I'm a ballerina.
I am 93 pounds.
- Take it slow.
Ecstasy.
Come up slowly...
and improv here for a second.
- Oh!
- Oh.
[both laugh]
- Okay, that was beautiful.
- Awesome.
- Let's move along
to our next victim.
- Raja, you're up.
- Yay! I get to touch
naked man body.
- Here we go. Ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- And...
- Yes, mama.
- Beautiful.
- I feel, um, unfaithful.
[giggles]
- And...it kind of looked like
a head job.
- Before you start going down
his body at the end,
hold it for a second.
- Okay.
[laughs]
Sorry about it. Okay.
[sensual music]
♪ ♪
- Yes!
- Now, this is the moment
right here.
We want to see it.
- Beautiful, you guys.
Keep moving.
[both gag]
- She's done that before.
- And...
- Bam.
- Yes, take me!
- All right, high kick.
- I'm tingling!
- Nice!
- I had to just really let go
and realize that you know what?
Raja, you are known for being
a sensual performer.
It was all about me doing
what I do
and doing it well.
- Hello, Alexis Mateo.
- Let's hit it, from the top.
- And...action.
[light rhythm]
♪ ♪
Sensuous.
Beautiful.
- Okay. You flip me?
- Alexis, you're going to have
to focus on your profile,
because when you turn front,
you have no--you're just...
both: Hair.
- [whispers] Such big hair.
- All right.
- And...action.
- And go, Jason.
[light rhythm]
♪ ♪
Profile.
- Beautiful.
That's beautiful.
Gorgeous, Alexis.
- Maybe some more arms.
- I like it.
It's like a live sex show.
- And...
yes, cha-cha around each other.
And go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
- Bam, baby!
- [laughing]
Bam!
- Okay, ladies, 25 minutes to
shoot the whole video.
- Grab your prop.
So, Miss Javelin,
you'll go first.
- Sure.
- Do it hard and fast.
- Keep the tip up.
Go.
- Beautiful. Great.
That looked good.
Bow and arrow, Alexis.
Make me believe that you're
a huntress.
And go!
Okay.
- Manila, you're up.
- Ooh!
[laughs]
- Action.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
That was nice.
Okay, and serving...discus.
Action on spinning
and...play back.
- ♪ They try
to keep you down ♪
♪ But there's no denying ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Greatest of them all ♪
♪ Never gonna fall ♪
- I think my earliest drag live
growing up
was being in talent show,
the little boy pageants.
Now I am in RuPaul's video
Champion.
I'm a champion.
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- Coming to this competition,
I knew that I was going to be
put through the wringers.
It's exhausting.
But the highs and lows, like,
all just kind of blended
into one fun ride,
and it's great.
I feel alive.
- ♪ You're a champion ♪
- I have told myself in the past
that I couldn't do anything
right
or I wasn't good enough.
Right now, it's just about me
showing off.
I am fearless, and I am beyond
proud of myself.
- ♪ You'll always be a hero ♪
[song ends]
- [gasps]
The last day ever!
- The last day!
- Oh, my god.
- We're back in the workroom,
and it's the very, very last
day,
and someone is gonna get a crown
tonight.
I'm so excited.
- I don't mean to be corny, but
let's just do a quick group hug.
Can we?
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, I love you guys!
- All drama aside,
it's just the three of us,
and went through
this whole thing together.
And it's very comforting to know
that two other people know this
experience as well as I do.
- Sisters forever.
- Okay, stop humping!
Oh, god!
- Alexis, what is that?
- I don't even care how I did
or how it comes out.
I'm in RuPaul's video,
motherfucker.
- Hey!
- Lick it. Lick it.
- You better work it out, miss.
- [laughs]
- Do you guys think
that you've changed,
like, being in this
competition?
- I think my performance style
definitely changed.
I feel like I've gone
to college, you know,
and I'm graduating or something.
- You know, honestly, like,
I feel like I've changed a lot,
because I never did drag
as, like--
you know, full-time, really.
So it's really cool
to actually experience
doing it, like, hard-core.
- I haven't changed.
I still the same, bitch.
My drag haven't changed at all,
'cause where I come from,
it just one way to the drag,
and that's read it in a book.
- Raja.
- What?
- Why do you think you should
win this competition?
- Because I'm fiercer
than you guys.
- [scoffs]
- Well, you got us there.
- [laughs]
- If I don't win,
I would love to see you
get crowned, Manila.
- Oh!
- Really soon, America will know
who will be
America's next drag superstar.
- [laughing]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl]
♪ ♪
[applause]
Well, hello, there.
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Tonight it's just family,
so let's get nuclear.
Michelle Visage!
- RuPaul!
- [laughing]
My muse.
Can you believe
it's almost over?
- I cannot.
Very sad but very happy night.
- Yes, bittersweet.
- Indeed.
- Santino Rice.
- Ru!
- Are you ready to crown
a winner?
- I'm ready.
We've got three amazing queens.
And I can't wait to see what
they bring to the stage tonight.
- Yes.
For the grand finale,
we challenged our girls
to become Greek goddesses for
my newest video, Champion.
Tonight they've put together
outfits
that will take your breath away.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
For the grand finale,
welcome Raja.
- All that jazz
and then some.
- Oh, Cabaret.
- Willkommen, bienvenue.
- I'm walking down the runway
for the last time,
and I'm just
in this moment right now.
I'm not really thinking
of the competition.
I'm just gonna rock it.
- Nothing beats a great pair
of legs.
- Bob Fosse.
- Yeah.
- Life is a cabaret!
Up next, Manila.
She done brought her own crown.
- [laughing]
- I'm walking down the runway,
and I'm just in my gown.
I've got sparkly jewelry
all over the place,
and I feel like a winner.
- Look at that train.
Work all of that train, mama.
- Chartreuse charmeuse.
- Mm, gentlemen prefer Manila.
Alexis Mateo.
Sunday in the park with Alexis.
- Yes, she can-can.
- I pick my showgirl costume,
because it's the last time
that the judges is gonna see me,
and I wanted to remind them
that this is who I am.
Alexis Mateo
is all about the show,
is all about the glamour,
and the stage is mine.
- And she vajazzled her head.
- She brings her own shade to
the runway.
- Yes, she does.
- Meet me in St. Louis.
Wow.
My top three girls.
Each of you won three
challenges,
which is pretty amazing.
Are you ready for the judges'
final critiques?
Let's go.
So, Raja, let's take a look
at highlights
from your performance
in the Champion video.
[RuPaul's Champion]
♪ ♪
[applause]
- I love your take on drag.
I love your Victor/Victoria
look.
You are a star.
But I would say I'm not
feeling you as a blond.
But it did look Grecian.
- Love this look on you
tonight.
And I love androgyny, especially
when it comes to beauty.
You really know how to work
a camera for a beauty shot.
But you would have been stronger
if you had more makeup.
- Manila Luzon.
Let's take a look at highlights
of your performance
in the Champion video.
♪ ♪
[applause]
- You got to do your scene
with Jason.
I could smell the chemistry.
- It was hard,
because I'm thinking, like,
"My boyfriend's
gonna kill me.
My boyfriend's gonna kill me."
- Well,
as an international star,
Sahara will just have to
learn to accept that.
- You've saved this,
and you just brought it
to us tonight in a big way.
I think it would look better
with smaller earrings.
But it's a lot of fun to see you
come out here.
And I love, you know, when
you're just, like, giving it.
If you could bottle that
for a beauty queen,
you would be a billionaire.
I think you looked stunning
in the video.
Some of the choreography was
a little bit awkward.
- Manila Luzon, from week one to
the top three,
you've been consistent,
never too old to be a princess.
And you are such a pretty,
pretty princess tonight.
The video,
I loved that little lift.
I've told you before I'm not
a fan of you as a blonde.
Your face was still gorgeous,
but you kind of lose you
when you do the blonde.
I love the streak.
That's about as blonde
as you should ever go.
- Alexis Mateo.
- Hola.
- Top three.
- Bitches, we did it!
[laughter]
- Tell me about your outfit.
- Today I wanted to show
who I am for real,
and, like, I'm a showgirl.
- I want to take a look at the
highlights from your performance
in the Champion video.
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ ♪
[laughter, applause]
- Yes!
- So how do you feel?
- I feel like when you want to
roll your "r" so bad, like...
rrrrr!
[laughter]
- I really thought you brought
the overall kind of athleticism
and almost Olympic quality to
this piece.
- I'm gonna be completely
honest with you.
You were one I did not expect to
see in the final three.
Every time I counted you out,
you brought it and shut me up.
All I can say
about the video is,
you stayed true to who you are.
Even in the Grecian times,
you were doing some cha-cha.
There was not a minute
in this whole competition
that you ever let down
your sweetness
and your vulnerability
and your honesty.
You're just adorable.
- Oh, Michelle said something
good about me, bitches.
[laughter]
I have to cha-cha for that,
'cause I'm so happy.
- Tonight before the judges and
I deliberate for the final time,
we'd like to hear
from each of you alone.
Alexis, you're first.
I want you to give me
a pro and a con
for each of your competitors.
- Raja's pro is the runway walk,
like nobody else
in this competition.
Something that I don't like
about Raja:
he's so hard to read.
Manila was the only girl
in the competition
who I really want to punch
in the face.
I was like, "Manila, I think
you're annoying," and she said,
"You know what?
I think so too."
And we actually got one thing
in common!
[laughter]
- I want your pros and cons.
- Every time I make a decision
to move forward in life,
I am my own enemy.
If I wish I could have changed
something about my life,
it would be how hard I am
when I judge myself.
But I am a fighter.
And I don't regret anything,
because it have make me
so strong
that I actually can say
I am my biggest hero.
- Alexis Mateo was one of
the first queens
that, like, really
stuck out in my mind.
I think she's an amazing
performer.
As for cons,
the drag that she does,
I've seen it before,
and it doesn't excite me.
I love Raja.
She's very fashion,
but sometimes
it's, like, a little bit
too, like, editorial.
Those are my cons first.
Get those out of the way
so I can end on a high note.
I'm kind of crazy
and a little unpredictable,
and I'm kind of stubborn
at times.
But I feel like I've proven
I can do almost anything.
So...I can be me for myself and
please other people.
- Alexis is a very, very
talented performer.
Cons: I don't really think
she thinks outside of the box.
Her marabou and her rhinestones
feels a little bit stagnant
to me.
It's always an entertaining
moment with Manila,
and I think that's awesome.
But Manila has a lot of growth
to do.
There's still a bit of
a template that she fits into.
I'm not really into templates.
- I want to ask you
about your pros and cons.
- For the first time in my life,
I can say
that I'm a beautiful person.
[tearfully]
It's taken a long time,
and it's been
a treacherous journey,
but I'm in this moment
right now,
and it feels so fucking great,
and I'm proud of it.
I'm very proud.
- Thank you, Raja.
While you and the other girls
enjoy an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
[engine starts]
Just between us girls, Manila.
She's amazing.
She can do everything.
- She is a knockout.
Her personality is fantastic.
If you're looking for somebody
to represent you
and RuPaul's Drag Race,
she's got
a wonderful stage presence
and can actually speak.
- I wanted to feel...
some sincerity.
She always stops herself
on an emotional level.
- I just happen to think
Manila is a superstar.
- And Manila has won
the last two challenges.
- She did.
- She's on a roll.
So let's move on to Alexis.
- You know how many times
I've counted her out?
- Tell me, how many times have
you counted her out?
- At least three or four times.
And then bam!
- Her Florida style of drag has
been considered, by many people,
to be too regional to be
America's next drag superstar.
- I never counted her out.
She is so authentic in what
she's bringing to the table
that I give her a free pass
on the over-the-top cha-cha.
- Her conviction is flawless.
Yeah, it's just flawless.
Let's move on to Raja.
- Sometimes I feel like she's
only worried
about the runway aspect
of the challenge.
- The bitch is bad.
- But does she do anything else
besides high fashion?
- Well, she won
three challenges.
- Yeah, she did.
- And she doesn't take herself
too seriously.
The bucket of blood,
remember that?
- Yeah, the Carrie thing?
- She takes genderfuck
and turns it into something
that's actually heightened and
intellectual and special.
- Her take on drag is very
different, very fresh and new.
- This is not going to be easy.
- All three of them are
superstars,
and they're all
equally as fierce.
- Silence!
This ain't over until they
lip-synch for their lives.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
It all comes down to this.
Based on your performance
in the Champion music video
and your heroic work
throughout this competition,
I've made some decisions.
- [exhales]
This is it.
- Alexis Mateo...
your smile and spirit
remind us all
of the joy that drag brings
to the world.
It breaks my heart
to say this...
but you are not America's next
drag superstar.
Thank you, Alexis.
- [whispers] Thank you.
- Now...sashay away.
- Thank you.
[applause]
It doesn't matter
if I didn't won.
Knowing the things
that I have done in my life
to get to this point,
it feels wonderful.
The sky is the limit for me,
and this is just the beginning
for something wonderful.
The jig is up, bitches.
- Two beautiful queens
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last
chance to impress me
and walk away with the title of
America's next drag superstar.
- My heart has never beat
faster in my life.
I felt like it was gonna jump
out of my chest.
- The time has come
for you to lip-synch...
for your life!
- I'm so excited.
It might be me that's the next
drag superstar.
So let's get this lip sync on.
- Good luck,
and for the last time,
don't fuck it up.
- ♪ They try
to keep you down ♪
♪ But there's no denying ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Greatest of 'em all ♪
♪ Never gonna fall ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Still standing tall ♪
♪ And you'll always be a hero ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- I'm lip-synching the song
the way that I lip sync.
I'm lip-synching this as Manila.
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ And when your story's told ♪
♪ And the truth unfolds ♪
- All eyes are on me,
and it's about me
really, really hitting it
and doing it Raja-style.
- ♪ With all the children
singing ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Greatest of 'em all ♪
♪ Never gonna fall ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Still standing tall ♪
♪ And you'll always be a hero ♪
[song ends]
[applause]
- Wowza.
- Ho ho!
- Oh, I love you.
- Oh, my god!
- Ladies...
I've made my decision.
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race...
America's next drag superstar,
is...
Raja.
[majestic music]
♪ ♪
- Congratulations.
You were so good.
- Manila, you are
an inspiration.
I want to thank you
from the bottom of my heart.
- Thank you.
- Now...sashay away.
- I can't even explain
being so close
and then just not being able
to get there.
I don't think I could have done
anything differently.
I wouldn't have changed
this experience for anything.
I wouldn't have traded it
for anything.
And I'm happy how far I made it.
I'm first runner-up,
so if Raja dies of old age,
then maybe I'll get the crown.
- Raja, my queen...
I bow to thee.
- [laughs]
Along with this title,
I can use it now
to talk to kids who have no clue
that you could be a star.
I just want to let them know
that it's all right to be
a social misfit.
It's okay to think outside of
the box
and think greater than
what you know.
- Now, prance, I say.
Prance, my queen.
- All hail the queen!
[RuPaul's Superstar]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Bravo!
- Work, mama.
- Work it, baby!
- Yes!
- Grand prize contributed
in part by ALandCHUCK.travel.
- The crown is mine,
the cash is mine,
and I am America's next
drag superstar.
♪ ♪
- And now the world premiere
of RuPaul's Champion.
- ♪ They try
to keep you down ♪
♪ But there's no denying ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Greatest of them all ♪
♪ Never gonna fall ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Still standing tall ♪
♪ And you'll always be a hero ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Hey ♪
- ♪ One dream ♪
♪ The will to fight ♪
♪ And all they can do is laugh ♪
♪ This time, you got it right ♪
♪ And no one can take it back ♪
♪ They try to keep you down ♪
♪ But there's no denying ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Greatest of them all ♪
♪ Never gonna fall ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Still standing tall ♪
♪ And you'll always be a hero ♪
♪ And when your story's told ♪
♪ And the truth unfolds ♪
♪ They will sing your praises
loud ♪
♪ 'Cause your story's gold ♪
♪ If the truth be told ♪
♪ With all the children
singing ♪
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- ♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Greatest of them all ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Never gonna fall ♪
♪ Still standing tall ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ And you'll always be a hero ♪