- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
- Her name is Mimi Imfurst,
but she's not first.
And I don't even think
she's second.
[exclamations]
- Alexis and I, as the twinbots,
we delivered.
both: Dragonauts away.
- All right, Miss Raja.
- India Ferrah.
Her clone does not sleep alone.
Mimi Imfurst.
- I think that I stand a good
chance of winning this one.
- Oh, damn the rules.
Let's call it a tie.
Shangela, Alexis,
you've won this challenge.
- Ooh!
- Delta Work, Shante, you stay.
Phoenix, sashay away.
And tonight...
It's time to get
totally leotarded.
[exclamations]
The dolls get physical.
- Feel it.
- [laughs]
And it ain't always pretty.
- Whoo-whoo-whoo.
- And extra-special
guest judges
fitness guru Susan Powter
and Latoya Jackson.
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Kryolan professional makeup,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails perfected
by Absolut,
and a cash prize of $75,000.
And may the best woman win.
- Eh.
- Poor Phoenix.
- Delta, you got rid of her.
- Oh, she said boots.
Phoenix is gone, and it's a new
day, it's a new challenge,
and I feel totally reenergized.
Raja, get ready to write
your name on here later.
[laughter]
- We won, girl.
- I'm a little surprised that
Shangela and Alexis won.
I think that I sort of went
a little outside the box
and was a little more sci-fi.
I felt like I got really close
to winning
the first challenge too.
- Mimi really does think
that Mimi's first.
- I mean, it's hard.
It's like, you know, you don't
want to be second best.
You want to be best.
- Really, I just didn't wanna
hear her talk.
[alarm blares]
- Ooh!
Girl, you've got she-mail.
Hello, drag stars.
all: Hi.
- If you wanna win this race,
you've gotta feel the burn.
So stretch, bend over,
and take it
like America's
next drag superstar.
Let me hear your body talk.
And remember...
- Ow!
- No pain, no gain.
[laughing]
- Oh, my god.
- Ooh, girl.
- Let me hear your body talk.
- Girl, you don't wanna hear
what this one has to say.
[laughter]
- Well, we just lost, girl.
I just lost.
- Hello, hello, hello!
all: Hey.
- Do you know what time it is?
It's time to get leotarded.
- Oh.
- In this bag is a drag queen's
best friend
and worst kept secret...
duct tape.
all: Oh.
- Now for today's
mini-challenge, you'll become
drag MacGyvers to customize
a sporty fashion leotard using
only these rolls of duct tape.
But first, you'll need
to split up into groups of two
and one group of three.
- Delta, Stacy.
- Immediately, Mimi decides it
needs to be
the three
plus-sized queens together.
- You three here? Okay.
- The last thing I wanna do is
be on a team with Mimi.
Like, that's the last thing that
I wanna do.
- Ready?
Steady...
Tape!
[shrieking]
- Whatever I 'm doing to you
in pink, you do to me in purple.
Carmen and I have a bunch
of neon colors.
And so our idea is to do, like,
a super '80s,
kinda '90s workout leotard.
Girl, my tuck.
- Whoo!
- Sorry, I didn't mean to touch
your dick.
- Don't worry.
- Alexis and I came up with the
concept of corsets, bustiers,
with a little bit of ruffle.
- Whoo, sister,
you got me together.
Hallelu.
Good thing I didn't need
those ribs.
Get up in there.
Ow, ow.
- This looks like a trash bag,
completely.
I mean, it really looks bad.
This is a disaster.
This looks horrible, and we're
completely mismanaging the time.
- Start over?
- Yeah.
- Get over here.
Come here, Stace.
- Sorry.
- We ought to tape these
into your ear.
- Your braid.
- Oh, my god!
I love it, I gotta wear it.
- One, two, three, go.
They're not gonna close.
The boots aren't gonna close.
- Oh, shit,
something just popped.
- Okay, ladies, time's up.
Wow.
Ooh-wee, y'all are leotarded.
Let's see how
my designing queens did.
Alexis and Mariah...
Category is duct tape.
- Alexis and I,
our outfits came out nice.
I feel good about what we did,
and I might even save it
for later.
- Let them have it.
Next up, Yara and Raja.
Letting them have it
in a Flashdance effect.
Carmen and Manila...
she's wearing
her duct tape iPod.
- We're giving fierce
jazzercise realness.
- Yes, ooh, la-la.
Shangela and India,
serving desert storm.
Yes, she's looking
for a few good men.
Last but not least,
Stacy, Delta, and Mimi...
The Supremes are back.
- There were parts
of the leotard
that didn't fit properly.
Everyone in the room
is looking at me,
and it's a really
uncomfortable feeling.
- Okay...
[laughing]
- That whole group
with Mimi, Delta, and Stacy
looked like two sisters
that had gotten pulled
into a girl group that they
didn't wanna be a part of.
- Okay, gym bunnies...
Now I've seen your leotarded
outfits, and...
The winning team is
Manila and Carmen.
- Ah! Wheeee!
- Condragulations, ladies.
Come on up.
Do you know what time it is now?
It's time
to get totally leotarded!
- Oh!
[applause]
- Now, a great drag queen knows
how important it is
to keep her charisma,
uniqueness, nerve,
and talent in tip-top shape.
So for this week's main
challenge, you are going to
produce your very own
inspirational workout videos.
[applause]
Yes.
Now, Manila and Carmen,
you are the captains
for this team challenge.
Manila, you won the toss.
Who do you pick first?
- Raja.
Thank god I won the coin toss.
Gag.
I want Raja because Raja is
the only person I've seen here
that's actually done a sit-up.
- All right, Carmen,
who do you choose?
- Hmm, I want a big girl.
I want Delta.
- All right.
- My first pick is Delta
because I wanted to form
the prettiest group,
you know what I mean, so I
picked the prettiest big girl.
- Shangela.
- Mariah.
- Mimi.
- Ah!
- So I choose Yara.
- Alexis.
- Yes.
- I love Stacy,
but I already got my big girl.
So I 'm gonna choose India.
- I get Stacy.
- Yay.
- No shade, girl, no shade.
I've come to realize that if
this was gonna be
a workout challenge,
they were gonna leave
the big bitch behind, honey.
- Captain Manila...
Captain Carmen...
you're in charge of assigning
each queen an exercise
and creating a sporty team look.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
All right.
- What's the--what's the name
of our video?
- It has to be hysterical.
- Transform yourself.
From flab to fierce.
- Mm.
- I have this idea.
What if I painted myself to look
like I was 85,000 years old,
and I was like, it's,
"Do you like my big ball?"
[giggles]
- What?
- Mimi gets that whole Miminess
of it all,
and it's driving me up the wall.
Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
- I'm gonna do the stepper.
- You said you wanted something
with your boobs?
- The boob shaker thingy.
- So she has the shake weight.
- Titty shaker girl.
- Is that funny?
- No, you should just call it
the shake n' bake weight,
and you just shake and bake,
do it from this side.
- That's right, that's right.
- You can do it from this side.
- There's times when I feel like
I'm not heard,
because a lot of people
in this competition
like to talk over you.
- I can do the jump rope; what
can you do with jump roping?
- Chuck-a-rope.
- [giggles]
- What about chuck-a-rope?
- Okay, yep.
- Our challenge today is to
create a workout video in teams.
- I want us to look like,
kinda like a rainbow.
Like Skittles.
You do blue, and you do green.
Do red. Do red.
I think I'm a good leader.
I think I'm a great leader.
I'm really good
at judging things.
- Something tastic,
since it's elastic.
- No.
- I listen to people.
- You can put one in here.
- No.
- Like, I could--I could this
one, like...
- No.
- Carmen is so bossy.
- Okay.
But what is that gonna be for?
I don't know if Delta's gonna be
able to do that.
- This is gonna be about
physical fitness,
and I'm completely terrified.
The fact is,
I sit before you 350 pounds.
And I would say not a week goes
by that I don't get a letter
from someone commenting on what
a pig I am, or how ugly I am.
Jesus Christ, I feel sick.
Thank you for picking me.
- Of course, you're my girl.
Delta really needs to work on
her self-confidence issues
because she's flawless.
I think she's sickening,
you know what I mean?
And...it's a shame.
- So we're doing busted, right?
- Don't look, like,
too crazy busted.
- And we're doing garage doors?
- Garage doors, girl.
One color on your eye.
- Where'd you hear garage doors?
- One of my friends from Texas
was, like,
making fun of some queens.
She was like, "that bitch came
out with blue garage doors
on her eyes."
- [chuckles]
I'm sitting here thinking
it's an industry term.
I was like, mm-hmm, yeah,
garage doors, girl.
- Hello, hello, hello!
all: Hi.
- How are my little endorphin
junkies doing?
Team Carmen, right?
all: Yes.
- Now I wanna hear all about
your workout video.
Now India, did you choose
your expertise?
- I was assigned.
I got the rubber tug.
- Oh, have you ever used one
before?
- No. I don't know nothing
about exercising.
I don't work out, I don't have a
gym membership.
And I 'm like, "oh, god,
this could be good or bad."
- What about you, Yara?
- It's called echar pa'lante.
- Oh, help me with that.
- It means move forward.
You wanna look like this, you
gotta work it out, darlin'.
So echar pa'lante.
- Work it out.
- [giggles]
All right, Delta?
- So I'm going
to shake and bake.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- Delta, can you come over and
show me what you've done there?
I'm already inspired.
- Well, we're gonna start with
the weight here.
- Yeah.
- So it's gonna go up and down.
- Ooh, ooh.
- And then you're gonna go...
- Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
- Do you feel it?
- Shake it, don't break it.
Oh, yeah.
I think I just lost five pounds!
- Feel it.
Ha, ha!
- Stacy, you better come up with
something quick.
- Okay, we need to come up with
something else
because I just heard "shake
and bake" over there.
- Well, we'll just change
the name of it.
- What are you thinking, Stacy?
- Spritz stick.
- What?
- A spritz stick.
- What the hell's
a spritz stick?
- I do think that Stacy's
a lovely person.
And you know, we'd probably have
a really fantastic time
listening to bullfrogs and
drinking sweet tea in the
backwoods that she lives in.
But I would lose my mind if we
had to be on the bottom
because of her.
- Well, hello, ladies.
all: Hello.
- Manila,
you're the team captain.
- Yes.
- What is your area of expertise
in this workout video?
- The step and strap.
Works your core muscles.
You bend down and strap your
heels together.
- Have you done it yourself?
Have you tried it yet?
- Girl, no.
- No.
Great, just let the camera roll,
and step and strap.
- Yeah.
- Manila was just clueless.
You have to be prepared
in front of Ru.
- Stacy, do you have
an area of expertise
that you're doing in the video?
- My name's actually
the sit and shake.
- The sit and shake?
- Lets you eat your chips.
And while you're doing that,
feeding your face,
you can just shake it off,
like, you know?
- I like it.
Yeah, but what if you don't have
one of these things here?
- A can of soup will be just
fine.
- Okay, I love it.
What about you, Mimi?
What are you doing?
- You gotta love me jump rope.
And it's when you got that man
that you don't wanna lose...
- Yes.
- You can jump rope, grab him,
tie him up, and don't ever
let him leave.
- Now just be careful jumping
rope with heels--safety first.
- Of course.
- Now...
Shangela, what
is your expertise?
- This is the hallelula hoop.
Kate Gosselin, she learned this,
and then she loaned me
this hair.
- Oh. Oh, okay.
- You get your hallelula hoop,
and then you say...
and that'll keep your hip.
And the hula hoop hits
the ground.
Ru is probably thinking,
"This ho don't even know
how to hula hoop."
Now listen...
- Okay.
- If it goes down--you see,
I'm single.
- [giggles]
- But if it goes down, you talk
dirty to it
and it'll rise back up.
- Oh, I see.
- Cardinal rule.
- Everybody is very funny on my
team.
I'm very concerned about that,
'cause I don't--
I actually don't
do comedy at all.
- All right, Alexis.
- I'm going to be working out
my upper body,
using the stretch
your upper body.
- Oh, I see.
- And I'm using, of course...
lip gloss.
The "lapilaviar" stretch.
- So it's like a cross-training
thing?
- Yes.
- Your lips don't lie.
- Okay.
All right, ladies, now remember,
your workout videos need to be
truly inspirational.
So I'm bringing in someone
to help you...
Stop the insanity!
Fitness guru and motivational
speaker Susan Powter
will be here.
- Whoo!
- To help you make this workout
video truly inspirational.
- Susan Powter?
I mean, she's legendary.
When I was growing up, I even
wanted to bleach my hair
as white as hers.
That was, like, my reference
when I went to the hair stylist.
- I've got a few words of
inspiration for you myself.
Don't fuck it up.
- [giggles]
- Bye.
all: Bye, Ru.
- Okay.
- Good job, team.
- Well, well, well!
Hello, team Manila.
Meet Susan Powter.
all: Hi, Susan.
- Welcome to the fitness world,
ladies.
- Our first exercise is called
the step...and strap.
- Give me more over-the-top
drag queen sexy.
- Step and strap!
- What's your name, honey?
- I am Manila Luzon, and you've
just worked out
to the step and strap.
- And that's a cut.
- Hi, everybody, my name is
Alexis Mateo.
And right now, we gonna--just
gonna work out all
our upper muscles.
- I think that was super cute.
I think you should go
over-the-top.
- Hi, my name is Alexis Mateo
Rodriguez Rivera Ocherat--
y todos los de mas.
- [laughing]
- Here we go.
The stretchy thingy-majingy.
Open the lip gloss, and we gonna
pull...your lips.
- Give me a little more
attitude.
- Stretch and lips,
stretch and lips.
Are you guys at home getting it?
You need to breathe.
[panting]
My titties were sweating.
Yes, you just gotta stretch
thingy-majingy lip gloss
with Alexis Mateo.
- Super cute.
Super cute.
- Tough act to follow.
- [deep voice] Well, hello,
ladies at home.
We're gonna increase some energy
and get rid of that unsightly
bulge in your pants, ladies.
Grab the ball and violently bang
your crotch for ten times.
Here we go!
all: Ah!
Two, three, four...
- Raja's character was just
totally crazy.
I just thought
it was really crude.
Not what you're gonna expect
from a drag queen to act like,
basically a dude.
- They call it, in the
infomercial industry,
that soft to camera moment.
- Mm.
- Where you do the "and you
can!"
And then you go,
"and you can also."
- Ah.
- It's that moment.
Give me a little swear
this is gonna work
for you moment, please.
- A lot of times, things don't
go the way that you plan them.
- Yes, yes.
- Okay, that happens for a lot
of us out there.
But let me tell you something.
You pick up the hallelula hoop,
and you put it back around
your waist.
And you work the hallelula hoop.
One, two, three, four,
I don't want that boy no more.
Five, six, seven, eight.
I am gonna find a date.
- From your hips to god's lips.
- Hallelu.
- Yes.
- Shangela was adorable.
Shangela is always adorable.
Like a little puppy or kitty
cat, they're always gonna be
cute, no matter...if they're
shitting on your carpet.
- Well, how you doin'?
My name is Stacy Layne Matthews.
Grab your plates, and we're
gonna take our sit and shake,
and we're gonna shake it.
Come on, girls.
- When you shake that, your
beautiful body shakes with it.
So if you're gonna be it, don't
just be it shoving shit in your
mouth.
Be it physically.
- Shake it!
Ooh, ugh.
- Excellent.
- Ooh, yes.
Shake it.
- Stacy Matthews surprised me.
I was so proud of her 'cause she
completely turned it.
And I say "get it, Stacy.
Eat that chicken, you bitch."
- Mm! Mm!
- Hello, everybody.
My name is Mimi Imfurst.
Take your jump rope...
chase after your man.
You're gonna grab him... oh!
Hold him up--
- Cut, cut, cut.
Just hold on a second.
Safety first, people.
We don't want anybody
to get hurt.
It's just feeling
a little disorganized.
Okay, everybody get up
and get untied.
- All right, here we go, jump.
Jump higher!
You gotta get higher, you gotta
find yourself.
I thought I did great.
I really wanted to create
a character
that really was memorable.
Quick, jump higher!
Faster, faster!
You wouldn't be able to forget
that voice.
'Cause perspiration is
inspiration.
- Team Carmen.
- Yes.
- Bitch, we ready to work it
out, and we're gonna pump it up.
Okay.
So...remember, catchphrase is
"work it out."
Work it out, work it out,
work it out.
Okay, so I just have a question.
Do I have to do it from here,
or can I walk in
and then start from here?
Or does it have to be very,
like, "welcome?"
- You can walk in.
- Do I get a little...?
Hello, everybody.
My name is Carmen Carrera.
And I would--am so excited to
welcome you to work it out.
All right, ladies, we're ready
to pop a squat.
You're gonna work everybody's
favorite asset.
So we're gonna go down... up and
around.
Down again.
And up the other way.
- Cut for a minute.
Now Carmen, we're asking you to
make a connection with the
camera, but we're actually
making a connection
with your ass.
- Well, yeah.
- Hello, ladies.
I'm here to show you one of my
favorite workouts.
It's called the rubber tug.
Gonna lower it down, ladies.
One, two, three, four.
- It was a little low energy.
- Give me more face.
- Yes.
- You've gotta--
give me more of that.
- Inspire us to get up off
the couch.
- Okay.
What we're gonna do is
we're gonna place it under our
toe, ladies.
Pull up...
- Oh!
- And down...
- Ah, it doesn't matter.
- [laughing]
- One, two, three, four.
- I was actually--it was
exciting watching the girls back
there, 'cause they were camping
it up a little bit.
- When you're making a video,
you have to express your
personality, and you have to
convince.
And I didn't get that from
India.
- Hi.
Hola! [speaking Spanish]
'Cause you like Latin guy...
[claps]
You have to work your body,
darling.
If you don't understand me,
don't worry--I will include
a translation
at the end of the video.
- [laughing]
- It's called echar pa'lante.
You gonna step on the step, and
you gonna cha, cha,
echar pa'lante!
Cha, cha, echar pa'lante!
- I feel like I am making a
workout video with Uber-Charo.
- Oop-a!
- And we are going to go ahead
and show you how to keep a tight
snatch to make sure that you
keep your man so he don't have
to come and bother me, okay?
- Get to what you're doing,
don't tell me what you're doing.
- All right, first you put your
ball...
in a nice, delicate position.
And stretch.
Ah, and bring it back.
Do y'all feel that?
Ah!
- I liked Mariah.
She did not bring it,
she did not have conviction.
You're sitting in front of
RuPaul and you're a drag queen,
you better pull it together.
- All right, I feel like my
snatch has been aired out.
- Hey, ladies, my name is Delta.
We're gonna start with one of my
favorite exercises,
the shake and bake.
We're gonna start with the small
weight.
Squeeze your boobs together,
that's always a good asset.
One, two, three.
Now if you're working out with a
partner, have them stand behind
you and reach around.
They can give you
a little bit too.
It's so fun to work out with
a partner.
- You should go over-the-top
with the shake.
Over-the-top! You like it?
Get vicious.
- One, two, three.
- Yes!
- Like that.
See how that feels?
Do it like that!
If you've got enough, you can
stick it right down inside there
and you can jump up and down.
This challenge started off to be
my worst nightmare.
But this challenge is gonna be
my strongest success.
- Nice job, team Carmen.
- Thank you.
- Now, ladies... tomorrow night
on the main stage,
come dressed in an outfit
that features
your favorite body part.
Because along with Susan Powter,
our extra special guest judge
will be la-luminous,
la-legendary...
Latoya Jackson.
- [gasps]
Oh, my god.
This is unbelievable.
I love Latoya.
I would jump up and get her.
- Go hit the showers!
- All right.
- Another day.
- Good morning.
- We're back in the workroom,
and today's runway challenge is
to pick something from your
closet that accentuates your
favorite or your best body part.
- I am wearing a dress that's
just low-cut, because I'm gonna
show off my boobs.
- I'm doing titties too, girl.
- Okay, there we go.
- I think I've showed it
already, so I 'm just gonna wear
something complimentary.
- Chaps.
You have a pair of chaps over
there you
about to put on, Carmen?
- I don't wanna be known as the
naked one.
That's not really what I wanna
go for.
And it just keeps coming up.
So I'm gonna do something that
Carmen would do, but just
a different kind of Carmen.
- Should I start out with a
ruffle cone?
- Yeah.
And then take it off?
Girl, I'm not, like, a skinny
twig.
You know, like, I look like a
football player out of drag.
And I will never look
like a woman.
My drag, it's more clown
than anything.
Did you always go by India?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- My brother's ex-boyfriend at
the time was my drag mother.
He got me started and he gave me
the name India Ferrah.
- Oh, so your brother's gay?
- Yeah.
- That's great.
That's really good.
- My family's really supportive,
so.
- That's so great.
My biological family, they threw
me out of the house.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Through all this--this awful
things that have happened to me
in my life, laughter is a way--
it's a coping mechanism.
Because if you can laugh at it,
you can deal with it.
- I think I worry too much what
people think,
and I've gotta get over that.
I was a little nervous 'cause,
you know, I got picked last.
Back at home, I'm a whole lot
more out,
and open, and humorous.
I mean, I feel like I'm not
myself here.
I'm not used to such big
personalities.
- Just be strong.
I've been on your team twice
now.
I've never been disappointed.
- Thank you, girl.
Well, you work it out just as
much, honey.
- Oh, that's 'cause I work in
the spirit of hallelu.
[laughter]
- When I frst came out,
I was like, well, I guess
this is perfect timing
for me to become a drag queen.
If I'm gonna be a queer, I might
as well be, like, the queeriest.
- The queeriest, yeah.
My interest in drag was just
because I loved clothes
and fashion.
- How was high school for you?
- I was picked on,
I was really awkward, I was
a little on the heavy side.
In my generation of growing up,
gay was just kind of disgusting
and kind of a subculture,
and drag kind of came
and saved me.
But it was hard.
I grew up in a very, like, Latin
neighborhood.
- You're in California?
- Mmm-hmm.
- So where'd you grow up?
- Gainesville, Georgia.
It's not a progressive city as
far as the thought process.
I didn't feel like there was
something wrong with me;
I just knew that people were
picking on me.
Kids don't understand that being
different
ultimately means you're gonna
become something special.
Even if you don't have, like, a
strong support system at home,
you have to get that
from within.
[laughter]
- And what?
Hey, guys.
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, hello, my dear.
- Hi, gorgeous.
- And I wanna welcome to the
Drag Race family my good pal
and makeup superstar, Billy B.
Hi, honey.
- Hey.
- I'm so glad you could get away
from Gaga to be with us.
- Thank you.
- And Susan Powter.
- Hi, Ru.
- So happy you're here.
- Thank you.
- And the multi-faceted yet
complex talents of Miss Latoya
Jackson is in the house tonight!
- Hello, gorgeous!
How are you?
- I am so happy you're here.
Welcome to my home.
- Why, thank you.
- This week, we challenged our
queens to make totally leotarded
workout videos.
Tonight, they're dressed to show
it off
and ready to pump you up.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
Raja!
- Not a stitch of makeup on.
- None.
- I've chosen my legs.
My inspiration for my outfit
was a milf/cougar who is sort
of waiting poolside for the
pool boy to come clean it up.
- Nothing tastes as good as
skinny feels.
Manila.
It's very Manila Deville.
- I wanna show off my face, so
I'm wearing a strapless dress,
pulling my hair up, so it's
very, like, "look at me."
- She looks like Erte a bit too.
- Yes, it's very Erte.
- It's got bride of Frankenstein
in there too.
- Yes, his second wife.
Next up, Stacy Layne Matthews,
from back swamp to the main
stage.
- My fat ass,
I'm gonna pull out
the skimpiest top that shows
off the biggest part of my
body, which is my tits.
- Add a little R&amp;B in there.
- Rear and boobs. R&amp;B.
This is India Ferrah.
- Ooh, Rapunzel.
- X marks the spot.
- I honestly chose the
see-through catsuit because it
shows my whole body.
I don't think anyone will have
trouble seeing my titties.
I mean, that's my favorite
body part.
- Not a shy girl.
- She is training the ponies at
the circus.
- I think it needs a whip
though, for real.
- Up next, Alexis Mateo.
- Oh, that's beautiful.
- Look at those hips!
- My best feature is
everything.
I'm gonna serve you hair,
face, hips, everything.
- I love the glitter.
The sparkle is great.
- I'm blinded by her beauty.
Up next, Mimi Imfurst.
- Mimi in the leopard!
Isn't it Bette Midler?
- It is Miss Kitty.
- I love my dress.
It's high camp, it's glamour.
And I think it's something
the judges haven't seen before.
- Wow.
- Very slimming,
the butt looks good.
- Meow, meow.
- Up next, Shangela Laquifa
Wadley.
- Pull up to the bumper.
- Oh! Oh! Yes!
- I choose to highlight my
shoulders.
The outfit that I had that
showcases my shoulders is one
I've had a little bit up my
sleeve.
- She's giving you a little
Kardashian.
- She's giving Kardashian.
- She's the forgotten
Kardashian.
- This is Kiki Kardashian.
They call this queen Mariah.
- Bring the drama, Mariah.
- The elegance of brown.
- I love the hair.
And all the colors are
coordinating, aren't they?
- My outfit, it complimented my
mood so much.
It was flowy, airy, sexy.
- Milk chocolate is what it is.
- Milk does a body good.
Up next, Delta Work.
- Work.
- Ooh!
- All right, Delta.
- She looks like Delta Burke,
doesn't she?
- I am geared up
for the judges.
I am ready to show the twins.
And I know that they're gonna
fall in love with my look.
- Priscilla Presley happening
in there.
- A southern girl.
- John Waters would love her.
- I love that hair.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yara Sofia.
- Her legs are gorgeous.
Look at that.
- I chose a short dress.
It is simple, but I am showing
my legs.
- Is she wearing stockings?
Those are her legs!
- Those are her eyes.
- She bought them.
- She has the receipt.
- Carmen Carrera.
Oh, she's all grown up.
- Seductress.
- I wanna show the judges
that I am versatile.
This beautiful gown is gonna
show off my beautiful ass.
- All about Jersey right now.
- She's Jersey-licious
right there.
- Yes, ma'am.
Welcome, dolls.
Earlier, the judges screened
your workout videos.
You competed as teams,
but tonight you'll be judged
as individuals.
Will the following queens
please step forward?
Stacy Layne Matthews,
Mimi Imfurst,
Yara Sofia, India Ferrah,
Alexis Mateo, Mariah.
Ladies...
you represent the best
and the worst of the week.
Raja, Manila,
Shangela, Carmen, Delta.
Good job this week, ladies.
You're all safe.
Leave the stage.
Now.
Ladies, it's time to face
the judges.
Let's start with Alexis Mateo.
Let's go to Miss Latoya Jackson.
- I love anything that sparkles,
of course.
And you are one sparkle.
It's just absolutely beautiful.
- Your look has, like, a moment
of retro Barbra Streisand
Hollywood glamour.
- As far as the video goes,
it was very Puerto Rican
Chrissy Snow.
- Yes! She was!
- From Three's Company!
- Yes!
- I thought that was
so different and clever
at the same time.
- Your one of the first
contestants
who brought real humor.
- Thank you, Alexis.
Next, Mimi Imfurst.
- Your video was much more
of a comedy skit.
- Today we're gonna help you
find you.
- You don't have to pull every
drag trick out of the hat
every single time.
- The video was a little bit
of a let-down.
It was like Divine meets
Sally Struthers.
- I really wanted to come in and
create a large character.
You know, I try to put the B
in subtle.
- It was hokey.
It was not good.
- I feel like you wasted
an opportunity.
Thank you, Mimi.
- Thank you.
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
I guess I don't have to ask you
what body part you're featuring
tonight.
- You look so much like my
relatives.
Is she related and I don't know
it?
- The back swamp Jacksons.
- [giggles]
- I have to say, having eaten
chicken in your workout segment,
you actually made us laugh
with you.
- And to incorporate that
into an exercise,
I think you did an excellent job
on what you had to do.
- Thank you.
- I liked it.
I like what she did.
- What I really loved was seeing
a personality.
We need more of you, Stacy.
- India Ferrah.
- It's the hat with the feather,
and the ponytail to
the floor, and the glitter lips.
Your boobs out with Xs and a
tarantula or something
on your vajayjay...
there is so much going on.
I think, "well, what is she
covering up?"
- Is every outfit gonna be the
bosoms featured?
Because that's what we've gotten
three weeks in a row.
- Okay.
- As far as your workout,
I wasn't inspired.
I didn't feel that connection.
- There was nothing. There
wasn't even a joke.
It was nervous.
- You could tell she was scared.
- Looking at the video, what
would you have done
differently?
- You know, more inspirational
words.
- It's not just the words.
Inspiration has to come from a
sincere place inside of you.
Thank you, India.
- Thank you.
- Yara Sofia.
You took a potential liability,
which is your accent, and you
made it work for you.
- That whole Latin thing and
that sexy swish,
you had everyone roaring.
- Echar pa'lante!
If you want that guy, you have
to work it out, darling.
- I think you are so hot.
I just have a problem,
outfit-wise.
- I can take it off if you want.
- [laughs]
Well, thank you very much,
darling.
Up next, Mariah.
What body part were you
featuring?
- My face.
- I love the fact that all the
different browns coordinate
with you quite well.
And they work.
- And then there's, like, this
Vegas makeup
that I think cheapens you,
and I think you're too pretty
for that.
- During the workout video,
I think your own sincerity
didn't shine through, and we the
audience didn't believe you.
- If you could think of your
personality
as your face, get that same
confidence,
it will take you to another
level, and that's the truth.
- Well, girls,
we have heard enough.
While you enjoy an Absolut
cocktail in the interior
illusions lounge, the judges
and I will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
Okay, now just between us girls.
Let's start with Alexis Mateo.
- I think she nailed
the bloody workout.
- I thought she was
the funniest one.
- Yeah.
- I like the energy.
- You worked in a workout video.
- Yes, I did.
- Was it difficult for you?
- It was, because unlike Susan,
I had never worked out before.
And I still don't work out
this day.
So I think once you start-- my
sister, she has to do it all
the time because
that's what she does.
- Right.
Let's move on to Mimi Imfurst.
The workout she did,
it wasn't funny.
- It was stupid.
- [laughing]
- Seriously.
- Right, it'd be a different
story if her shtick had
inspired us or at least made us
laugh.
- That's what I'm saying.
- Thing is, Mimi's always been
teetering
throughout the competition.
And I think she may have gone to
the other side.
Stacy Layne Matthews.
During her workout routine,
something was coming out.
- I know!
- There was potential.
- I like the fact that she made
fun of herself.
However, I don't feel that she
has what it takes to be
the next drag queen.
I just don't think so.
- Will she be in the bottom two?
That's the question.
India Ferrah.
- I hated the way
that she looked.
- I liked her so much.
I liked her.
- She's got a good energy.
She tried to do the double
entendre
with the rubber and the double X
magnum thing.
It just came off dirty
and not clever.
- Bottom line is,
her workout was boring.
- Yara.
Now what she did in that workout
was hilarious.
Who knew that she would do that?
- She's very sexy.
- Yes.
- Extremely sexy.
- She needs to burn
that dress though.
- You have it out for her
and that dress.
- I hated the dress too.
- Mariah.
I wasn't crazy about the snatch
tightening thing.
- It was like, eh.
- It was gay cruise humor.
- And the delivery wasn't good.
- Not at all.
- She has a beautiful face.
- For this title,
pretty isn't enough.
- All right...
[claps]
Silence!
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your totally leotarded
workout videos
and your performance
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Yara Sofia, your joy and
enthusiasm need no translation.
Condragulations, you're safe
from elimination.
Alexis Mateo...
combining lip gloss with your
thingy-majingy, you've created
a new workout craze.
You are the winner of this
week's challenge.
You will receive a $2,500 gift
certificate to gilt.com.
Yes, that's gilt.com.
Plus immunity from elimination
next week.
Thank you, Alexis.
- Thank you guys so much.
- India Ferrah...
On the runway, your look
was too much.
In the challenge,
you gave too little.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- My knees start shaking, and
I'm just standing there like,
"oh, my god, what am I gonna
do?"
- Stacy Layne Matthews.
In your challenge, you ate
the scenery...literally.
And you made us laugh with you.
But still, we feel you are
holding back.
Condragulations, you're safe...
for now.
- I'll bring it.
I think RuPaul gave me
a second chance.
And I just want to be more open
and be myself
so people can actually see who I
really am.
- Mariah...
you are a bronze beauty.
But your workout performance
was pale.
Mimi Imfurst...
you showed us your glamorous
side on the runway.
But in the challenge, your
slapstick got sloppy.
Mariah, condragulations,
you're safe.
- Thank you so much.
- Mimi Imfurst...
I'm sorry, my dear, but that
means you are up for
elimination.
- When Ru says that I'm in the
bottom two,
I'm totally surprised.
I think that now anything goes.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your
last chance to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-synch for your life!
Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
-  Mm-mm-mm-mm
Don't leave me this way
I can't survive
I can't stay alive
Without your love
Oh, baby
Don't leave me this way, no
I can't survive
I can't stay alive
Without your love
Baby, don't leave me
This way
- I'm like, "well, bitch, step
it up."
You gotta make sure that you're
always the one that's in front.
[low growling]
- What the hell
is she thinking?
You can't be lifting up
drag queens.
- I was honestly scared.
And all I could do was scream.
Get her off of me!
-  Outta control
Satisfy
I need a man
The need in me
- [laughing]
- Whoo!
[applause]
- Ladies...
I have made my decision.
Mimi Imfurst...
Drag is not a contact sport.
India Ferrah...
Shante, you stay.
- Whoo!
- Mimi Imfurst...
you are, and will always be,
part of an elite group
of drag queens.
Remember that.
Now, sashay away.
- Thank you.
[sniffs, sighs]
I don't agree with the judges.
I don't think I should've been
in the bottom two.
I know what I do best, I do me.
And I'm just gonna keep
doing me.
I'm Mimi Imfurst.
Not Mimi, I'm like everyone
else.
- And to my girls...
condragulations.
And remember, if you can't love
yourself, how in the hell are
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen!
- All right, let the music play.
Grand prize contributed in part
by aLandCHUCK.travel.