- Tonight, on RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited!,
the superstars
of season two return,
and the fur flies.
- Some of these girls
in the competition
need a personality lift.
- Fuck you too, bitch.
- Watch as my girls dish
a little bit of love...
- Pray for me
and pray for my son.
- That's the call that I waited
my entire life to hear.
- And a whole lot of shade.
- This woman's gonna cuss me
the [...] out.
[laughing]
- Hey, I'm not done talking yet.
You will speak when I'm done.
- Ooh.
- Security.
- And we announce your choice
for this season's
fabulous Las Vegas
Miss Congeniality Award.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
[car engines racing]
Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race:
Reunited!
People are always asking,
"RuPaul, what's the secret
to the show's success?"
Well, the answer is simple.
It's magic.
Before your very eyes,
12 supernatural men turn
into bewitching beauties
and do things that mere mortals
can only dream about.
Why, these drag queens
are just plain wicked.
And they got more tricks
than Jesse James
and Tiger Woods combined.
And just as they cast
their spell upon the nation,
one by one--poof, poof--
they vanish.
But tonight, through the magic
of television,
you can thank your lucky stars,
because all our queens
are back--
tucked, plucked,
and ready to conjure up
a little realness.
First up, these two queens came
to RuPaul's Drag Race
representing the South.
Can I get a big hallelu for
Miss Shangela Laquifa Wadley,
and from Atlanta, Georgia,
Miss Nicole Paige Brooks.
Next up, Miss Two-Piece
and a Biscuit herself,
Mystique Summers Madison.
The last time these two queens
were together,
they were lip-synching
for their lives.
Please welcome back Sonique
and Morgan McMichaels.
Hello, ladies.
all: Hi.
- [laughs]
All right, girls, let's dish.
- Uh-oh.
- Shangela, was that corn
on your wrist?
- Ooh! Yes!
This is my new Gaga-inspired
"cornsage."
- A-mazing.
- Yes, I've learned a little bit
in the last year.
- Now, you'd been doing drag
for just a few months
before coming to Drag Race.
Do you think you were too green
to be on Drag Race?
- No, I definitely came
to this competition to compete,
to be a drag superstar.
I mean, did you see the
lip-synch for your life? Okay?
I definitely came to party
with the people.
But you guys said that I needed
a little bit more time.
This wasn't RuPaul's school
for girls, all right?
All right!
So I left, learned a little
something,
and then went and won
this California Entertainer
of the Year pageant
and came home with a crown, ow.
- Okay.
[laughing]
So you're snatching trophies
and corn.
- Honey, I'm snatching
everything,
and hopefully a husband is next.
Hallelu.
- Thank you.
All right, Nicole Paige Brooks
from Atlanta, Georgia.
- Yes, sir.
- I know that you are
a fierce drag mama.
Uh, you're also
a fierce drag papa.
- Yes.
- Did your son get
to see the show?
- He saw the Barbie part,
when we did the Barbies,
and he's like,
"Oh, Da-da's on TV."
And he got really excited.
But, um, he hasn't seen Nicole
yet.
But there's pictures of me
all over the house,
and you ask him who that is,
and he's like, "I don't know."
I don't think that it's all come
together yet, but it will.
- How old is he?
- He's four.
- Now, you didn't last as long
as some people predicted.
- Yeah.
- Now, what were
your frustrations
with the competition?
- I really...liked all
the sorority of the girls.
You know, we were pretty unified
when we were here.
And then I was shocked to see
Raven talking about everybody
behind our backs.
To be honest, my feelings--
- Were you really?
- I was really surprised.
- Really?
See, I thought Raven was
very up-front, like me.
- You didn't say nothin'
behind my back.
- No, of course, not, but,
like, I didn't think Raven did
either.
- Well, we will discuss that
when Raven comes out.
- Yeah.
- All right, Mystique.
Now, you said you were bringing
up the plus-size gals.
Did you get a lot of support
from the community?
- Yes, I got a lot of people
saying, "Thank you for showing
me that I can go out there
and just be me and not conform
to, like, society's thoughts."
- Now, some people felt
that you had given up
on the last challenge,
that you had sort
of thrown in the towel.
- There's a lot of issues
with that.
I live in Dallas, Fort Worth.
And a lot of the gangs and stuff
was acting up in Mexico,
and they was kidnapping
Americans.
'Cause my mom works in Mexico.
So that morning, I heard that a
lot of Americans was kidnapped.
So in my head, I was like,
"I don't know
if it's my mom there."
- She's not a drug mule,
is she?
- No, she is not!
- She was okay, right?
- She was okay, be--
- Well, I have to ask, then,
about why the schmatta blouse
and the black pants.
- I mean, the black pants,
they were busted.
- But the thing is, I wanted
to be, like, you know,
the up-to-date,
country type of thing.
- Time out! Please.
Real quick.
I'm a native Texan.
And you said I'm representing
the people who really dress
like this in Texas.
This is representative
of how we dress.
That is not representative of
how everyone dresses in Texas.
And your makeup skills are not
how everyone in Texas
does makeup.
- True.
- Well, Mystique, you look
beautiful tonight.
- Thank you.
- You look gorgeous.
All right, Sonique.
- Hi.
- Now, I gotta say,
the elimination
between you and Morgan
was one of the toughest
I've ever done.
'Cause you were both incredible.
- Thank you.
- Did I get it right, though?
- I actually--I don't know.
I thought I was prepared
and everything like that,
and I've learned so much more
about myself
and about my drag
and everything.
But I--I felt like
the whole time I was here,
I was in a dream.
- Was it a sweet dream or
a beautiful nightmare for you?
- My mind was always
somewhere else.
- Like, where else?
What are you talking about?
- I don't really feel
that people got a chance
to get to know who Sonique is.
- And I've heard that there's
something you want to share
with us concerning that.
- I don't know,
I was always just so...
Um...it's very personal,
and I don't want to...
- Can I check on her?
- We'll give her a moment.
- [crying] I know
they don't understand.
And that's--
and that's the reason why
I've been so unhappy
for so long.
- Hey, kiddo, you okay?
What is it, honey?
Talk to me.
- I haven't been happy for
a really long time in my life.
And I've never understood why.
I just had to be honest
with myself and...
I've...
I'm a woman.
I'm not a boy who dresses up.
The--I feel like the only thing
I've ever done right
was go to a doctor
and start transitioning.
I've never been more happier
in my entire life.
- Good.
You want--would you...
join the group again?
- Yeah.
- Maybe we could talk
a little bit about it.
- I'm proud of you.
- Come on, baby.
- Thank you.
I'm so happy.
How's my makeup look?
- Destroyed, bitch.
- Don't do that to me.
- All right, ladies,
Sonique is back.
Do you feel safe to share
something with the group?
- I always knew that there
wasn't something right.
I couldn't ever be boy enough.
I've always been a girl.
I've always been a girl
trapped in a boy's body.
I started doing drag.
And...there was just something
about it that wasn't enough.
And I've--I went to a doctor,
and he put me on testosterone
blockers,
and then moved me to hormones,
and my levels are even,
and I've never been happier
in my whole life.
- Well, I know a lot of people
get it confused--
what a transsexual is and what--
- There's a line between drag
and transgender.
Most transgender girls
do not do drag.
You know, they want to live
their life solely as a woman,
where drag queens want to get
out of drag and be a man.
When I go home, I ne--
I dread taking off my makeup.
- Listen, I'm so happy and proud
of you for being so courageous.
'Cause I know how hard that is.
You know, I--I'm a man,
I do drag,
and that's what I do for work.
But for you to make
this realization,
to be happy performing
but also to clarify
not only for all of us,
but for yourself,
I applaud you.
And I think it's so courageous.
And you have our support, this
family here, forever, any time.
[light applause]
All right.
Moving on
to Miss Morgan McMichaels.
Now, I hear that you are
transitioning from being a man
into a butch man.
Is that right?
- [deep voice] Absolutely.
[all laugh]
We're going in different
directions, Sonique and I.
- Now, Morgan, you and Mystique
had your moments together.
- Did we?
- When?
- Let's take a look.
- Oh, here we go.
You have no class
and no manners.
- No class, no manners?
You piss me off some more,
I will whoop your fucking ass!
Bitch, I am from Chicago!
[laughs]
- Wow.
Morgan, that was intense.
- You know, at the end
of the day, I'm a man.
And I'm not gonna let people
disrespect me.
Now, everything that I said
during the fight,
obviously it was elevated,
and it was heated.
And, you know,
your makeup is your own,
and your hair is your own,
and everything that you do
to make Mystique is fabulous.
I think you're
an amazing entertainer.
- Why, thank you.
I love you too.
We should make out later.
- Ew.
- [laughs]
See, no, we had a heart-to-heart
since the whole fight.
- Yeah, we've spoken.
- We spoke.
Some people think we don't talk,
and we're just pissed off
at each other.
- People are under the illusion
that one fight has ended
any chance of a friendship.
- Are there any girls that you
haven't kept in touch with?
- I haven't spoken
with Tatianna.
Like, watching the episodes and,
like, watching the comments
she made about me,
I was not surprised.
I think I was more disappointed.
- So you found out more about
what she said
once you watched the show.
- Once I watched the episodes,
and she kept calling me a whore,
and I needed to be knocked off
my high horse,
I think it was
from her own insecurity,
'cause I never said a bad word
about Tatianna.
- Well, you'll have a chance
to speak with Tatianna
face-to-face,
and all the other girls,
when RuPaul's Drag Race:
Reunited! continues.
Welcome back to RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited!
Our next doll
is a dancin' queen.
Welcome back, Sahara Davenport.
From sizzling San Juan,
it's Miss Jessica Wild.
Escandalo!
When this queen's in the house,
it's a barrel of laughs.
Give it up for Pandora Boxx!
This next queen's natural beauty
is undeniable.
Welcome back the ravishing
Tatianna.
The song you just sashayed out
to is the Bangkok Booty Mix
of LadyBoy,
available on iTunes.
Sahara, now, during the show,
we found out that your mother
was a minister
and that your family wasn't that
supportive of your drag career.
Since the show, what's happened?
- One night,
I was heading out to a gig,
and I got a text from her:
"I see you on RuPaul's show,
and you look fabulous.
Call me."
And I was like, "Oh, my God,
I'm gonna call her,
and this woman is gonna cuss me
the [...] out."
- You thought
it was an intervention?
- Yeah, I thought
it was an intervention,
but I actually called her
the next morning.
She was like, "Oh, my God,
I'm so proud of you."
- Would you say
RuPaul's Drag Race
is bringing families together?
- Christian, black families
together!
- All right, praise--
- Hallelu!
[laughter]
- What reaction
do you get from fans
who've watched you on the show?
- I get Facebooks all the time
from little boys who are asking
me questions like,
"I want to tell my mom.
I don't have the strength.
I don't have the courage.
Please help me."
And it's just like,
"I didn't know I was signing up
for that," you know.
I thought I was coming on,
you know, to--
to be fabulous and show
the world my talent and,
you know,
increase my booking fee.
[laughter]
But the show definitely
has given me a voice,
and it's taught me that,
outside of just the performance,
that we all have a voice
and have a responsibility
to not only our community,
but to the world,
to share and help those in need
as much as we can.
- That's lovely,
and you're absolutely right.
Thank you, Sahara.
Now, Jessica, you had some
issues with your English.
- Yes.
I was so scared when you called
me that I'm on the show.
Because I don't speak English.
But I think, at the same time,
"I'm not gonna quit.
I'm just gonna do it."
- Well, I think your accent
is absolutely charming.
- Sometimes I'm lost,
but I'm acting like...
"Oh, oh, yes.
"Oh, my God, the judges?
"Oh, I love it.
I love it."
- What's the wildest thing
people have written to you?
- A mom write me that her son
want to be a drag queen.
And her son have ten years old.
And she said, "Now you show me
that my son is a special,
and I need to love him more
and more."
So I teach people that my mom
love me, no matter what.
So you need to support your
family, because we are specials.
- Yeah.
Thank you, Jessica.
- Thank you.
- Pandora, now, Entertainment
Weekly called your elimination
the most controversial.
And at one point in the show,
I called you the Susan Lucci
of Drag Race.
You came very close
to winning challenges,
but you never won a challenge.
Do you hate me?
- I was the one
that keyed your car.
- Oh, it was you!
- Yeah.
I feel much better now.
- Oh, good.
So, Pandora, you made
a very brave admission
at one point in the show.
Let's take a look.
- I tried to kill myself.
- Oh, no, sir.
- I didn't understand.
I didn't know what gay was.
I knew I was totally different,
I felt totally alone.
I thought that, you know,
"Well, I'll just take
all these pills
because I don't--
I can't deal with it anymore."
- Now, that was very brave,
and I was very moved by that.
What's the reaction been?
- I've gotten many emails
from people
saying that they have gone
through the same thing,
and they've felt
the same emotion.
And I actually got, probably,
the most powerful email.
Somebody said,
by hearing my story,
that they said
that I saved their life.
I burst into tears.
I was blown away by that.
- It's amazing the power
that you have as queen,
and it's quite a gift.
I also remember that you talked
about your father,
and that he, you know, wasn't
that accepting of what you do,
and that he had been ill.
- He always accepted me being
gay, but the drag thing,
he just didn't want
to really acknowledge.
- Was there any closure there?
- There was a moment
before he passed away.
It was actually a week
And he called me and he said
that he watched Drag Race,
and that he was so proud of me,
and he was my number one fan.
And that's the call...
[choking back tears]
That's the call that I waited
my entire life to hear.
- That's beautiful.
And so many have been waiting
for that call.
Do you have anything to say
about the people out there
who have been waiting
for that call?
- I would just say that know
that you're good enough,
and you're perfect
the way that you are.
And you have to affirm
your life,
and that's what I did before,
but it was amazing to at least
have that moment
before he passed away.
- Well, no matter what happens,
I mean,
you always kept us laughing,
and that's worth $1 billion.
- Can I get paid a $1 billion
for it?
[laughter]
- I love that outfit,
by the way.
It's your Drag Race
official dress.
- It is.
You know, I'll just go
into merchandising for it.
- I think it's brilliant.
Yeah.
- By Marco Marco.
Well, I came up
with the concept,
and then he did it for me.
- It's brilliant.
- Changed a few things.
- Yeah, it's great.
- It's got it all: the checkered
flag, the runway--
Brilliant.
I figure if
I couldn't win the race,
I'll at least win the race in
this outfit.
- Yes, absolutely.
And I'm sure Santino will have
a lot to say about that outfit.
- [laughs]
And I'm sure I won't listen
to him again.
[laughter]
- I thank you, Pandora.
- Thank you.
- Tatianna.
- Hey.
- T-A-T-I.
Yeah, you were one controversial
character on the show.
- Evidently.
- During the show,
you were pretty beat up
by the other girls.
- There was a few nights
that I went back to the hotel
and just cried and didn't really
want to talk about it.
'cause I didn't want people
to see
that they were getting to me.
- Did it affect you?
- It definitely affected me.
When I left here, I didn't want
to be around drag queens
for a good minute.
[laughter]
I'll say that right now.
I did not want to.
- Now, in a mini-challenge,
we asked you to throw shade
in front of everyone.
And you kind of froze up.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yet...
[laughs]
You weren't shy about
criticizing others
during your interviews.
- Oh, no.
- Let's take a look.
- Oh, boy. Shall we?
[laughs]
I am so happy
that someone said something
about Morgan's whoreness.
Sonique, she always got
that stank face.
Raven all of a sudden decides
that she to blossom, verbally.
These sparkling 30 years that
she's got behind her,
there's just so much there
that she just can't hold it in.
She's just got to spread it.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Do you think it's okay to say
something behind somebody's back
as opposed to--to their face?
- I didn't come in with,
like, a strategy of,
"Well, I'm gonna be nice,
and then I'm gonna cut 'em,
you know, behind the scenes."
Like, it wasn't like that.
I wanted to speak of others how
I would want to be spoken about.
When someone comes at me wrong,
then that rule's going out
the window,
and I'm talking some shit.
- When did I ever say or do
anything to you
to make you say something
about me?
Because I never was
that way to you.
- No one said every single thing
that they thought
to that person.
- Well, neither did you.
- No one did.
I know, I know,
and I'm not saying I did either.
- I definitely did.
You're a little more reserved.
I mean, sure, your legs--
you have great stems, honey.
But you know what I'm saying?
But I just didn't appreciate
the fact that, you know,
you totally slung me, like,
"Oh, she's a whore."
- I didn't mean literally
you are a whore.
- Right.
- Certainly not.
- So, Tatianna, the biggest
critique from the other girls
was that they felt you were
getting by on your looks.
Now, how did that make you feel?
- It kind of pissed me off.
- Kind of pissed you off
or really pissed you off?
- It really pissed me off.
- Tell me about it.
- It truly pissed me off.
I'm more than a face.
I have something to say.
I have thoughts.
- You're a great pair of legs
too.
- Thank you.
I think that you saw
that I was progressing,
and that I was growing,
and I feel like all the other
girls chopped it down to,
"Oh, well, she's just pretty.
She's just Rebecca."
And I'm like,
"No, I'm more than that."
Just because I have a more of
a realistic type look sometimes
doesn't mean that I'm any less
of a queen than anyone else.
As long as I have a dick between
my legs and a wig on my head,
I'm a drag queen.
- Dressed.
- Point-blank, period.
And that is the way that it is.
- The criteria gets down
to the charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent.
And you really can't even
compare all of you, you know?
You're all winners.
Coming up, we'll be joined by
Raven, Jujubee,
and America's Next Drag
Superstar, Tyra Sanchez.
The new Tyra.
Welcome back to RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited!
Let's welcome back the Laotian
in the house,
the incomparable Miss Jujubee!
Early in the competition,
this next queen almost sashayed
away, twice.
But she dug deep,
stepped up her game,
and ended up in the top two.
That is so Raven.
This last doll always
stole the show.
And some of these queens
want it back.
America's next drag superstar,
Miss Tyra Sanchez!
[applause]
Tyra!
- Hey.
- My queen.
Mwah. Mwah.
Gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- Have a seat, darling.
You're all here.
How 'bout that?
Look around you.
These are your sisters.
Win or lose, love or hate,
we are family.
[shaky voice]
And I am your mother.
- Oh.
- Mommy.
- Jujubee.
- Hi.
- You talked a little in the
show about being a gay Asian.
Have all the Gasians out there
contacted you?
- Yes.
- What have they said?
- They--they say
that it's an inspiring feat
for me to be on television
and talk about my culture
and actually speak Laotian.
And, you know,
my family's really happy.
I'm very excited.
- Have you talked to your mom?
- I have not.
- Now, if your mom
is watching this,
is there anything
you'd like to say to her?
- Thank you for giving me life.
You know, I mean, that's...
That's really
what I have right now.
It's--it's been ten years, but
I need a little bit--I need--
I need a little bit more time.
- Another ten years?
- No, I wouldn't--I don't know.
I-I feel bad, and I feel
for her, but I'm not ready.
Maybe Jujubee's gonna help bring
that out,
but it's just
a struggle for me still.
- So you didn't become
America's Next Drag Superstar.
- Mm-hmm.
- What is next for you?
- I'm still gonna
keep doing drag.
I mean, I wanna be in movies.
I wanna be onstage.
I wanna--I wanna play Angel
on Broadway in Rent.
I wanna do it all.
- I think that's gonna happen
for you.
The opportunity has opened up
for each of you.
The fact that you made it
into this competition...
eh, uh...
just under 300 years old.
I know some things, and the fact
that this happened--
don't take it for granted,
ladies.
The world is yours, but it
depends on what you put into it.
- I agree.
- Now, Raven, you were
in the bottom two twice.
- Mm-hmm.
- And you ended up number two.
How'd you pull that off?
- I knew when I fucked up.
Like, I knew when I did a bad
job, and I owned up to it.
My chicken was the most horrible
chicken in the fucking world.
Welcome to another...
Oh, shit.
- So your chicken was funky.
- Really funky, girl.
I was so focused on having,
like, a Southern accent...
So then I see that Jessica
was doing a chicken voice,
I'm like,
"I'm such a fucking airhead."
Why wouldn't I do
a chicken voice?
- Now, Raven, you were not shy
during the competition,
and you were liberal
in speaking your mind.
Let's take a look.
- Nicole's gone.
Praise the Lord.
She has acrylic toenails...
with white French tips.
Tatianna's an airhead.
All she's been doing the past
couple weeks is...this.
Tatianna is about face value.
So fuck you, Tatianna.
- Fuck you, too, bitch.
- Mwah.
- Let me put it out there
real quick.
- Tatianna, how do you feel
about hearing all that?
- Um...
I think my feelings
are easily explained.
You're jealous.
You're insecure.
No one that feels that great
about themselves
has to put others down
the way that you do.
I have had very negative
feelings towards you
since the end of that show.
Now, I know that
I said some shit.
But really, though, how do you
say something like what you said
to people--like Nicole.
I think Nicole genuinely
thought she made a friend.
- We were not talking about
Nicole and I right now.
We were talking
about you and me.
- Okay, well,
then let me get back to it.
- But, I mean, that is a fact.
I really did think
I found a friend.
I was gagged by that.
- Until the point--
- Okay--
- I'm not done talking yet.
You will speak when I'm done.
- Ooh.
- Honey.
- Security.
- She has gotten everything that
she wanted to say out about me.
It's my turn.
And I never said anything
hurtful about you.
I said that you run your mouth,
'cause you do.
But I didn't, like--I didn't
go for, "Oh, she's fat.
"Oh, she's an airhead.
"She's dumb, she's nothing.
They're living for someone
that's nothing."
Bullshit.
- When my opinion was asked for,
is when I gave it.
- When you were in an interview?
- When I went into the
interview, they would say,
"What do you think about this?
What do you think about that?"
Here's my opinion.
So if it came off and sounded
shitty,
sorry that it sounded shitty.
- No, you're not.
Don't give empty apologies.
You're not sorry for shit.
- Okay, well, then I'm done.
- 'Cause I haven't heard
from you.
The only thing I've heard from
you was, "You're gorgeous."
And then another message,
"You're gorgeous."
- 'Cause you are gorgeous,
and I've told you that
since day one.
You, out of everyone in this
competition,
has the most beautiful face
in this competition.
- I'm more than a face.
- It's just malicious,
just gay faggotry
that I just was not thinking
we were gonna run into here.
- Well, guess what.
We are making a TV show.
So don't sit here and act like
we were filming an episode
of 7th Heaven.
- I didn't say that.
- It's a fucking drag
competition.
- Yeah, I know, but, I mean,
but they were all smiling
in my face at one point.
- I never smiled in your face,
and I never hung out with you.
So you can sit there and say
that we were cool
and we hung out--we never did.
Every one of you, even Morgan,
can sit here and say,
"You're a fucking bitch."
I don't care.
- That's evident.
It's very evident.
That's the problem.
That is your problem.
Your personality is for shit.
- It's not a problem actually.
- You are the one
that is face value.
Your outside is gorgeous, Raven,
but your insides are dark and
nasty, and I don't like you.
- You were pretty bitchy
yourself, so there.
- I wasn't that bad.
I was not like you.
I wasn't like you.
Let's be clear.
The people I spoke shit about,
I'm sorry, at the point in time,
they deserved it,
and I was mad.
But I didn't deserve
what you said about me.
I didn't deserve it
and neither did anyone else.
- So you going, "Oh, I pity you
for the face you have,"
that's not the same thing?
- There's a difference.
I'm sorry, but there's a
blatant, obvious difference.
- I know Raven really well,
and Raven's a beautiful fucking
person.
I know you really well,
and I know you're a fucking
beautiful person.
You guys have such
the same traits
that it doesn't work.
Do you know what I'm saying?
And I hate--and I hate--
and I hate to say that to you
and to you, because I know you
don't like that,
but there's a lot
of similarities.
So live with it or just don't
talk to each other.
- And I will say,
on my last night--
or my last day there,
I had a conversation with you,
and I said, "You know what,
"we do have things in common.
I don't understand why you hate
me so much."
And it's almost like you look at
me, and you see--
- Well, I don't hate you.
I don't hate you, Tatianna.
- The things that you say,
I can't fathom--
not hating someone,
but then feeling justified
and not wanting to apologize
for the things that you said.
- If it hurt your feelings,
okay, then I am sorry
that it hurt your feelings.
I am not sorry for saying it.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Now, we are overly sensitive.
But your feelings are not facts.
And I said this to the first
season,
because they got their panties
in a bunch
over things that are said.
Listen, kiddo,
things are gonna be said.
And you're all highly
intelligent,
you're all highly sensitive.
You have to not let it
hurt your feelings.
Raven is a little more seasoned.
So her skin is a little bit
thicker, basically.
- It's weathered.
- It's--[laughs]
Raven, you're under a lot
of heat right now,
but you've also made millions
and millions of fans.
Would you have done anything
differently?
- I wouldn't have said a lot of
things that I did or said them
the way that I did.
I realize I don't speak
eloquently.
I'm not a lady.
- Oh, no, I think you speak
very eloquently.
- Well, thank you.
But I--you know, and I have
the mouth of a trucker.
So I'm like--I guess you could
say I'm an eloquent trucker.
[laughter]
I would have worded things
a lot softer.
Because like Pandora said in one
of the Untuckeds,
that the next drag superstar
needs to be
basically not such
a wretched cunt.
- [laughs]
- So I would have worded things
differently.
- Really?
- Yep.
- Now, Tatianna,
Raven apologized,
but you still seem
to be holding onto it.
Why is that?
- 'Cause, you know,
I am sensitive.
And the things that she said
did bother me.
And when I came here I, "A," had
no friends in the drag world.
I had also never traveled
by myself before.
I'd never been on a plane
I had never been
away from my family
as long as I was by myself.
So I think it just--
you think of someone
in your head a certain way,
and when you watch it,
it's completely different,
it kind of--it hurts.
- Yeah.
- And I should not have been as
vocal as I was about Tatianna,
about you, again,
and I'm gonna speak to you.
I apologize.
- So, kids, this is the perfect
time for a little hug.
- For your mother.
- Aw.
Well, Tatianna, Raven,
I hope you feel better.
I know I do.
Welcome back to RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited!
Tyra Sanchez.
- Hi.
- America's Next Drag Superstar.
Now, some people probably think
this is a controversial decision
to have you as
the Next Drag Superstar.
Of all the girls, you received
some of the harshest criticisms
from the other competitors.
Expressions like
"lazy bitch,"
"immature,"
"mannerless."
- "Satan's baby."
How's that make you feel?
- When I watched it, I realized
that, at the time,
I was all those things that they
were calling me.
All I can do is, like, apologize
to Sahara and to Tatianna,
all the girls, Jujubee, whoever.
If I hurt your feelings,
if I did anything to,
like, make you upset,
like Pandora, or anyone else,
I can only apologize.
I can't take back what I did.
But I can only make
from this day forward better.
- Well, you know, a lot of
people who have written in
have very strong feelings
about you.
You know,
they acknowledge the fact
that you are a fierce queen,
but your behavior on the show
turned them off.
Is there anything you want
to say to them?
- And all I could ask is that
for them to reach out
and pray for me,
pray for me and pray for my son,
like, for us
to have a better life
and to be better people
within ourselves.
- Um, coming back here,
you know,
you get to reconnect with people
you haven't seen in a while,
and I saw a complete change
in Tyra.
She's completely not the--
not the same Tyra
that I fought with.
She's not that Tyra anymore.
- What's changed?
- Just the general demeanor.
It just seems like she's
a lot more like, "Hello."
It looks like she wants
to try and integrate.
I didn't get that on the show.
It would be everyone hanging out
and then Tyra separating herself
to a certain extent.
- I think she was just
so focused on a goal,
and that she didn't want to come
and hang out with everyone
because then she would end up
not being focused
on the next day's challenge
and could possibly end up
in the bottom two.
- Is that true, Tyra?
- Before I came here,
I didn't have a place to stay.
I was sleeping
on my drag mother's floor.
I didn't have a job.
When I came here,
my goal was to win.
If I went home empty-handed,
like, that wasn't an option.
But my mom, like,
she always teached me,
when you want something,
you pray for it.
And so I stayed prayed up.
That's what I call it,
I prayed up.
When I went into the hotel,
I didn't want to hang out.
I stayed in my room and, like,
I would ask God for ideas,
creations for the next
challenge, or what to do on,
like, on the runway.
Give me the idea that I need
to win this challenge.
- She's young.
She have the opportunity
to change, and I think she did.
And I just want to say
that I'm so proud of you.
And I feel great that you are
the Next Drag Superstar,
because you have
a lot of talent.
A lot of people love you,
and we are going to support you
in your career.
- I'm a fan, I really am.
Like, watching the show,
you can't take it from her.
Watching the show I'm like,
"The bitch turned it."
- Well, listen, I think that
your prayers were answered,
and I think that people
will pray for you
and your success as America's
Next Drag Superstar.
I have to say, you came here
with a drag mother
who clearly taught you
the rules of drag.
In the wedding challenge,
you come out on your knees
behind the biggest bouquet
of flowers I've ever seen.
You peekaboo around it,
throw the flowers in the air,
and jump up
without support on your feet.
And when I called you out
after your runway presentation,
you had tears in your eyes.
And you pulled the veil
over your face back
in the back of the room.
Bitch, your pussy was on fire.
That shit was fierce.
Now, I'm--I told you,
I'm just under 300 years old.
Seen a lot of queens.
That kind of behavior
that you had clearly learned
from another elderly queen
such as I,
that's magic.
That's magic shit
right there.
- Thank you.
- Now, Tyra, how do you think
winning the crown will
change your life?
- This is opening so many doors
for me, and not only me,
for my son, just to make
his life better
and to give him the things
that I didn't have.
I actually got custody of him,
so now, this month, he's gonna
be staying with me
from this point on.
And I just, like, have everyone
helping me out in so many ways.
- Tyra, I just have to ask you.
Aside from your beautiful,
bejeweled bosom,
is there a secret
to your smile?
- Yes, I got a new smile,
not because of the reading
that we had.
- Miss Tyra,
was your barbecue canceled?
Your grill is fucked up.
- Oop!
- The barbecue is back, honey.
- The barbecue is back on.
And not because of what people
were saying on the Internet.
I did it for myself.
Got it fixed,
got it straightened.
I even got my voice deepened.
[laughter]
- Can they do that?
- They can do that.
It goes deeper and deeper
every day.
[laughter]
- All right, coming up,
the girls get their chance
to judge the judges
as RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited!
keeps on keeping on.
Welcome back to RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited!
Now, drag queens are always
getting judged.
Every once in a while,
it's nice to give a little back.
So, girls, sharpen your claws
for two of my favorite people
in the world.
Please welcome back our resident
biological woman,
Merle Ginsberg,
and the always fashionable
Santino Rice.
Now, the two of you
are L.A. party people.
Who out there surprised you
that were fans of the show?
- I did a little job
interviewing people
on a red carpet,
and I had to interview Johnny
Weir, the great skater,
and I'm so excited to meet
Johnny Weir.
And I put out my hand, he goes,
"Oh, I love you.
I love Drag Race."
I was like, "I can't even
believe this is happening."
- Now, Merle,
this season on our show,
what stood out fashion-wise?
- Well, Tyra's looks
just blew me away.
They really did.
They were so Paris runway,
Christian Dior.
And I just kept wondering,
how the hell did she do that?
- When you are
in a situation like this
and the whole world is watching,
yeah, you hot glue things
to your body,
you super glue earrings
to your ears.
You see where people's
dedication and passion is
and how bad you want this.
- You chop off those toes
to fit in those shoes.
- Yeah.
- Now, Santino, you saved
your harshest criticism
for Pandora Boxx.
Tell me this, Pandora,
how did it feel
when you were being critiqued
on the runway?
- It was horrible.
It's hard to be up there getting
critiqued, and it did affect me.
And by the wedding challenge,
that's really where I kind
of--I had a breakdown.
I had a breakdown in my room,
because I just went in there and
just cried because I was like,
"I don't know what to do.
"I feel like I'm listening.
"I feel like I'm trying
to do what--
the best I can and to take
everybody's critiques
and do it."
But when you're told that,
"I don't like your style,"
I kind of didn't know
where to go from there.
- All I could say is, Pandora,
do you feel like,
out of all these queens,
you have the best personal style
and you were the most
fashionable every challenge?
- Um, I definitely don't feel
that I was,
but that's not
my strongest suit.
- Sure.
- But, you know,
I can hire a stylist.
And some of these girls
in the competition
needed a personality lift,
and you can't get one of those.
- You're right.
You're absolutely right.
And seeing you today, Pandora,
I think you look amazing.
I think what you're wearing
is funny, it's young.
You look stylish, hip,
but there were times
where you came out,
and it seemed like it was kind
of a rehabbed pageant gown
or something that wasn't quite
up to your personality
and your comedic timing.
- It's about knowing thyself
and presenting that
on the stage,
and you can never go wrong.
- The biggest thing I learned
is not to second-guess myself.
Because every outfit that got
a really harsh critique,
there was another one that I was
gonna wear instead and I said,
"Wear that other one."
and I changed my mind
at the last minute
and just kept what I had on.
So I wish I would have listened
to my inner voice that said
that, you know, "You need to--
You need to wear
the better outfit."
- What do you have to say about
Santino's outfit tonight?
- [laughs]
- I love homeless chic.
I think it looks great.
[laughter]
- You know what, let's all
together, all the contestants,
let out a primal yell directed
towards the judges' panel
over here.
Just yell it out.
One, two, three.
[all yelling]
- [laughs]
Merle, Santino, thank you
so much for coming back.
Now when we return,
the viewers have voted,
and I will announce your choice
for the fabulous
Las Vegas Miss Congeniality
and the final lip-synch
for your life.
So don't fuck it up.
Stay tuned.
Welcome back to RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited!
Well, my dolls, it's been
a wild, magic carpet ride.
Thanks for taking drag out
of the closet
and into the hearts of America.
Once again, all hail the queen,
Miss Tyra Sanchez,
America's Next Drag Superstar.
[applause]
Now, to see Tyra in person on
the Logo Drag Race Tour,
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks,
check the schedule
on LogoTV.com.
And that goes
for all these queens.
Don't let the love end here.
Google 'em, friend them
on Facebook, tweet 'em.
Do whatever you have to do
to see them in person.
Now, the fabulous fans
of RuPaul's Drag Race
were asked to vote
for the one queen they felt
was the most congenial,
or as I like to say,
the least shady.
The results are in,
and it was a landslide.
Susan Lucci, the streak is over.
And the winner of the fabulous
Las Vegas Miss Congeniality
prize is...
Pandora Boxx!
[cheers and applause]
Come over here
and get your prize, girl.
Oh, "con-drag-ulations," Mommy.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
You've won tickets to see
the one and only,
the legendary Cher!
Yes!
[applause]
Plus airfare, three days, two
nights in fabulous Las Vegas.
- Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.
You like me.
You really like me.
- [laughs]
I hope you feel
the love tonight.
Now, finally, for all
you future drag superstars
out there watching,
go to RuPaulsDragRaceCasting.com
for your chance to compete on
the next season
of RuPaul's Drag Race
and share your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent
with the world.
Ladies, this is it.
The time has come for you
to lip-synch for your lives
to the new remix of my song
Main Event,
available on iTunes.
So don't fuck it up.
Let the music play.
[lively dance music]
Here we go again
Chapter two
Turn another page
Walking in the rain
Oh, my God!
Paint a smile
Upon my face
'Cause I won't let
The spotlight
See the heartbreak
In my love life
When the laughter
Starts to fade
All the drama
Takes center stage
This is the main event
Are you ready
Hey!
Dance into your soul