- Previously on
Rupaul's Drag Race...
- Hey!
[all screaming]
- Sahara and I have
been friends forever.
- I hope that I don't fall
into that role of babysitting
when I should be really, like,
cutting their bra straps.
- You must create
your best drag look
using just these curtains.
Oh-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
You have a child?
- I do have a son.
My son is, like,
my major motivation
for winning this competition.
- All right!
She is throwing
some serious 'shay.
Morgan McMichaels, you are
the winner of this challenge.
You will receive immunity.
- I don't fucking
like being just safe.
- Mystique, based on your
unforgettable presentation,
I'm giving you
a get out of jail free card.
Sahara Davenport, Shangela,
the time has come for you
to lip sync for your life.
- Ohh!
- Sahara Davenport,
Shante, you stay.
Shangela, sashay away.
And tonight...
today, I'm gonna
give you a chance
to street walk
a mile in my shoes.
Wigs will fly.
- You stuck me with these
fuckin' bitches.
- And heads will turn.
- I think we might be
in trouble.
- Help me.
- With extra special
guest judges
Kim Coles and Dita Von Teese.
- [cheering]
- The winner of Rupaul's
Drag Race will receive
a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics
and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com,
an exclusive one-year
PR contract
with the leading LGBT firm
Project Publicity,
be featured
LA Eyeworks' legendary
designer eyewear campaign,
and headline Logo's
Drag Race tour,
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks
and a cash prize of $25,000.
And may the best woman win!
[alarm clock beeping]
- Walking into the workroom
this morning
was a little weird 'cause we
didn't have Shangela with us.
- Sahara?
- Yes, darling?
- Here's Shangela's face.
- Ohh!
What am I gonna do with it?
I'm trying to take the attitude
that it's a clean slate.
Trying not to have the weight
of what happened the other night
on my shoulders.
She's gone,
so we won't need this anymore.
This is now my station, guys.
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl!
You got shemail.
Good morning, racers.
It's RuPaul here with your
drag-u-weather forecast.
- All right.
- This week, we can expect
a high-pressure system,
followed by storms of,
"Hell no!"
"Oh, no, she di'n't,"
and, "What you call me, bitch?"
but before this week is over,
I guarantee with 100% accuracy
somebody in here
is gonna make it rain.
All right?
Okay?
- Make it rain.
- Rain?
- Hey, girls.
[cheers and applause]
Now, today I'm gonna
give you a chance
to street walk
a mile in my shoes.
Oh, dear!
Today's mini-challenge
is a makeover,
where you'll be turning
a lady into a tramp.
The lady in question is me.
[gasps and laughter]
Or, as I like to say, mini-Ru.
[laughter and applause]
Now, as you girls see, there are
only six supermodel dolls,
so you'll be working in pairs.
And there's
an odd number of you,
which means one person
will be working alone.
Now take a moment
to choose a partner.
- We'll do it together.
- The Atlanta girls
are working together?
- Let's do it?
- Hell, yeah.
- Raven and Morgan?
- New York!
- New York?
Okay, yeah.
Tyra and Jujubee.
Jessica and Tatianna.
- I'm alone.
- Mystique works alone.
- Always.
- Ladies, you'll have
30 minutes for your makeover.
Feel free to use the materials
we've provided.
Now, when I return,
I want to see
these little ladies turned
into six bad girls
that work hard for the money,
if you know what I mean.
Are you ready?
Set...
go.
- My number one goal was to grab
the whole plate of fabric.
- Tyra and I ended up
with most of the stuff.
- We had got what we wanted,
and then let everyone
get our sloppy seconds.
- We did not get left nothing.
I got, like,
one handful of scraps.
Oh, my God!
- 30 minutes, bitch.
- Okay.
- I think her heel
should be broken.
- [laughs] Definitely, yeah.
- What about these boots?
- I think she needs
hooker heels.
- But I seen hookers
out there with boots on.
- I love working with Tyra,
but sometimes he just kind of
wants to do
what Tyra wants to do.
- The purse should
match the shoes.
- No, it shouldn't match
the shoes, diva.
- These are not heels.
These are rhinestones.
- She's tucked real good.
[laughing]
I think what I'm gonna
miss most being here
and not in Atlanta is
the fact that I won't be able
to spend day-to-day time
with my son, Lucas,
who's 3 1/2, and I miss him.
We play every day.
- Hello, dolly.
- Uh-oh!
- Wow! [laughs]
- Where's the glitter?
Where's the glitter?
- You use all my glitter.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- You tramp.
- Work.
- Glue these shoes on.
- Okay, ladies, time's up.
It is time to reveal
your makeovers.
- I got Shaquanda here.
- Uh-huh.
I call her
a broke-down stripper.
When she want to be naughty,
all you got to do
is turn her around,
she's ready for access.
- Hey!
- With her nice little
rose tattoo.
- Tatianna and Jessica.
- This is both of us.
She's got my eyes, but her lips.
- What is this doll's name?
- Wild Whore.
- [laughing]
- Pandora and Sahara.
- Our girl is called
Shafreeforal.
She's had a little bit
of a rough night.
She has lost her shoe.
[RuPaul laughing]
- Her other heel is broken,
but she still has
the heel in her hand.
She hasn't lost it.
- It's her good shoe.
- Yes.
- Sonique
and Nicole Paige Brooks.
- Well, you said
it could be a bad girl,
so the baddest bitch we know
is my drag mother
Shawna Brooks,
so she's styled after her.
- Wow, look at that.
- Yes, with the matching boots,
and always one titty out.
- Tyra and Jujubee.
- This is Cherry.
- Oh, Cherry.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Oh, wow.
- And she has one tooth missin'.
- That's okay, girl.
Is that a skirt?
- Um, it's a skort.
- Look, she is dealin'
crack back here.
- More hair to comb,
more cheeks to powder.
That's all it is.
- That's right.
That's what we tell her.
- Morgan and Raven?
- This is Lady Mayhem
from the House of Chaos.
- Gorgeous,
look how cute that is.
- Just a little, tiny thong
with a nice sequined strap.
- All right, ladies,
that was quite the show.
The winning team is...
Pandora Boxx
and Sahara Davenport.
[applause]
Miss Shafreeforal.
- Shafreeforal won!
- Congratulations, girls.
Now, this week's
main stage challenge
is inspired by my feature film
Starrbooty,
where I play
an undercover hustler.
Word, holla, hey!
And a diva is a female version
of a hustler.
This is your chance to unleash
your inner pussycat doll
and to show us that you can use
your brains and your beauty
to make it rain.
In two teams,
you'll be competing
as burlesque dancers.
You'll be judged on your ability
to work as an individual
and in a group.
Pandora, Sahara, since you won
the mini-challenge,
you are team captains.
Pandora, who do you pick first?
- Uh, Morgan.
- Ooh, yay.
- Sahara?
- Jessica.
- Jessica!
- Sonique.
- Jujubee.
- Raven.
- They was going after the girls
who are skinny
and go out there naked.
I'm not all, "Oh, my God,
they didn't pick me,"
cry, cry, cry.
No, it's not my personality.
This ain't high school.
- Tyra.
- Tyra?
- I wanted to be
in Pandora's group.
She had all the tall,
skinny, pretty bitches.
- Tatianna.
- Tatianna!
[applause]
Sahara, your choice.
- We're gonna go with Mystique.
- It's all about the titties.
- And that leaves
Nicole Paige Brooks.
- Save the best for last.
I was picked last, which I was
really surprised about,
to be honest.
- Nicole was left last
because this is a sexy contest,
and she's not sexy.
- In a moment, you'll meet
two top burlesque performers.
They're gonna give you
a crash course
in pole dancing,
with poles provided
by Platinum Stages,
plus each team
will be responsible
for styling
your burlesque outfits,
using materials courtesy of
Michael Levine Fabrics.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman...
win!
- We're gonna go with one print
'cause they don't match.
- I know they don't speak,
but it fits.
A girl in this on stage,
a girl in this, a girl in this,
a girl in this, and then another
girl in that,
and then that'll go fine.
You get what I'm sayin'?
- I don't like that.
I want us all to be in the same.
We're gonna all be in the same.
- Guys, we really need
to work as a team,
'cause I'm gonna
get frustrated.
Tyra's being difficult.
"I want this, I want this,"
it's all about her.
- Can I say something,
team captain?
- Sure. What is it, darling?
- This red fabric
that you chose?
- Uh-huh?
- It's shitty.
Like, really shitty.
- Tyra!
- Do you guys need a extra
person in your group?
- We're tired of all
your bitching out there.
- Pandora?
- Yeah?
- Do you not like me?
You didn't choose me
to be in your group.
I was hoping and praying
that you would choose me.
- I'm sorry.
- Now, look, you stuck me
with these fucking bitches.
- Oh, my God, I am in a group
with, like, Satan's baby.
- Our challenge
is to create a burlesque act.
We're getting
pole-dancing lessons.
- Today, we're going to be
teaching you a few basic tricks.
- Oh, Lord.
[laughing]
Here we go.
- Gorgeous.
[applause]
There was a lot of vagina
in my face. [laughs]
I was like...
- Ladies, this is dropping it
like it's hot.
- Oh, my God!
- How do expect me to do that?
It doesn't move on me.
- Well, so who wants
to get started?
Any volunteers?
- La-la-la-la-la!
I'm a flexible bitch
that can drop it like it's hot.
We gonna get on the pole
and do a upside down butterfly,
just have fun with it.
- Oh, yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Ohh!
- Wow!
- Very good.
- Whoo!
- Wow!
[applause]
- [laughs]
That ain't sexy.
I want to try that again.
Your titties
are distracting me.
- I'm sorry. They--
that's what they're there for.
- Nicole is really sexy
and really sexual,
so I'm not really worried
about being, you know,
a tease,
'cause it's kind of what I do.
- Release and spin.
Much better!
Very good.
See?
That was awesome.
- Nicole cannot bring sexy back.
- Anybody else?
Come on, girl.
- Tyra, go.
- I can't.
- Oh, Tyra, go.
- I cannot do that.
- You have to do something.
- The way that I learn
is by watching others do it.
I'm not going to get up there
and just use
someone else's ideas.
- I'm the group leader,
and we all know
that the group leader's
the first one to go down,
so I am just hoping and praying
that everyone pulls through,
especially Miss Tyra.
Now how you guys feel
about the dancing?
Are y'all gonna be
okay with that?
- I feel like a whore slut.
- Is that a bad thing?
- Yes, that's a bad thing.
- But you're a bad girl,
remember?
- But I'm a bad girl,
I'm not a bad slut.
I feel that pole dancing, um,
it's kind of a little ho'-ish.
- I think we should just be
very positive about it,
and then it'll all come
together.
- It's fine,
as long as everyone cooperates.
There's no "I" in "team,"
after all, right?
- But there's a "me," girl.
- So far, I'm not quite clickin'
with the choreography,
just 'cause I want someone
to really, like,
slow it down for me so I get it.
- Pandora's just kind of
standing off to the side.
She's not really doing much,
so I tell Morgan,
"Girl, you should
choreograph this."
- I'm not trying to be bitchy,
but if you want, like,
choreography done,
like, let us do it.
There was a lot
of confusion going on,
and the time was
running out.
- I'm not reading you, by any
means, but you know what I mean?
Like, it's so confusing.
- Yeah, I mean, I'm just trying
to set it up at the beginning,
that's it.
- I went into shut-down mode
for a little bit,
because everybody
was just talking,
and it was very frustrating
and irritating.
I was like, "Oh, Christ."
- The two weakest people
should be in the back.
- Yeah.
- That's just an opinion.
- Okay, well,
let's just practice this,
and then as we figure out
who the weakest is
we'll move 'em around.
- Okay, let's try this.
Ready?
- I could be a bigger bitch.
- So can I, girl.
Miss Tyra decides that she
can't rehearse in heels.
- Are you gonna have me
rehearse like this?
You're gonna have me complainin'
about my feet hurtin'.
I know how my body works.
- Five, six, seven, eight...
- I'm just sitting back.
I'm puttin' everything
together in my head.
I'm sayin', okay, girl,
do this and do that.
Like if they asked me now,
"Girl, do the routine,"
I would do it,
and I'd do it better
than what they did in there.
- We need to pick a color
that's gonna work.
- Well, if they're
not using this,
I think we should use this.
It's the most colorful,
and it's just sitting here.
- Do we need
to find out for sure
if they're not using that?
- No.
- No, they said they're done.
- 'Cause they're doing
that right there.
- This'll be hot.
- I think this is gonna pop
with black, I really do.
- Hey, that's our fabric.
She just took all our fabric.
- Because it's our fabric,
honey.
- I could have swore
you guys said
you were done with your fabric.
- No, we had all our fabric
over here that we were using.
Sorry you misunderstood.
- No, there was
no misunderstanding.
I have ears,
and they hear very well.
- No one's here to share.
We're not here to help.
We're not even here
to be friends.
- Did you need this fabric?
Well, do you need it,
or do you not need it?
- Hey.
- You owe me one.
- Thank you, darling.
- Cute, by the way.
I love them.
- Are you tryin' to be
fierce to me, Miss Tati?
- No!
I think they're cute.
- Just makin' sure, girl.
Just makin' sure.
- You think a lot, don't you?
But you think wrong
all the time.
- I do.
- You should think harder.
Thank you.
- Hi.
Hello, hello, hello.
Wow, look at this.
How's it going so far?
- I think it's going good.
- And do you feel like
you're really the leader?
- Um, I didn't
at a certain point, no.
I think that there's just
a lot of strong personalities.
- Really? Here?
- Just a few.
- Among drag queens?
- Do you feel as though
you've been an effective leader
for your team?
- Most definitely.
I think the end result
will show that as well.
- So you're okay that
one of your team members
is over there sleeping?
Are you worried?
- I am worried.
I am worried.
- Mm-hmm.
- What am I to do?
- Well, it's, you know,
hard out there for a pimp.
- Don't wake her up.
She'll scream.
- Tyra, sweetie.
Darling?
Sweetie pie.
- Tired.
- You're tired?
- Yeah.
- Why you so tired?
- I don't know.
When Ru woke me up,
I'm like, "Shit!"
- Now, why do you think
everybody else is so busy,
but you have time to nap?
- Um, they're hot-gluing.
- Uh-huh.
- And I sewed, and it took me,
like, five minutes
to make my costume.
- You know,
you will be judged on
not only your individual,
but how well you work
with the group.
- I'm good.
I'm perfectly fine.
I don't have any doubt.
- All right, get back to bed.
All right, girls,
one last thing before I go.
Now, I'm gonna take you all
on a little field trip tomorrow
to Dragonfly.
It's a hot Hollywood club,
where you'll be performing
your main challenge
in front of an audience
of 100% grade "A" men.
Beef, honey. Beef.
Now, I want you to make sure
to bring your charisma,
uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
Bye, y'all.
See ya.
[applause]
- I'm excited to get out
and it be a room full of men.
I can't fucking wait.
- Hey, girls,
welcome to Dragonfly.
This week,
Santino, Merle, and I
are joined by our
special guest judges,
one of my favorite funny ladies,
Kim Coles is here.
[applause]
And our extra
special guest judge,
the queen of burlesque,
Dita Von Teese.
[cheers and applause]
Now, in a moment, the team
that makes the most money
will be safe
from elimination this week,
and the girl on that team
who earns the most
will be the winner,
but first, what would
Rupaul's Drag Race be
without a little twist?
Today, you'll have two ways
to earn those dollars, honey.
While one team is working on
this stage,
the other will be
selling it on the street.
You hear that, Tyra?
Not you.
I'm talkin' about Tyra Banks.
[laughter]
- I hate goin' out the door
in drag in the daytime.
- And by "it," I mean cherry pie
gift certificates.
Cherry pie
gift certificates, sir,
courtesy of Cafe Audrey.
And one more thing.
Don't fuck it up.
- We have 60 minutes to sell
some cherry pie
gift certificates.
Help me out, buy some pie.
Team strategy is to get
out there and sell, sell, sell.
- Hi, would you like
to buy a cherry pie?
- Please, please,
don't make me beg.
- Please!
I need money!
- Does anybody want cherry pie
gift certificates, $5.
I don't know how
to approach people.
No?
Do you understand me?
Can you hear--
am I here?
Anybody?
Bueller?
- Buy the pie, baby.
Buy the pie. Please buy the pie.
- I think we might be
in trouble.
- Please help me.
- We're confident.
We're the pretty girls.
We're gonna sell sex, and isn't
that the name of the game?
- Nicole was having difficulty
with the choreography.
Big and messy
is not gonna cut it.
[cheers and applause]
[applause]
- I made a lot of money.
It rained on me a few times,
and I like to be wet.
- While I'm on stage,
I'm so incredibly nervous.
My heart is going
"Whum, whum, whum."
I feel like my boob's
gonna pop right out.
[cheers and applause]
- And as you pick up
crumpled money,
it looks like a lot more
than it is.
I realize it didn't rain.
It was enough to buy
a nice dinner
at the sizzler or something.
- Cherry pie.
all: Cherry pie!
Cherry pie!
- Oh!
Also I can do that for you.
- I got a dollar.
- Thank you, yay!
- Here's one dollar.
- Thank you.
- Thanks a lot.
Thanks.
- Ooh.
Watch your--
think soprano, though,
when you talk, girl.
- Hi, would you like to buy
a slice of cherry pie?
We got cherry pie
gift certificates!
- Tyra's surprising me,
actually.
I'm like, wow,
she actually has a personality?
- Hi. Would you like to buy
a slice of cherry pie?
- $5--
thank you, sir.
- You're welcome, okay.
- I looked like a $2 whore.
My grandmother's gonna kill me.
What you want?
- Let me see you guys
do a dance for this $20.
- Okay.
- I see her from the corner
with a $20 bill,
and I'm like, "Wait!
That's mine."
- Oh, yes!
- Miss Sahara, you stealin'
this sale from me, girl?
- The audience really
kind of got into it.
[cheers]
- They were all loving it,
eating out of
the palm of my hand.
I felt kind of like
I might have been
the skankiest on stage.
- I'm a nervous wreck
being in front of Dita.
She's the epitome of burlesque,
and there she is,
lookin' at you, you
know, judgin' you.
- We went out onto
Hollywood Boulevard,
and we're trying to sell
these gift certificates,
and there's Christians
and children and--oh.
I'm not cut out for this.
- You know you want
a taste of cherry pie.
- Nicole was loud.
- I'm serious, it's right there.
You're almost at Audrey's.
You know you want the pie.
- Raven, I always just kind of
saw her standing like a statue.
- You guys want to buy
cherry pie.
I can tell you love cherry pie.
- Sonique is rude.
- How much money do you have?
- Uh...
- Yes?
- Uh, well, I have some--
- You're wasting my time.
I got an hour.
- My time is expensive, too.
- All right, well,
then hit it, 'cause so is mine.
- Hey, daddy.
Nobody wants cherry pie?
- Morgan, she's like,
"Hey, daddy."
La-la-la-la.
- We like pie.
Do you like pie?
- Cherry.
- Cherry pie.
- I don't like
to carry myself like that.
I'm sweet in the streets
and, you know,
a freak in the sheets.
- Cherry...
pie.
- I look over at the judges,
and Dita Von Teese
was smiling, honey.
You can't crack her.
She sits there with this just
straight face, just beauty.
- All of our arguing
and bitching
and nagging at each other,
like, finally paid off.
- I feel excited.
I'm going to work that crowd.
- Whoo!
- Ow!
- I think I did a great job,
because I have a lot of money.
- Yeah!
- My strategy for my solo
is just to wow the crowd.
[cheers]
- Sellin' cherry pie.
Come and get it.
- Hello.
I love your hat.
- [pretending to cry]
Please, somebody buy cherry pie.
They just were running, running.
- You guys like cherry pie?
- He's running.
He's running from somebody.
They're like,
"Aah! It's a t-girl!
It's a t-girl!"
- Because I can't dance,
I figured I'd be sexual
and playful.
Every girl needs lip gloss,
right?
[cheers and applause]
- I'm thinking, do whatever it
takes to get your money.
[cheers]
[kicks stage]
- My strategy is to demand money
from the men.
- I hope it pays off.
- Ow!
- [sighs]
Are you tired?
- Very much so.
- Elimination day is today.
Everyone's on pins and needles
because no one knows
how to measure
the other team's work,
so we're just anxious
to see who's on the bottom.
- Somebody stole
my mommy's picture.
I walk in the room,
and, you know,
first thing I'm thinkin' is,
got to say hello to Shawna,
my drag mother,
and she's not on the wall.
I've been robbed!
If anybody sees a 8x10
of Shawna Brooks,
maybe it got set
on their station by accident,
'cause it was on this wall
yesterday and now it's gone.
Being away from my family
was more than
I thought it was, you know?
I have a 2 1/2-year-old, Lucas.
He's at home,
and I miss him the most.
- Are y'all gonna
let him watch the show?
- When he's, like,
four or five maybe.
Hopefully, there'll be
an appropriate one to show him.
I'm just hopin'
that he's proud of his life.
Gonna be able to show him
I am at the top of my game.
He should be proud of what
his daddy does for a living.
He's gonna be able to say,
"My daddy's a drag superstar."
[laughs] You know?
- You guys still have
all your fathers, yeah?
- My father has cancer
right now, so...
- Oh! Mine--
mine passed away of cancer.
He had lung cancer.
- I don't really know--
I mean, we don't know
how long he has.
My father was just diagnosed
with cancer.
He's, you know, on chemo
and going through all of that.
- My father was always
just really upset about it,
because he knew
he was gonna die,
and he didn't know how we were
gonna take care of ourselves.
- So sad.
- Yeah, I mean, it is,
but just this, Pandora.
Just tell him you love him.
That's all.
I don't want to talk
about this anymore.
- I don't, either.
I gotta put makeup on,
and I don't want it to smudge.
- Yeah, okay.
-There's a lot
of mixed emotions.
There's a lot of feelings
going on around the room.
People are wondering
which group's gonna be
up on the chopping block,
but still,
at the same time trying to hurry
and get ready
for the main stage.
[applause]
- Well, hello, judges.
- Hello.
- Hey, Ru.
- Have you recovered
from yesterday?
- That was insane.
- Oh!
- I thought it was fantastic.
- I enjoyed it very much.
- I wish my whole life
could be that.
- You wish your--
- I do. I do.
- Now, this week, the girls
were split into two teams
of burlesque dancers to see
who could earn the most dollars
dancing for tips and hustling
with cherry pie gift
certificates.
Tonight, I've asked them
to come decked out
in their high-class drag.
Are you ready, judges?
- Yes.
- Ready.
- Gentlemen...
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Sonique-a-nique-a-nique-a.
Oh, she's making a Sonique boom.
[laughter]
- With the lights goin'
and the music goin',
it was perfect,
so I hope they think I did good,
because I felt like
I did pretty good.
- Yes, ma'am, sell the garment.
Oh, my, this dress is wicked.
Are you a good witch
or are you a bad witch?
- When I head up my runway
and I feel like a diva.
- Almost looks like
toilet paper cozy.
[laughter]
In a couture sort of
toilet paper cozy kind of way.
- [gasps]
Wow, dark lady.
- She will take your man, honey.
- Yes, she will.
- I wanted to do something
simple that I could dress up.
I know I look fierce.
- I'm callin' that Cher 2010.
- Yes.
- Sahara, oh!
Stop in the name of love.
- [laughing]
- I feel great.
I'm sparkling,
the judges are smiling.
- Bob Mackie would be proud.
- I'm just livin', honey.
- Pandora Boxx.
- The shoes match the dress
kind of like the carpet
and the drapes.
- Yes!
- I like that dress because
it's a little bit different,
and I really thought that
it would make me stand out.
- Very L.A.
I came out to L.A.
to be an actress-slash-model.
- Actress-slash-model.
- Jujubee!
Is this a hostile takeover?
[laughter]
- I felt like Eartha Kitt.
I'm servin' fish, honey,
and this ain't trout.
- Jujubee Fabulous!
- Nicole Paige Brooks.
- She looks like Courtney Cox.
- I looked like a real girl.
I looked like a model
on the runway,
which anybody wants me to model
their dress, sign me up.
I'll be more than happy
to do it.
- Yes, mama!
- Mystique Summers Madison.
Girl, your pussy is on fire!
- Oh!
- My outfit for the runway
is a nice, simple kind of
evening gownish,
'cause I'm a gown bitch.
- That girl will eat Beyonc
in one swallow.
- [laughing]
- And she is telling you,
"I'm not going!"
- Send me Morgan McMichaels
from the secretarial pool.
- I didn't want to wear a gown.
That's boring to me when
everybody else is doing it.
- Oh, executive realness.
- [laughs]
Executive realness.
- Oh, my sweet gherkins!
There's a new Tyra in town.
Tyra Sanchez, the other Tyra.
- I know I looked good today,
because it was elegant,
it was over the top,
and it was still drag.
It gave you everything
you needed.
- I love the nappy pompadour.
- Yes, mama.
Tatianna Von Furstberg
Zeta-Jones!
- [laughing]
- She's giving Galliano
realness, yes.
- The look I'm going for
is Rihanna going to prom,
so I did the little
Rihanna bob with it.
I'm feeling pretty confident.
- Very real.
Ladies, it's time to reveal
which team made the most money
and is safe from elimination.
And the winning team is...
Sahara Davenport's team.
[applause]
Congratulations.
You're all safe.
The winner of this challenge
is...
Sahara Davenport.
[applause]
In addition to immunity
next week,
you've won a $1,500
gift certificate
from sequinqueen.Com.
Thank you, ladies.
Now you may leave the stage.
[applause]
Pandora Boxx, your team is up
for elimination.
What went wrong?
- I think maybe we just
didn't work the crowd enough
or something.
Now, let's talk about
your presentation
on the main stage today.
- I'm not loving
the overall look.
Visually, though, I thought
maybe you could have
pulled the parts together
a little better.
- This dress is not my favorite,
either.
I'm not a fan of the bands.
It kind of looked--
at first, I thought,
what was it, duct tape?
[Santino laughing]
- Thank you, Pandora.
- Thank you.
- Sonique, now, you really
made it rain on the stage,
but you came off
a little bit rude
on the street.
- My time is expensive, too.
- All right, well, then hit it.
- I was rude to, like,
one or two people,
but, I'm sorry,
it was hot out there.
I was in a hurry.
I was trying to raise
as much money as I could.
It was a challenge. You would
do the same thing, right?
- I do sassy,
I don't do bitchy.
Nicole Paige Brooks.
Now what are you serving
on the main stage?
- This was actually just
a backup that I brought,
because the first gown I had
technical difficulties with.
- I thought, more than anyone
when she walked out,
I was like, "Whoa! Is that
a real girl over there?"
And I like your little Megan Fox
tongue thing that you did,
but don't do it too much
like she does,
or else it loses effect.
- You could have looked like
a young Janice Dickenson,
but it came off
kind of like a drunken
Janice Dickenson at times.
- Ha-ha!
Our next lady is Tatianna,
a vision in purple.
How do you feel your hustler
game came through
on the challenge yesterday?
- I think it worked pretty well.
- One thing I really noticed was
one of the guys
asked your name
when you were done.
Nobody asked
anybody else's name.
They were fallin' in love
out there.
I called you Kim Kardashian
on steroids.
- Ooh, yeah.
- But in a good way.
- Yeah.
- In a good way.
Kim wished she looked that good.
- Raven, doin' the solo.
You didn't make
a lot of money there.
- No, I didn't.
When I started seeing
the other girls come back,
I thought, "Fuck,
I fucked this up."
- What would you
have done differently,
knowing how it went?
- I wouldn't have moved as much.
I would have gone
to the edge of the stage,
laid out, and let them
just throw the paper on me.
- Lady ATM.
[Santino laughing]
- You're very femme fatale.
I was a little bit scared.
I would not leave my man
in a room alone with you.
- Don't do it.
I'll work it.
[laughter]
- Morgan McMichaels.
- Yes.
- You have immunity.
- Yes, ma'am.
- You know, in a minute,
I'm gonna have to send
someone home.
Who should it be and why?
- The weakest person in the
group, you know, is Tatianna.
- Tatianna, who do you
think should go home today?
- I'm just gonna go with Morgan,
because she has immunity.
- Tatianna, that's an answer
for the Miss America contest,
not the Rupaul Drag Race
contest.
Nicole, same question.
- Send 'em all home.
- Send all these bitches home?
- Ooh!
- Okay.
Send all these bitches home.
- I mean, they eventually
all have to go,
so, I mean, I don't want
to be the one who goes,
so send 'em all.
- Raven, who would you
send home tonight?
- I would say Tatianna.
I don't think she wants to be,
like, a grand, superstar diva.
I think she's comfortable
being a beautiful girl.
- No.
- [laughing]
- Not the case.
If I was comfortable
being a beautiful girl,
I was a beautiful girl at home.
That's not why I'm here,
to be, like, pretty.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Just my opinion.
- All right.
Pandora, who should
I send home tonight?
- I think that the ho that made
the least amount of money
should go home.
But I don't know who that is.
[laughter]
Ladies, while you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
Thank you.
[engine starts]
This is the hardest part.
They're all fabulous kids,
but one of them has to go home.
Nicole Paige Brooks brought in
the least amount of dollars,
and Raven was second to last.
Raven seemed like she was
out of her element.
- The performance wasn't
my favorite performance,
but I think today she was
really exciting to watch.
- Had I not talked to her,
she was gonna be my bottom two,
but I like that sense of humor,
I like that little edge.
I'm not ready to see her go yet.
- Right. Now, Tatianna.
She's green.
- When I saw her dancing, I was
like, "She's the prettiest one."
- Do we give her the opportunity
to blossom on this show,
or do we say, "Look, honey,
you got to come prepared."
- She's gorgeous, however,
she didn't know how to make
her disadvantages
her advantages,
and everybody else here does
seem to know how to do that.
- Let's move on to Sonique.
- I definitely sort of sensed
a little, you know,
sort of feminine sweet like,
"I know I was kind of bitchy
to people on the street, but I
won't ever do it again, 'kay?"
- [laughing]
- Pandora was actually one of
the team's top money earners.
- She didn't stand out for me.
- I know you didn't like
her outfit.
- I hated that outfit.
- I equated it to, like, she
just got off the Greyhound bus.
Maybe that worked
to her advantage.
Maybe people like to see that
kind of starving, hungry look.
You know, maybe that's why
she made so much money.
I don't know.
- So she may not give
kind of great ass,
but she gives great sass.
- Yes.
- I just like her
sassy attitude.
- Nicole Paige Brooks.
She got a little lost
in the crowd. Do you agree?
- I do agree.
[imitating steady tone beeping]
That's death
in this competition.
- I kind of like the highs
and the lows.
The kind of bipolar.
To me, that makes life richer.
- Sure.
- And I'm just getting Prozac.
- Silence!
Bring back the girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your Starrbooty-licious
challenge
and tonight's presentation
on the main stage,
I have made some decisions.
Morgan McMichaels,
you have immunity this week.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Sonique, on stage, the crowd
was turned on by your body,
but on the street, people were
turned off by your mouth.
No one wants a cherry pie
that bites back.
You're safe.
Nicole Paige Brooks,
you brought in
the least amount of money.
I'm sorry, my dear,
you're up for elimination.
- I was surprised I was
the lowest earner of tips.
I really thought that my
exuberance on the street
would have pulled me
out of the bottom.
- Pandora Boxx, you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Raven, you were the second
lowest earner,
and in a moment, you'll have
a chance to prove yourself.
You're up for elimination.
- When she told me
I was up for elimination,
my knees locked,
my head got dizzy.
I literally thought
I was gonna pass out.
- Tatianna,
sharpen your claws, baby.
It's a jungle out there.
You're safe.
Two queens stand before me.
I've consulted with the judges,
but the final decision
is mine to make.
This is your last chance
to impress me
and to save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lip sync
for your life.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
- And now,
it's time for a breakdown.
[laughter]
- Oh, yes!
[cheers and applause]
- I've made my decision.
Raven...
you will live to fly
another day.
Shante, you stay.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Nicole Paige Brooks,
you are a fabulous queen.
I send you home to carry on
the fine tradition
of the Atlanta queens
who have come before you.
Now, Sashay...
away.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
The fact that I even
walked through these doors
is overwhelming to me,
and definitely didn't think
I'd be leaving this soon.
I'm ready to go home
and see my baby.
- Ladies,
you know competition is hard.
Ain't no half-steppin', mama.
You have to bring it.
That's what we're here for.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen?
all: Amen.
- All right.
Let the music play!