- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
This week you'll be doing your
best celebrity impersonations.
- I do a really good Pink.
Rock and roll, baby.
- I like playing
hide the cucumber.
- [laughs]
- The only thing Beyoncé's done
funny is fall.
- I almost just jumped
out this chair at your ass.
- Tatianna, congratulations,
you're the winner
of this challenge.
- Thank you so much.
- Morgan, Sonique,
you're up for elimination.
- ♪ Two of hearts ♪
♪ Two hearts that beat as one ♪
- Your lip-synch was one of
the tightest we've ever seen.
Sonique, sashay away.
And tonight...
I expect a "dragstravaganza."
The dolls go
from blushing brides...
- I'm getting married, y'all.
- To dragzillas.
[record scratches]
- Tyra's a complete bitch.
- Shut the fuck up,
or I'll make you shut up.
- Oh!
- With extra-special
guest judges
fashion photographer
Mathu Andersen
and club diva Martha Wash.
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX Cosmetics
and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com,
an exclusive
one-year P.R. contract
with the leading LGBT firm
Project Publicity,
be featured in L.A. Eyeworks'
legendary designer eyewear
campaign,
and headline Logo's
Drag Race Tour
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks,
and a cash prize of $25,000.
And may the best woman win!
[alarm beeps]
- Meow.
Oh, Sonique.
- Sonique was one of the new
friends that I really enjoyed.
It was tough
going up against her.
But at the end of the day,
this is a competition,
and I'm out for blood.
- Who's gonna take it off?
- I will.
- Oh.
- It'll be satisfying.
I am happy that Sonique's gone.
She just always had
a negative comment.
- So do it.
Clean my mirror.
[laughter]
- I won, and she got sent home.
So I really just wanted
to take in the moment
and feel satisfied
wiping her message away.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- You should be proud
of yourself.
- A lot of people
don't believe in Tatianna,
and she proved to everybody
that you don't know anything
here.
[alarm sounds]
- Ooh, girl!
You got shemail.
Hey, dolls, to prove to me
that you're the next
drag superstar,
you're gonna need to make
a real commitment--
one that could last a lifetime,
or at least until the next
best thing comes along.
Pull yourself together
and you could
have your cake and eat it too.
'cause when it comes
to RuPaul's Drag Race,
honey, we've only just begun.
Ohh!
Hello, hello, hello.
- Hello.
all: Hi!
- Congratulations
for making it this far.
It's getting fierce up in here.
For today's mini-challenge,
we're gonna have ourselves
a little wrap party.
Now, each week
on the main stage,
you turn out one dazzling outfit
after another.
I want you to apply that same
creative genius
to these plain white boxes.
To "queenify" your box,
you need to use
the gift wrap we've provided
plus pieces from your own drag
wardrobe
and something that belongs to
one of your fellow queens.
You have 30 minutes
to complete this challenge.
And when I return, I'll decide
who has the prettiest box.
I'll see you in a few, okay.
- Juju?
- Yes, honey?
- Can I borrow your bird?
- Yeah.
I decide that I want this box
to just be a golden box.
Tyra looks over and she makes
a little comment and she's like,
"Oh, she's using the same
wrapping paper."
- The other queens
are copying my style
because the critique I get from
the judges is usually good.
Maybe I'm inspiring them.
Like, maybe they want to
be like me.
- Hey, Juju, think I could use
a piece of your jewelry?
- Go ahead, baby.
- Thank you.
- Can I borrow
some of your glitter?
- Go ahead, girl.
- Don't sprinkle
all my glitter around
like you did with the shoe,
though.
- All right, ladies.
Time's up.
Ladies, I'm here
to inspect your boxes.
Can I hold your box?
The card on it says, "To Ru,
from America's sweetheart,
Tyra."
I love it.
- I chose the pink
because offstage
I'm a little more delicate,
a little feminine.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Yeah, girl.
- Wow, there's a lot going on
here, Morgan.
- Yes, there is.
It's, you know, loud and fuzzy
and furry and colorful.
- Edgar Allan Poe
would be so proud of you.
- It's dark and sparkly
like RuPaul.
- [laughing]
Pandora Boxx.
- I like the pink and the blue.
It kind of says, "He?
Her?
I don't know what she is."
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Jessica Wild.
- Yes.
- Ooh, she's got a hot package,
all right.
So who is this a picture of?
- This is Gladys, my mom.
- Oh, really?
Oh, this is your mother?
- Yes, she is my gift
and my heart at the same time.
- Did you borrow something
from someone else?
- I took her scent,
and I sprayed the box.
- So you have the only
scented box?
- Of course.
- Oh.
- The colors are signature Tati.
I borrowed a stone from Juju.
Thank you.
And it has different dimensions
'cause there's different sides
to me.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- All right.
All right, ladies,
I've inspected your boxes.
But I need to pick just one.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Caw-caw, caw-caw.
- What?
- Caw-caw.
- Who?
- This box is dark-sided.
[laughter]
I choose this one.
I want this one.
I'm going to embrace
my dark side, Raven.
Raven, you are the winner
of this challenge.
And now for the good part.
You may open your boxes.
Go ahead, open them up.
So far I've asked you to wrap
your boxes
using something old,
something new,
something borrowed,
and now this envelope.
Something blue.
- "RuPaul cordially invites you
to the wedding
of David and Raven.
Ceremony to take place tomorrow,
main stage."
- That's right, you are invited
to your very own wedding.
Yes, my dears, you'll be both
the bride and the groom.
In addition to customizing your
own fabulous,
dragged-out wedding dress,
you will pull together
your best male drag
using tuxedos provided
by Selix Formalwear.
Later, you'll pose
for a wedding portrait
courtesy of Polite in Public,
which we'll show
on the main stage.
And here come
the wedding dresses.
Wow, look at that.
So, Raven, since you won the
mini-challenge,
you get first dibs
from all these wonderful
wedding dresses,
courtesy of RK Bridal.
Plus you get to choose the order
that the other girls
choose their dresses.
- Remember who helped you win,
baby.
- Remember that Raven hat,
darling.
So ♪ go, Raven ♪
♪ Go, Raven ♪
♪ Pick a gown out ♪
♪ Pick a dress out ♪
♪ It's your wedding ♪
Have you been married before?
- Never.
- Are you sure
that's the one you want?
Okay, who gets to choose next?
- I'm thinking it's me.
'Cause I'm like, girl,
I helped this bitch win. Mm.
- I'm gonna go with Morgan.
- All right.
- I'm sure everyone knew,
she's gonna pick Morgan first.
And I did.
So what?
Get over it.
Boo-hoo.
- I'm like, girl, that was
a mistake on your part.
- All right, Raven,
who goes next?
- Juju.
- Oh, my god, I'm so excited.
- [laughing]
- I'm getting married, y'all.
- Sahara.
Mrs. Wild.
- All these names
were being called.
I'm like, I'm gonna be last.
Obviously, I'm gonna be last.
Raven is jealous of anyone
that has talent.
- Ms. Sanchez.
- Ha ha!
- I like a challenge,
so I'm gonna go with
the ugly one.
- Pandy bear.
- And that leaves Tatianna.
Ladies, do you promise to have
charisma, uniqueness, nerve,
and talent
till death do you part?
all: I do.
- Then so be it.
I expect a "dragstravaganza."
Help yourself
to the fixin's bar.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
[shrieks] Oh, dear!
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- Tyra pushes
the wedding dress cart
in front of the fabric cart.
- Dear!
- Girl, you are so damn shady.
- Ah.
- Tyra pushed the rolling rack
in front of
the rest of the girls.
So Tatianna
pushed the rolling rack
on top of the girls.
- Ow.
- Miss honey,
that's dangerous, darling.
- Cutthroat queens.
Not so cute.
- Get out of my mirror, bitch.
- Sorry.
- The challenge basically is
marrying yourself--
bringing the feminine
and the masculine qualities
together
to make one amazing wedding.
- Tatianna?
- Yeah?
- You were chosen last.
I don't think it was personal,
though.
I should have been chosen first,
- First?
- 'Cause I helped her win that
fucking challenge,
don't you think?
- In all honesty, yeah.
- But it's okay.
No hard feelings, diva.
It's all right. It's all right.
Every time Raven
gets to choose something
and every time Morgan gets to
choose something,
it's, "I pick Raven.
I pick Morgan."
Like, I'm surprised we don't
have a name for them yet.
Rorgan.
Maven.
Hey, Morvens.
- Is it corseted in?
- Douche bags.
- [belches]
Our wedding day.
- I think that the competition
is threatened by us.
I'm sure that
they're looking at us like,
"These bitches
might do a thing or two."
- Raven and I
are helping each other,
but we're still
gunning for the same prize
and we'll do whatever it takes
to win it.
- It's so funny no one
chose the dress that I wanted.
- Which dress?
- The one I got.
I got the ugliest dress,
and my first thing I did
was to go and cut it,
make it shorter.
And then less than,
like, 30 minutes later,
everyone is cutting
their dresses.
Sahara's dress
looks the same way,
and then Jessica's dress
looks the same way
and Morgan dress seems to be
going the same way also.
And it's just like, "Oh, my god,
you guys, be creative.
Be your own selves.
Be unique."
- Hello, brides.
all: Hey, Ru!
- Just checking in.
Now, you know, every bride
wants to look her best
on her wedding day,
so I brought in a pro.
Makeup artist extraordinaire
Mathu Andersen.
Say hi to Mathu.
- Oh, thank you. Thank you.
- Mathu has worked on some of
the biggest divas in the world
like Beyoncé Knowles,
Janet Jackson,
and of course, me.
He's here today to give you
some valuable makeup tips.
Listen and learn, ladies.
Tyra Sanchez.
Mathu here is gonna give you
some tips.
- I don't have a lot of notes
for you.
With a face like yours--
so beautiful.
It'd be so easy to take you to
completely unclockable.
I just want it to look
a little moister.
A little dewiness
just along the highlights.
Some of the other girls do it.
- I think it's because
the other girls' face get oily.
My face doesn't get oily
in drag.
- I do have oily skin.
I'm 30 years old
and I still look fuckin' 22.
'Cause I have oily fuckin' skin.
- Hello, darling.
- Wow. Look it here.
- You know what you're doing.
You know the shapes
you're going for.
The whole thing just needs to be
finessed and smoothed out.
And it is--sometimes it gets
a little bit magic marker.
I recommend always building
all your contouring
into the base.
- This challenge
is gonna be tough,
because I have a point to prove.
That point is I don't deserve to
be in the bottom two again.
- Hey, Pandora.
- Hey.
- Wow. Look at this.
I barely recognize this.
- Yeah, you said
you didn't want "off the rack,"
so I'm going way off the rack.
- Smart girl.
- You're super cute.
I think you could be
really beautiful.
Think Goldie Hawn, really.
Like--'cause see, she has, like,
a simple eye.
Lashy, softer, bigger
and really plump,
'cause you've got great eyes.
Play with that.
- Hi, Jessica.
Wow. Look at this.
- My wedding is going to be
an extravaganza.
- I love an extravaganza.
- Sometimes your face
worries me.
This is a problem.
Your highlights are so bright
here and here and here
that it looks as though
you have stubble.
Maybe it's about
putting the dark under
and then highlighting the jaw,
and really, there needs to be
a lot more blending.
- All right.
- Hi, Sahara.
- Hi, Ru.
- So tell me about your dress.
- I'm gonna cut it up
and make it shorter
and add some volume
to the bottom.
- Now that will go underneath?
- Yes.
- And you have enough fabric
here to support that?
- Uh, yes.
- And you're gonna pad?
- And I'm gonna pad, yeah.
- You've got
a lot of work to do.
- I do. I do.
- Yeah.
- You're so young in person.
- Ooh.
- She's a little old-looking.
Looking at your face now
and it doesn't have
the closed-in thing
that Sahara gets.
This thing always scares me
and this--
- How do I fix that?
- Try a little--something
that's just a little brighter
along there.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Well, hello, Tati.
- Hello.
- Your makeup's
all over the shop.
It's all over the place,
and sometimes it's beautiful
and sometimes it's like,
"What the hell is she doing?"
But you're so beautiful,
and you don't have to be
overly draggy.
And there's girls
who have made a career
on being that beautiful.
Just depends on what kind of
girl you want to be.
But don't rest on those laurels.
- No, definitely not.
- Thank you, Tatianna.
- Thank you.
- Juju.
- Hi, Ru.
- Wow.
I see jewels for Juju.
What do you call this color?
- Tawny sunset.
I love that.
- I'd like to see Jujubee's
version of natural makeup.
I use the Mariah Carey
reference.
And I don't want it
to be natural,
but I want to believe
that it's natural.
I want supernatural.
- Okay.
- That's your challenge.
- I will do it.
- Raven.
- Hello, hello.
- You won the mini challenge,
so you got to pick
your dress first.
- Yes.
- Are you happy with it?
- Yeah, I took
the whole thing up.
I started up here by pinning it
and hand sewing.
- So let's talk makeup.
- I would like
to see you introduce
a smidgen of color
into your makeup.
I can see that it's like, "Oh,
this person really knows their
way around their face."
But you could warm this up and
same with your jawline contour.
- Okay.
- Ladies!
Mathu and I will see you
tomorrow on the main stage.
And our extra-special
guest judge
will be one of
my musical heroes...
the legendary Martha Wash.
[applause]
- I'm so excited about
Martha Wash being a guest judge.
I have listened
to her music forever,
and I love her voice.
- Don't fuck it up.
See ya.
Come on, Mathu.
- Today we're shooting
our male half of the photo,
our groom side.
And then tomorrow
we're taking the bride.
We're gonna meld them together.
I'm excited to see
how it's going to look.
- There is slight anxiousness
because I'm not
the most masculine guy.
I never grow a beard.
I don't grow a mustache.
- You know, growing up,
I would sit there on the counter
and watch my mom do her makeup.
You know, I didn't really
watch my dad shave.
I was more interested in
the lipstick and eye shadow.
- You know, doing drag on top
of being gay, you know, at 14,
it was kind of an escape.
Like, I get to be someone else.
I get to be as feminine as I
want to be and then I don't get
pointed out for it...
um, or made fun of for it,
because a lot of people, you
know, didn't know I was a boy.
So this is gonna be just
completely different.
- When I did my makeup as a guy,
I knew I was the first one
in the mirror,
and so I went ahead
and I drew the facial hair on.
Then I look over and then
Sahara's drawing on
the facial hair,
then Pandora's drawing on
the facial hair
and Tatianna comes
and draws on the facial hair.
And it was pissing me off
because this is my hard work and
you're, like, stealing my idea.
So I'm hoping I go on the stage
first tomorrow.
That way, everyone that comes
behind me will look like,
"Oh, I got that from Tyra."
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Morgan.
- My name is Joe.
Nice to meet you.
- It's a pleasure.
- So we're gonna be creating an
illusion here today.
- Story of my life.
- Just imagine that there's
another person next to you.
Look right here.
One, two, three.
Yeah, big motion.
Yeah, that's great.
- My groom is a punk rocker.
He just probably
rolled out of bed
and threw on a leather jacket
and a tie
and came to the chapel.
- One, two, three.
- I do feel comfortable having
to perform as a male, but I have
a little more confidence when
I'm in drag.
I feel a lot more glamorous,
a lot more pretty.
- There's been such a focus on
the girl, the girl, the girl,
that when it was time to be a
boy, I was so stressed that I
was like, "Oh, my god,
it's time to be a boy."
So I had to just push that aside
for a second
and consider the direction
that I want to go.
- One, two, three.
[chuckles] Excellent.
Nice.
- I am smiling in my picture
because if I have
the opportunity
of being married
with Jessica Wild,
I am going to be happy.
- Two, three.
Excellent.
Very nice.
Perfect.
Let's do one just for fun.
Two, three.
Excellent.
What inspired your choice
in outfit?
- Well, he is a police officer.
- A little smile.
- I'm really feeling
like a drag king.
Like, I'm not feeling
like a guy.
I'm feeling like I am a girl
dressing up like a guy.
- And you're gonna look
right here.
Two, three.
[chuckles] Excellent.
- How does everybody feel
about marriage?
Who's getting married?
Who's not?
- I'm not getting married.
- Why?
- 'Cause I'm a bitter bitch.
- Well, with that attitude,
girl.
- I wanna marry my husband.
- You wanna marry your husband?
[laughing]
- I call him my husband.
I am in a relationship,
I do have a boyfriend.
I would love to marry him
one day.
Gay marriage is a human right.
It's our right to be equal.
It's not a, you know, luxury
to have gay marriage.
It's a need and it's a right.
But I tell you this much,
though...
gay people not being allowed
to marry,
to me, is a kick in the ass.
- ♪ I feel like ♪
♪ A ray of light ♪
- Do you think Tyra singing
could be, you know, deemed--
- Huh?
- I'm saying
do you think your singing
could be deemed
attempted murder?
- I'm offended.
[singing indistinctly, off-key]
- I totally wanna get married.
- [continues singing]
- If you had a gay wedding,
do you think your family
would be supportive?
- There's the religion thing.
- They're Christian?
- Yeah, my mom's a minister.
I don't know, because she seems
to be more accepting,
and you know, loving.
I think she'd come.
This is who I am,
and this is the way
I'm going to live my life.
And I've come to terms with it.
And my mom doesn't quite
understand it
but is working towards accepting
and, I guess,
loving that part of me as well.
- ♪ All the time ♪
- Would your family
come to your wedding, Tatianna?
- Oh, I don't know.
[chuckling]
I really, honestly,
wouldn't even--
- ♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah ♪
[continues singing indistinctly]
- This bitch...
is pissing me off.
- ♪ Oh ♪
I'm just in my own world.
Honestly, I wasn't paying
attention
to any of the other girls.
♪ Whoo ah ♪
♪ La ♪
♪ Ah ooh ♪
- It was really loud.
It was sounding really
obnoxious.
She was trying to annoy
everyone around her.
She really is singing that song
over and over again,
just to get to
me, this fucking bitch.
- [singing off-key]
- She's so self-absorbed.
She's rude.
- ♪ Ah ♪
- I finally was just, like,
I've had enough.
- ♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
- Shut the fuck up!
I told her, "No one wants to
hear your mouth.
Why are you such a bitch?"
- I put the earphones back in,
and I went back to singing.
She didn't ask politely.
♪ I'll never fall again ♪
And I just went on,
continued my dress
and continued to do
what I needed to do
to win the competition.
♪ Fly ♪
- Good morning.
- I think Tyra is a complete
and utter bitch.
Everyone's getting sick of her.
She has way too much
of a diva attitude.
It's not cute.
- So what do you guys think
is gonna happen today?
- Um, I don't know
what's gonna happen today.
- What would you like to happen?
- I would like to happen
what everyone wants to happen.
- I want that bitch to go home.
- Why don't you go ahead and
just speak your mind, my dear?
- I'm just annoyed
with people's attitudes.
- I guess it really shows
how people really are, you know?
- Exactly.
- And I don't feel as though
the next drag superstar
is going to be a little bitch.
- Don't talk about me
like I'm not in the room.
Say it to me.
- All I can say is...
whatever, pig.
- [laughing]
- Yesterday
we did the groom photo,
and today we're doing
the bride photo.
♪ Ah ♪
- I don't feel anything today.
This is not my regular makeup.
- Yeah.
- I'm scared.
- Santino is going to
rip in half...Sahara.
I think that Sahara will be
lip-synching for her life.
- I think Sahara's dress
is a little funny.
But she's going for
a Swan Lake look,
so that's working in her favor.
And she's going to be en pointe,
which is a tough call.
And hopefully
it pays off for her.
- No, I'm going to walk down the
runway...
like a fairy princess.
- Tyra needs all this help,
and she's just being ignored.
- Oh, fuck this shit, man.
- I haven't seen her help me
with anything.
I haven't seen her help
anybody else with anything.
- Ah!
- Stupid bitch.
Do you know sometimes
when you meet people,
and you think
they're great people
until they open
their fucking mouths?
Keep burning yourself, bitch.
If she screams one more time
with that hot glue,
I'm gonna just,
like, pull my eyes out.
I mean, why would you hot glue
things to your fucking skin?
- Ah!
[Mendelssohn's Wedding March]
♪ ♪
- [laughing]
Hey, guys.
Well, hello, Santino.
- How you doing, Ru?
- Merle,
you look lovely tonight.
- Hoping that I actually
could be the bride.
- [laughing]
- Now, Mathu...
- I love your hair.
- You do?
- I do.
- [laughing]
- It's divine.
- And Martha Wash.
I'm so happy you're here.
- I'm glad to be here too.
And you look fabulous, darling.
- Thank you.
This week, the ladies
were creating their vision
of the perfect bride and groom.
Are you ready
to see how they did?
all: Uh-huh.
- Gentlemen...
start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
Sahara, wow.
- Hold me closer, tiny dancer.
- Swan Lake.
- I've dreamed about having
a Swan Lake wedding
ever since I was young.
- Married in a tutu.
- It's tutu much.
- Morgan McMichaels.
November Rain.
She's serving a little
Pam Anderson there too.
- I start off like I'm bridal,
and then I start
throwing some sass into it,
and you know,
it's supermodel-esque.
- I'd like to sit on her
loveseat.
- That's the Lacroix--
- Lacroix, the pouf.
Absolutely.
- More cushion for the pushin'.
- Tyra Sanchez, the other Tyra.
Oh!
- I feel great.
My dress looks amazing.
- It's daddy's little girl.
He's paying for everything.
Raven!
She's been hitched, look!
- My dress looked amazing.
I felt like a cupcake.
I felt very cute.
- Look at that nice little line
of bow detail.
- Paris gets married.
- It is very Paris, isn't it?
Paris Hilton.
Jessica Wild...
- My darling,
you do take a hint or two.
- She did your makeup.
- Makeup's a lot better.
- It's my wedding.
And the makeup
helped me with the total look.
- Look at our daughter!
Our little girl's all grown up.
Tatianna.
Look at that keyhole
by her no-no hole.
- I liked my dress; then
I hated it at the same time.
But I was still proud of myself
that I did something with it.
- She's a voluptuous bride.
The implants took.
- Yes, they did.
Pandora Boxx,
oh, wow, look at that.
- Very romantic.
- I wanted to come across
as a very pretty bride
that's very excited
to get married,
and just very demure.
- Very innocent eyes.
- Oh, she did the thing
with the makeup too!
- I'm well pleased.
Like a gorgeous endive salad,
crisp and delicious.
- [gasps]
Is this our Jujubee?
- The gown fits very nicely.
- I want them to see the full
package,
so I'm going to go slowly.
And I'm going to be
very elegant.
And I want you to see
every single angle.
- Look at the back.
Oh, that's beautiful.
- Now instead of
a pearl necklace,
she went for the pearl
down the back.
Oh, yes.
Hello, my blushing brides.
It's time to unveil
your wedding portraits.
Jujubee.
Oh.
What a cute couple.
- I hope you didn't sign
that prenup.
- Honey, he's rich.
- In the picture,
she's not really into the groom.
But I think somehow it works.
- Even though
there's a man in that picture,
it's still sort of
all about her.
- She's a man-eater.
- [laughing]
Thank you, Jujubee.
- Thank you.
- Jessica Wild.
Oh, my goodness!
You've got yourself a hot one,
honey.
- They really
make a cute couple.
- They really are cute.
- The dress I like
except for the piece on the top.
- She's wearing her veil
on her shoulder.
- I could see that you love to
go for the big
and the layers and the ruffles,
but I want it to go away.
I just want to see you.
- Pandora Boxx.
You seem a little tentative.
- I'm scared
of my first marriage.
It was either the option of
going to jail
or getting married.
- Oh, I see.
- Just doesn't do anything
for me.
- Really?
- No.
Marriage, going to jail.
Maybe I'd do the time
for a while.
- [laughs]
- There's a lot of backstory
that I can read
into this picture.
Adds a lot of comedy to it.
- I'm kind of having an organza
orgasm over this dress.
- Oh, really cool.
- I love organza.
- Can we get a napkin over here?
- [laughs]
- Tyra Sanchez, the other Tyra.
Is that R. Kelly?
And she looks like Donna Summer
in that picture right there.
- You look like a porcelain doll
with the makeup.
- Thank you.
- I love it.
- Huge bouquet, Tyra.
- The huge bouquet is because
it comes from
my last husband's funeral.
- Oh, okay.
- I love how big
your bouquet is.
I love the whole shape
and silhouette of your dress.
You were this close
to being bridezilla,
but you are perfection.
- What blows me away is that
you added this little...lace?
- I hot-glued it to my leg
along with these to my arm.
- You're gonna have to
take a flame torch
to get that off of
there.
- You're like an old-school
drag queen,
but fresh and new to us.
- Thank you.
- Hi, Tatianna.
- Hello.
- Ooh. He's hot.
He's gorgeous.
Thug love, baby.
- You're really fortunate
to have immunity this week
because I hate this dress.
- The face is so killer that
you want the clothes
to live up to it.
- Mathu, is this a "xana-do"
or a "xana-don't"?
- It's a xana-don't.
- Sahara Davenport.
- I remember being a little boy
who dreams
of a fairy-tale wedding,
like Swan Lake
or something very ethereal.
- I thought the presentation
was fabulous.
I loved it.
Dress I'm not so sure about.
- When you're not en pointe,
it's not a good look.
It looks a little crafty
and homemade,
and the fit is off.
- Raven.
Oh, how cute.
He looks older than--
- He's 36.
- He's 36 and you're 16?
- Going on 16.
- Ooh!
- Oh, I see.
- [laughing]
- What--okay,
then you're jailbait.
- She's jailbait.
- Love that.
Love your turquoise accents,
love the bows.
You have the most expensive
looking dress up here.
- It's kind of like this fluffy,
girly, flirty dress,
but she's still packing a wallop
somewhere.
- It's under the skirt.
- Yes!
[all laugh]
- Morgan McMichaels.
She's a punk dude.
- I'm not sure
about the punk look.
- It's neither here nor there
for me.
I'm not crazy for it.
- It's more of a costume versus
a wedding gown.
I'm just not loving the shape
overall.
- You know, white pumps
are the sign of a true hooker.
And I love you for that.
Tonight's gonna be more
difficult than I thought.
And I need your help.
What are the judges not seeing
on the main stage
that we need to know?
Tatianna?
- Um, I don't think
that you're seeing
that Tyra's a complete bitch.
- That was frank.
- Thank you.
She has this diva attitude,
like I am America's sweetheart.
But she's not.
- I completely agree
with what Tatianna says.
I don't think that the face
that you see of Tyra
is what we're seeing backstage.
Everyone asked Tyra to be quiet
and not sing obnoxiously loud
for an hour.
- ♪ Aah, ooh-ooh ♪
- I asked her to stop nicely.
And she was like, "okay."
And then I walk across the room,
and it's like lah, lah,
lah-ah-ah-ah.
- ♪ La ♪
- She was almost saying,
"Shut the fuck up,
or I'll make you shut up."
It, like, really,
really pissed me off,
'cause she talks so much shit
about so many people
but won't say it to their face.
- You really
shouldn't play the victim.
It doesn't suit you.
You don't do it well.
- I was not doing that to make
anyone upset
or, like, make anyone unfocused.
- Bullshit.
- Then maybe next time
I will sing,
and maybe she'll get
another horrible dress
like she has on now.
- Tyra, do you think this really
has to do with the music
or something else?
- They're testing me.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it's like, kind of
pissing me off.
Morgan, do you think
I'm a bitch?
- No, I think you have a goal.
- Raven, do you think
I'm a bitch?
- No.
Sahara, do you think
I'm a bitch?
- I think sometimes
you're selfish.
- I think you need manners,
girl.
- Just because I--
when you give me a compliment
I don't give you one back
doesn't mean
I don't have manners.
- Girl, I know I'm gorgeous.
You don't need to tell me
anything, miss thing.
Just get yourself some manners
so you won't look
so damn stupid.
- [laughs]
- We're gonna move beyond this.
I think this is
another challenge
that we will all
have to overcome.
And we'll have to take it
into account.
Just promise me
we will be queens.
Now, while you wait in
the Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
Let's start with Jujubee.
- I'm a huge Jujubee fan.
She comes out here,
she works the runway,
her style choices are always
very nudge-nudge, wink-wink.
It's charming.
- I think the dress
drowned her out a little bit.
You know, there was a lot
going on.
- I told Jujubee last week
to turn up the fire.
And I'm not sure
if she's turned it up
to full capacity.
Jessica Wild.
Now, I liked the dress because
it actually works for her.
- I didn't like the top part.
- The fan thing? Yeah.
- It was very quinceañera.
I think her style is pretty bad.
- Mathu, she did take your
pointers with the makeup.
- And I am well impressed that
she did do it.
She didn't have the heavy brow.
- Right.
- And she took her bang away.
- That's right.
- Pandora Boxx.
Now, Martha,
you did not like her dress.
- It didn't do a thing for her.
She just dissolved
into that dress.
- She went for a whole other
persona, this kind of--
- She took a chance.
- Bridal realness.
I thought it was a full show.
- My problem with
Miss Pandora Boxx all along
is it's like, um, blah.
Like all of her fashion
choices--
It's not even like, "they're
hideous; they're horrible"
as it's like, "Eh;
there you are."
- Miss Tyra "boom boom" Sanchez.
She's a showgirl.
She's the one your eyes go to.
- I was blown away.
- For Tyra, the biggest problem
is what?
- All the girls hate her.
- I think
she's a great performer.
I don't feel
a lot of warmth from her.
- Her attitude sucks.
And if it was up to me,
I'd vote her off right now.
- Tatianna.
If she did not have
immunity this week,
she would be in the bottom two.
- Hello.
- Yes.
- Tatianna gets the beautiful
thing a lot.
- Yeah.
- But she gets the ugly dress
thing a lot too.
She gets the ugly dress thing
a lot.
She's gotten that
more than once.
- Sahara.
Did not like her dress.
- Skimpy tutu.
- It wasn't enough tulle.
I mean, for drag,
you have to exaggerate things.
- Sahara was a little dry.
- Yeah, she was a little dry.
Raven.
I loved Raven's outfit.
- She was the other standout.
Love the bows.
- I was loving her Elle bride
blue shoe.
- Morgan McMichaels.
I have to say
I did not like her dress.
- A pouf skirt
is kind of hard to pull off.
- She never does
serious fashion.
She always does costume.
- Did Morgan improve her makeup?
- She's still doing
her signature Morgan look,
but it didn't look magic marker
this time.
- [claps]
Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring the girls back.
Ladies.
As we witnessed here tonight,
tensions are running high.
I will not tolerate problems
between my girls.
We are all in this together.
Now, based on the wedding
challenge
and your presentation
on the main stage tonight,
I've made some decisions.
Jujubee.
Today in that dress,
you owned everything.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Jessica.
Mucho escandalo.
You are safe.
Tyra Sanchez.
This week, you raised the bar
on this competition.
Again.
Please do not
lower its standards.
- I'm scared that Ru is going
to look at me and say,
"Tyra Sanchez,
you are in the bottom two."
- Tyra Sanchez.
Congratulations, you're
the winner of this challenge.
- Thank you.
- In addition to receiving
immunity next week,
you've won a five-night
villa vacation
at the Hyatt Palm Springs.
Thank you, Tyra, you may join
the other girls.
- Thank you.
[Mendelssohn's Wedding March]
♪ ♪
I'm just in tears.
I was, like, boo-hoo crying.
[sobbing]
I thought that I was going home.
- Tatianna.
Based on the judges' feedback,
your bride would have been left
at the altar.
But you have immunity this week.
You're still in the race.
- Thank you.
- Sahara Davenport.
Your presentation
was very Swan Lake.
Unfortunately, that story
does not have a happy ending.
I'm sorry,
you're up for elimination.
Pandora Boxx.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Raven.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
I should have won
that fuckin' challenge.
Everyone in that fuckin' room
will agree with me.
- Morgan McMichaels.
- [laughs]
- Why are you laughing?
- I always laugh.
It's a nervous thing, I think.
- I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip-sync performance
to Carry On
by the one and only Martha Wash.
Now, this song means
a great deal to me
because when my mother,
who had suffered
from a long bout with cancer
finally passed away,
I was listening to this song
incessantly.
It has a lyric--
mama said, never give up.
And I've used it as my anthem.
I want each of you girls
to know that,
even through adversity or death,
love and energy lives forever.
Now.
This is your final chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lip-synch...
for your life.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ I stand alone ♪
♪ In the eye of the storm ♪
♪ Pressures all around ♪
♪ Mama used to say ♪
♪ Never ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Never let your spirit bend ♪
♪ Never ♪
♪ Never give in to the end ♪
♪ I'll carry on ♪
♪ When the valley's deep ♪
♪ I'll be strong ♪
♪ I stand alone ♪
♪ In the eye of the storm ♪
♪ Pressures all around ♪
♪ Tryin' to wear me down ♪
♪ But it's all right ♪
♪ I won't give up the fight ♪
♪ I said, "Lord, lift me up" ♪
♪ Let me rise above ♪
♪ I'll never ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna
take my pride ♪
♪ I won't stop ♪
♪ I will not be denied ♪
♪ I'll carry on ♪
♪ When the valley's deep ♪
♪ I said I'll never ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna
take my pride ♪
♪ I won't stop ♪
♪ I will not be denied ♪
♪ I'll carry on ♪
♪ I'll never sleep ♪
♪ Till the new day dawns ♪
♪ When the valley is deep ♪
[applause]
- Ladies.
I have made my decision.
Sahara Davenport.
Shante, you stay.
- Yes.
If I have to, I'll take each of
these bitches down one by one.
Morgan McMichaels.
- Yes.
- Take strength in the words
of Martha's song.
A new day will dawn.
Carry on.
Now...
sashay away.
- Thank you.
[applause]
- I couldn't even look.
When she was walking off,
I would not look at her.
I would not look up.
- Hello, mom.
I'm coming home.
I didn't serve it the way the
judges wanted me to serve it.
I'm not bitter, I'm not crazy.
I haven't cared what people
thought about me
the whole time I've been here.
I'm not gonna start now.
I care about
what I think about me.
And if I'm happy with me, then
that's good enough, right?
- To all my dolls.
We'll see you next week.
And remember...
If you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen.
- Let the music play.
[RuPaul's Jealous Of My Boogie
playing]
♪ ♪