- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
And then there were three.
Jujubee.
- What a sin. Ah!
I have never been blown
like that.
- I just absolutely loved her.
I thought she was dynamite.
- Miss Tyra.
Was your barbecue cancelled?
Your grill is fucked up.
- Tyra Sanchez, the other Tyra.
- I'm America's sweetheart.
Happy birthday, Mr. President.
- What do the bags say?
They say "Santino"?
[uproarious laughter]
It's daddy's little girl.
Tyra Sanchez, you raised the bar
on this competition.
Oh, my sweet gherkins!
You tore it up, Miss Thing.
Raven.
- Am I a ten?
Cocka-doodle-doo.
- The blending.
It's severe up in here.
- A perfect ten.
- I would not leave my man
in a room alone with you.
- Don't do it.
I'll work...it.
- One of you will be crowned
the next drag superstar.
And tonight...
[all screaming]
The final three queens
go head-to-head
and toe-to-toe.
- Oh!
- Snap out of it, girl.
In this season's
stunning conclusion...
Ladies, America's
next drag superstar is...
[cheering]
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics
and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com,
an exclusive
one-year PR contract
with the leading LGBT firm
Project Publicity,
be featured in l.a.Eyeworks'
legendary
designer eyewear campaign
and headline
Logo's Drag Race Tour
featuring
exceptional Absolut drinks,
and a cash prize of $25,000.
And may the best woman win.
- Top three, bitches.
- Oh, I know that's right.
- Get up in here.
- "Do you to the fullest.
Love, Tati."
I saw so much more in Tatiana.
She just kind of halted
and stopped.
- You gonna clean this mirror?
- Why do I have to clean it?
- 'Cause you out-lip-synch her.
- And you sent her home.
And that was your friend.
- How did you feel having
to lip-synch for your life
a third time?
- I thought I was going home.
- Memoirs of a Gay-sha:
The Story of Jujubee--
both: I'm still here.
- What if I wasn't here,
though?
- Then Tati would be here, and
there would be no competition.
Only a competition
between me and Raven.
- We're in the top three.
- Ah!
[all laughing]
There were two times
where I thought, "Fuck."
And it was the times
I was having
to lip-synch for my life,
and I thought, "Damn it."
- Oh, there were three times
where I thought that too.
- But we made it, bitch.
- I thought I was going home
that week
when all my bridesmaids
fucking jumped on me.
- I think you need manners,
girl.
- You don't need to tell me
anything, Miss Thing.
It was just like,
"I need to let her know."
'cause I didn't want you
to go home and--
and be like that with people
and have people talk about you
and you not wonder why.
- But you said it
in front of Ru,
which made the judges think
a completely different thing
about me.
- It did at the time,
and now they see it
differently,
and they see that you've grown.
So I did you a favor.
[clicks tongue]
- Ooh, girl.
You've got she mail.
Well, look who's here.
The best of the best.
You stand on the shoulder pads
of a dynasty of drag queens
who have come here before you.
So forget about those
bickering real housewives.
They ain't seen
nothing yet...
till they go head-to-head
and toe-to-toe
with the realness
that's about to explode
as one queen survives the fight
to be crowned
America's next drag superstar.
[car engine running]
- Surprise.
- Good for us.
- Hello, hello.
- Whoo.
I'm shocked.
I'm like, "Oh, my God,
what are you guys doing here?"
- Congratulations on making it
into the final three.
all: Thank you.
- We're here because RuPaul
is getting ready
for your final challenge,
inspired by some
of the great bitchy catfights
of all time.
You'll be costarring
in RuPaul's new music video,
Jealous of My Boogie.
- You'll need to learn
to fight dance
with choreographer
Ryan Heffington.
- And then with video director
Mathu Anderssen
you'll each have your moment
to act opposite RuPaul
in an over-the-top
dramatic scene.
- Plus, you'll work
with style expert Robert Verdi
to turn out two looks
inspired by '80s
power bitch fashion.
- This is your moment to show us
every bit of the charisma,
uniqueness, nerve,
and talent you've got.
- Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And for the last time...
both: Don't fuck it up.
- Not only are we that one step
closer to winning this,
but we're now gonna be
in RuPaul's new video.
[all screaming]
So we need to be on our A game.
This is the final challenge.
- [lisping] I'm so excited
right now, guys.
- Hello.
- Hi, ladies.
How's it going?
- Hi, I'm Jujubee.
- Hi, I'm Ryan.
- The first thing
that we go out to learn
is the fight choreography
with choreographer
Ryan Heffington.
- So let's go from the top.
Let's come up here.
The inspiration for this piece
was taken from the classic
TV show Dynasty.
It's bitchy, it's exciting,
it's campy.
So from the get-go,
it's a stomp, stomp, stomp.
You're a video vixen now,
yeah, okay?
I just think they really have
to be stars,
you know, when they're
in front of the camera.
They should already be living
as if, you know,
they are the new RuPaul.
- ♪ Can't stop now ♪
♪ Won't slow down ♪
- Five, six, hup.
- ♪ I gotta emulate the BPM ♪
- Go.
Up, down, up, up, ah.
Up, up--
- Ryan's very just high-octane.
He's very, like, "Duh, duh."
- [scatting]
Ooh, uh, fucking fierce, uh.
Pop pop, pop pop.
Four, five, six,
seven, eight.
Click, click, click,
click, click, click.
Hup, hup, hup.
Walk it out.
A little bit of booty
thrown in.
Pff, pff, pff,
pop pop, pop pop.
Yes, cool.
- He is the tiniest
little fiercest
little white man
in the world.
- Circle, circle, circle,
circle, circle, circle, circle,
and circle and circle
and circle.
- Fuck, I keep--
I forget that part.
I think it's gonna be hard
counting out those first beats
to know when we start circling
like a shark.
- Raven's a little bit slow
picking up choreography,
and that's a little bit
of a concern.
Click.
Other side, click, click.
- So it's--
- Not back to front.
- Okay.
- Let's listen to it 'cause
what--it's really fast, okay?
- Tyra's really monotone
with her attitude,
which makes me
a little bit nervous
because you need to be
hitting it in rehearsal
in order to hit it later on.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
This has to be bigger.
Don't fake it, yeah?
If they don't bring
their personality
and the steps are a little shy
of being what they should be,
it could be a disaster.
So and then I think from there,
you guys just kind of catfight
like true Dynasty fashion.
This is where it gets
really dramatic.
Five, six, seven, eight!
It shouldn't be
six, seven, eight.
It should be six, seven, bam!
And smack her, okay?
- Keep your heels off my toes.
- Keep your toes
under my heels.
I hope these bitches
don't take my eye out.
- And you're just gonna put
your hand on her wig.
So you have to really be careful
of her heels.
- The timing needs to be perfect
so it looks real.
- Hit, five, six, seven, eight.
Uh-huh.
Jujubee's overall realness
of being totally catty
and bitchy,
if she can really bring that
up to another level,
it'll be great.
Let's go back from here.
Just shake it down.
We have 15 minutes.
Let's go.
Ah, ah, ah.
See, you have to hold.
You come across, Raven.
You go one, two, three, four,
and look, six, seven, eight,
then walk, two, three, four,
to shove.
- Got it, okay.
- Yeah?
- When you're doing it
with three people total
and two of them are nailing it
and you're over there,
like, barely hammering it--
I'm thinking this is
gonna be a catastrophe.
- Okay, cool.
Thanks, ladies.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- I know y'all jealous of my
[high-pitched voice] boogie.
- Don't be jealous
of my boogie.
- Oh, my God,
I feel so fierce.
Did you guys ever think
that when you were a little boy,
that you were gonna be
in a RuPaul video?
- No.
- No, me neither.
I thought I was gonna be
a doctor.
We have a ton of stuff to do
for this video shoot, okay?
We have to do a scene
with RuPaul.
We have to learn the words.
- Ru?
- Who is it?
Like, with attitude.
We have to prepare
a fight scene,
and then we have lunch
with Ru.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- Hi, Ru.
- Tyra Sanchez, have a seat.
- Thank you.
- The other Tyra.
Two.
- Thank you.
- You've come a long way.
- What's been the toughest part
of this?
- Staying focused
and not worrying so much
about my son
and what's going on back home.
Like, and I'll pray to God,
and the tears just fall.
- Why do you cry, though,
when you pray?
- Because I just feel
that God is listening.
I held it in for a long time,
and, like, that's what made me,
like, angry.
- Anger is always
a symptom of fear.
What are you afraid of?
- I'm afraid of losing my son.
I really, really want to be
a better father to Jeremiah.
- So winning this contest
would mean what to you?
- I've been through so much
from being kicked out
to living on my own
and then raising a son.
So it's like a fresh start.
Just because I made mistakes
doesn't mean his life
has to be a mistake.
I was so surprised that I told
her about things in my past,
what went on with me.
Ru has definitely, like, grown,
to be, like, my drag mother.
- Thank you, Tyra.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Jujubee.
How are you?
- Hi.
- What's going on? I'm Robert.
- Nice to meet you.
Robert Verdi is giving me
a consultation.
I'm like, "Oh, my God,
you smell so good
and you're so handsome."
- I'm gonna give you
an outfit to wear,
and I'm gonna help you pick out
an '80s look in your wardrobe.
You have to channel these
dramatic fabulous women
of the '80s.
Are you aware of any of them?
- No.
- What year were you born?
- '84.
- Oh, my God.
- I know.
- [mouths words]
What do you think you're
gonna do for this challenge?
- Does this do anything?
- These two things
go hand in hand?
- Yeah.
- It looks more
Ringling Brothers than '80s.
- I've seen
Whitney Houston's videos.
She just looked
like she was going to the prom.
- This has an '80s vibe,
but the shoulder would be...
- Bigger, right?
- More defined.
The waist would be more defined.
Who were the women
in the canon of history
that you look to
for inspiration?
- Honestly,
I look at Mary J. Blige,
and I look at, like,
the Beyoncés and all that.
- It's not really history.
- Yeah, and, you know--
- That's contemporary.
- I'm a little nervous.
I have no idea where to start.
- Hello, Raven.
- Hello, how are you?
- Have a seat, darling.
- We get to go have
a one-on-one lunch with Ru.
- Oh, a buffet.
- Yes.
- Would you like a mint,
darling?
- Just one.
- Just the one.
- There.
- Thank you.
Sitting there having lunch
with RuPaul
was one of the most surreal
things I've ever done.
- You know,
I wonder what it's like
to be sequestered this way.
Do you feel like
a prisoner of war?
- I mean, I do miss
talking to my mom.
I speak to my dad, you know,
a couple times a month.
I guess I'm closer with my mom
than I am my dad.
- They're not together.
- No.
- When did they separate?
- When I was seven.
- You know, I--
my parents divorced
when I was seven also.
It was really tough on me,
and I think I went into music,
into sort of
an imaginary world.
What reaction did you have
to their divorce?
- I look at my mother.
She's, like, my golden
Oscar statue, you know?
And I love her.
And when I saw
what she went through
with my father's divorce,
it killed me.
And I swore, I said,
"I will never do that
to anybody in my life."
And whenever I've gotten
into a relationship,
it's really killed me
because I'm, like,
"Why do I have to be
my mom now?"
And a lot of times when you're
with someone and they hurt you,
you don't want to have
anything else to do with them.
- Expectations
lead to resentments,
and when you allow people
to just be themselves,
the relationship
can really grow.
- It was very nice to sit there
and talk with Ru one-on-one
and it be about me,
not all about drag and shop
and all that.
- Our lunch has to end now.
Can we get a doggy bag?
- Thank you.
- [laughing]
- Tell me about your persona.
Tell me about Tyra.
- Well, Tyra is, like,
sophisticated, glamorous.
- Okay, you're gonna be
shooting a video,
and your characters
are going to be styled
to look like they're
'80s vixens.
It was a decade of power
for women,
and women were really defined
stylistically
with very sharp shoulders,
very small waist,
and some bling.
- I wasn't born
when the '80s were hot.
I was born in the late '80s,
like, '88.
- You have the privilege
of working
with one of the most amazing
performers in the world,
who draws inspiration
from the most incredible women
in history.
And you should probably
take a minute to research
because I think you'll be able
to refine your character.
- Darling.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- How are you?
- Have a seat.
- I will.
- How many
of these delicious mints?
- Just two.
- The two.
I'm on a diet,
so I'll just have one.
You were in the bottom two
three times.
- Three times.
- How did that happen?
- Well, I've been in
the bottom two three times here,
and I've been in the bottom two
a lot of times beforehand.
- Tell me about that.
- Just growing up, you know,
having people
just make fun of you.
I used to answer to faggot.
- Really?
- I just accepted it
'cause I knew it wouldn't stop,
and then finally, I just said,
"You know, don't call me that."
- Wow.
You know,
you got a lot of strength
for such a young lady.
What do you think your dad would
think of you in this contest?
- Oh, he would give me
the biggest hug,
and he would say,
"Go for it."
You know,
now it's Jujubee's journey.
Talking to Ru today,
she brought up situations
that I never talk about,
and it was just so comforting
to have her just listen.
- Thank you, darling.
- Thank you so much, mama.
- All right,
I'll see you later on.
- So do you have
any reference point
for what this challenge
is about?
- I would picture
the Carringtons.
- You do picture
- Yes.
- So you do know who they are.
- Are you the oldest
of the remaining--
- I'm the oldest.
- So you actually have
maybe an upper hand in it
'cause you were more in tune
to this decade
than the other two would be.
- Yes.
If you want to work
and you want to have longevity
in this business,
you need to know a little bit
about everything.
- [laughs]
I love that jacket.
How many shoulder pads
are in yours?
- Two.
I'm like--
- Are you ready?
Are you ready?
- You got black nail polish?
- Mm-hmm.
Should I even risk it
and try to polish them?
- That's up to you, girl.
This is a competition.
- Let's make movies.
Okay, here we go.
- So I'm the first one out
for the dramatic scene with Ru.
- Action.
- RuPaul.
- Who is it?
- Step into her, Raven.
- RuPaul.
- Who is it?
- I really need to talk to you.
I know that--
I forgot what my--my line is.
- Cut.
And action on Raven.
- RuPaul.
- You know I can't see you
before the show.
It's against the rules.
- Well, I'm sick of your rules,
I'm sick of your challenges,
and I'm sick of your show.
- Cut.
Try and get a little more
roller coaster in your ride.
- Okay.
- Do you know what I mean?
- I'm sick of your rules,
I'm sick of your challenges,
and I'm sick of your show.
What about me?
What about Raven?
- I was a little disappointed
at first with Raven,
but she took direction,
and she paid attention,
and there was
an actual progression.
- What about Raven?
Oh! Oh. Oh!
Oh! Oh.
- Ru?
- Who is it?
- I am so glad
I caught you alone.
- Cut.
Can you just make it
a little more seductive,
just throw in a bit of that?
Action.
- What about me?
What about Tyra?
- Snap out of it.
Pull yourself together, girl!
- Cut.
I want you to play this
a little bit--
it's like
when she shuts you down,
be really hurt
when she slaps you,
be really hurt.
- Like, hood?
Like how hood?
- Go for it.
- Oh, hood or hurt?
- Hurt.
- When he said "hurt,"
I thought he said "hood."
- Well, do we want that?
- That sounds pretty good.
- I am sick of your rules.
What...about me?
- Snap out of it, girl.
You better pull yourself
together.
- You are just jealous
of my boogie.
- [laughing]
- Hello, darling, you gorgeous
little shoulder-padded monster.
- I feel 100% confident
about this.
I was a theater major, honey.
I know what to do.
- And action.
- RuPaul.
- I can't see you
before a show.
It's against the rules.
- I'm tired of these rules.
I'm tired of the challenges.
I'm tired of this show!
What about me?
What about Jujubee?
Ah!
[babbling tearfully]
- Jujubee came fully loaded
and a surprise
by throwing herself
on the floor.
- You're jealous of my boogie!
- But Jujubee
just is a drag clown.
Cut.
Cut, cut, c-cut, c-cut, cut.
- Right from the top, please.
- Would you do it
once more for me?
- What about me?
What about Jujubee?
- Snap out of it.
- [singing indistinctly]
♪ Jealous ♪
Oh, yes, I'll do that.
Oh!
It's time for us to shoot
the dance routine
for RuPaul's video.
I'm so excited!
It's us three.
We're the Supremes right now,
okay?
And we have to shoot
this video,
and it needs to be perfect.
Are we all doing bodysuits?
- Oh, those look too big.
- Raven and I got ready
so quickly.
- Yeah, you could see my
bathing suit lines in it.
Oh, well.
- We picked out our outfits.
We put it on.
I feel like Lucy Liu.
- I don't like these.
That looks too small,
doesn't it?
- Tyra had to go
through every fucking thing.
- Can I fit this?
Can I put on a tutu?
I don't like this.
Look at my stomach.
You don't buy stuff in my size,
do y'all?
- Girl, they gave me
these clothes; they fit me.
You're just a little taller
than I am.
Like, you can find something.
- This isn't gonna work.
At all. None of this.
I have so much to choose from.
It was just so hard
to choose something
that would top everything
I've done this entire season.
- How are you feeling, Tyra?
- They didn't have no fucking
Clothes to fit me.
And now I don't feel pretty.
- Action!
- One, two, three, four,
five, six!
Hup, hup!
[RuPaul's Jealous of My Boogie]
- ♪ Can't stop now ♪
- While we are performing
this routine
in front of the cameras
and everything,
I realize that
we're shooting a video.
And I'm like,
"Jujubee, be in the moment
and just do it
and just be fabulous."
- ♪ Can't be easy,
I don't envy them ♪
- Five, six, hup, girls!
- ♪ Let 'em scrutinize ♪
- And hup!
Hup!
- In the catfight,
he wanted us to make it real.
And I'm showing, bitch,
this is serious.
We're in a catfight.
Don't be jealous of my boogie.
- ♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
- In a real fight, you don't
hold back because she's pretty.
- ♪ Jealous of my boogie ♪
- [laughs]
- I didn't pull
anybody's wigs off.
Tyra snatched
Ms. Raven's wig twice.
- My wig didn't come off.
I had it pinned on
the right way.
They knew we was shooting
a video.
- You got three drag queens
rolling around
on top of each other.
There's heels, wigs,
jewelry, nails.
Something's bound to happen.
- Ow, my eye.
Ow, ow, ow.
- You okay?
- Ow, ow, this one.
Is it bleeding?
- No.
- Oh, my God.
- Open it up.
You want me to blow?
- It went right
into that heel.
Let's just give Jujubee
a moment.
- Do I look fine?
If I look fine,
I'll keep going.
- You look fine.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Fix your wig.
- [grunts]
- Yeah, I think she's got
the fighting thing down.
- Do I even have makeup
left on my face?
- Yes, you do.
- Ow.
- Yes.
[clapping]
- Y'all bitches
got your ass whooped.
- You okay, mama?
- It burns.
But I can't do anything
about it.
I just hope it doesn't swell up.
There's a cut right there.
And it's bruising right here.
I put makeup over it,
a little bacteria cream,
and I was like,
"Let's just keep doing it."
This doesn't look '80s to you,
huh?
- I think it looks more '70s.
I see Juju and Tyra,
and I realize they don't know
a thing about Dynasty
or Knott's Landing
or Dallas, none of that.
- Why wasn't I born earlier?
- So I think maybe I have
an upper hand
on what my look should be.
I'm channeling Lisa Lisa,
I'm channeling Kelly LeBrock,
and I'm channeling Tina Marie.
- All I know is
'80s style is tacky.
It's huge ass shoulder pads.
It's big unruly, ugly hair,
really tiny waists,
and fat asses.
There we go, dahling.
- The way that
I'm gonna pull it together
for the '80s challenge is,
like, they had big hair,
they believed
in their chandelier earrings,
and they like
the Lite-Brite colors.
Do I look '80s?
- Yes.
You look like you're going
to the prom.
- What's wrong, mama?
- Nothing, baby.
My eye is just in pain
right now.
- Okay, well, basically
what we're gonna do is,
you're gonna be sharing
the same space.
I want you all to write "no"
at the same time.
- Okay.
- So, you know, it's like,
"No, no, no, no."
Yep. You ready?
Okay, here we go.
- Standby, track.
Here we go.
Track in.
- Track, please.
- I was giving
Michelle Pfeiffer bitch
when I was looking at myself
in that mirror.
I was like,
"I look fucking good."
- ♪ Hey, DJ ♪
♪ Love the way ♪
♪ I lose my inhibitions
when you... ♪
- I know that I should win
this competition tonight
because I have worked
so much harder.
- ♪ I'd rather boogie
than try to fit in ♪
- I feel like I'm in my bedroom
lip-synching
to one of RuPaul's songs.
It's not me shooting
a music video.
It's me just being crazy
and just having fun.
Every boy in America sings in
front of the mirror to RuPaul.
You didn't know that?
- Purr for each other
a bit more.
- ♪ I see you looking ♪
- Okay, ladies, find it.
- ♪ I know you're watching ♪
- ♪ No, no, no ♪
- ♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
- Nice.
- [laughing]
Ooh, it's the last day.
[laughter]
- This is it.
- I know.
- So we all get into
the workroom this morning,
and we realize
this is the last time
we're gonna be walking in here.
And it's nerve-racking.
None of us can call it.
None of us knows
what's gonna happen.
- Did you honestly expect this?
- Yes.
- Me too.
[laughs]
- If you win, can you imagine?
- I know.
And it would gag
a whole bunch of people
that didn't believe in me.
- And that's the thing
I'm excited about.
There are those people
who are like,
"I think Raven's boring."
Yeah, so don't dance around it.
Don't sing live.
But I'm fierce at what I do,
so eat my fucking shit.
- How is it gonna change
your life, Tyra?
- I'll have a place to stay,
first of all.
And I'd be able to get my son
to come.
Like, he'll be able to stay
with me
and live with me there.
- Where are you staying now,
girl?
- Girl, I stay
with my drag mama.
I stay on her couch.
I need this.
I couldn't dare go home
without the crown and the title
of being America's
next drag superstar.
- So is anyone nervous?
- No.
Are you?
- I'm nervous.
- I'm not nervous.
And I know being nervous
is normal and fine,
but I'm ready.
- [laughing]
- Hello, judges.
How are you, Santino?
- Doing great, Ru.
- Merle, how are you tonight?
- I'm nervous for the girls.
- We've made it
to the final lap.
Tonight, we're crowning
America's next drag superstar.
Santino, Merle,
you've been here
since the beginning.
You know these ladies
inside and out.
So tonight, there are no
guest judges, Miss Thing.
It's just family.
- Good.
- [laughs]
- Now are you ready for their
final main stage presentation?
- Ready.
- Bring it on.
- Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Jujubee.
Ooh.
- Le pouf.
- I love this dress.
Oh, I was living for myself,
girl.
I wish I could have seen
my reflection.
- Yes, touch all of the skin.
- Touch all of the skin,
darling.
Oh...
I think Jujubee must have
bronzed her panties.
Ooh. Cabaret.
2010.
That's so Raven,
that's so cabaret.
- I feel fabulous.
I feel like, "Wow, I'm here.
I made it."
And I'm coming out
the way I want to come out.
- Willkommen
to RuPaul's Drag Race.
And all that jazz.
Ooh.
Yes, mama. Style proper.
Tyra Sanchez, the other Tyra.
Yummy.
- Do you know
where you're going to?
- Yes. Mahogany.
I'm a winner, baby.
- I am so nervous right now.
And it hit me that, bitch,
you have a great chance at being
America's next drag superstar.
- The Beverly Hills Hotel.
- Ah, yeah.
- Polo Lounge.
- Yes. Poolside.
Oh, Tyra, darling.
Dive into the deep end.
Mm, the water's fine.
- [laughs]
- Welcome, ladies.
Tonight, one queen's life
will be changed forever.
Which one of you has
the charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent
to be the next drag superstar?
Let's find out.
Jujubee.
Let's take a look at highlights
from your final challenge.
- ♪ I hit the scene ♪
♪ They turn green ♪
♪ It can't be easy ♪
♪ I don't envy them ♪
- ♪ Oh, ho ♪
- ♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
- I am tired of the rules.
I'm tired of these challenges.
I'm tired of your show.
What about me?
What about Jujubee?
- Hmm.
- Oh...
- Snap out of it, Jujubee.
Wow.
[laughing]
- Wow.
- Tell me about
the acting challenge.
Was it difficult?
- Not stepping into your light,
that was really, like,
my concern.
- Trust me, I moved all
the girls out of my light.
- If this was
a regular TV show or movie,
I would say, "Jujubee
is overacting like crazy."
But for Dynasty '80s,
it was perfect.
- I'm a little let down
that you've chose to wear
this dress at the end here.
I get where you were going
with it,
but not the perfect dress
for this evening.
- I think the necklace makes
the dress look less expensive
and less fashion.
- Do you want me
to take it off?
- Sure, if you want
to take it off.
- No, no, I'll take it off.
- Let's see what it looks like.
- Yeah, you look
so much more expensive and chic.
- Oh, right, yes, it does,
actually.
- I'm gonna leave it right here.
- Okay.
Now, if it winds up
in my pocketbook,
don't hate me.
- Girl, there's
three stars missing.
You can already have it.
[laughter]
- Next up, the other Tyra.
- ♪ I know you're watching ♪
♪ I know you're watching ♪
♪ I know
you're watching ♪
♪ I see you looking ♪
♪ I know you're watching ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
- I am sick of your rules,
your challenges, your show.
What about me?
What about Tyra?
- Snap out of it.
The fighting.
[chuckles]
You were pretty rough.
I couldn't take my eyes off
of you in that scene there.
- Usually when you see
girls fight,
they're not worried
about being pretty.
It's, "I'm gonna beat
this bitch ass,"
and so I'm like--
that's all I'm thinking.
I just wanted that
to really happen.
- You snatched her wig off.
- I didn't do it intentionally.
It was like
I was reaching for her,
and the wig came off, but--
- You didn't do it
intentionally twice?
- [laughs]
- Love the hair.
Love how just open
and popping your face is.
It's really stunning.
Overall, I think
it's a great look.
- Now, are you gonna let
your son watch this show?
- I think that this might be
the first time
that he realizes
what daddy does.
And I'm--I'm pretty sure
he's gonna--
we're gonna sit down
and watch it together.
- All right, Tyra.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- Now let's move on
to Miss Raven.
- ♪ Don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't, don't, don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't, don't, don't, don't,
don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't, don't, don't, don't ♪
- ♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
- Well, I'm sick of your rules,
I'm sick of your challenges,
and I'm sick of your show.
What about me?
What about Raven?
- Come here.
Closer.
Let mommy make it better.
That was just too good
to pass up!
What was the toughest part
about the acting challenge?
- Looking at your face.
- [laughs]
I get that a lot.
[laughs]
- You always looked beautiful,
but that was--
probably the hardest part
was looking at your face
and trying not to just be
like--
- [laughing]
Now, what are you serving us
on the main stage tonight?
- Well, I have this corset,
and I think this just
kind of speaks for itself.
- What does it say?
- I'm the next drag superstar.
- [laughing]
- Don't slap me again,
please.
[laughter]
- I'm so in love
with this outfit.
I love a black, like,
floral thing
because you expect organza
and petals
to be kind of pink.
And when they're black,
it's kind of like this
weird Gothic feeling.
- In the fight scene,
there was a period of time
over a minute
where I couldn't even see you.
Tyra was standing up,
and, like, you kind of got lost.
- I didn't want to hurt anyone,
so I didn't go for it
completely.
- Your '80s look,
it was totally '80s.
If there's any time
in this whole competition
that you really looked
like Kelly LeBrock,
it was--
it was that time.
- All right.
Thank you.
Ladies.
While you wait in
the Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
[car engine turns over]
Okay, here we are
at the moment...
- Oh, my God.
- That it all boils down to.
Let's start with Jujubee.
She has star quality.
- Mm-hmm.
- But is she
the next drag superstar?
- To me, in the context
of these three people,
she looked a little bit
like a tourist.
Her level of iconography
in terms of fashion and beauty
is not where the other two's is.
- She excelled
in the book challenge
because she's a clever girl.
She's clearly the most
intelligent of all the girls.
- I'm not sure.
- Really?
- I think Tyra
is incredibly intelligent.
- Let's talk about Tyra.
She's not polished.
She is very hood.
She's very street.
But the fact that she's learned
these old-school tricks
that we've seen displayed
on this stage
at such an early age
and wowed us with them--
even her tenacity to
"accidentally" rip her wig off,
you know, she's saying,
"I'm here."
- Right.
- "I'm the star."
- I love people
who are the shit
and know they are the shit.
I get both of that from--
from Tyra and Raven.
- Yeah.
- I just think her personality
is so interesting and complex.
And that is part of stardom.
- She's been able to show us
so many different looks
and be
so many different women.
- Raven is really more
the fashion-forward girl.
Raven has
undeniable star quality.
- Superstar quality.
- Mm-hmm.
You know, normally right now,
I would say
I've made my decision.
But I can't say that I have.
I must see them lip-synch
for their lives
to make my decision.
Silence.
Bring back...my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
We've reached that point
in our journey
where one path ends
and another begins.
I'm so proud
of each and every one of you.
- It almost seems like
RuPaul's got a shotgun
and is just waiting to, like,
"Okay, you're not it,
you're not it."
That's what it feels like,
a sitting duck.
- Jujubee.
You've brought a light
to this competition
week after week,
a light that nothing
and no one can extinguish.
You are a bright star.
But sadly, you are not
the next drag superstar.
I'm sorry, Juju.
- Thank you.
- We will see you soon.
But for now, sashay away.
- Bye.
I'm not bitter.
I'm disappointed.
I wish I was up there
lip-synching.
But I'm still a winner,
and I'm proud of my girls.
I'll get my time.
"Love, Juju...B."
- Tonight, my two best girls
will lip-synch to my single
Jealous of My Boogie.
- This is my first time
I'm gonna have to lip-synch.
I am so nervous right now.
- Ladies, this is your last
chance to impress me
and win the title
of America's
next drag superstar.
- I'm ready to win this shit.
- The time has come...
for you to lip-synch...
for your life.
Good luck.
And for the last time,
don't fuck it up.
[upbeat pop music]
- ♪ Don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't, don't, don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't, don't,
don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't, don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't, don't, don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't ♪
- ♪ Hey, DJ ♪
♪ Love the way ♪
♪ I lose my inhibitions ♪
♪ When you spin ♪
♪ And I don't care ♪
♪ If people stare ♪
♪ I'd rather boogie ♪
♪ Than try to fit in ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be
jealous of my boogie ♪
♪ You can say
that you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you
looking ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be
jealous of my boogie ♪
♪ You can say
that you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you
looking ♪
♪ Don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't ♪
♪ Don't, don't, don't,
don't ♪
- I just went out there
and did what I usually do
and what I've done
for most of my drag career.
This is all about me.
- ♪ Oh-ho ♪
- ♪ Turn it up ♪
♪ Let 'em scrutinize ♪
- ♪ I know you're watching ♪
- ♪ Way up ♪
♪ 'Cause the night is mine ♪
- ♪ I know you're watching ♪
- And I went
to the judges' table,
and I stood right there
in front of them.
I really gave it to them.
- ♪ Yeah, up
under flashing lights ♪
- ♪ No, no ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be
jealous of my boogie ♪
♪ You can say
that you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you
looking ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be
jealous of my boogie ♪
♪ You can say
that you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you
looking ♪
♪ I know you're watching ♪
♪ I know
you're watching ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
[laughter]
- [laughing]
Bravo, brava.
- Brava.
- That was amazing.
- Wow.
- Ladies.
I have made my decision.
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race,
America's next
drag superstar, is...
Tyra Sanchez.
[applause]
- Oh, my God.
[hyperventilating]
- Girl, turn to the camera.
You want to take your shoes off?
Girl.
Do you need someone?
Can we get someone over here,
please?
She can't breathe. Literally.
- [continues hyperventilating]
- Tyra, you're gonna be okay.
- Are you okay?
- Okay, do you need water?
Do you need--
Does she need to breathe
in the paper bag?
- [exhales deeply]
It's like I had
an out-of-body experience
and I just--
for some reason,
I forgot to breathe.
- Just relax for now, Tyra.
We're gonna get your wig
back on your head.
Take your time, baby.
Tyra, you're gonna be okay.
We're gonna continue.
Raven.
I want to thank you
from the bottom of my heart.
You are unforgettable.
And that...is so Raven.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, my dear.
Now sashay away.
- [silently] Thank you.
I came in second place.
That's an amazing thing
out of 12 people.
I'm gonna leave this competition
with my head held high.
I'm gonna go off
and do something fierce,
fabulous, fun, and funky,
the four Fs.
- My queen.
- Go girl.
Yes!
- Wear this crown with pride.
The other Tyra is dead.
Long live the new Tyra.
[applause]
All right.
- Being America's
next drag superstar
is going to change my life
dramatically.
I'll be able to take care
of Jeremiah,
and I'll be able to start
his future now.
- Tyra, let the world be
jealous of your boogie.
Now walk.
[applause]
- I am Tyra "the other Tyra"
Sanchez.
And I am America's next drag...
superstar.