- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
Reading is fundamental.
- My new book is going
to hit stores soon.
It's called Young, Broke,
and Fabulous.
- Tatianna, thank you
for being here.
- Thank you, and let me tell you
about this beverage.
- Uh, good luck.
- Fuck.
- I'm a little worried
about your confidence level.
- If you're gonna look
like a coke whore,
take the joke even further.
- Raven, you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
Two queens stand before me.
Tatianna, shantay you stay.
- Are you playing with me?
- Jessica, sashay away.
- Thank you from the bottom
of my heart.
- And tonight...
"Which one of you bitches
is my drag mother?"
The dolls get a challenge
for the ages.
- Whoa, Jesus.
- I've got a safety pin.
I thought, like, a low cut.
- And a real life lesson...
- Oh, I had dreams about this.
- I think that my drag mother
hit on me.
- With extra special
guest judges
Cloris Leachman
and Debbie Reynolds
And NYX Cosmetics' Toni Ko.
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX Cosmetics
and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com;
an exclusive one-year
PR contract
with the leading LGBT firm,
Project Publicity;
be featured in l.a.Eyeworks'
legendary designer eyewear
campaign
and headline
Logo's Drag Race tour
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks;
and a cash prize of $25,000.
And may the best woman win!
[alarm blaring]
- [groaning]
Oh, I cannot handle
your weight.
- There's only five of us left.
Jessica was the last one to go.
And it's kind of sad
because we all liked Jessica.
- Oh, mira, mira!
"I love you girls.
Viva Puerto Rico!"
I miss Jessica, but I still have
my girl Tatianna.
You know, most people here
don't agree with that situation.
- Aw, Jessica.
- I honestly thought she was
gonna be, like,
in the top three.
- Me too.
- I thought so too.
- People are upset
that Tatianna's still here.
And I was shocked too.
I was like, "Wow,
Jessica's sending Tatianna
home tonight."
- But that's not the case.
Raven loves to hear
her own voice.
- Why did you look at Ru
and go, "Really?"
- 'Cause I wasn't expecting
to be safe.
- So do you think
you shouldn't be here?
- No, I don't think
I shouldn't be here.
I just wasn't expecting
to be safe.
- But you questioned it.
- I was just pretty shocked.
[laughs]
- That lack of confidence,
that's not a superstar.
Questioning yourself
is gonna make them go,
"Okay, does she really not think
that she's that good
to be here?"
- Honestly,
I'm a little tired
of having to defend
my confidence
or my want to be here.
I could give two fucks less
what anyone has to say.
- How do you all feel
about the judges?
- Yeah, I love the judges too.
I feel like I have gotten
some mixed messages.
They want me funny,
but they want me glamorous,
but they don't,
and then they do.
He said to me, "I don't like
your style at all."
Like, where do you go
from there?
How am I ever gonna impress him
if he doesn't like my style?
[alarm sounds]
- Ooh, girl, you got shemail.
You know, a famous beauty
once said,
"After age 40,
a woman must choose
between her face and her ass."
Well, clearly this bitch
never met a drag queen.
Youth may be wasted
on the young,
but trust me, you want to be
the next drag superstar,
well, your future is staring
at you right in the face.
[engine roaring]
- Do we have to wear
a fat suit?
- Something about babies
and old people and...
- Maybe we're gonna go in
for surgery
to get our ovaries removed.
- Hello, hello, hello!
all: Hi!
- My babies,
look how far you've come.
Today your mini challenge
is all about
your beautiful baby faces.
In a moment, you'll have
to match this season's 12 queens
with their baby pictures.
The one who makes
the most matches
in the least amount of time
wins.
Raven, are you ready?
- Yep.
- Ladyboy, baby boy, go!
- All right. Yes.
Oh!
I see a little tiny baby
and a big ol' Mystique face
on it just looking up like,
"How you doin'?"
Done.
- There is definitely
an urgency
with me wanting to win
this mini challenge
just because I had
such a rough night
having to lip-sync for my life.
- Every second counts.
And where is the Puerto Rican?
- [laughing]
What the fuck is that?
- Now, you all did a great job.
I want to reveal
the correct matches.
This is of course,
Nicole Paige Brooks.
Morgan McMichaels.
Sahara Davenport.
And look at this
little lady here.
Remember her?
- Shangela.
- That's right.
Is that my little buddy
next to her right there?
- Oh, I thought that was Chucky.
- That's Sonique.
This little laddie, Tatianna.
- Yes.
all: Pandora Boxx.
- Jessica Wild.
- Doing nudes as a baby.
Oh, and look here.
- Aww, Jujubee.
- The other Tyra.
And this, of course,
is baby Mystique.
Now, I have to explain this.
Mystique lost all of her
family photos in a fire.
Now, Tyra, you got 12 right
in 57 seconds.
Jujubee, you only got ten right,
and it took a minute
and 33 seconds.
Pandora, you got 12 right
in a minute and 24 seconds.
So Tyra's still ahead.
Raven, you also got 12 right
in one minute and six seconds.
- Oh, damn.
- And, Tatianna, you got
12 right in...
51 seconds.
Congratulations.
You won the baby face
mini challenge.
Now for today's main challenge.
Life goes by so quickly.
Before you know it,
you're a golden girl.
This week, you're gonna get
a chance to grow old gracefully.
I have some special guests
I want you to meet.
Welcome, gentlemen.
Please, introduce yourselves.
- I'm Michael, a writer.
- Edward, I'm a displaced
mortgage accountant.
- Don, retired teacher
and filmmaker.
- Dustin, former
ballroom dance instructor.
- Steven May, owner
of a real estate brokerage.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
- I was just like,
"Oh, what are we doing?"
- Now, we are lucky
to live in a time
where we can be more open
and honest than ever before.
And we have these men
and their generation to thank.
Now it's your chance
to show your gratitude
by making them fabulous.
- Oh, no!
We are going to have to put
old men in drag.
- For your main challenge,
you'll transform
these silver daddies
into your drag mamas.
It's a NYX Cosmetics
golden girl makeover.
And, ladies, I expect to see
a definite family resemblance.
In addition
to your NYX Cosmetics,
you can use your own drag
plus shoes
from Le Dame Footwear
and wigs courtesy
of Wig Pro Collection.
Don't hold back, because this
is your mama we talkin' about.
Tatianna, as the baby face
mini challenge winner,
you get to pick first.
Take a closer look.
You can look at the teeth.
- Smile.
[laughter]
- Yeah, look at all of them.
"Which one of you bitches
is my drag mother?"
All right.
- Of course, Tatianna goes up
and picks the one
that I knew she'd pick:
the pretty one.
- Tatianna, you're not done yet.
Now you get to pair
the other queens
with their drag mama.
- Oh, shit, I'm gonna get
one of these two bastards
at the end.
She's giving me
one of those two.
- Hi, Mama.
- Yes.
- How are you?
- So sweet.
- Juju did whisper to me
who she wanted,
and that's my girl.
Everyone else I just kind of
was like, "You here."
- Mom!
- The Boxxes.
- You here.
- Aw, isn't that sweet?
Dustin Sanchez.
- I did consciously
leave Raven for last.
Steven, you're the mother
of Raven.
- Oh, how sweet!
- Hi, Mommy.
- Aw, that's gorgeous!
- Sure enough,
the last one I get,
the one with the full
fucking facial hair.
I'm like, "Okay, bitch,
you watch.
I'll turn
this motherfucker out."
- Now, I need you to show me
that charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
runs in the family.
Now, I'm gonna leave you
to have
a little mother-daughter
bonding time,
and I'll be back
a little bit later.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best "womens" win.
- Do you got a walk?
- I don't know how to do a walk.
- Come on, it's one, two--
- Oh, wait.
- In early gay liberation,
I did what we called skag drag.
Gender fuck.
You know, where we, like,
wear combat boots
and frilly dresses.
- I see a fierce diva
in my drag mother.
So I think that Tatianna
did a good job pairing me up.
Thank you, Tatianna.
Tss.
- This is, like,
3/4 of an inch taller,
and that's just enough to send
me into the orthopedic ward.
You know what I'm saying,
darling?
- Yes.
So Michael, um,
does have a limp.
- Whoa, Jesus.
- I think
some of the other girls
might think I made
a bad decision choosing Michael
because of his leg.
- Mm-hmm.
- But, um, who cares?
- Ouch! No way.
- Really?
- This is gonna take some work.
- Oh, man.
- I'm so excited!
The main challenge is gonna be
us turning these fabulous men
into our drag mother.
- I've got a safety pin
and I've got a spear.
I-I wear all kinds of junk
in here.
I-I put in all this stuff
for today.
- Wow.
- I thought maybe you'd do
something interesting with it,
like a low cut.
I wanted to give you
that option.
- Thank you for the option,
but we're gonna cover that up.
We're not--we're not gonna
show that off.
My mother's gonna be
sexy conservative,
fierce, confident,
and beautiful.
- I had a very interesting
experience
of being a part
of early gay liberation.
So I know what life is like
being in the closet
and out of the closet.
- The point of this challenge,
I think,
is respecting your elders,
respecting people
who have fought for you.
At the same time, encouraging
and helping someone else
to be as fierce as you are.
And my mother will not
be bearded.
- [laughs]
- Just don't think of, um,
the little Chihuahua
and the master.
That--no, no.
But if you want to do
master and slave,
that could work too.
If I want to be master...
- He's a little bit
of a dirty man.
- Oh, I had dreams about this.
- And I think that my
drag mother hit on me.
- It looks older
than I want to look.
No.
See, if we could get an
attractive-shaped one of these,
it would make my face
look a little thinner.
- I think bigger hair
would make your face
a little thinner, though.
- But didn't you see those,
though, on me?
It was just like...
- No, but you have--
just trust me.
I've been doing drag too long
to know that a flat wig
is gonna help out a big face.
- 'Cause what I was thinking--
- Were you not listening to me,
Mom?
- No!
- Just shh.
- I am a challenge.
- Michael is very theatrical.
- Because I've had a number of,
uh, injuries and health issues
that have caused my body
to look kind of beat up,
like I told you.
And that is your job,
to fix me up.
- Transforming someone older,
the face is a little bit harder
to transform.
The body may be a little bit
harder to transform.
Obviously, the skin
isn't as smooth and taut
as it is when you're younger.
- You're lucky 'cause I don't
have to shave here.
- You already take care of this?
- No, I don't have any.
- Oh, you just had it removed?
- No, it just fell out.
- Oh.
- Hello, hello, hello!
Hi.
Ooh, these gorgeous wigs.
How's it going out
with your new mommy?
- It's Contessa Touché.
- Contessa Touché.
- Mm-hmm.
- Wow, I love that.
What do you have planned
for your drag mother's outfit?
- She wants to just look
really elegant.
- Uh-huh.
- And she doesn't want to look
too old.
- Or too fat.
- Really, the only
challenging thing with Contessa
at the moment
is her confidence level.
- All right, carry on.
Hi, Raven.
- Hello.
- Hi, Steven. How are you?
- Hi, Ru.
- Does Steven
have a drag name yet?
- It's Golda Lamé.
- Golda Lamé.
Now, now, you know that this
is your challenge.
You will be judged
on this challenge.
- Yes.
Tatianna picked me last.
She thinks she's being cunty
by giving me someone
who had a full facial beard
and is a little older-looking.
I'm gonna turn it out
and show her,
"No, bitch, you didn't get it."
- All right, well, bring it.
- It's been broughten, honey T.
[laughter]
My drag mother,
if she was a woman,
would take her bra off, burn it,
never wear a high heel
in her life,
have a bush this big.
We're gonna dip her in Nair
and pull her out
and get her dressed.
- You got a lot of work to do,
so good luck.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
- Hey, Ru.
- Well, well, well.
What's going on?
- I'm already nervous
because I've never done
anyone else's makeup.
So I'm kind of scared.
I don't know how to do it,
'cause I hate
doing my own face.
- You do?
- I don't like doing makeup.
Like, I would rather sit there
and have someone do it.
- You know, you got
a lot of work cut out for you
and not a lot of time.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
All right, Tatianna.
- Hello.
- Why did you pick Michael
as your drag mama?
- Face and eyes.
- And you got to assign
all the other queens
to their drag mothers.
- Mm-hmm.
- What was your strategy?
- I really didn't have one.
- You didn't have a strategy?
- Well, Raven believes that, uh,
you chose her drag mother
because she had a beard.
- No, I mean,
you can shave a beard.
- Because, you know,
if you had,
that would've been
really fierce.
- There was a slight strategy,
but I'm not trying
to announce it to the room.
- All right, Tatianna, who uses
no strategy as her strategy,
good luck.
- Thank you.
- Pandora Boxx.
- Hello.
- And Mrs. Boxx.
- Just call me Litter.
- Oh, I love that.
Pandora and Litter Boxx.
- Yes.
- The umbilical cord
is still attached.
- Oh, dear!
Yes, that's--that's, I think,
illegal in 40 of the 50 states.
- I think it is, yes.
- Would you like to demonstrate
your walk?
- Do I have to keep
my clothes on?
- You can keep your clothes on.
- I didn't want to.
- Do it as if you were
stark naked.
Yes, show us
what you're working with.
Oh, okay.
Mama Litter.
Well, keep on keeping on.
See you, Miss Litter.
- See you.
- All right, gather around,
ladies.
Tomorrow,
our special guest judges
will include founder and CEO
of NYX cosmetics, Toni Ko,
plus two legendary
Hollywood stars--
the academy award-winning
actress Cloris Leachman...
- Oh!
- Cloris is also providing you
with clothes
from her Clorisline collection.
And last but certainly
not least,
the unsinkable
Miss Debbie Reynolds
will be here.
[laughter and applause]
- My mother is so excited.
She's like, "Oh, my God,
I love her, oh, my God!"
I'm like, "Yes,
you see that excitement
"that you have for those girls?
Now we need to put that
into our performance."
- Oh, and one more thing.
Tomorrow, in addition to your
fierce runway presentation,
you must perform a lip-sync duet
with your drag mother
to my song Main Event.
- Oh, my God.
How much more can we do
in this one challenge?
I want to cry.
- Now, good luck,
and as Mama used to say,
"Don't fuck it up."
- Your mama workin' it out?
- Oh, she is. She is.
- She workin' you out?
- She's teaching me
a new dance.
- I just want to see.
- I wanted the blue one.
- Cloris Leachman
is providing us
with her own clothing line,
called Clorisline.
And it's probably a good idea
to incorporate
something in that
since she's a judge.
- Mama, look what I got you.
- Your homework is to shave,
shave, shave, shave.
The challenge for today is,
we got a group
of older gentlemen
which we are to transform
into our drag mothers.
A lot of shaving.
- I guess it grew back.
- Just a little.
[laughs]
The twist is that we have to do
a mother-daughter lip-sync.
- ♪ All the drama takes
center stage ♪
- I yelled at my mother,
and look,
she's on the couch with her
heels on learning the song.
I said, "Bitch,
you better listen
to that shit ten times."
- ♪ Strike up the band ♪
- It's supposed to be
a mother-daughter, right?
So I'm dividing it up
between the two of us.
- I know that Michael
has ideas,
and he's definitely
making them known,
but, you know,
when it comes down to it,
I'm the one
that would be sent home,
so I have to really get
my vision out there.
My style of performing is,
I don't have a plan.
- No plan?
- When I'm by myself,
I have no plan.
- I'm confused
about whose line is what.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, where's mine?
'Cause I just wrote it down.
Let me find--
Do you--
- No, not me.
- Okay.
- Tatianna's mom looks
really pissed off.
- [sighs]
- Uh-uh, more attitude.
Do the hip.
The time has come for us to do
the runway and rehearse, honey.
We only have 20 minutes.
Hold your head up high,
miss honey.
And then right up here,
we gonna stop,
flirt, kind of rub yourself
a little bit like this, right?
Pretend you're Celine Dion.
Do you feel sexy?
Confidence.
- Uhh...
- Without confidence,
we're Tatianna.
- ♪ Disco ♪
♪ Leave your problems ♪
♪ At the front door ♪
- We both have a similar idea
of what we want to do.
- ♪ This is the main event ♪
♪ Are you ready ♪
- Michael was definitely
telling me
about how he used to work
at a disco.
So he really felt a connection
to the music.
I did so poorly last challenge,
and I really want
to make that up to the judges
and make them see
that they kept me for a reason.
I'm happy!
- Good.
- I'm just trying
to figure out clothes.
And it's really because
they haven't liked
a lot of stuff
that I've done on the runway
that I'm like, "Okay."
Just staring at my wardrobe,
thinking,
"What the fuck
am I gonna do?"
- Is this supposed
to be incorporated
into what you're creating?
- We can, we don't have to,
but I really want it to be fun
and, like, a little
over-the-top.
We are gonna be judged on
how well we transfer my essence,
the essence of Pandora.
So if my essence
is bad fashion,
then my mom's gettin'
bad fashion too.
- Rub it in.
Like, caressing your own body
and then just shoot it
out of your fingertips.
Just really extend your fingers.
- My drag mother and I
are going to do
a little cha-cha
that she taught me,
and the reason is because
when we're onstage,
the judges are going to see me
and my drag mother.
So I want them to see a part
of my drag mother in me.
Four, um, two, three--
- Oh, this is the dance.
Yeah, so it was two, three,
four, and one.
See, I've changed
the choreography already.
- While rehearsing
with my drag mother,
every time she would start
over, she would change it.
I'm a little scared.
I don't have much time
to learn,
and I don't want him
to mess up either
because he'll be dancing
in heels.
We probably need
to try that again.
- Have you ever put on
panty hose before?
- No.
- Can you do a running
back handspring?
So we get out
onto the main stage
for our 20 minutes of rehearsal.
My drag mom has bad eyes.
So I can see her standing there
and kind of, like, looking like,
"Where are you?"
as I walk out there,
and I know that the lights
are gonna be even brighter,
so I'm like, "This bitch
is not gonna be able to see
what she's doing."
Try walking by yourself.
You're so dainty about it.
[laughter]
Stop.
Put your hand on your hip
and then turn.
- Turn.
- All the way around.
- Okay.
- And then walk back.
So I'm like,
"Okay, stand there.
"Basically you follow my lead.
"Do what I do.
Don't fall off the stage."
And just stay there, yeah.
And then bring your hand down.
Put it over your heart.
She needs direction.
Like, she needs you to say,
"This is where we're going.
"This is when we're walking.
This is what we're doing."
Turn. Walk toward each other.
Is that too much for you?
- No, it's okay.
- Okay, so go to that corner
over there.
So I'm hoping she doesn't fall
or break something.
Pretty easy, right?
- Uh, no.
This is a lot to learn.
- ♪ Chapter two ♪
♪ Turn another page ♪
- We literally only had
about ten minutes
to hear the song before.
The lip-sync isn't down
for either of us.
I mean, I don't know the song,
my drag mother
doesn't know the song,
but really, it's rehearsal time,
so we have to go through
the choreography.
And then this is where
I'll pose,
and you do something
a little dirty.
- ♪ Starts to fade ♪
- Creating a monster.
- I think I am.
I think I've created a monster.
Back, Litter Boxx.
Back to your spot.
- My mother's hairy.
My mother has hairy arms,
hairy knuckles,
hairy back, and that beard
is going buh-bye.
- Raven's, uh, grooming.
- Beauty salon.
I had to shave
my fucking mother.
So you're done, Mama.
- Thank you, daughter.
- How do you feel, Mama?
- The performance
is gonna be difficult.
I wasn't expecting that.
I don't know
if I'm gonna be able
to memorize all these lyrics.
- I'm gonna go sit down.
I'm exhausted.
- Yeah, go ahead.
- None of these bitches
better die overnight.
They better not.
Gonna come back tomorrow,
"Your mother died last night."
- [laughing]
- Morning.
- Hello.
- Well, it's your day of beauty,
Mother.
- So today our challenge is,
we have to turn
a 60-year-old man
into our drag mother.
They need to embody
our persona,
and they have to perform
with us a lip-sync
to Main Event by RuPaul.
Are you excited for today?
- Yeah.
I'll be more excited
when I find out that you stay.
- It's definitely odd
to be bonding
with someone twice my age,
but I already feel very close
to my drag mom.
- It's nerve-racking.
- It is.
- [laughs]
- I've never had a drag mother
before.
I'm so happy.
- It might be easier,
because, you know,
you might get makeup on it
if you take it off after.
- Oh.
- Oh, God.
My drag mother, Litter Boxx,
has arrived in a red, white,
and blue bikini.
- You blowin' me?
- All I thought is,
"Just do the makeup.
"Do the makeup, Pandora.
Don't look."
- Who is Oscar Wilde?
- I went--who is Oscar Wilde?
Who is Oscar Wilde?
- Oh, my gosh, are you serious?
- Who is Oscar Wilde?
- That's no homosexual
over there.
- We are here to educate
the young.
- She told me, and I was like,
"Great, fantastic."
- There is a pantheon
one should learn.
- Look straight up
at the ceiling.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, I'm sure he knows
Harvey Milk with all the--
- Yes.
- Can y'all stop talking to her?
'Cause she needs to close
her eyes.
- Okay.
- Well, he can close his eyes
and talk at the same time.
- Well, obviously she can't,
because she's opening her eyes.
I was just like, "Mom,
get your shit together!"
- I'm just a little worried
about the time constraint,
getting not only myself
but Annalisha ready too.
- And then pull that up.
I'm getting my mom dressed,
and I realized that Mom
doesn't have the body
that I need Mom to have.
[duct tape ripping]
So I took duct tape and I put
duct tape all around Mom
just to give her the hips
that she needed
and that she deserved.
- No, I'm not.
- [laughs]
- [laughing]
Hello, judges.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hello, Ru.
- Well, well, well,
Cloris Leachman, darling,
how are you?
- Excellent, thank you.
- Santino, how are you tonight?
- You are making a spectacle
of yourself, Ru.
- Really?
- And I love it. I love it.
- Merle, what about you?
How are you doing?
- I am just freaking out
over my fine feathered friend.
- Aw, you're sweet.
Debbie Reynolds, you are
and you will always be
America's sweetheart.
Thank you for being here.
- Thank you for having me here.
- Toni Ko, you're finally here.
- How are you?
- The girls love NYX Cosmetics.
It's fantastic!
Well, we have a show for you
tonight.
This week, our ladies
were challenged
to transform a silver fox
into a golden girl.
Are you ready for a little
mother-daughter fashion show?
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win!
This is Raven and her
drag mother, Golda Lamé.
- She's totally freaked out
about walking.
I just was very nervous
that she was gonna fall.
I mean, doesn't walk in heels,
but she's sparkling,
and she's loving it.
- Mama mia!
[laughter]
A cougar and her cub.
Pandora Boxx and her
drag mother, Litter Boxx.
This is the Boxx family.
- And she's gonna show us
her box later?
[laughter]
- Oh, dear God.
- I'm feeling really good
about our outfits.
They're kind of, like,
you know, showgirl today,
showgirl yesterday.
There's sense of comedy
about it.
- It's 10:00.
Do you know where your
drag mother is?
This is Jujubee
and the Contessa Touché.
- My drag mother
is feeling spectacular.
She has stepped
into the boundary of Jujubee,
and she feels wonderful.
- "I'm pretty, Mama.
I'm a pretty girl."
Tatianna and her drag mother,
Annalisha.
- My drag mother
does have a limp,
but, um, she's pushing
through it,
and she's not letting it
stop her.
[laughter]
- No, you are gonna phone me
later.
- Tyra Sanchez and her mother,
Big Tyra.
- My drag mother was having
a very good time on the runway.
She has the attitude,
she has the walk,
and she has the smile.
She was very comfortable
and confident in drag.
- The apple bottom don't fall
far from the tree.
[laughter]
- It's time for our mothers
and daughters
to make their performance debut.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the main event!
♪ Here we go again ♪
♪ Chapter two ♪
♪ Turn another page ♪
♪ I'm walking in the rain ♪
♪ Paint a smile upon my face ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't let ♪
♪ The spotlight ♪
♪ See the heartbreak ♪
♪ In my love life ♪
♪ When the laughter
starts to fade ♪
♪ All the drama
takes center stage ♪
[laughter]
- It's so important to have
a little trick up your sleeve,
especially at this point
in the game.
- ♪ When you step
into the disco ♪
Whoo!
♪ Leave your problems
at the front door ♪
- My drag mother's funny,
and we had a good rapport.
We're having fun, we're campy,
and I'm thinking
that I'm giving the judges
what they want.
- ♪ This is the main event ♪
♪ Are you ready ♪
- I wasn't nervous at all
because we rehearsed it
and we were very confident
in our routine.
She just let loose,
and she wowed the judges
and put a smile
on everyone's face.
And so I thought it went great.
- ♪ Strike up the band ♪
♪ Bang the drum ♪
♪ Like the beat of my heart ♪
- After we've run through it,
you know, a million times,
and she freezes kind of,
and I'm like,
"Mom, my place
in the competition
is on the line
if we don't get this right."
And it looks messy.
- ♪ Faster, faster ♪
♪ Exhilaratin' ♪
Go, mamas! Go!
- I can tell
she's getting tired.
And I can sense, like,
she's not gonna make it back.
So as the music ends,
I grab her and take her
to the back.
- Yay!
[cheers and applause]
- 'Cause, I mean,
I would do that for my mom.
- Gorgeous!
- Will they do that for me
when I leave here?
- Yes, they will, absolutely.
- Thank you. That'd be good.
- Hello, ladies.
RuPaul's Drag Race,
the next generation.
I'm having a senior moment...
and I'm loving it!
Raven, let's start with you.
- This is Ms. Golda Lamé.
- Let's take a look
at your drag mother before.
Ooh!
- Wow!
- We used a dark brown
eye shadow.
We didn't want to use pencil
because it looks a little harsh.
- I can see that you're wearing
the exact same makeup.
- I am.
- You guys coordinate
without matching too much,
and it works
for both body types.
- Your lip-sync
was very, very good too,
which I noticed right away,
because in films,
that's what we always did.
I mean, people thought
we were really singing.
Well, we did sing, but we had
to then sing to our record,
so it's not easy
to lip-sync correctly,
and you did a super job.
And I've never seen anybody
quite dance like the mother.
You won't give Ginger Rogers
any contest, you know?
[laughter]
- Raven, is there anything
you want to say?
- Thank you for this experience
and for allowing me to work
with Steven.
I respect Steven so much
because he did a lot
as far as the gay rights
liberation.
I thank you.
- Thank you.
- Aw!
[applause]
- It's because
of people like Steven
that we are able
to do this show.
Pandora Boxx, please introduce
your drag mother.
- This is my drag mother,
Litter Boxx.
- Aw!
Hi, Litter.
Welcome.
Now, Pandora, your drag mother
also has a reputation
for being a nudist.
- It's a lot easier
being a nudist
than it is being a drag queen.
- I agree.
[laughter]
- Is she wearing her Clorisline
panties underneath the outfit?
- She is--I hope she's wearing
some panties.
- Now let's take a look
at your drag mother before.
Wow.
- I wanted her to look like
a more mature version of me.
I wanted to do a softer liner.
- You look like me!
- I thought so too!
- I love the high energy
and the comedy,
and I love Mom coming out
and giving us attitude
and you pulling her back like,
"Oh, I'm so embarrassed."
- Mom was wanting to shine
and give more and more,
and you were kind of
pulling her back,
and that was--
- Had the mother been drinking?
[laughter]
- Jujubee.
- This is my mother,
Contessa Touché.
- Oh, wow.
- We're going
for the natural look.
- Yes, of course.
- Of course.
I did do a little eye shadow
to just kind of cut
into the cheek,
down the rims of the nose.
I used my Ru glue
to cover the eyebrows.
- I really wish Mama
would have had a longer do.
- The one thing that I thought
you did too much of was,
your mouth was open so wide,
and all the words--
lip-syncing, you don't need
to do that.
- Mama's lip-sync kind of
fell apart in a couple places.
- Tatianna.
- This is Annalisha.
- Ooh!
- Wow!
- We actually used a little bit
of, like, a red lipstick
to counteract the beard color.
I used the pink blush
on the apples of the cheek
just to give a little flush.
- I would've used
a brighter color lips.
- Older ladies do not wear
dark brown lips
unless they're Judy Davis.
- I thought your lip-sync
was very good.
The walker killed me.
I loved it a lot.
- Your facial expression too,
I loved it.
I thought it added
to the whole performance.
- You were really funny.
- Thank you.
- Tyra Sanchez.
- My drag mother's name
is Tyra,
which makes me
the other Tyra.
- That's right.
- Oh!
- I mixed a couple
of the colors together
to get her skin color,
and then I took
some of the blush
and I put just a little
on her cheeks,
and I put, like, a nice
metallic silver onto her bone
to make her eyes stand out
a little bit more.
- There's a lot of fun
in that hair.
Your style translated
onto your mother.
You're the only one who really
did identical outfits.
- I should've known you'd have
a classy Park Avenue
fashionable mother.
On Mom, though, I might have
toned the lip down.
The makeup's a little heavy.
- Now, Debbie Reynolds
is quite the hoofer.
- I knew you'd--I knew
she'd pick right up on that.
The dancing,
it was exceptional,
choreography, the stage work.
The mother, with the hair,
could've been a little less,
but then, you know, uh,
that's the kick of it.
- Thank you, ladies.
Now, while you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
[engine starting]
All right, just between
us girls.
First up, we had Raven.
- Raven did a great job
with the transformation.
Her mother did look like Raven.
- She did have
the essence of Raven.
What really carried the day
for me
is that Raven seemed
so protective of her mother,
who's a tiny little person
who couldn't walk in heels,
and we haven't seen that many
sweet sides to Raven,
and the mother brought out
the sweetness in her.
- You just kind of really felt
a kinship growing.
It's gonna be
a buddy system there.
- That's what we're about here
at RuPaul's Drag Race:
putting families together.
Pandora Boxx and her mother.
- Pandora's mother, Litter Boxx,
actually was funnier
and kind of stole the show.
- And I thought the mother
was really playing a part too.
She was playing the tough mama.
- Her mother kind of
showed her up a little bit.
- Jujubee.
Cloris, you commented
that her mouth was just open.
She was doing the old trick,
"Peas and carrots," you know,
when you don't know the words?
- It put me off
because it was so exaggerated
that it wasn't real.
- Well, that's what I'm looking
for in my drag queens:
realness.
- They both look very beautiful
and exotic,
but I just did not like
that hair.
- Tatianna.
- I had so many other things
written on other people
that I only have "wheelchair"
written there,
and if you can make anything
out of that...
[laughter]
And wonderful design, I think,
of the dresses.
- I have to say, I liked her
mother's dress better than hers.
I thought that long dress
made the mother look
like she had a great,
sexy body.
- Really, overall,
I think Tatianna
might have pulled it out
this week.
- Tyra Sanchez.
- I just thought Tyra
was so beautiful,
even though
you didn't ask me yet.
[laughter]
- Well, this is the--
this is the moment now.
Oh, you're giving a--
- Ooh!
- Oh!
I did think the mother's makeup
was a little crazy exaggerated.
- Well, I'm with Cloris.
I vote ten.
They were very chic.
I didn't like the mother's wig,
of course not,
but obviously, it was
a little bit of humor there.
- So is that a ten or what?
- I vote for a ten, yeah.
- Ten, that's three tens.
[laughter]
- Okay, silence.
I have made my decision.
Bring back the girls.
Welcome back.
At this point, it's not about
who's the worst.
It's about who's the best
of the best,
the next drag superstar.
Tyra Sanchez, the other Tyra,
you proved that two Tyras
are better than one.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Tatianna, this week,
you came from behind
and rolled over the competition.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Pandora Boxx,
you're a funny girl,
but tonight you were
outperformed.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I thought that I was campy
and fun.
I really gave it my all.
I really, really worked hard.
It's like a kick in the balls.
- Raven, for giving
the most dramatic makeover
and literally carrying
Golda Lamé,
proving that she ain't heavy;
she's your mama--
Raven, congratulations,
you're the winner
of this week's challenge.
- Thank you.
[applause]
- You and your drag mother
have won a four-day,
three-night stay and massage
at the luxurious East Canyon
Hotel and Spa in Palm Springs.
- I felt so amazing,
and I knew that Tatianna
was back there
just grinding her toenails
in the tip of her fucking heel.
Thank you, Tatianna,
for picking out my mother.
- Jujubee, you are
a special queen.
But tonight, you and your
mother were out of sync.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I'm in the bottom,
and I can't blame anybody
but myself.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-sync for your life.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Shake your love ♪
♪ I just can't shake
your love ♪
♪ Shake your love ♪
♪ I just can't shake
your love ♪
♪ Shake your love ♪
♪ I just can't shake ♪
♪ I just can't shake
your love ♪
- It's really
kind of heart-wrenching
to lip-sync with Juju
because I love Juju,
but I really want to prove
that I've got what it takes.
- ♪ Shake your love ♪
♪ I just can't shake
your love ♪
- It's hard to try
to beat your friend.
It's a weird position to be in.
- ♪ Shake it ♪
♪ Your love ♪
- I look at Pandora.
No, I don't see a star
in her at all.
- ♪ Love ♪
♪ Do-do do-do do-do do-do ♪
♪ Do-do do-do do-do ♪
♪ Do-do-do do-do ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Shake your love ♪
♪ I just can't shake ♪
♪ I just can't shake
your love ♪
♪ Shake your love ♪
♪ I just can't shake ♪
[applause]
- Bravo! Bravo!
- Okay, I've made my decision.
Jujubee...
shantay you stay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Pandora, you shared
your talents
and opened your box
for the world to see.
There's no stopping you.
Now sashay away.
[applause]
[laughter]
- It's hard to constantly get
harsh criticism,
especially when you feel like
they're being harsher on you
than everybody else.
I did really want to win.
But what I brought here wasn't
what they were looking for.
Fuck 'em.
- Four queens remain.
Congratulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get a amen in here?
all: Amen.
- All right, let the music play.