- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
For the first time ever,
each of you will be singing
live.
[feedback whines]
- This ain't working.
- I think Tatianna definitely
knows she's the weakest one.
- Y'all ready to rock and roll?
- [screaming]
- ♪ This is for my girls... ♪
- This is a Headbanger's Ball.
- [screams]
- [mumbling words]
I am screwing up RuPaul's song
right in front of her face.
- Two queens stand before me.
Jujubee, Shante, you stay.
Sahara Davenport,
sashay away.
And tonight...
Reading is fundamental.
The library is open.
- Oh, Ru, we have a under-grown
orangutan.
- And the dolls get
a real education...
- If you don't know
what a golden shower is,
that's very naive.
- With extra-special
guest judges
best-selling authors
Jackie Collins
and Gigi Levangie Grazer...
And Absolut Vodka's
Jeffrey Moran.
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Nyx Cosmetics
and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com,
an exclusive
one-year P.R. contract
with the leading LGBT firm
Project Publicity,
be featured in L.A. Eyeworks'
legendary designer
eyewear campaign,
and headline Logo's
Drag Race Tour,
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks,
and a cash prize
of $25,000.
And may the best woman win.
- ♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ Ru-Ru-RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ best woman win ♪
[alarm beeps]
- Oh.
- Look at this.
- "Live, love, believe.
Sahara."
It's your fault.
That why she is not here.
- How did it feel to finally
lip-synch for your life?
- I don't want to talk
about that.
Oh, my gosh.
The last challenge I...
sucked.
I never want to lip-synch
for my life ever again...
ever.
- You said you used to do
musicals in high school, right?
- I did.
- How were people with you
in high school?
- I was everybody's friend,
really.
I didn't really have...
- Were you out in high school?
- Yeah, totally.
Like, how--how the hell
am I gonna hide that?
[laughs]
- I got picked on
in high school.
They used to throw papers at me
and stuff.
Everyone referred to me
as "that gay boy James."
- In Spanish,
the word are more bad.
[speaking Spanish]
- You want to hear it
in my language?
- What?
- [speaking native language]
Doesn't that sound dirty?
Imagine being called that
by your uncle.
- Yes.
- Wow.
- When I was young, I--
everybody have fun about me,
because I'm gay.
I want to take dance class
before,
and I can't, because I'm scared
that my mom said,
"My son is gay?"
- I tried to kill myself.
- Oh, no, sir.
- I didn't understand.
I didn't know what gay was.
I knew I was totally different.
I felt totally alone.
I hated myself, for,
like, years,
and I thought that, you know,
"Well,
"I'll just take all these pills,
because I don't--
I can't deal with it anymore."
- I was pretty shocked
when Pandora shared
that she attempted suicide,
and she was really, really
depressed.
- But there's still,
once in a while,
that little voice that says,
"Oh, no one likes you,"
or, "You're not good enough."
And it's tough.
I mean, I don't think
it ever goes away.
The adversity that
I've gone through being gay
has made me stronger
and really has made me
who I am today,
and I'm really happy
with who I am.
- Can I get a amen up in here?
- Amen.
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl,
you've got shemail.
[laughs]
Oh.
Hey, racers.
I want to read you
a little story
called Drag Fun
with Dick and Jane.
"See Dick.
"See Dick try on Jane's pumps.
"Strut, Dick, strut.
"You better work, Dick.
And they lived 'draggily'
ever after."
Now, that's my kind
of fairy tale.
What's your story?
Hello, hello, hello.
- Hello!
- Hi!
- My exceptional girls.
Now, as drag queens,
we shrug off a lot of insults.
So when we get our chance
to throw an insult,
we turn it into a high art form.
We call it reading,
or throwing shade,
and it's part of our culture.
For today's mini-challenge,
you will read
your fellow queens.
The library is open.
- I don't read people.
- Of course you don't, Tyra,
'cause you're Christian.
Come over here, girl.
Here are your reading glasses.
Now, what I want you to do
is go down the line.
I want you to read
these bitches.
Read. Starting with Tati.
- Oh, wow.
We have Eminem doing drag, mama.
- Oh.
- Oh, wow.
And standing right next to her--
is that Dumbo flying in?
Oh, mama.
Is this Jujubee?
Darling,
let me get to your level.
- Oh!
- Oh, Ru, we have
a under-grown orangutan.
- Oh, and next to her--
Darling, how old are you?
And the one on the end?
Oh, just look at her, Ru.
Are you going swimming,
or are you doing drag, mama?
What is that?
- Wonderful.
The library is closed.
Tatianna, come on down, honey.
The library is open.
- Ugh. I don't want to do this.
- Go.
Smile for me.
Don't smile.
Do you pick up satellite
with those big ones?
[suspenseful music]
I can't do this.
- Dig deep, darling.
- I just couldn't think of
anything to say.
That's totally not my scene.
I'm lost. I'm gone.
- Tatianna got up there
and froze.
She runs her mouth about people,
but doesn't talk
when she absolutely has to.
I'm shocked
Tatianna's still here.
- The library is now open.
- You think that is big?
You need to see another thing
that I have for you, bitch.
You are so fat, girl.
[laughter]
What are you doing here, mama?
Go back to Chinatown, girl.
You are a gringa, puerca.
- Oh. Oh.
- You, the top model?
When I see your face,
I said [speaks Spanish].
- La biblioteca is closed.
All right, Jujubee.
- I'm not nervous.
I'll read a bitch.
I will read you to filth.
Miss Tyra,
was your barbecue cancelled?
Your grill is fucked up.
And, Miss Tatianna, Miss honey.
You think you're so soft.
Not by the hairs
of your chinny chin chin.
[laughter]
And let me tell you something,
puerca.
You won't understand this
anyways.
[speaking native language]
Get my gist?
Do ya understand?
Pandora...
Can we talk about sun tanning?
And you!
Legendary, you think you are.
Legendary?
Looks like leg and dairy.
- Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
The library is closed.
Oh.
Okay.
Pandora Boxx.
- Tyra Sanchez,
if you are America's sweetheart,
America needs
a heart transplant.
Tatianna,
all I hear when I put my ear
up to yours is the ocean.
Jessica Wild.
Those drag clothes look like
a donkey funked a piñata
and threw up.
Jujubee,
with that gaping thing
you call an asshole,
I think I could go spelunking
in there.
- [gasps]
Spelunking.
- Raven, the frosty bitch.
I think I see penguins
circling that pole.
- The library is closed.
Ready for the flavor
of the Raven?
- You got a grill that could
put Black &amp; Decker
out of business.
- Ooh!
- Everyone thinks you're pretty.
I do think you're pretty.
I think you have
a beautiful face...
for radio.
- Oh, oh, ooh, ooh.
- You want to call me
a top model, mami?
Bend over and take it
like a man.
I'll be your top...
model.
- Oh, that's cold.
That's cold.
- Honey,
don't you know a thing about
doing a manicure
and a pedicure?
Fix them hooves, honey.
Pandora,
by the looks of you,
you're going through the change
of life, honey.
- Oh, oh, oh.
She done closed the libraries.
Ooh, child.
I need to duck and cover,
'cause y'all bitches is throwing
beaucoup shade.
But the winner is...
Jujubee.
- I win! Finally!
- Congratulations, miss thing.
Now, I wanted to take
this moment
to introduce you to
Absolut image czar
Jeffrey Moran.
- Hey, ladies. How are you?
- Hi.
- To be the best,
you have to be daring enough
to do things
a little differently,
and we've done that recently
with a brand-new flavor
that we're gonna debut here--
Berri Acai.
And what we want from you today
is just that.
We want you to be
a little different,
a little exceptional,
because just like you,
we believe that in
an Absolut world,
every cocktail is
an exceptional experience.
- Now, ladies,
"exceptional"
is the word of the week.
Now, I've had the chance
to write two books
about my own
exceptional life experiences,
including my recent book,
Working It:
RuPaul's Guide to Life,
Liberty,
and The Pursuit of Style.
Writing a book is a great way
to let people know
who you really are.
For this week's main challenge,
you need to come up with
your own book,
an autobiography,
that highlights
the most exceptional moments
in your life.
They should shed light on
who you really are.
Now, later on,
you'll be working with
a team of photographers,
Idris and Tony, to create
the perfect book cover.
And I'll be back a little later
to check on your progress.
Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- Jujubee.
- This is my creative
inspiration, okay?
- That's your thinking cap?
- It's my--
it's my thinking hat.
- Our main challenge today
is to come up with a concept
of what our book would be
and then design the cover
for the book.
- This challenge is so different
from all the other challenges,
because it's about us letting
people know who we are.
- I dedicate my book to Beyoncé.
- [laughs]
- This might be the turning
point for some people.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hello.
- How's your autobiography,
Miss Jane Pittman?
Do you have a title
for your book?
- The Woman in Me.
- Is this funny? Serious?
- It's more serious.
It's, like, how the woman,
which is Tyra,
helped me, like, get back to
loving people
and understanding people and
allowing people to love me back.
As a teenager,
I made mistakes.
I was out on the streets.
I had a son on the way.
So it was, like,
a little scary.
And to express it and put it out
has been a little challenging.
- Now, the cover of your book,
any ideas?
- I don't have any yet.
- If you want to be
behind this book,
you have to own it here.
Any questions?
- Nope. None.
- Okay.
Hey, Miss Raven.
- Hello.
- Do you have a title
for your book?
- Young, Broke, and Fabulous.
- [gasps]
I love it.
- My favorite chapter is LTR--
long-term relationship.
The long-term relationship
I found
is the relationship with myself.
- Ooh, you're getting close
to home here.
- Yes, girl.
- Well, I would just advise you
to strategize
who you see buying this book.
[both speaking Spanish]
Now, what's your book about?
- A kid.
He always have dreams,
daydreams,
and at the end,
all those dreams
he make come true.
- Well, you know,
there are a lot of dreamers.
I just want to make sure
that the people know
that this book is about
Jessica Wild.
And a gorgeous picture
on the cover.
A title that's kind of funny
to say or cheeky.
So think about those things,
okay?
- All right.
All right.
I'm very worry
about my own thing.
I'm thinking in Spanish and
writing in English,
and I don't have a lot of time
for work on this.
- Hi, Tatianna.
- Hello.
- Tell me the title
of your book.
- It's called Tati:
From Teen Queen
to Drag Superstar.
- Sounds salacious.
- It's about my life
prior to becoming Tatianna.
I started doing drag
when I was 14.
I came out in fifth grade.
- Well, it's a great story.
And a lot of people need to hear
that story.
How are you gonna convey that
on your book cover?
- I just want me on,
like, a big, huge stage.
I absolutely think people can
learn something from my story.
And I might have a little bit
more experience
than other people
give me credit for.
- All right,
so get back to your makeup,
and make a real pretty cover.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Hey, Pandora.
- Hey.
- So what's the title
of your book?
- Out of the Boxx.
- Hello.
- It's about discovering myself
through dressing up
like somebody else.
- Mm.
- And really kind of finding
your inner strength,
and not listening to that voice
that says
you're not good enough.
There's a couple times that
I had tried to kill myself.
- Oh, honey.
Was there a turning point?
- Through theater
and discovering that,
I kind of felt people
that were like me,
and that's when
I discovered drag,
and I started to come out
of my shell
and be more open
and like myself more.
- So you can honestly say,
"drag saved my life."
- Yes.
- I always think of you
as the funny one,
the Goldie Hawn of the group,
and now it's--
it's interesting.
You tell me the story of
your dark night of the soul.
It adds depth to your character.
- I think that with a
lot of people that are funny
and a lot of comedians, there is
some darkness that's there,
because that's what they use to
combat that, was their humor...
- Sure.
- And their laughter.
- It's such a pleasure
to meet you.
I've read all your books.
[both laughing]
What's the title we have there?
- Memoirs of a Gay-sha:
Jujubee's Journey,
and I'm Still Here.
- Jujubee's Journey,
- My target audience
for my book is gay Asians.
When you're a gay Asian male,
they don't see you as that.
They see you as a woman who
was born into the wrong body.
That's definitely not me.
It basically starts out
with my childhood,
the discovery
of my homosexuality.
- Wait a minute. Hold up.
- I know, right?
- Your homosexuality?
- I know, girl.
And then I touch on, you know,
like, the loss of my father,
and then my move across America.
- How do you say "fierce"
in Laotian?
- I would just say Juju.
- Juju.
[laughter]
- Juju, huh?
- All right, ladies.
For your main challenge,
in addition to
your book cover photo shoot,
you'll be doing an interview
with celebrity journalist
Marc Malkin.
This is a really great time for
you to show off your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve,
and talent.
You'll also be judged
on your ability
to seamlessly work in plugs
for your upcoming book,
as well as
the Berri Acai Absolut cocktail.
The more you can plug your book
and the Berri Acai,
the better.
Now, tomorrow on the main stage,
our special guest judges will be
two best- selling authors--
Gigi Levangie Grazer...
and the one and only
Jackie Collins.
Lucky, lucky, lucky bitches.
- Jackie Collins.
Are you serious?
She embodies what a diva is.
- And to quote
one of my favorite authors...
Don't fuck it up.
- The main challenge today
is to take photos
for the cover
of our autobiography
and do an interview.
- How you doing?
I'm Idris.
- Tyra.
- Nice to meet you.
- Tony.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- What would you like to do
today?
- Well, the title of my book
is The Woman in Me.
- They're in charge.
They're supposed to direct us
and tell us their vision.
- It's not just about a dress,
you know,
or how the girl looks.
they've got to commit
to their concept.
- The concept is three pictures
of me--
me holding on to the past,
accepting the present,
and looking towards the future.
I don't know how the other girls
are at photos,
but I'm very photogenic.
- You're melting
under these lights.
- It was burning hot.
All my makeup
started sweating off.
I was like, "Oh, shit."
- 30 seconds.
- Tyra's just--
she was melting.
If she were doing a workout book
where you had to be sweaty,
then, yeah,
it would be great.
- I was thinking of taking
the chest that's over there...
- Okay.
- And having me
coming out of it.
- All right.
So let's get the stuff.
- I want my book cover
to be funny,
and my concept is to have myself
coming out of a box.
Lust over me, bitches.
- Okay.
- All right,
so what are we doing?
- One here, one here.
- Just think about your time.
- If you guys want to,
like, face away,
and then just kind of glancing
over at me like, "Damn."
- Okay.
- Now, how do you want them
looking at you,
'cause right now they're kind of
looking at you
like you're crazy.
- No, like you want me.
[laughter]
I can't look at the pit crew
and direct them,
because I'm supposed to be
looking at the camera.
And they weren't
very cooperative.
So finally I was just, like,
"Get the hell away from me."
- Hello.
- Okay, I want to be sitting
at a yard sale,
and I want to sit
in that pink chair.
I knew my idea
for my book cover.
I'm at a yard sale.
I've got to find the shit
and get it together.
I want the award,
the radio,
the bust, and then this phone
right here.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- What's the idea
for the book cover?
- I just want to look good.
- Whatever you want.
- Let's try to work
this shit out.
- Okay.
- That's mannish, isn't it?
- You look a little wide.
- Ooh.
- Jujubee could have used her
time more wisely.
She had extra minutes.
- You know, she came
out with one prop,
a fan in her hand,
and half the time,
that fan was on the floor.
What are you thinking about
right now?
- About my dreams.
- It kind of looks like you're
just standing there staring off,
so you really have to think
about all of your dreams
and let that come out.
[camera shutter clicking]
Honey, why don't you think about
something else,
'cause it looks a little...
- All right.
Oh, my God.
I love doing things perfect.
And I think I lost things
from my hands,
you know?
- What were your other ideas?
- What?
- You wanted to use
some other props?
- She kind of came in defeated.
- And if you come in defeated,
then you are defeated.
Think about something that would
pertain to your dreams.
- Can I take it?
- Yeah, of course.
You can take anything you want
from here.
- Nice. There you go.
Believe in it.
- I believe.
- What is this?
This thing is caught
onto my dress,
and I can't take my dress off.
They have to stop my time.
Immediately after photo shoot,
you have less than five minutes
to change
and get to the interview.
Jessica.
- What?
- Is it okay if I put on your
corset really quick?
- Yeah.
- Now I have more pressure.
Now I have a bigger challenge
to know that I only have
such and such amount of time,
and I need to get this done.
- There was a lot that went into
this challenge.
Tatianna didn't change
her costume at all.
She went straight from her
photo shoot to her interview.
I didn't really see an effort
in that.
- We need to talk about the book
or about drag life?
- The book and the alcohol
is the main focus.
The two really important things
during the interview
is that we have to pitch
the book
and the Berri Acai
Absolut vodka.
- How do you say
that berry drink?
"Acia"?
Berri Ac--
- It's acai.
- Acai.
- Acai?
A-ca-I.
- Guys, is it "Berri Acai,"
or "acai berry"?
- We're going to have
an interview
with celebrity reporter
Marc Malkin,
and as I sit down in the seat
and there's just a camera
in front of me
and they start to put
the earpiece in,
I realize
this is a satellite interview.
He's not going to be here.
- Oh, my god.
There's nobody here?
And he can see me.
But I can't see him.
- Hi, Raven.
- Hi.
Where's the guy at?
- What's going on?
- Is this via satellite?
- It is satellite.
Why should you win
RuPaul's Drag Race?
- Well, first of all, I'm young,
broke, and fabulous.
My new book
is going to hit stores soon.
- What's this new book?
- It's called Young, Broke,
and Fabulous.
- I have the full package.
I have personality,
I have sense of style,
and I have great, big,
white teeth.
- Why are you better
than the other girls?
- I'm better because I'm
Jessica Wild, and I'm unique.
- Now, with all these
drag queens living toge--
- Oh, I love that Absolut acai.
Oh, my God.
- So how many times have
straight men hit on you?
- Every time I've gone out
in drag,
I've gotten hit on
by a straight guy.
Sometimes I'll be like,
"Back it up.
I'm a dude."
If they're just
giving a compliment,
I just say, "Thank you."
So I must be doing something
right.
- It's so exciting to be a part
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
It's almost as exciting as
my new book, Out of the Boxx.
- The book is called
The Woman in Me.
I know how to love,
know how to give, and celebrate,
like I am with this berry
...drink from Absolut.
- I just got finished
writing a memoir,
and I call it
Memoirs of a Gay-sha.
- Where do you hide your candy?
- There's a lot of candy going
on down here.
It's not true what they say
about Asians, honey.
- Every once in a while,
I'll have a cocktail.
My drink of choice
is the Berri Acai from Absolut.
- Do you always drink
when you're doing media?
- No, it's my first time,
but I love that drink.
- What kind of vodka is it?
- Berri Acai vodka.
- Berry Absolut.
- Berri Acai.
- Tatianna,
thank you for being here.
- Thank you.
And let me tell you
about this beverage.
- Oh, good luck. Got to go.
- The only thing
I might have screwed up on
is not mentioning the book.
But everything else, I felt like
I was--I was on point.
- Jessica,
thanks for being here.
- Thanks,
and I have my new book.
- What was that?
- The name is Jessica Wild:
The Dreams of a Golden Child.
- Fantastic.
Thanks, Jessica.
Good luck.
- I love that drink.
- Hola, hola.
- How your hooves be, Juju?
- How's the leg and dairy?
- Yesterday we had to read
each other.
I actually like
all of the queens that are here,
and to read them,
you kind of have to
make fun of them.
- I'm sure everyone's
had a little inkling
of their feelings hurt.
If anyone was offended,
I'm sorry
that I spoke the truth.
- I wasn't offended.
If you can't laugh at yourself,
then go home.
- It's hard to talk shit
about flawlessness.
[laughs]
- Since Morgan's been gone,
Raven all of a sudden decides
that she wants to blossom
verbally.
- Tatianna, did you just
not want to do it?
- No, I just couldn't
stop laughing.
These sparkling 30 years
that she's got behind her,
there's just so much there
that she just can't hold it in.
She's just got to spread it.
- Like, Tatianna froze
and didn't read anyone really.
Do you think they're gonna
look at her and be like,
"What's going on, girl?"
- Raven might have been trying
to rattle my cage.
I think that she's been hoping
that I go from day one.
I did well.
I didn't drop my book.
I got the drink in.
I just completely forgot
about the book.
- Tatianna's an airhead.
She should have been in
the bottom two last week.
All she's been doing
the past couple weeks is this.
Just my opinion.
- Thank you.
- ♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
- Hello, judges.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hey.
- Santino, how are you tonight?
- We're gonna have a great show.
- We are.
- Now, Merle,
are you ready to hear from
our budding authors?
- I'm very, very excited.
- Gigi.
- Hi, Ru.
- Hi, darling.
Now, your most recent novel,
Queen Takes King,
maybe after tonight
you can write a sequel.
- Queen Takes Queen?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Co-write it.
- Done. Done and done.
And my buddy Jackie Collins
is here.
Hi, darling.
- Hi, darling.
- I love the title
of your new book,
Poor Little Bitch Girl.
That's great!
- I should have dedicated it
to you.
- You should have.
And Absolut's image czar,
the exceptional
Jeffrey Moran.
- Hello, darling.
- All right.
Inspired by my new book,
Working It:
RuPaul's Guide to Life,
Liberty, and the Pursuit
of Style,
this week,
the ladies were challenged
to pitch us their autobiography,
design a book cover,
and field questions
from an entertainment reporter.
Tonight they're dressed
to the nines
for their book launch party.
Judges, are you ready
to take a look?
- Ready.
- Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Tyra Sanchez,
the other Tyra.
- The dress that I chose
is very skin-tight.
You can actually see the shape
of my body.
- Is Jennifer Lopez
missing something?
- She is missing something,
and she'll never get it back.
[laughter]
- I know the judges
look forward to me
transforming my look.
- Oh, yes.
Style proper, Sanchez.
[cheers and applause]
Oh!
- No, she didn't.
- Poor little bitch girl.
- I'm glad my boyfriend's
not here.
I would have just lost him
on that one.
[laughter]
- Jujubee.
Now, Gigi,
is this a starter wife?
- That's the finisher wife.
I don't think anyone
would ever leave that.
- I always make eye contact
with every single judge.
It's, like, the complete
opposite of shade.
It's the "hey, hey, hey" look.
- Oh, yes.
Tatianna.
Ooh, it's a jailbreak.
- [gasps]
You know, they say never wear
horizontal stripes
unless you're Tatianna.
- I'm not really super
glammed-out
like the other girls,
but I'm thinking
I look really good.
- Pandora Boxx.
[gasps]
Oh, darling, yes.
She's full of surprises.
- I'm going down the runway,
and I'm thinking glamour.
but, you know,
there's still that element
of fun.
- If Courtney Love looked
like a woman...
- Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
[laughter]
- Jessica Wild.
- Now, she looks like a heroine
from one of my books.
- Which one, Jackie?
- Lucky Santangelo.
- Jessica Santangelo.
- Today is my party.
I love that dress.
- Jessica Wild
from Puerto Rico.
Raven.
Oh, darling.
That's so not Raven.
[laughter]
- I decided to go with
something
a little more super glam.
I feel like I should be
in Greek mythology,
and they should write a story
about me.
- A star is born again.
- She has a politician lover
on the side.
- Disco scandalous.
Hello, ladies.
My Valley of the Dolls.
Tyra Sanchez,
let's take a look
at your book cover.
Oh, okay.
What's it about?
- My past.
How I held on to it for so long
and held grudges against people.
I was a very, very mean,
arrogant bitch, that--
- And the problem
with that is...?
Let's take a look
at your satellite interview,
where we asked you to promote
not only your book and yourself,
but also the Absolut
Berri Acai cocktail.
- I know how to love,
I know how to give,
and celebrate,
like I am with this berry...
drink from Absolut.
- You didn't incorporate
the "acai" part of it.
- I'd rather not fuck up
the last ending of the name.
- If you're gonna be paid
by a corporation,
you should probably figure out
how to say the name.
- I'm not thrilled
with the cover of the book.
- I felt it was a little busy.
but I love the concept.
I was very happy to see that
you took it so seriously.
- Jujubee, let's take a look
at your book cover.
- Memoirs of a Gay-sha:
Jujubee's Journey,
I'm Still Here.
[laughter]
I just want to show people
that you can go through things,
take that negative energy,
turn it around,
and use it to live.
It's a lesson.
- Love the title.
I'm very big on titles.
My new book is called
Poor Little Bitch Girl, so...
But that is a great title,
and I think you'll attract
not only a gay audience
with that title,
but with a straight audience
who's interested in reading
about your life's experiences,
especially coming from
an Asian family.
- It reminds us
of a great book already,
so that was very clever
thinking.
- There's a lot of candy
going on down here.
It's not true what they say
about Asians, honey.
- By the way, I know a number
of big Hollywood moguls
who would like to, uh,
take you out, if you ever--
if you're ever available.
- Tatianna, you're giving this
not jailbreak,
but jailbait look.
Let's take a look
at your book cover.
- Ooh.
- Superstar.
- My book is about
becoming a drag queen at 14,
dealing with the backlash
from that,
but still going forward
and not letting anyone stop me.
- Now, where was that person
when you walked down the runway?
I'm a little worried about
your confidence level.
- This dress, it could be
three stripes shorter.
- Shorter.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'm giving up
on trying to figure out
what's short enough
and what's long enough,
because...
- It's just slightly too long,
and it's starting to kind of
give a more
Morticia Addams look to it.
- Straight men love
to hit on me.
Every time I've gone out
in drag,
I've gotten hit on
by a straight guy,
so I must be doing
something right.
- Tatianna,
thank you for being here.
- Thank you.
And let me tell you
about this beverage.
- Unfortunately,
you did not mention
the name of the book.
Maybe it's fortunate,
because I'm not crazy about
the title of the book,
Tati.
Because Tati, I mean,
can be T-A-T-T-Y.
That's an English word
that means kind of not great.
- If that's the way
you squeeze in the cocktail,
we might have had a fight
in the car
on the way
to the next interview.
- Thanks, Tatianna.
- Thank you.
- Hello, Pandora.
- Hello, RuPaul.
- Oh, boy.
You got to use the pit crew.
- My book is about
how drag taught me
to gain self-confidence.
- Pandora, if you're wearing
this to be glamorous,
it's not working for me.
- This fabric is playing
with glamour,
but playing with, like,
funny glamour.
- If you're gonna look like
a coke whore,
take the joke even further.
- What kind of vodka is it?
- It's Berri Acai vodka.
- Missing my brand,
that was tough for me.
- Pandora Boxx, what do you
have to say for yourself?
- I just want to say that
my book,
Out of the Boxx:
How Drag Saved My Life,
is now available online
and in stores.
[laughter]
- Jessica Wild,
can we see your book?
Oh, wow.
Look at that.
- The cover looks like
the cover of a book,
like, a nine-year-old girl
would buy.
It could be a little more
sophisticated.
- Now, with all these
drag queens living toge--
- Oh, I love that Absolut acai.
Oh, my God.
The name is Jessica wild...
The Dreams of a Golden Child.
- Your interview got into,
like, train-wreck territory.
- On there, it sounded like
"dreams of a golden shower."
Do you know what that is?
- No.
- If you don't know
what a golden shower is,
that's very naive.
[laughter]
However, I like the cover.
It's a little pretentious to
have an Oscar on the front of it
because-- [laughs]
Who knows?
- I'm not crazy about the cover
I feel like you could use
some of that Jessica Wild
imagination,
make a bigger splash
with that cover.
The interview
was basically so bad
that I wouldn't change a thing.
[laughter]
- Now, Jeffrey, you got your
product in there a lot.
- Yeah.
It was a little too sloppy.
I would probably have fired you
in the car
on the way home
from that interview.
- Raven, darling,
I love your fro.
- It was straight earlier,
but it's so humid back there.
[laughter]
- Let's see your book.
Oh.
- I've come from so many
broken things--
broken family, broken home,
broken relationships.
This is showing how to find
your inner strength.
- Why should you win
RuPaul's Drag Race?
- Well, first of all,
I'm young, broke, and fabulous.
Young, Broke, and Fabulous.
- Well, I am extremely
impressed.
Do you know how many times
you said the title?
Even I have trouble--
I do do it sometimes,
but that was really great.
And you did it with style.
You bought it right in right at
the beginning of the interview.
I loved that.
Good for you.
- You're so sultry.
I feel like you could teach me
how to be more of a woman.
- I think you could teach me
- I don't think s--
[laughs]
- I'm a man in a dress.
[laughter]
- Thank you, ladies.
While you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
[engine turns]
Let's start with Tyra Sanchez.
- I like the title of her book.
[deep voice]
The Woman in Me.
[laughter]
- One of the best dresses
we've seen this season.
And I like the book, and I like
that she revealed a little bit,
'cause we don't see a lot
of vulnerability in her.
- Uh, Jujubee.
- I thought she was dynamite.
He had a fantastic personality.
She came across as really alive
and bright--
very, very bright.
I liked her a lot.
- I think she probably crossed
over the good-taste line,
but we could have probably
lived with that.
- Tatianna.
- It did look like
she was part of a chain gang.
I'm sorry, I couldn't get over
the dress.
It just went on and on and on
and I thought it was hideous.
It looked like Olive Oyl.
- I didn't get--
pick up any confidence
from her whatsoever.
- Pandora Boxx.
You know,
she's been consistent
in her ability
to just be a real player.
But she doesn't take it
to that next level.
- She looks like a girl
that's just stepped off
the Greyhound bus
and quickly
turned into a coke whore.
- That sounds like a book
I'd read...
[laughter]
And Jackie's written it.
- Yes.
Yes, I've written it.
- Jessica Wild.
- Title of her book
wasn't right.
- I mean, she was hilarious,
but not on purpose.
But this is kind of
a serious thing
and it's like, you really have
to step up to the plate
or the dance floor,
as it were.
- This is branding.
Clearly,
Jessica did not understand
the intricacies of that.
Raven.
- She showed this great
personality.
and, uh, the hair was fantastic,
the dress, the book--
Young, Broke and Fabulous.
Not young, not broke,
but fabulous.
[laughter]
- There's a lack of
vulnerability, though, in--
in Raven.
- And there is such a thing
as overselling, you know?
She needs to practice
some restraint.
- All right, then.
Silence.
Bring back the girls.
I have made my decision.
Welcome back, ladies.
You are all my heroes.
And you know that I know
what it took
for each of you
to get here tonight.
So no matter what happens,
you are champions.
Tyra Sanchez,
the next drag superstar
needs to be
consistently dynamic.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Jujubee,
you had us at "gay-sha ."
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Tatianna,
you're young and talented...
but you fumbled your interview.
And you came to the main stage
dressed like a referee.
- I'm sorry, my dear.
you are up for elimination.
- When I find out
that I'm in the bottom two,
my mouth goes completely dry.
I'm not ready to go home.
- Pandora Boxx.
The judges were not
absolutely impressed.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Raven.
What can I say?
You're young, broke,
and fabulous,
and you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
Congratulations, Raven.
You've won a glamorous
shopping spree
at the legendary house
of L.A. Eyeworks.
- I finally won
a fucking challenge.
And it was a big win to me.
Thank you.
- Jessica, you went wild
in your interview,
but your cover did not snatch
any trophies from the judges.
I'm sorry, my dear.
you are up for elimination.
- I need to win this,
because I don't think
that I did a bad job
for going back home today.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
to lip-synch
for your life.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[Sister Sledge's
He's the Greatest Dancer]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Oh, what? Wow ♪
♪ He's the greatest dancer ♪
♪ Oh, what? Wow ♪
- I'm watching them perform,
and I see Jessica's doing
a little bit too much for me.
- ♪ He's the greatest
dancer ♪
- This is my last chance.
I have to win
the lip synch for my life.
- ♪ I really wasn't caring ♪
♪ But I felt
my eyes staring ♪
♪ At a guy who stuck out ♪
♪ In the crowd ♪
♪ He had the kind of body ♪
♪ That would shame Adonis ♪
♪ And a face ♪
♪ That would make
any man cry ♪
- Tatianna starts
doing her thing,
just being very sensual
and sexy,
and it was amazing.
- ♪ Oh, what? Wow ♪
♪ Oh, what? Wow ♪
♪ He's the greatest dancer ♪
♪ That I've ever seen ♪
♪ I love your moves ♪
♪ Oh, what? Wow ♪
♪ He's the greatest dancer ♪
♪ That I've ever seen ♪
[laughter]
- Great job.
[applause]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Tatianna...
Shante, you stay.
- I was in pure shock.
I thought I might have misheard.
- Are you playing with me?
- Thank you, Tatianna.
You may join the other girls.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- Jessica,
follow your wildest dreams,
my golden child.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you from the bottom
of my heart.
[applause]
I'm very proud of myself.
Be here is one of my dreams.
I make my dreams come true.
I'm a winner.
Amo a Puerto Rico.
- And to my five
remaining queens,
remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get a whoop-whoop?
- all: Whoop-whoop.
[laughter]
- Let the music play.
- ♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
♪ You can say that
you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you
looking ♪
♪ Don't be jealous ♪
♪ Of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be jealous... ♪