[Main Event playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Here we go again ♪
♪ Chapter two ♪
♪ Turn another page ♪
♪ I'm walkin' in the rain ♪
♪ Paint a smile upon my face ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't let ♪
♪ The spotlight ♪
♪ See the heartbreak ♪
♪ In my love life ♪
♪ When the laughter starts
to fade ♪
♪ All the drama
takes center stage ♪
♪ Strike up the band ♪
♪ Bang a drum ♪
♪ Like the beat of my heart ♪
♪ Oh, you left before the end ♪
♪ Before our story
had a chance to start ♪
♪ When you step
into the disco ♪
♪ Leave your problems ♪
♪ At the front door ♪
♪ You know, the world
don't have to end ♪
♪ Long as the deejay record
spins ♪
♪ This is the main event ♪
♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ Just let the music ♪
♪ Dance into your soul ♪
♪ Just a faster exit ♪
- Welcome to an extra special
episode of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Come along for the ride
as we sneak a peek
at the contestants'
outrageous audition tapes.
We'll count down
the top ten fits and fashions
of the runway,
with special guests Ongina,
Shannel,
and last year's winner,
BeBe Zahara Benet,
and outrageous moments
from our celebrity
guest judges,
plus an up close
and personal look
at our final three--
Raven, Tyra,
and Jujubee.
- ♪ Make you lose control ♪
♪ This is the main event ♪
♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ Just let the music ♪
♪ Dance into your soul ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Ohh, ohh, ohh, ohh ♪
♪ Uh, uhh ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ Ru-Ru-RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
- Welcome to an extra special
episode of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Honey, this hour is jam packed.
- Face.
- Beauty face.
Because when it comes
to RuPaul's Drag Race,
too much is never enough.
- $5.00.
Try something new.
- But before we race
to the finish line,
let's go back
and pay our respects
to the nine amazing queens
that didn't make it
to the winner's circle.
- Hey, everybody,
look at me.
Here I am.
- We are in my home.
I'm gonna show a few
of my things to you.
- Hey, RuPaul
and casting directors.
- I'm the one
you're looking for!
- Now, when Shangela
sent in her casting tape,
she'd been doing drag
for only three months.
- Now, you have to forgive me
because I had to drag myself
out of bed
to pull this video together.
[sniffles] Bitch think
he got the swine flu.
[sniffles]
- But what she lacked
in experience,
she made up for in enthusiasm,
showmanship,
and attitude.
- Some bitches,
when they in drag,
they are catty,
hateful hos.
But nobody likes a hateful ho.
Mm-mmm.
No, you need to be sweet
to people.
Girl, I got diesel breath.
[laughter]
- It's every single...
- Our next queen,
Nicole Paige Brooks,
was tasteful
and sophisticated.
In short, Atlanta eleganza.
- Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi!
- Hey!
- Wait a minute!
We just started,
and y'all are already breaking
my number one rule,
which is what?
If I can hear you over me,
you need to what?
- Shut the fuck up!
- You may remember me
from RuPaul's Drag Race
season one,
when I almost made it,
and you got to see
my audition video on the show.
Just in case you don't remember,
here it is.
My name is Nicole--
my name is Nicole--
my name is Nicole Paige Brooks.
RuPaul.
- RuPaul.
- I need you to pick dada
this time.
- I need you
to pick dada this time.
- [laughing]
- We knew we loved
the marvelous Mystique
from the moment she shared
her most important
beauty secret--
two piece and a biscuit.
- Well, I already ate
that one piece,
and here's the other,
you know.
That two piece and a biscuit
can give you hips and curves
and everything else.
Drag for me
is a creative outlet,
and it's an expression on life,
and it's the art
of the illusion.
You know I'm a size 0,
the infinite number?
- ♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
- Gotta eat that breast
and that biscuit
just to keep
that girlish figure.
Smooches.
- The lady Sonique
was nothing if not versatile.
She rocked so many looks,
she had us flippin' out.
- That's my Catwoman mask.
My new Catwoman mask.
Actually, the Black Cat.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, yeah.
- These are my drag mother's
fire torches.
I gotta show you those.
[blowing]
- I knew that Morgan McMichaels
was my kind of queen
when she invited us
to check her out
in a back alley.
- My favorite place to walk
and give you a catwalk show
is in the alley.
I'ma start from way back here.
- ♪ Stroll down the runway ♪
♪ Another payday ♪
♪ Cover of magazines ♪
- So we're on a tour.
This is RuPaul's Drag Race,
in a audition video,
and this is my closet,
ladies and gentlemen.
We have bags of hair,
leather chaps,
leather leather,
leather leather shiny things.
You know drag queens
love shiny things.
- Sahara Davenport's
audition tape
showed some sass,
some class,
and even a little bit of ass.
- Hi!
I'm Sahara Davenport!
Drag means, to me, freedom
of expression definitely.
What I can say
is drag has taken me places
where my career as a dancer
was unable to.
If I had to describe Sahara,
I would say
she has the grace
of Debbie Allen.
Whoo!
And she's a big ol' man,
like RuPaul.
[laughing]
- Sexy Latina Jessica Wild
earned her spot on the show
by winning
an online casting contest
at rupaulsdragrace.com.
- For me, Jessica
is a gift to myself,
because it gave me opportunity
to do things that as David
I was afraid to do.
- In drag,
comedy and timing
can be as important
as a tight tuck.
Pandora Boxx's
hilarious audition tape
proved she understood
the importance of all three.
- Tell us, Pandora Boxx,
what is the secret
to your success?
- Well, Michael, you see--
Oh, hold on.
I hope you don't mind
if I do something.
- Uh...okay.
- I'm 37 years old...ooh.
I just--that's the first time
I think I've said it out loud.
It's only been a week.
I don't know if you know,
but I did audition last year.
I didn't make it, clearly,
and I'm not bitter.
It's a kind of like
a little, um...
like a Swiss Miss kind of--
well, it's best
I just show you.
[claps]
Here I am.
♪ Yodelay, yodelay ♪
♪ Yodelay-ee-hoo ♪
- Tatianna's audition tape
was second to none
when it came to femininity
and sheer beauty.
- And if I don't get chosen
this time,
I'm gonna try again
next season
and the season after that
and the season after that.
And you're eventually
going to get tired
of seeing my face,
so it's in your best interests
just to get it over with now
and put me on the show, 'kay?
- All these girls
have sashayed away,
but even though
they left the race,
they're still
spreading the love,
and you can catch their acts
all over the country.
Find out where.
Just go to rupaulsdragrace.com
and click.
- Can I get a amen.
- ♪ A-a-a-a-men ♪
Oh!
- This year's queens
tore up the main stage
like never before.
And to help me
count down the top ten
most unforgettable
fits and fashions,
I've invited
three unforgettable queens
from last season--
the divine Ongina,
the fabulous Shannel,
and last season's winner,
the queen herself,
the incredible
BeBe Zahara Benet.
Cameroon!
[laughter]
Hi, ladies.
- Hi, Ru.
- Welcome back
to the Drag Race.
- Thanks for having us.
- Shannel, you moved
to another city.
- Seattle.
- Now, did RuPaul's Drag Race
change your life?
- The world.
All three of us--
we've just been in every city,
and it's been--
it's been amazing.
- Yeah, I've been reading
about you all,
and, BeBe, you moved
to a new city, too, didn't you?
- New York.
- People recognize you
on the street?
- Yeah, and that's
overwhelming too.
- So you've been watching
the show.
- Crazy 12 girls
you have there.
- I put together
the top ten list
of the most unforgettable
fits and fashions
on the runway.
Coming in at number ten
are the death-defying drops
of Miss Two Piece and a Biscuit
herself, Mystique.
Whoa!
Wow.
It always felt like she was
gonna break something.
- She dropped it
like it was hot.
- She sure did.
[laughter and applause]
Now, do any of you
do splits at all?
- Mm-mm.
- No?
I would think you could,
Shannel.
- I'll juggle, but no splits.
- Yeah, only in the comfort
of my own bedroom.
- [laughing]
- Honey, she had one foot
on the dresser.
- I think big girls
are always fabulous, though.
- Being a big girl,
you knew
that she had to pull out
all the stops.
- She's pretty too.
- She is pretty.
- Very pretty.
She's not afraid
of the cosmetics.
- No.
- She will get in there,
and she'll paint
for the Rose Bowl, honey.
- Yes, indeed.
Oh, yes.
She baked it
like Betty Crocker.
She did a thing
called cooking her makeup.
Do you guys cook?
- I mean, the queens
have to cook.
- Well, it's when you put
your foundation on your face
and you let it sit and warm to
your own body's temperature...
- I never knew that.
- So that it's--yeah.
- I cook.
- I'm cooking right now,
right?
I'm actually wearing
a Crock-Pot right now.
- Oh, okay.
- [laughs]
- Bet you can't guess
where it is.
- [laughs]
- I'll give you a hint.
It's near my lovin' oven.
[all laugh]
- I really like
her personality.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- Now, after the burlesque show,
we asked our girls
to walk the runway
in their best high-class drag.
Coming in at number nine
is Miss Tatianna,
who brought it home
in Galliano realness.
Now, what did you think
of her dress?
- It was prom-y,
a little too short.
- I would've liked it
to have swept the ground.
- And a little train.
- Mm-hmm.
- Maybe not the earrings
with the necklace.
- But, you know,
give or take a necklace
or an earring or two,
that was one of her best looks.
Now, everybody knows my girls
are the crème de la crème,
but coming in at number eight
is Miss Jujubee in her getup
from the
Starrbootylicious episode.
Now, Jujubee was wearing her
"Imelda Marcos goes to the prom
in the Ashford &amp; Simpson
collection from Sears" dress,
but it was gorgeous.
You know, normally
that could not work,
but something about her humor
pulls that off.
- She seemed very bubbly
and kind of peppy.
I think she paints
really, really well.
- Reminds me
of a little Ongina.
[laughter]
- I like her
because she's Asian.
So go, Asians!
- Without the hair.
- Well, yeah.
No, she's--
I really like that dress.
- Yeah.
- I mean, you know,
if I wore that dress,
it would probably drown me,
but for her, it works.
- It works for her.
- And I think it's gorgeous.
- And, you know,
there's a certain consciousness
that Jujubee has that is, um...
it's kind of got a wink
to everything that she does,
and it made it work.
- She was a real transformation,
too, from boy to girl.
- I was surprised.
- Big difference there.
- Yes.
- Big difference.
- Yeah.
I think with a lot
of the kids this season
that the difference is huge.
- Yeah.
- I like her boy name too.
It's Airline.
- Oh, that's right.
- Yeah, it's amazing.
- Yeah.
- No, I think that her--
She could actually use her
boy name as a drag name, yeah.
- Sure.
- But Jujubee is great.
- Jujubee is fantastic.
Do you know the meaning
of "jujubee," what that means?
- No.
- I think it's a--
- It's a candy.
- Yes, well, the--
it is, I think, in Thailand,
the truckers who are
traveling cross-country
chew this candy to stay awake
at night.
- Because it gets stuck
in your teeth
and then you can't even separate
your gums,
and you spend more time
picking it out of your teeth
than you do swallowing it.
- She has pizzazz,
and she's always going, "Pah."
- In the Country Queens episode,
Jessica Wild's country couture
left the others in the dust,
and it has her coming in
at number seven.
Was she bootylicious or what?
- Hip-alicious, bootylicious--
she's padded for life.
- Now, of course,
she was padded.
Now, you don't pad,
do you, Ongina?
- No.
- And, of course, Shannel
doesn't need to pad,
because she's got it.
- Junky trunk, right?
- Now, um, our queen--
any tips for padding
for the kids out there?
- Um, I don't pad.
- Oh, you don't pad?
[laughter]
- I don't pad.
- That's a lie.
- Do you think
that Jessica's pad job
was acceptable by our queen?
- Well, you know what?
- I just--of course it's due.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I think it was--yeah.
It was realistic,
but then again,
you have to figure out
how tall you are
and how short you are
to make it that realistic.
- Right.
- You know?
- So I shouldn't get that made.
- Well, you can get it made,
but you have to--
- In that size.
- You can make it to your body.
- Oh, okay.
- Right.
- Some girls, you know,
only pad here
when they really should pad,
like, say, from the knee up,
or they may have--
They may--a lot of times,
girls, I think
will put their pads too low,
too,
because they want to hear
a lot of hip hugger things.
And then they've got, you know,
an ass that sits on the ground,
which, I mean,
I'm the last one to talk,
but, you know, see...
- Well, I think that Jessica
did her padding very well
this time.
Now, we asked our judges
to work the runway,
and divas like Kathy Griffin,
Dita Von Teese,
and Miss Debbie Reynolds
showed us queens a thing or two
about being fabulous.
Coming in at number six
are the stunning runway stylings
of our Drag Race judges.
What'd you think
of our star power
on the runway this year?
- Kathy Griffin coming out
with the damn bar--
but I love
Debbie Reynolds too.
- Debbie Reynolds.
- Oh, my God, she's adorable.
- She introduced herself
as Princess Leia's mother.
And Henry Rollins--he gets
sexier with age, actually.
- If you need a housekeeper.
- Talking about sexy,
Dita Von Teese...
- Oh, yes.
- Amazing...
- Yeah, true living pinup.
- In the Rocker Chick challenge,
my girls had
to transform themselves
into rock star divas.
And together, they come in
at number five
on the countdown.
- I was really impressed
with Raven and Tatianna.
- ♪ This groove
is for my girls ♪
♪ Little lady boys and girls ♪
- Especially Raven--
I think that the hair was just--
the color contrast
was really hot.
- Well, she was paying homage
to Terri Nunn,
who was from the group Berlin,
and that was Terri Nunn's
trademark hairdo.
Now, I know that you did
the rap on my song.
- Yes.
- And you have a song out now.
- Yeah.
- What's it called?
- I'm the Shit.
- Oh, God.
[laughter]
Now there were a lot of looks
this season
that drew inspiration
from history's
greatest superstars.
But in the Once Upon a Queen
episode,
a star was born,
and that's why Raven
is number four
on the countdown.
- I love Raven, and I also am
a huge Streisand fan.
So I loved it
'cause it was Goldmember
meets The Main Event.
- It was a very surprising look
for her.
- She took out her piercing.
- She took out her piercings.
- Which made the look
a little bit more high glamour,
because if she would have
kept them on,
then it would have not worked
for me.
- Although I kind of
secretly would love
to see Barbra Streisand
with those piercings.
- Yeah.
- Can you imagine?
Maybe she is pierced...
Down there.
[laughter]
- For the busy drag queen
on the go,
versatility is a must.
So I love it
when a single outfit
suddenly turns into two
or three or more.
Coming in at number three,
behold the many country looks
of Tyra Sanchez,
the other Tyra.
- If you're going to work
with the first outfit
and then you have to run out
to lunch
on the second outfit
and then dinner on the third--
- Right, and then
the escort agency calls.
[laughter]
- I like reveals,
because I think it keeps you
very interested
and it's, like,
the "oohs" and the "ahhs"
and really gives you
that whole showgirl
aspect of it.
- Yes.
In season one,
there were a few little spats
between the contestants.
Right, girls?
- Maybe.
- Just a few.
Well, this season,
we had a shootout
at the Drag Race Corral.
Coming in at number two,
it's the terrible Ts,
Tyra versus Tatianna.
What are the judges not seeing?
- Tyra is a complete bitch.
- She talks so much shit
about so many people
but won't say it
to their face.
- The reality is in this field
there is so much cattiness.
After having been dressed
for so many hours
and under the lights
and all of that,
you know, tensions are high.
I mean, God knows in our season,
I mean,
I had lots of frustrations
myself.
Things happen.
Sometimes you just have
to vocalize it.
- All right, kids, we are down
to number one in our countdown.
- Ru, can I say something?
I think it's time I take over.
- Uh, BeBe, you may be
the next drag superstar,
but it's still my show.
- Well, I think the moment
has come for us
to reveal the most unforgettable
fits and fashion
from the runway all worn by you.
- Me?
- You!
- Obviously you.
- Oh, my God.
I'm back.
- My favorite
is the very Lacroix one
with the pleats
and the three shades of cream,
beige, and a little lavender.
- I think that looks so pretty.
- That was our Wedding show.
I played the mother
of the bride.
- It's gorgeous.
- Then the red and black.
- Right, now that was very
Miss Ross.
- But it was so beautiful.
That was so striking
and the silhouette
of the body...
- And I love
all the ostrich feathers
on the lilac dress,
the strapless.
- What made some of those
outfits so fantastic
was the fact that you
changed hair color.
- Well, Mathu always wants
to top himself.
I think with
the punk rock outfit,
I think that's probably
the biggest hair
I've ever worn in my career.
Ladies, thank you so much
for stopping by.
I'm so happy
for all of your successes,
and I can't wait till we're all
on the RuPaul Drag Race Tour
all over the world.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- Thank you
for making it happen.
- You guys make sure
you tune in next week
to see who will be crowned
the next drag queen superstar.
Now, I hope you're hungry...
- [belches]
- Because I've been digging up
some tasty tidbits,
unseen morsels,
and delicious
behind-the-scene nuggets.
[growls]
all: Cherry pie! Cherry pie!
Cherry pie!
- Now naturally, there was
some fierce competition
between the queens.
- It's a competition.
- But what impressed me the most
was the mutual love and support,
because when it comes to drag,
support is essential.
- I'm trying to get this bitch
just to stay on.
I hope I can make
some new drag sisters
to really give me some tips,
help a bitch out.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- We all genuinely want
each other to look good.
- Do you have time, baby,
to help me just put this on?
- People that are
helping each other,
they're helping each other
because they want them to stay.
- And so you just take
your white,
highlight all this area,
and make that pop.
Granted, this is a competition.
It's also a learning experience.
- You, like, want me
to wrap it around you?
- Put--poom, poom, poom, yeah.
This look too bad?
If you are going to win,
you are going to win
no matter what.
That's why if I need
to give you my panties,
I give you my panties,
because if I'm going to win,
I'm going to win
with or without panties.
- Our girls weren't afraid
to talk about anything,
including a drag queen's
best kept secret.
I'm talking about padding.
Are you a padded queen?
- I do pad, yes.
- I wear hip pads, yeah,
but I don't wear a butt pad,
'cause I have
a little bit of a--
- Okay.
- Did you see my ass?
Did you see my hips?
Boys don't have that.
I molded that.
- I think you've got
quite a shape there.
- Well, yesterday,
I wore hip pads.
- Wow, some of these girls,
they're pretty cute,
but if you're trying to do drag,
use your pads to look
at least like a girl.
- Now, you don't have padding.
You're not a padded queen.
- I like being thin.
I like--I modeled myself after,
like, a supermodel.
We're not like that in L.A.
We don't pad.
That's an East Coast, Midwest,
Southern thing
where they're pageant girls.
- It's private,
you know what I mean?
I'm putting on my body.
- This season,
the drag queens proved
that they were talented
celebrity impersonators.
But behind the scenes,
these queens
stepped up their game
and started doing each other.
- Nicole Paige Brooks
from Atlanta, Georgia.
- "Nicole Paige Brooks
from Atlanta, Georgia."
- [laughs]
- [mocking laugh]
- I hot glued it to my leg
along with these to my arm.
- "Tyra, can you pass over
that hot glue gun, please?
"I'm fixing to glue
some rhinestones
onto my gown that
I'm trying to fix and make."
- I'm doing Sasha Fierce,
but technically,
I'm doing Beyoncé.
- "I love Beyoncé."
- As drag queens,
we make our own families,
but when the girls talked
about their real families,
the emotions ranged
from admiration
to something more complicated.
- "Dear son,
this is your mommy speaking.
"You're a very talented child,
and you could be
whatever you want."
She wrote me a note once before
when I was competing
for something
when I was, like, 20,
and I've kept it.
"So remember, if you don't do
what you're trying to,
I'll be behind you
with my belt."
- So your mom
said she's gon' beat you
if you don't make it?
- Yeah, basically.
- Damn.
- I'm really fortunate,
because a lot of people
don't have that family base,
you know?
Especially in our community.
And I'm just lucky to have a mom
that's so supportive
and I love very much.
- My father's one
of the toughest Scotsmen.
Like, he's a man's man,
you know?
And he was so okay
with me being gay.
He was like, "I love you.
It doesn't really matter
as long as you're happy."
And I was like, "Bizzle."
- To each his own.
- Absolutely.
- Like, when people
find out you're gay
and they're like,
"You know God loves you,"
yeah, I know he does.
Imagine what the world
would look like
if there weren't gay people.
Eww.
- I loved hearing
all the girls' backgrounds.
But Jujubee's sense of history
was positively Shakespearean.
- Did you guys know
the word "drag" is an acronym
that Shakespeare created?
- "Dress resembling a girl."
- It was actually a side note
for his plays,
because back in the day,
the players of the stage
were all men.
- They were ladyboys.
- One thing there was
no shortage of was girl talk.
- Whoo!
- Think it was gay pride
last year or something.
I got a taxi, and we go home.
I was, like, in drag in bed
like, "Come on, baby.
Let's do it."
[chuckles]
And he's like, "No!
You're Sahara!"
- Well, and people ask him,
you know,
if we have sex when I'm in drag
and all that stuff, so...
- There's ever been a night
where you're just messy drunk?
And you're just like,
"I don't want to take this off.
Let's just do it."
- No.
- Now, you know I love
a good catchphrase.
The time has come...
for you to lip-synch...
for your life.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
And don't fuck It up.
But this season,
I had some serious competition.
- Work.
- You better work, bitch.
- I'm not a bitch.
I'm America's sweetheart.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Are you going through it?
Are you going through
some psychological changes
in your life?
- I'm not.
- I'm not either.
- Now, I know you're
a two piece and a biscuit.
- As long as that two piece
and a biscuit is there,
I am perfectly happy.
- [laughs]
- I got my two piece
and a biscuit
waiting on me anywhere I go.
- During my worldwide tour,
I stopped in Texas,
and I did meet mystique,
and she wanted to be tipped
with a two piece and a biscuit.
- Two piece and a biscuit.
Mystique gone but not forgotten.
[laughter and applause]
Now, it's been
an incredible season...
What do the bags say?
They say "Santino"?
[laughter]
Dripping with charisma,
uniqueness, nerve,
and talent.
- Marker.
- Welcome to another--
Oh, shit.
- And I'm not just talking
about the queens.
I'm talking about the judges.
Sassy Santino
and our resident fashionista,
Merle Ginsberg,
not to mention our star-studded
panel of guest judges.
- That, to me,
was a complete turn-on.
- [gasps]
- Kathy, did you know Jessica
was padded?
- I am too actually.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I've been padded
for the last ten years.
[laughter]
- The judges brought a lot
of life experience to the show,
and the contestants
were all ears.
- You must not listen
to the interviewer.
If he says,
"Where are you from?"
you say, "Well, actually,
I'm from so-and-so,
but in my book,"
and then you name the book.
You always have to bring it in
yourself,
'cause they're never
gonna bring it in.
- I started working
in a strip club,
like, with the regular girls.
You could walk into the club,
and you could find
that there was one girl
everyone was trying to be like,
and they're all doing
the same thing,
so it doesn't make
financial sense.
- So your lip sync
was very, very good too,
which I noticed right away,
because in films,
that's what we always did.
It's not easy
to lip-synch correctly,
and you did a super job.
- In the real world,
if you get arrested
and don't speak English,
the court
appoints a interpreter.
But here on RuPaul's Drag Race,
language barriers
are just part of the fun.
Did you tuck your candy?
Did you hide your candy?
- My candy?
- Yes.
Um, como...
- Huevos.
- Huevos el pollo?
- Oh, my--this?
- Something with Angela
at the end.
- Everyone has a problem
with my name.
- I was gonna say Kangela.
I'll change mine to Kangela.
- 'Cause a lot of kids
are calling you Shan-gella.
- Or Shanga-linga.
She called her
Shanga-linga.
- I do have an ointment
in my dressing room for that.
Yeah, you know,
a lot of the judges
mentioned Tyra's deep voice.
- When you transform into Tyra,
why doesn't your voice change?
- In fact, Santino
didn't just mention it.
He worked it.
- [in deep voice]
I think that Tyra should stay,
but sometimes when I see her
and she's talking to me,
I just think, "Who is this dude
talking to me?"
- [laughs]
- I'll give you $4,000
to stop that right now.
- Right, right, me too.
Now, most queens aren't shy,
but this is a family show.
So you have to use
a little discretion.
And nothing says discretion
like a double entendre.
- Anybody that's eating
my cherry pie
raves about it.
- How's the crust?
- Crispy
and a little tender
in the middle.
- And the fruit?
- Always ripe.
- Is it juicy, Pandora?
- It's overflowing with juices.
- Would you say your cherry pie
was succulent?
- I would say it's succulent
and a bit moist.
- Oh.
- [laughing]
You getting hungry, Kim?
- I'm getting hungry.
- Now, for some queens,
the ultimate praise is when
people think you're a real girl.
- It's really a woman,
isn't it?
- It is really a woman.
- I knew it.
I knew it.
- It's called being fishy.
- When you walked out,
I really did have
that same moment that Dita had.
Is that a girl?
I think that's a girl.
There's an imposter in the show.
It's a girl.
Check her crotch.
- Well, maybe we have
a real scandal here.
Maybe she's actually
a real woman.
- What?
- Ever thought about that?
- I will walk off this set.
- I will kick her ass.
- I was give her a pap smear
in five seconds,
and I will get
to the bottom of it.
- This season, we not only
dished celebrities.
We ate 'em for lunch.
- I mean, I love everything.
I'm gonna be the Paula tonight,
I think.
I'm the Paula
of the RuPaul show.
- I know a number
of big Hollywood moguls
who would like to take you out
if you ever--
if you're ever available.
[laughter]
- I really like Lady Gaga
a lot.
She's almost like
a drag queen herself.
- Almost?
You're very kind.
You actually did more work than
Britney does in her concert.
I mean, you actually sang
in your concert,
which is something
Britney does not do.
- I like that wig.
It looked good.
You know, I really did see--
Leslie Stahl
has a good wig as well.
Leslie, I'm so sorry.
- At the end of the day,
I hope I'm less of a judge
and more of a teacher.
And the best way to teach,
of course, is by example.
Earlier today, I had my face
lifted for a fifth time.
Why?
Because I'm dedicated to this,
children.
You are a burning sensation,
and I don't want an ointment
to clear it up.
You have to use what you've got
to get what you want.
You know, my friends call me
the MacGyver of drag.
I will take a wire hanger and...
- A Maxi Pad.
- And jimmy-rig
a lighting system
in a hotel room.
- What happens sometimes
is that my nuts pop,
and it reminds me
that I'm a dude.
- [laughs]
- So I try to go right back
to being feminine,
so that's what happens.
- Yeah, I mean, I know--
everybody knows
about popping a cherry,
but nobody talks
about popping a nut.
- No.
- It is part of doing drag.
So in case you missed
any of the fierce action...
- You pushed me!
You pushed me!
- Here's a fast-forward
flashback
of this season's competition.
- Cheeseburger, Taco Bell,
and a Diet Coke on the side,
girl.
- On the first day,
the Gone with the Window
photo shoot
tested the queens' ability
to get real,
to get glamour,
and get blown.
- I've never been blown
like that in my life.
[laughter]
- Then everybody had to channel
their inner Scarlett O'Hara
and style an outfit
from a set of curtains.
Morgan McMichaels,
you are the winner
of this challenge.
Mystique, based on your
unforgettable presentation,
I'm giving you
a "get out of jail free" card.
Sahara Davenport, shante,
you stay.
Shangela, sashay away.
Next, we divided the queens into
two teams of burlesque dancers,
and each team had to work hard
for the money...
[cheers and applause]
Then take to the streets
and represent.
- You got some money for me?
- Does anybody want
cherry pie gift certificates?
- Help me out.
Buy some pie.
- Be soprano, though,
when you talk, girl.
- Hi. Would you like to buy
a slice of cherry pie?
- In the end, Sahara won,
and Raven
and Nicole Paige Brooks
had to lip-synch
for their lives.
Nicole Paige Brooks,
you are a fabulous queen.
Now sashay away.
Next, the girls
had to shoot a commercial
for Disco Extra
Greasy Shortening.
- Hi.
Welcome to another
home-fried meal.
- Wait, can you stop?
Can we cut?
Can you--
is it home-fried male?
- Is it home-fried male?
- Home-fried meal.
- Meal. okay.
Thought she was
gonna fry up a boy.
- On the main stage,
the girls turned it out
in front of country legend
Tanya Tucker.
- Wow.
Awesome.
- Tyra stepped up her game
with three outfits in one.
Tyra Sanchez, you tore it up,
Miss Thing.
And it was Mystique's turn
to, well, split.
[laughter and applause]
- Next, we asked the girls
to channel
their best celebrity
impersonations
for a little quiz show
we call The Snatch Game.
- I'm so--
I'm a little embarrassed, Ru.
- Are you embarrassed?
- I'm a little embarrassed.
'Cause I just wrote, "I've got
a lovely bunch of coconuts."
[laughter]
- Britney,
Dumb Dee Dee's so dumb,
last night, she got arrested
for driving without a...
- A baby in her lap.
- A baby...
[laughter]
Tatiana took the prize,
and Sonique bent over backwards
to try and stay in the game...
when she and Morgan
had to lip-synch
for their lives.
This choice
has never been so difficult.
Sonique...
sashay away.
For the next challenge,
we asked the girls
to customize wedding dresses.
And Tyra's "singing"
and her hot glue gun
got on everybody's nerves.
- [off-key singing]
Ah, shh...
- Keep burning yourself,
bitch.
- Ah!
- But on the main stage,
the judges went all
Lady Gaga over Tyra's look.
- You look like
a porcelain doll...
- Thank you.
- With the makeup, I love it.
- Tyra Sanchez,
congratulations.
You're the winner
of this challenge.
When it came time
to lip-synch for your life,
Sahara was really
on her toes.
And poor Morgan
got left at the altar.
- ♪ When the valley is deep ♪
♪ I said I'll never ♪
- For the next challenge,
the guest judge Henry Rollins
joined Terri Nunn,
and the whole house was rockin'.
- Ah!
- ♪ Uno, dos, tres, quatro ♪
- ♪ T ♪
all: ♪ A, T, I ♪
♪ T, A, T, I ♪
- You know what,
Eddie Murphy?
- Ah!
- You cannot have this,
ladygirl, honey.
- Jessica won,
so Jujubee and Sahara
had to lip-synch
for their lives.
- ♪ Black velvet ♪
♪ If you please ♪
[sultry music]
- Sahara Davenport...
sashay away.
When the girls regroup,
they hit the books to create
their own autobiography.
- It's so exciting to be a part
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
It's almost as exciting
as my new book Out of the Box.
- The book is called
The Woman in Me.
- I just got finished
writing a memoir,
and I call it
Memoirs of a Gay-sha.
- I have my new book.
- What was that?
- The name is Jessica Wild:
The dreams of a Golden Child.
- Well, first of all, I'm
Young, Broke, and Fabulous.
My new book is going
to hit stores soon.
- In the end, Raven was
the hands-down best seller.
Raven, you're young, broke,
and fabulous.
Tatiana and Jessica Wild had
to lip-synch for their lives.
And it was the closing chapter
for Jessica.
- Thank you from
the bottom of my heart.
- So the next challenge
had the girls working
with some gay pioneers
from the Stonewall era.
- Which one of you bitches
is my drag mother?
- Whoa, Jesus.
- I thought maybe you'd do
something interesting with it,
like a low cut.
I put in all this stuff
for today.
- And these silver foxes
turned into golden girls.
- Oh, dear.
[laughing]
- And in the end, Raven
carried herself to victory.
Yay!
[applause]
Pandora, you opened your box
for the world to see.
Now sashay away.
[laughing and applause]
Next, the girls were nominated
for the first annual Diva Award.
[women vocalizing]
♪ ♪
all: Bitch.
- On the main stage,
the girls served
some serious mean teen fashions,
dished up some extreme D.C.
executive realness,
and gave Hollywood's
red carpet beauties
a run for their money.
- I feel wonderful, fabulous,
gorgeous, beautiful.
- Gorgeous.
- In the end, Tyra outdiva-ed
the other divas.
Tatianna, you made
this competition fun and fresh.
For that,
I have just two words.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
And then there were three.
all: Amen.
- In just one week,
Raven, Tyra, or Jujubee
will walk away with the title
of America's
next drag superstar.
The winner will also receive
a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics
and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com,
an exclusive
one-year PR contract
with the leading LGBT firm
Project Publicity,
be featured in l.a.Eyeworks'
legendary
designer eyewear campaign,
and headline
Logo's Drag Race Tour,
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks,
and a cash prize of $25,000.
If you think
you know these divas,
think again.
Because behind
the fabulous dances
and fierce facades,
there's a whole lot of heart
and soul
you've never seen until now.
When first we saw Jujubee's
audition tape...
- Hi, RuPaul Drag Race,
my name is Airline.
- We were wowed
by her transformation.
[gasps]
Jujubee.
- And do you have anything
you want to say
to your fans out there?
- I just want to say thank you
for all the years that
you have been supporting me.
- Sweet and bubbly
to feisty and fierce.
- And you!
Legendary you think you are.
Legendary
looks like leg and dairy.
- Oh-ho-ho!
- Jujubee wasn't afraid
to share some of the pain
from her past.
Where do you get your sense
of humor from?
- My father passing away
when I was 15.
- 15?
- Yeah, and from then on,
it was just, like,
you know, I can't be stuck
in this little ball.
- Right.
- And I can't, you know,
cry about it anymore.
He was like my king.
He did everything for me,
he taught me everything I knew,
he knew that I was gay
before I knew I was gay.
He dragged me to school
every morning,
and the last thing
he would always say
before I left the car was,
"And don't let those kids
tell you anything different."
He's like, "I know
what they say about you.
You can do
whatever you want to do."
And--and that's what I'm doing.
- But Jujubee's
positive attitude
is positively infectious.
- I have the full package.
I have personality,
I have sense of style,
and I have great big,
white teeth.
- I thought she was dynamite.
She had a fantastic personality.
- I'm already happy
about just being here.
But if I win,
everybody gets a puppy.
- Our next finalist
is the other Tyra--
the beautiful, the gorgeous,
the alluring Tyra Sanchez.
- During my transformation,
when I start feeling like Tyra,
it's backstage,
putting on the makeup.
But it all comes into place
when I hear them say...
- Tyra Sanchez.
- Hear that crowd screaming.
And then once that music starts,
my heart stops for probably,
like, a split second.
And it starts beating again,
but it's not my heart
at that point.
It's Tyra's heart
that's beating.
- Tyra.
Ah.
- It's kind of Rita Hayworth.
- It's very Rita Hayworth.
Gilda.
- Yes, Gilda.
- Tyra had to overcome a lot
to achieve what she had.
- I grew up in probably, like,
every project in Orlando.
Like, at the end
of every school year
someone got shot or murdered.
- And in real life,
this hot drag mama
is a young dad.
- I do have a son.
- Jeremiah.
Oh, that's the tattoo you have.
- Yeah.
My son makes me smile
every time I see him.
My son is my motivation
to keep going,
to make his life better.
- You know a family that
drags together stays together.
I would love to be
America's next drag superstar
to, like, inspire more people
to, like, let them know
that they can do it too.
- Raven is a Southern California
girl down to her roots.
- You guys need look no longer,
because the best queens
are in Southern California.
- Raven!
Oh, darling!
- I love doing drag
because I love
the transformation.
I love being able to transform
from a guy into a girl
and then at the end of the night
being able to take it off.
- Raven!
- I definitely do not want
to be a girl.
I love myself, who I am.
It is an art form.
- Now, Raven
landed in the bottom two
early in the competition...
Raven...
I'm sorry, but you're up
for elimination.
But proved she had the stuff
to make it to the final three.
- Why should you win
RuPaul's Drag Race?
- Well, first of all, I'm
Young, Broke, and Fabulous.
If I were to win
RuPaul's Drag Race,
it will help to show people
that drag's cool,
'cause it's fucking cool.
Drag's cool.
- Well, there you have it,
the fabulous final three.
And if you've been groovin'
to any of my songs this season,
you can find them all
on my album Champion,
available on iTunes.
Or read my book Workin' It!
on sale everywhere.
Join me next week
for the grand finale
of RuPaul's Drag Race
to find out who will be crowned
America's next drag superstar.
But most importantly,
remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
buy my album and my book?
All right,
now let the music play.
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be
jealous of my boogie ♪
♪ You say that you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you
looking ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be
jealous of my boogie ♪
♪ You say that you are not ♪