- Gorgeous.
Innocent.
Sexy.
There's some new glamour girls
in town.
And they're sittin'
on a big ol' secret.
I'm back!
[cheering]
That's right, we're back
for an all-new season
of RuPaul's Drag Race,
the search for America's
next drag superstar.
[cheers and applause]
We have 12 hot new queens
willing to do whatever it takes.
- Cock-a-doodle-doo!
- Even if that means
they've got to drop, drop...
drop it like it's hot.
[all groan]
And in the end, it all comes
down to this.
The time has come...
for you to lip-synch...
for your life.
Are you ready for the ride
of your life?
- That, to me,
was a complete turn-off.
- More stars.
- Yes, ma'am.
- More fierce.
- Shut the fuck up,
or I'll make you shut up.
- More drama...
- Can we get someone
over here, please?
She can't breathe.
- Than ever before!
- Gentlemen, start your engines.
[car engine starting,
tires screech]
- A new season
of RuPaul's Drag Race is
about to burn rubber in three...
two...
one.
- Holy shit.
Oh, wow.
I'm first.
I'm Nicole Paige Brooks
from Atlanta, Georgia.
I get to pick my spot,
I guess.
Oh, wow.
I am what I call
a southern belle,
or a very Atlanta girl.
I want to be on the end.
I'm a Cancer, so I'm a big--
just a big mama.
No...
I think I want to be
on this side.
No, that's the changing area.
I want to be on this end.
- Hello, somebody.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- I'm Nicole.
- Hi, Nicole.
I'm Shangela.
- It's nice to meet you.
Tell me your name again.
- Shangela, like Angela,
but with an s-h, like "sh."
Shangela Laquifa Wadley,
the debutantess
of the deep south.
All right for the country
bitches in the house.
Shangela is
a little bougie, okay?
But she's also your home girl.
How long have
you been doing drag?
- For 15 years.
- No, ma'am.
- Uh-huh.
- All right,
you've got to be perfected.
- And you?
- Only five months.
- Oh, wow.
- Fairly new.
- I hope that I don't fall into
that role of babysitting
and start, like,
fixing people's shit
when I should be really,
like, cutting their bra straps.
- What's up, bitches?
My name is David.
In drag, when I've got on tits
and tights, I go by Raven.
Bitch, this is fucking fierce.
- Oh, take a look around, girl.
Get you some.
- You didn't bring a purse
or nothin'?
- I don't carry a purse.
I stick it all in my tits.
- [laughs]
- I like to be that mysterious,
dark ice queen.
And, like, I think I have a look
that people might be
a little intimidated by.
Am I a ten?
A perfect ten.
- What a sin! Ahh!
- Oh, ohh!
- My name's Jujubee.
I'm 25,
from Boston, Massachusetts.
- I'm Nicole.
- I'm Juju.
- Juju? I love that name.
- Bitch, no, you are
Kimora Lee Simmons.
- Jujubee's just
this fabulous Asian girl.
She's very, like, poppy
and, like, fashion forward.
She loves accessories
and she likes glitter...
'cause it's wicked spah-kly.
- I'm Sahara Davenport.
I'm 25 years old.
And I live in New York City.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Oh, hey.
- Aah!
- Aaah!
[both screaming]
- Sahara Davenport came in.
Sahara and I went
to college together
and have been friends forever,
and I had no idea
she was gonna be on this show.
[both screaming]
- Excuse me, pardon me.
What were you saying?
- [squealing]
- Morgan, Morgan, Morgan!
- Bitch!
- My name is Morgan McMichaels,
and I am 28 years old.
- When I saw Morgan walk in,
I wanted to die.
- Hi.
- Ohh!
See, I know somebody.
Morgan's like my sister.
Like, we started doing drag
at the same time, same club.
- Hi, I'm Nicole.
- People think that
since I'm pretty and I'm sexy
that I should just do slutty
all the time.
I'm just eating
solid food again.
- Hello.
- I'm Mystique.
- Hi!
- I'm Mystique Summers.
I am 25 years old.
Big girls are gonna represent
this year.
Cheeseburger, Taco Bell, and
diet coke on the side, girl.
- Ohh!
- Wow, some of these girls,
they're pretty cute,
but fuck them skinny bitches.
It's a big girl's world.
- Oh, my god.
My direct persona name
is Jessica Wild.
I'm from San Juan,
Puerto Rico.
You like Puerto Ricans?
- I'm 1/4 Puerto.
- I've taken a Puerto Rican.
- My biggest fears in the
competition is with my English.
But if I don't understand
something, I am going to smile.
Uh-oh!
- My drag name is Sonique.
I now live in Atlanta, Georgia.
- Holy shit!
- Oh, my god.
- Oh, my God!
- This is Sonique.
Now I know somebody.
- My mom sent me
to a military school in hopes
that she would get
a little soldier.
Needless to say,
she got a drag queen.
[laughs]
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
[all greeting her]
- Some pretty bitches in here.
- My name is Tatianna.
I am 21 years old.
both: Mwah. Mwah.
- It's a pleasure to meet you,
Miss Tatianna.
- First time I walked out
of the house in drag,
I was 14 years old.
I don't know how I had the balls
to do it,
but I went to school in drag.
It was my closest taste
of being, like, famous.
Thank you.
- Hey, fake ladies!
[all greeting her]
- I'm Pandora Boxx, and I'm
30-blah-blah years old.
Hey, girls.
- Hi, I'm Jujubee.
- I'm Pandora.
Pandora is definitely a melting
pot of different people.
You know, there's like a dash
of Madonna,
a sprinkle of Goldie Hawn,
and a big chunk of Kathy Griffin
thrown in there.
And she has to kind of like fuse
it all together
into this melted pot of goo
that becomes Pandora.
- Do you sew?
- I do sew.
- Aah! Yes, ma'am!
- I made this.
- You better work.
Look at this.
- Me and miss Pandora, we're
gonna be real good friends.
- Oh!
- Here's another one.
- Oh, excuse me.
- I am Tyra Sanchez, and I'm 21.
- Beautiful.
- How gorgeous.
- Da-yamn.
- It's sickening.
- What a body.
- I do think
that I'm the prettiest one.
- Tyra, all right.
Are you bankable, girl?
- [chuckles] Yes.
- I came in,
I had my Rihanna hair on.
My body was right, breasts were
right, makeup was right.
Everything was on point.
I was very much a lady.
- I'm super-excited to get
to know the girls.
Different personalities,
different genres of drag,
different styles of drag.
I really couldn't make
a judgment
on who was the strongest
and who was the weakest.
- Ooh, girl!
You got she mail.
Welcome, racers,
to another glorious season
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
You're here today
because, well,
none of you were smart enough
to leak a sex tape
and land your own
reality TV show.
[laughing] No, no, no.
You've come here to compete
for the title
of America's
next drag superstar.
But to win it,
you've got to earn it, Tina.
Fasten your seatbelts.
This year's ride is gonna be
longer and harder,
with more twists and turns
than Kim Kardashian trying to
wiggle out of a pair of Spanx.
So let's put the stiletto
to the metal.
RuPaul's Drag Race is
about to blow you away.
[cheers and applause]
Hello, hello, hello.
Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race.
- When I see RuPaul enter
the room for the first time,
I'm in a state of shock.
- I am gagging
at the lovely extravaganza.
Wonderful. Hello.
- Tatianna.
- Holy shit.
I'm shaking the hand
of a legend.
- Nicole Paige Brooks.
- From Atlanta, Georgia.
- That's right, the ATL.
You're Pandora.
- Pandora Boxx.
- Pleasure to meet you.
Great, great.
- It's really, really cool to
have somebody that you idolize
come over and just--and say
your name immediately.
- You're all so gorgeous.
- I was a little star struck,
I guess.
- I'm so happy you are all here.
Anybody who steps out
of the house
with a pair of high heels
and a wig is my hero.
We searched from coast to coast,
and you are the chosen 12.
[cheers and applause]
All of you are here because you
have charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
But do you have that little
something extra it takes to win?
The stakes are high, ladies,
but the rewards are fabulous.
In addition to walking away
with the title
of America's next drag
superstar,
the winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive
a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics
and become the face
of nyxcosmetics.com;
an exclusive, one-year PR
contract
with the leading LGBT firm
Project Publicity;
be featured in L.A. Eyeworks'
legendary designer eyewear
campaign;
and headline
LOGO's Drag Race tour,
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks.
And a cash prize of $25,000.
[cheers and applause]
All right, ladies, enough talk.
Are you ready
for your close-ups?
[all cheer]
- Good.
Now, please put your hands
and legs together
for top celebrity photographer
and my good friend Mike Ruiz.
[cheers and applause]
- Okay, ladies, your first
official Drag Race photo shoot
is inspired by one of my
favorite movies of all time:
Gone With The Wind.
- [gasps]
- Yes.
Now, you'll each pose for Mike,
and then we'll choose
the one queen
who gives the best face, face,
face, I give face, beauty, face.
- Oh, my gosh, it's here.
Competition's on, bitches.
[camera shutter snapping]
- Today, we're doing
a photo shoot
which is inspired
by Gone With The Wind.
- What does she need to know?
- It's the height
of the Civil War.
You need to straddle the cannon,
work the piece of fabric, and,
you know, kind of
interact with the guys.
They're being thrust into
an environment, which, you know,
they're unfamiliar with and they
didn't have any preparation for.
- Yeah, straddle that cannon,
hon.
- Hold on...hold on right here.
- [laughing]
- And here we go.
- All right!
- Oh, lord! Oh, my God.
- Aah!
- Work! Work the fabric!
- Storm comes up, and they're
snapping pictures.
And I don't know what to do.
- Watch your hair!
Your hair is covering your face.
- Work the camera, Jujubee!
Work!
- I feel a little tug
in the back of my leg,
and I think it's gonna fly off,
so I'm grasping onto it.
And then my lashes are just
flapping back and forth.
That's all I can focus on.
I didn't know where the camera
was at this point.
- We got it!
- All right!
How do you feel, Jujubee?
- I have never been blown
like that in my life.
[laughter]
- Yes, you got a
lot of firepower
between your legs, girl.
Don't nobody make a sudden move.
She might blow it.
- When I saw the fan,
I was excited.
'Cause fans make
everything prettier.
- Okay, and...there we go!
- Ooh! Lord Jesus!
When they started cranking up
the fan, I was just like,
ugh, really?
- Watch your hair in your face.
All right, we got it!
Sonique, ride that cannon.
- Yeah, that hits the spot.
Pandora's box is on fire!
- All right!
- Jessica's a girl gone wild!
Yeah! Serve it!
Suzanne Sugarbaker!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Hoo hoo hoo!
Triumphant!
As god is my witness.
Uh-oh!
Those damn Yankees took
everything from you!
- Morgan McMichaels had
a problem
with having her wig fly off,
and she tried to recover
from it,
but I find
that she never really did.
- 3, 2, 1!
Okay, we got it.
That's it.
We did get a good shot,
but it was a struggle.
Thank you, Morgan.
- Thanks, Morgan.
Wow, the competition has
just begun
and they're already flipping
their wigs.
- Honey, how was it?
- I mean, this wig
went on vacation, girl.
She flew right off.
- [laughing]
- As I see everybody changing,
the thing that stood out most
to me is, kind of forget,
like, how much it really takes
to transform somebody
and how amazingly different
they can look
from--from one to the other.
- I wonder what everyone's
gonna look like out of drag.
I hope some of you are
attractive boys, like me.
- [laughing]
- Nicole Paige Brooks.
- From Atlanta, Georgia.
- That's right.
- And I will never go hungry
again.
- All right.
- Am I gonna pinch your nipples?
Ohh! They bounce too.
This one's jealous.
- Oh, I think it's leaking.
- Nicole had all
of the southern charm,
but I felt like
in the photoshoot situation,
you know,
she wasn't delivering couture,
she was delivering, you know,
little catalog.
Look off into the distance,
off into the horizon.
Too far off, too far off,
sister.
Sahara Davenport had a really
great understanding of her body
and how to move.
Although she didn't have
that same understanding
with her face.
- We're gonna sit you
on that cannon
with these
two gorgeous soldiers.
- And I'm like, "Oh, my god,
you want me to stand
next to them?"
- Don't teeter over it.
- I can't cross my legs,
anything.
The skirt is so tight.
I'm like trying my hardest
to be perfect.
- Chin down a little bit.
Remember the camera's down here.
- Chin down!
- I felt that I could
have did better.
I should have been just, like
more focused
on the picture itself.
- We got it!
- Got it! Wonderful.
- Be aware of the camera.
Pretty, pretty face.
- Pretty face.
Think Franklin mint plate.
- Ha ha, yeah.
- I wanted to bring
the most fiercest possible.
- Chicken cutlets!
Chicken cutlets.
- But my boobs were falling out
the top of the dress.
RuPaul's screaming,
Mike is screaming,
and through my head is going,
"bitch, pull it together.
Look at that camera
and pull it together."
both: Yes!
- Cover up, dear.
[laughing]
Ooh, is that a possum
in the woods?
[laughter]
Yes, yes!
War is hell!
But you look gorgeous!
- [laughing] Right.
All right, we got it!
- Gorgeous!
- That is
what I'm talkin' about.
- Yes.
- [sighs]
I love a good blow job.
- [giggles] Brat.
- That was amazing.
Ohh.
I was able to spread my cooch
and air it out.
- Immediately, Raven and Morgan
were kind of off-putting.
- [gasps]
Oh, my god.
- We're all staring
at each other,
'cause we're just in shock.
You is naked.
- I think Morgan is gonna get
on my nerves.
- Son of a bitch.
- Oh, wait, wait,
these are my wigs.
- Do you usually do your own
hair and makeup, or...
- Um...technically, well, no.
The answer is no.
I felt that people
were looking down on me
for only doing this
for five months.
It just made me feel more
determined to show them
that I can do it.
Bah, bah, bah! Whoop!
Uhh!
- Hey, dolls.
Come on down.
Gather around.
Mike and I went over
all your photos.
You each did a great job.
But only one of you
can be the best.
The winner of the first
Drag Race photoshoot is...
Raven.
- Oh, my god.
[applause]
Congratulations.
- I think me winning the
first challenge is gonna make
the other bitches
kind of open their eyes,
'cause I plan on winning
the grand prize.
- Have fun tonight,
'cause when it comes
to RuPaul's Drag Race,
tomorrow is another day.
[alarm beeping]
- Gather round, dolls.
Now, if you haven't guessed
by now,
Gone With The Wind is
the inspiration
for your first main challenge.
Now, Scarlett O'Hara was one
fierce bitch.
She survived the Civil War,
the fires of Atlanta,
and the ransacking of Tara.
And still, she was able to turn
out a drop-dead gorgeous outfit,
just using the curtains
in her window.
And now it's your turn to do
the same.
Inspired by
Miss Scarlett O'Hara,
you must create
your best drag look
using just these curtains,
courtesy of smith+noble.
And in the work room, we've got
some used home furnishings
we picked up at
Out of the Closet
that you can use to accessorize.
You'll wear your own wigs,
shoes, and undergarments.
And when it comes to makeup,
NYX Cosmetics has you covered.
Tomorrow, you'll be debuting
your stunning
"gone with the window"
drag looks on the main stage.
Raven, since you won
the photoshoot,
you get to choose
your curtains first.
Choose wisely.
Take your time.
That's what winning
the challenge gets you.
Take note, girls.
- I'm gonna go with these.
- You're going with those?
- Yes.
- No, don't pick that one.
- In a moment, I'm gonna let
the rest of you fight it out.
And remember, only one
matching set of curtains each.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
[giggling]
- There weren't no ladies on
that set today.
There were men
running for curtains.
You pushed me! You pushed me!
- This is mine.
- It is on now.
- I dashed for the first set
of curtains I saw.
And along came Tatianna,
and she grabbed the same one.
- Reach all you want to.
Reach all you want to.
- Y'all could go get
another one.
- This is mine.
I was like, back up off.
I wasn't letting go.
And so she didn't hold on
any longer after that.
I win.
- I got to the curtain first.
And I pulled it down first.
It really wasn't that classy
of her to do that.
- Ooh, I broke a nail.
- Keep it moving, bitches.
- No, sir!
- The rules of the challenge
are pick a set of curtains
and make your costume from it.
We also have to incorporate
homewear,
pieces from Out of the Closet.
- I'm going to be flawless
with this.
- Pandora, get that table back
there; you can have that one.
- I was trying to figure out
where I was going
and where we were putting
our stuff.
And then Shangela said,
"come over here,
come over to this station,
and we'll work together."
And I was like,
"You want to work together
because you don't know how
to sew, and I know how to sew."
- Could I beg you just to, like,
show me how to sew
that little piece together?
Quickly.
- I guess.
- Hey, I'm not gonna ask him
to do it for me.
I want to learn.
But I need to be right there
next to the teacher.
[squeals]
Look at this.
Look what happened.
Is that supposed to happen?
- Oh, what are you doing?
- I did it.
I just pushed the foot pedal.
- If I don't get to finish my
outfit 'cause I run out of time,
then I'll be like,
"Damn you bitches!"
- Sahara, I'm sewing.
Thank you!
- You better work, diva.
Work!
- Oh, my god, Pandora.
- Mystique felt like the fabric
wasn't plus-size girl-friendly.
What size are you?
- 22.
- Really?
- Mystique looks like she's
making a huge pillowcase.
For Mystique to sit there
and think that her curtains
are not plus-size-friendly
is a crock of shit.
- Bitch...I'm doing
something wrong.
- You're doing something wrong?
- Mine is broke.
I broke...
- You what?
You broke the needle?
- No, I just broke
the whole machine.
Yeah, this is an issue.
- So now we're fucked.
- I should get ready,
'cause I'll have to lip-sync
for my life in a minute.
- Hey, is anybody home?
all: Hello.
- Clean up this mess!
No, just kidding.
Keep working.
Hi, Mystique.
- Hey, girl.
- All right.
How's it going for you?
- Kind of rough.
- Rough? Really?
- Oh, you don't have a, uh...
- No.
- Dress for it.
- This is the biggest one.
- Why don't you pad it?
- I don't got time for that.
- Well, this challenge is about
overcoming adversity and--
- Oh, yeah.
- You'll do it.
- Like I said, fucking bitches
fucking up the house.
- I'm gonna come over here
to Shangela.
- Hey, Ru.
- What's your inspiration?
- Well, this is gonna be a hot
gun concoction.
- I see.
- Along with--I'm gonna also do
some sewing, and Pandora 's
kind of helped show me
the machine.
- I see.
- I might be the new bitch
on the block,
but in order to be on the show,
I quit my job, because I love
performing as Shangela.
So I have 100% committed myself
to this.
- Oh, my goodness, corn?
- Yeah.
- Are you gonna be using corn?
- It is "the south will rise"
meets Children of the Corn.
- I've seen great potential
in you,
so you've got to--you've got
to bring it, honey.
Tyra.
- Hi.
- Hi, honey.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
Now, you have a child.
- I do have a son.
His name is Jeremiah.
- Jeremiah --oh, that's
the tattoo you have there.
- Yeah, tattoo on my arm.
- Why, Jeremiah?
- Um, we wanted a name from
the bible.
My name comes from the bible,
so--
- Tyra 's in the bible?
- No, not Tyra.
James is in the bible.
- [laughing]
He was born the first week
of my 12th grade year.
It's like the first time I'll be
away from him this long.
My son is, like, my major
motivation
for winning this competition.
- You know, a family that drags
together,
stays together.
All right.
- Thank you.
- Sahara, hi, honey.
- Hi, Ru.
- You put a lot of work into
this bustier.
- I have.
- And is this the vision you had
from the very start?
- I don't know where I'm going
with it, to be honest.
- Are you a little worried
about that?
- Of course I'm worried!
I still want to be gorgeous,
but I also want to have a good--
a good garment to show.
- Yeah.
I think you got a little bit
more work to do,
so I don't want to keep you.
- All right, thank you.
- Hello, Tatianna.
- Hello.
- This is what you wanted.
- Yes.
- But you haven't gotten
very far here.
- No.
- What's going on?
- Looking at it from
a distance,
I chose it 'cause it looked like
it more of a silver hue
that I could maybe do
silver shoes with.
- Right.
So you're looking for an accent
to match your shoes.
- Mm-hmm.
Because to me if you have a--
- You have big feet?
- 13.
- Yeah, well, that never
stopped me.
- But I also don't like to show
my toes.
- You don't like to show
your toes.
- My big toe is shaped
like a doorknob,
and so I don't think
it looks good
in open-toed shoes.
- Well, I mean, just...
crazy--I have got to see
your toe.
Can I please see your toe?
Because you can't go through
life...
- Hiding my big toe?
See?
It's just too big.
- That is a gorgeous toe.
I know people who would pay
to suck that toe.
- [laughs]
- I say let it go.
Let it go.
And that advice is gonna help
you in this competition.
You have to go for it,
and don't let anything
stop you.
- Okay.
- Free your toes...
And the rest will follow.
- [laughs]
- Hey, Jessica.
Can I see what you're doing?
- Yes, I get this because
I love the color,
but it is very clear,
and I have problems
with that,
because I don't want to look
like I am naked.
- You don't want to look
like a whore, do you?
- No!
Not on camera.
- [laughs]
Maybe after the show.
- Yeah.
- What's underneath here?
- I use a corset.
- Oh, is it a corset
you brought from home?
- Yes, and I make this.
- I make in...
Sorry,
explain it in Spanish.
- Just a little top,
and you could say it in Spanish
if you like.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- Okay...
[speaking Spanish]
- Si.
- [speaking Spanish]
- Muy bien, muy bien.
Ooh.
- Because it's going to give
a special touch.
- Oh, wow.
Now, do you pad anything?
- I don't have a lady body.
- Can we see?
- I have a guy butt.
- [laughing]
- And I need to make the curves
of a lady.
- I can't wait to see it
on the main stage.
- Thanks, Ru.
- All right, I'm gonna move
over here
to see miss Morgan
and see what you're up to.
- Hi.
- What are your plans for?
- Okay, now, I'm not sure what
I'm gonna do with the sleeves.
But I think I'm gonna do
the high neck
and maybe try and incorporate
this into it.
- Ah, wow.
- I got this.
- Uh-huh.
- You know, which is huge.
I could use this as a skirt,
really.
- And you feel like you have
enough time?
- Um, I will make time.
I will get it done.
- I see.
All right, ladies.
Gather round.
I'll see you tomorrow on
the main stage,
where our extra-special guest
judge will be...
Kathy Griffin.
- [gasping]
- I really identify with
Kathy Griffin.
I love her, so I'm excited that
she's gonna be here.
- Now, remember, in this world,
you only get one chance to make
a first impression.
So don't fuck It up.
Good luck.
See you soon.
- I'm kind of scared about what
the judges are gonna say.
With this hot-ass mess I'm gonna
wear out there tomorrow,
this is gonna be brutal.
- Whoo! Burning!
[all chattering]
- Tonight is my first day that
I'm going to walk the runway.
So I have a lot of great
emotions.
- Are you nervous?
- Yeah. Yeah, I am.
The only thing on my mind
is finish this garment.
- What you think, Sahara?
- Ooh, yeah.
- I think Mystique is a mistake.
- I love doing drag because
I love the transformation--
the costuming, the hair,
the makeup.
The glamour of it all.
It is an art form.
- To be able to change yourself
into a completely different
person
is very empowering.
- Yes.
- Yes!
- Hey, you guys.
So happy to see all of you.
Santino,
so good to have you back.
- I've missed you.
- Merle, you look marvelous
tonight.
- My world's been empty
without you, Ru.
- Hey, Mike, what do you think
of our queens so far?
- Oh, I'm very impressed.
- And miss Kathy Griffin,
welcome to the show.
- Ru, I cannot believe that you
dismembered our first lady
and stole Michelle Obama's arms.
They are perfect, as are you.
- Okay, judges, for this week's
challenge,
inspired by miss
Scarlett O'Hara,
the girls had to turn
out a breathtaking drag look
using just curtains
and some used home furnishings.
Are you ready to see what
they've created?
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- I think that I do have
a good chance
at winning this challenge.
My dress looks amazing.
- I love the fabric
of the underdress.
It's actually the carpet
and the drapes.
- Oh, wow.
- And they don't match,
and they don't need to,
not today.
- That's so 2000.
There is nothing dirty about
this Sanchez.
- Here comes some sass.
- Yes, sassy miss Raven.
- My runway walk is giving them
a little hip action.
Flip of the hair,
working it out,
giving them sex.
- I do like the focus
on the waist.
- Yes, now she--
- Even when there isn't one,
she kind of manufactured one.
- That's right.
- Which is essential
in your business.
- Wow.
- Sonique, boom.
- Yes.
- Southern belle, African,
playboy mansion,
all rolled into one.
I definitely think that no one
else came up with that concept.
- I wonder what she uses
that rod for.
Here is Jujubee.
- I feel great--
sickly, gorgeous.
I wasn't going for pretty.
I was going for fierce.
I put on my feathers
and I felt like a big ol' style
warrior goddess.
- Lauren Bacall would love
that collar.
- Yes.
- She will wrestle you
to the ground for that collar.
- Everyone's doing redhead,
Kathy.
- Look at those gams.
- The legs are killing me.
- I didn't really know what
to do.
The lights are in my eyes.
I see Ru 's teeth glowing
at me.
Freaking out inside.
- She's serving some
Raquel Welch there,
and I don't just mean her hair.
- Sahara.
- Uh-oh, it's raining.
- She is throwing
some serious shade.
- We'll see her poolside
in South Beach.
- I'm excited to work
the runway.
That's one of my favorite
things.
- I like the mix of the blues.
- Yeah.
- Looks great.
- It's refreshing.
- As I step onto the runway, it
can be a little intimidating.
You don't want to fuck It up in
front of RuPaul.
- There's corn hanging
from her hand!
- What is that corn doing
there?
- I've been corn cobbed.
- It's a co--you been
corn cobbed?
- Yes.
- Jessica Wild.
- Wild flower.
- It's inspiring, a movie that
I never saw.
But in my imagination,
that girl is amazing,
like Jessica, so...
- How did she get it back from
the sweatshop so quickly?
'cause it looks like it took
many, many children
to make those flowers.
- You're absolutely right.
- It's a lot of work.
- Morgan McMichaels.
Look at that body.
- My attitude is a positive
one.
I will not go home.
This challenge
will not send me home.
- I love the little belt
and the little belly jewel.
- I love the little eyelids
there.
- And I never met a grommet
I didn't like.
- Yeah, grommets are fabulous.
- Me too. I don't know
what that is, but I agree.
- [laughing]
All right!
- That's not just an outfit;
it's a lifestyle.
- Who needs a hybrid
when you could have a basket
on your head?
- I pulled out every single
trick that I have in the bag.
- Ohh!
[laughter]
- If I was gonna go home,
I was gonna be memorable
for something.
- Nicole Paige brooks.
- My outfit's like the madame
running the saloon
down the street
from the Tara
that's burning down.
- Yes, miss thing's got a little
bustle in her hustle.
Vivien Westwood
does Vivien Leigh.
- Oh, my God,
I wish I 'd said that!
- Pandora Boxx.
- I can't believe that bitch
went into my purse
and took that wig.
I just can't even believe it.
- It's like a body double.
- There's only one chance
I'm gonna get
to walk a runway in front
of Kathy Griffin,
and I am wearing that wig.
- Hello, dolls.
I have to say,
anyone who has the courage
to break free
and follow their heart
is my hero.
Based on your "gone with
the window" challenge,
your photoshoot,
and tonight's presentation
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Jujubee.
Tatianna.
Raven.
Sonique.
Jessica Wild.
Nicole Paige Brooks.
Here's the bad news.
None of you are the best.
And here is the good news.
None of you are the worst.
Congratulations...
you're all safe.
- I don't fucking like
being just safe.
I wanted to be one
of the top ones.
- As you move forward in this
competition,
I have one piece of advice
for you.
Step up your game.
You may leave the stage.
For you six, one of you will be
the winner of this challenge.
And for one of you,
it's curtains.
Now, we're gonna begin
with Tyra.
So these are the curtains
you started with.
- I would have liked
to have seen
just a little more originality.
- I don't mind that it's not
necessarily innovative,
but it is a very classic shape.
- I have a very small criticism,
which is just maybe have a
little more fun with your face.
Smile, more facial expressions.
And remember, it's drag.
So give me face.
- Let's take a look at your
photograph with Mike Ruiz.
What was going through
your mind?
- Pose, but don't fall.
- I disagree.
I think falling on those
two guys
would have been the best thing
that could have happened
that day.
- Shangela, tell us what this
outfit says about you.
- Well, you know, a little fun,
a little rough around the edges,
because I'm fairly new
to the drag world.
- Your bust line
is non-existent.
There's no waist definition
there.
- Wow.
- I think you need to have
a better understanding
of how to relate your face
in a photo shoot situation.
- Morgan McMichaels, what does
your outfit say about you?
- I thought warrior.
- I love it.
I love it because I'm calling
you Chergefani.
You're like a little Cher,
a little Fergie,
a little Gwen Stefani.
- And Cher wore something like
that in her Half Breed video.
[imitating Cher]
In Half Breed.
[laughter]
- It reads as a lot
of different things,
and that could have gone
horribly wrong.
But it worked.
- So how much?
[laughter]
- Pandora Boxx.
- It's like looking in a
mirror, it really is.
- Kathy, would you say she's
the most beautiful
of all the queens?
- Well, obviously.
[laughter]
- Wow!
Now, see, I wish that some
of the energy in this photo,
you could bring to the main
stage in your presentation.
- Here, you're very demure
and girly.
There, you're like belting it
out like Judy Garland
on barbiturates
and amphetamines!
- Mystique Summers Madison.
- I'm torn about the dress.
Remember, it is the first
impression.
- I may be a big girl,
but I can get down with
the skinny bitches
and wear something short
if I want to.
[laughter]
- Now, is that your breast
coming out?
- Got milk?
[laughter]
- All the humor we're seeing
from you now,
I would loved to have seen
in that picture.
- Yes.
- That's right--
know who you are,
and deliver at all times.
All right, Sahara Davenport.
Your first impression for us.
- Well, my boyfriend's Asian,
so I went with the parasol.
- Well, nothing says Civil War
like my Asian boyfriend.
[laughter]
I love the dress, I just don't
think it's draggy enough.
- I agree; it probably could be
a little more flamboyant.
- I'm a New Yorker.
I'm always on the move.
So I decide to do something
a little more contemporary.
- But, with that said, you know,
this is a drag competition.
- Yes.
Well, thank you, ladies.
While the six of you untuck in
the Interior Illusions lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
Thank you.
Okay, now just between us girls,
we've got a little work to do.
Let's talk about Mystique.
That outfit was raggedy as hell.
I mean, the split was even
raggedy,
but it was entertaining.
- If they were at a drag show
and she did that split,
all the gays would go crazy
and cheer.
Bad dress, though.
- Her humor kind of sells,
like, the raggedy dress.
- Shangela.
- Too old-fashioned looking.
- She had a lot more
personality
in the question and answer part
that the walk.
So she definitely could really
learn how to perform, I think.
- We're not judging potential
a year down the line.
We're picking a drag superstar
today.
- Today.
This is RuPaul's Drag Race;
not RuPaul's School for Girls.
Sahara.
- Chic and wonderful and sweet
and great poses,
but I don't know if she really
has the fabulousness.
- Exactly, you know.
It's all about
the razzle dazzle.
You know, and we didn't really
get to really see that.
- Tyra.
- Beautiful, great visual.
Great dress, great hair,
great makeup.
Where's the personality?
- Wessonality--none whatsoever.
Morgan McMichaels.
- I didn't really get
the fun personality.
- I loved the concept.
Overall, just a really
well-executed look.
- Pandora Boxx.
- She was really humorous,
and I thought her look
was great.
- She needs that sort of drag
personality like that.
"I'm taking the stage,
I'm owning it.
I'm here, bitches."
- With that said, silence!
Let's bring the girls...
back in.
Welcome back, ladies.
Tyra Sanchez...
The judges loved your look.
But...do you have
the personality
to be the next drag superstar?
Congratulations.
You're safe.
Shangela...you have an
irrepressible energy,
but can energy make up
for a lack of experience?
I'm sorry, my dear.
You're up for elimination.
- I expected to be
in the bottom group.
Now I'm thinking in my head,
let's turn it out.
- Morgan McMichaels, you made
a lasting first impression
with the judges,
and you are the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
- Thank you very much.
- You will receive immunity
from next week's elimination.
- Yes.
- Plus, you'll be doing a
photo spread
for Interior Illusions
that will be featured in
Lux magazine.
Congratulations.
- Thank you very much.
- Winning any challenge in this
competition is amazing.
But to win the very first one,
I set myself a high bar.
- Pandora Boxx,
congratulations.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
[applause]
- Mystique Summers Madison.
There is one word
for your outfit.
Raggedy.
But...based on your
unforgettable presentation...
I'm giving you a get out of jail
free card.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Pull it together, my dear!
[applause]
- Since I was almost cut, now
I'm gonna work even harder,
because I believe I still could
be the next drag superstar.
- Sahara Davenport.
This pains me.
You're a beautiful doll.
But your personality did not
shine through tonight.
I'm sorry, my dear.
You are up for elimination.
- My heart fills with tears.
It's so crazy,
because I'm here to win,
but, like, I don't want to go
against my friend.
- I expected to be in the bottom
two for this week,
but I did not expect to be going
against Sahara.
Sahara and I went to college
together
and have been friends forever.
- Two queens stand before me.
This is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourselves
from elimination.
The time has come...
for you to lip-synch...
for your life.
And remember, good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[techno music]
Stroll down the runway
Another payday
- As I'm performing,
I'm looking at the judges,
and some are making great eye
contact with me,
and others are looking
only at Sahara.
So I'm thinking, turn it up,
Shangela, turn it up.
And that's what I did.
Cover girl
- Whoo!
- I looked over and she had
ripped her skirt off
and was going crazy.
I'm gonna have to shut it down.
Cover girl
Put the face in your walk
Head to toe
- When she hit the floor,
I'm like, yes, yes, bitch.
Work it.
Stroll down the runway
Another payday
Cover girl
Put the face in your walk
Head to toe
- It looked like Mortal Kombat.
[laughter]
Walk
And what
[laughter and applause]
- Wow.
Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Sahara Davenport...
Chantay, you stay.
- Yes!
- Congratulations, girl.
- [whispering] I'm sorry.
- [whispering]
Please, you don't have to...
I love you.
- It's a bittersweet moment.
I'm happy that I survived.
But, of course, I'm sad.
You know, I sent my friend home.
- Shangela...
you have only just begun.
But I have a feeling
we haven't seen
the last of you yet.
Good luck, my dear.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you all.
[applause]
[laughter]
- It was disappointing.
If I was to lose to anyone
in this group,
I'm glad it was
my sister Sahara.
That was a great experience,
and now it's time for me to pack
these wigs and go home.
- This was truly
a bittersweet victory.
Congratulations, ladies, for
surviving your first challenge.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen.
- Now let the music play.
Don't be jealous
of my boogie
You can say that you
are not
But I always see you
looking
Don't be jealous
of my boogie