- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
- Big girls are gonna represent
this year.
Fuck them skinny bitches.
- Pandora, you stuck me
with these fucking bitches.
Oh, my God.
I'm in a group with, like,
Satan's baby.
I could be a bigger bitch.
- I need money!
My biggest fears in
the competition is my English.
Please help me.
- Raven, during the solo,
you didn't make a lot of money.
- Fuck.
I fucked this up.
- You're up for elimination.
Nicole Paige Brooks,
sashay away.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- And tonight...
Well, howdy, y'all.
The dolls will be gagging on
the eleganza.
- Aah!
- And it don't taste like
chicken.
- Did you just put shortening
in your crotch?
- Cock a doodle doo!
- With extra special
guest judges
Kathy Najimy
and Tanya Tucker.
- Whoo!
- The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX Cosmetics
and be the face of
nyxcosmetics.com,
an exclusive one-year
P.R. contract
with the leading LGBT firm
Project Publicity,
be featured in L.A. Eyeworks'
legendary
designer eyewear campaign,
and headline
Logo's Drag Race Tour
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks,
and a cash prize of $25,000.
And may the best woman win.
[alarm beeps]
- Oh, God.
- Oh, wow.
- Not a picnic.
- Oh...
- We're eating something.
- Do we have to eat?
- Oh, Lord.
- As we walked into
the work space,
all I saw was one long table
with ten chairs.
Something is going in my mouth.
I know that much.
- Just hope it ain't
no cherry pie.
- Nicole says, "Be safe, bitch."
- There's more room over here
now.
Coming back into the work room
after Nicole had left
and I had to lip synch
for my life, it felt good
that I had beat her.
Being in the bottom two, bitch?
No.
- I bet that's nerve-racking.
- I did not come here
to lip synch for my life.
I came here to win.
- We love you, Nicole.
- But you got to go.
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl.
You've got she-mail.
Cock a doodle doo.
Howdy, racers.
Are you
a coal miner's daughter
or just a boy named Sue?
Well, either way,
for this next challenge,
you best pray that Jesus
takes the wheel.
And remember,
no matter what happens,
I will always love you.
[laughs]
Well, howdy, y'all.
[cheers and applause]
Well, my, my, my.
Go on, now.
Sit a spell, y'all.
Now, Georgia is where my career
really took off.
I am a country queen at heart.
In those early years,
I had no money.
I would eat anything.
And now that's what
you're gonna do.
[groaning]
- Mystique's gonna finally win
a challenge.
Finally.
- Your mini-challenge
is a taste test
to figure out if what
you're eating is chicken...
or what.
What?!
Or chicken.
Chicken or what?!
The first two queens
to get three points
will be the winners.
Oh, and please put on your
blindfolds.
- Oh.
- No, sir.
- I did not know that this was
gonna be drag Survivor.
- Here is y'all's first course.
Ready?
Let's eat.
- Mm.
Answers please.
The correct answer is "what?!"
They were bull testicles.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Nothing says country cuisine
like bull testicles.
Okay, ladies.
Second course.
Dig in.
It's finger-licking good.
All right.
Answers please.
The correct answer is "what?!"
Mystique has two right.
Morgan has two.
And Pandora has two.
What you just put in your mouth
was soy chicken.
- Oh, okay.
- Isn't so bad.
Third course.
Dig in.
[ominous music]
- Ew.
- I'm thinking that it's, like,
a rat tail or something.
I knew that wasn't chicken,
honey.
- Chicken or what?!
The correct answer is "what?!"
Now, what you just put
in your mouth...
were frog legs.
- Oh!
- Ladies, we have a three-way
tie between Mystique...
- Hell yeah.
- Pandora, and Morgan.
In front of you is a basket of
chicken, rabbit, alligator,
and deep-fried cow brains.
Mm-mm.
The first two queens to finish
everything in their baskets
and show me their empty mouths
will be the winners.
Are you ready?
Dig in.
Melts in your mouth.
Not in your hands.
- I had a plan.
Chew halfway, fill your mouth
with water, swallow.
- Fuck these skinny bitches.
Yummy.
You have to eat everything.
- Hell yeah.
- All right.
Empty mou--all right, she ate
everything.
Mystique is--we have a winner
over here.
- Mystique might as well have
picked up the basket,
opened the hatch,
and just dropped it down.
She was done like that.
- It's down to Pandora
and Morgan McMichaels.
Morgan has two morsels left.
- Swallow, Morgan.
Swallow.
- I took one swallow of
cow brains, and I just ralphed.
- Aah!
- You're still in the game.
You're still in the game.
- Come on, Pandora.
You got it, girl.
You got it.
- We got a second winner
over here.
Morgan McMichaels.
- [belches]
- Congratulations,
Mystique and Morgan.
You're winners, baby,
and the captains for your next
group challenge.
- Congratulations.
- For today's main challenge,
you'll be shooting a commercial
for Disco Extra-Greasy
Shortening.
That's Disco--Extra-Greasy.
And you're gonna be selling it
country-queen style.
Okay, Mystique.
Who do you choose?
- Pandora.
- Pandora, come on down.
- Raven.
- West coast.
- Juju.
- Laotian in the house.
- Sahara.
- I was picking strategically.
Other people was probably not.
They was picking friends.
Tatianna.
- Tatianna.
- Sonique.
- So Jessica and Tyra remain.
- Mystique kind of looked at me
like, "Who?"
And I was like,
"Fuck no to Tyra."
- The spicy Latina.
- Jessica.
- It didn't bother me at all.
They saved the best for last.
- Here are two scripts for your
commercials.
One for fried chicken
and one for fried fish fillets.
Mystique, you get to pick one.
- I'll get the closest one...
- All right.
Both commercials have the same
country queen characters.
Your commercials will debut
tomorrow on the main stage.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- We have fried fish fillets.
- Fish?
- I like some fish.
- There's a little concern in
my mind about Mystique leading.
- We're gonna have you as
Disco Critter.
You have this line
and you have that line,
then that's it.
- I picked Jessica because
I didn't want her
to have a part where she has
to actually listen
to everybody mingle in with
everybody.
You don't know that much
English.
- All right.
- Ellie Mae?
- I'm a chameleon, darling.
I can do whatever I need to.
- Aunt Judy Faye,
and Baby Girl.
- Baby Girl.
- Who wants to do
Aunt Judy Faye?
I asked the girls who they felt
they wanted to do.
Then I made the executive
decision.
Do you want to do Ellie Mae?
- Yeah.
- Do you want to do the baby?
- Doesn't matter.
- I think she has more
of a baby face.
- I do too.
- I'll be the baby.
I'll be the baby.
- Everyone wanted to be
something, you know, fun,
something, you know, pretty.
- Disco Critter, do you want
to do that part?
- You're gonna be, like,
a chicken.
- A chicken.
- So I get the Disco Critter,
which is a fucking chicken.
And it really pissed me off.
- Okay, so Raven
has Disco Critter.
Raven is the best makeup artist
in this competition by far.
I knew that Raven would be able
to execute the character
with her personality
and her makeup skills.
- Yeah, I'm gonna be
a fucking chicken.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Welcome to another
home-fried meal.
Welcome to another home...
- Do you need help
learning that?
- What?
- Do you need help
learning that?
- No, no.
- Okay, okay.
- The girls said,
"We give the chicken
because don't talk a lot."
At the end, I realize
the chicken talk a lot.
Welcome to another
home-fry meal.
- Mystique decides to give
Jessica
the opening and closing
monologues, I'll say.
They weren't just lines.
- Shortening?
- Shortening.
Shortening.
- Shortenin'.
- I'm kind of scared.
- [groaning]
- Uh, I hope this don't
fall apart.
- The main challenge today
is to put on a commercial
for Disco Extra-Greasy
Shortening.
- Oh, Auntie, I just had the
worst day of my life.
- Ellie Mae,
why ya in such a state?
- We only had about three hours
to learn the lines.
- It's that mean
Billie Joe McAllister.
He's been picking on me all day.
My biggest worry for the team
at this time is just getting
the lines in.
Mystique, she's working
double time.
both: Disco Extra-Greasy.
- I think Mystique's doing
a fabulous job.
I am surprised.
I like her a lot.
- Greasy--
- [hissing]
- So are you happy
with who you picked?
- Yes. I think
this is the best team.
Mystique, she fucking swallowed
that basket like the only one.
- She took the basket
and went "gulp."
- Words are words.
People think words don't hurt
'cause they're just words,
but when you hear it
every day...
Fuck everybody else.
- Okay, everybody.
One more time.
Go ahead, Jessica.
- Anna Grain--
Grain Annie?
- Granny.
- "Granny ain't," right?
- No, Granny's separate.
Granny is just one person.
- Oh, Aunt Judy.
Always in my life, when I want
something, it's not easy,
but I am going to keep going,
and I am going to work.
- Howdy.
all: Howdy-do, Ru?
- So this is the McCoys,
isn't it?
- Yes, ma'am.
- The Real McCoys.
You think you know your lines?
- Yes.
- I'd love to hear 'em.
- Welcome to another
home-fried meal,
courtesy of Disco
Extra-Greasy Shortening.
- Auntie, what's for dinner?
- It's your favorite, Ellie Mae.
- Why, it's so delicious.
- And crispy too.
- And crispy too!
- Now, McCoys,
what's your biggest concern
going into this challenge?
- My group from the previous
challenge was in the bottom.
- Right.
- And now that I'm team leader,
I don't want my group to be
in the bottom.
I'm up on the chopping block.
If I'm in the bottom group,
then I'm up for elimination.
You know?
And I think the person in charge
should be...
- Are you basing your characters
on people
in real life or television?
- My mom.
I'm just kidding.
- Is it a sexy Disco Critter?
- It's a fun, funky, fresh,
and country Disco Critter.
But it's gonna be more
of, like, a...
I guess you could say a--
a chicken.
- Uh-huh.
- It's a chicken.
There's no way
to make this pretty.
- All right, McCoys, well,
carry on.
I'll let you finish
getting ready.
- I'm really confident.
I think we're gonna win.
- Well, hello, Hatfields.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hi!
- Come on over and talk to me.
I want to hear about
your characterizations.
Now, I asked the other kids
to do an impromptu
table reading.
You think you're prepared enough
to do one for me?
- I'm not ready.
- And action.
- Welcome to another m--
Ugh.
Welcome to another fried, hot,
meal.
The...
Ooh.
- It's that
Billie Joe McAllister.
He...
He says I like fish.
- Every Hatfield woman does.
She does,
and there's another line.
Ain't that right, Granny?
- That's right.
We all love fish.
- I don't know if it was just
the pressure of doing it
in front of RuPaul, but it just
really just flopped.
- Still a little bit
underprepared for the challenge.
Jessica, did you choose
your role,
or was your role assigned
to you?
- No, my leader.
- And you chose Jessica
to have a role
with so many lines because...
- I know she'll turn it out
and have fun with it.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm nervous that if we fail,
I'm gonna go down,
because I'm the captain.
I'm responsible for everything.
- McCoys, can you come over
to this table?
Gather round, kids.
Ladies, in a moment, you'll be
shooting your commercials.
And I'm sending in a pro
to help coach you
with your performances.
You'll be working with
our special guest judge
Kathy Najimy.
- Whoo!
- One last thing.
There's a little twist.
I want you to swap scripts.
So now the Hatfields
will be the McCoys,
and the McCoys will be
the Hatfields.
- She switches
the fucking scripts.
- Sorry for the last-minute
change, but that's showbiz.
- We're definitely gagging.
- Don't fuck it up, y'all.
Bye.
all: Bye.
- It really pissed me off.
Because we're now having
to not only
learn new lines
but get dressed.
Oh.
- Here we go.
Let's start again.
- This is gonna separate
the girls from the women, honey.
- It's time for Team McCoy
to do our commercial.
We look ugly, fabulous,
and we're owning it.
- Oh, how "purdy" you are.
Of course you know Kathy Najimy.
- Hi.
- She will be directing
the commercial for you all.
- All right,
we're gonna kick butt
on this, okay, you guys?
- I can't believe
she's standing
in the same room that I'm in.
I'm just--I just want to pee
everywhere, just soak myself.
- Here we go, people.
- I am going to feel that I am
a pollo,
so the chicken enter fierce.
- Take one.
- Hi!
Welcome to another
home-fried meal
courtesy of Disco
Extra-Greasy Shortening!
- Cut.
That was great.
Go a little slower,
'cause we really
want to understand
what you're saying. Okay.
- Welcome to another
home-fried meal!
- Wait, can you stop?
Can we cut?
Can you--
is it "home-fried male"?
Is it "home-fried male"?
- Home-fried meal.
- Meal. Okay.
- Comida!
- Thought she was gonna
fry up a boy.
- Hi!
Welcome to another
home-fried meal!
- Howdy, Auntie.
What's for dinner?
- It's your favorite, Ellie Mae.
- Is it a Tic Tac?
- Cut.
Ellie Mae--everything she's
saying
should be sex, sex, sex,
even though she's saying
something else.
- What's for dinner?
- It's your favorite, Ellie Mae.
- Auntie, I want you to chain
smoke through the whole thing.
- It's Granny McCoy's famous
fried chicken.
- Cut.
Lots of energy, people.
- What is it, Auntie?
- Oh, please tell her.
The suspense is boring me
to pieces.
When I'm on stage performing,
I tend to use my body a lot,
and this was all face.
That Ellie Mae's dumber than
a box of rocks, ain't she?
- Baby, can you make a tiny bit
of a more baby voice?
- Like this?
- Yeah.
- Oh, please tell her.
The suspense is boring me
to pieces.
- I lost my line.
Okay, I got it. I got it.
I got it.
- And go.
Action.
- Shit.
I really did lose it this time.
Wait. Hold on.
- We just need
to pick up the speed.
We only have 30 minutes.
- My secret ingredient
is Disco Greasy Shortening.
- And cut.
- That's a real moment
that she could take.
- Yeah.
Grandma, when she says
"something special,"
give me a little of this.
Like, "Of course
you got something special."
- That's the same age I was
when I won your cousin's heart
thanks to Granny's
special ingredient.
- Cut.
- Granny didn't beam with pride
when...
- When I said the thing,
which is the third time.
Does not take direction well.
Grandma, if you don't
turn your head
when they say
"special ingredient,"
I'm gonna run through this thing
and turn it for you.
You have a minute to show
America who your characters are,
so you have to really
pump 'em up.
- I'm super stoked.
Welcome to another
home-fried meal.
- Cut.
Critter, we need more energy
and comedy from you, 'cause you
are in a chicken outfit,
but you're doing a very--
sort of a Meryl Streep thing.
Let's think of a chicken voice.
- I'm thinking the whole time
country accent, Southern accent,
and then I'm told,
"Don't do that;
sound like a chicken."
Welcome to another fun-filled
evening--oh, shit.
- Exit and come on again.
- Marker.
- Welcome to another--
oh, shit.
I think I could sell ice
to an Eskimo
but not dressed as
a fucking chicken.
- Chicken, did you do your own
makeup?
'Cause you look a little like
the Joker.
It's scaring me a little bit.
I always like the funny.
- I realize that you're
directing us,
but at the same time, like,
make it seem a little more fun.
- Marker.
- Welcome to another
home-fried meal
courtesy of Disco's Extra--
- Cut. Disco.
Remember,
the money is "Disco."
- Every take, they were telling
her to be energetic,
be energetic.
They should only
have to tell you one time.
- [imitating crying]
- Oh, what's happening?
- Oh, Auntie--
- Cut.
Ellie Mae, when you're
coming in, it's--
I feel like you just saw
an alien
or there's something crawling up
your bottom.
Ellie Mae, she's just all sex
and sad
but not totally freaked out.
- Sexy sad.
And you are the sexiest thing
in the world, right?
You know how to do that.
- Oh, Auntie.
I just had the worst day ever.
- Poor dumb Ellie Mae.
Who's gonna tell her that
she smells like fish?
- 'Course you like eating fish.
All the Hatfield women do.
- Cut.
Auntie, what's your character,
honey?
- She thinks
she's kind of the boss.
- Okay, then more of that.
- Okay.
- And then, Baby,
I was gonna tell you to do
a high voice but don't.
You go lower and deeper
and madder.
It's hilarious.
You're the baby
just out of prison.
I love it.
- [laughs]
- Billie Joe says
it ain't natural
to like fish
so much.
- Well, that's because
he hasn't had a taste
of Granny Hatfield's
fresh fried fish.
- Auntie, meaner and louder.
- Sonique kept falling
in and out of character.
She didn't stay in character
when the cameras were rolling.
- Do it again.
- The quickest way
to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
- Especially when I make it
with Disco
Extra-Greasy Shortening.
- Okay, take it back.
Faster, louder,
and, Granny, turn towards me.
You're really funny,
but I want to see you.
Feel it.
You are your characters.
- You should invite Billie Joe
over here
so he can get a taste
of my fish.
- With Disco, you'll get there
in no time.
[record scratches]
- Granny, did you really
just put shortening
in your crotch?
- Morgan--
she wasn't funny at all.
She was crude.
- A little less
with the crotch shots,
just 'cause
it's a family commercial.
Okay, Baby,
don't change a thing.
- He says I like eating fish.
- Poor dumb Ellie Mae.
- It is awful good.
both: And crispy too.
- Mmm-mmm!
- Great.
- Good job.
- I'm happy, and I'm confident
with what my team did,
and hopefully the judges
will see that.
- Good work, Hatfields
and McCoys.
Now, as Kathy knows,
in show business,
the last shot of the day
is called the martini shot,
and this is yours.
Please enjoy
some Absolut cocktails.
Now, dolls, you were asked
to bring your best country duds
from home, and tomorrow you'll
get the chance
to wear them
on the main stage.
We'll be joined by our
extra-special guest judge,
country legend Tanya Tucker.
- I love Tanya Tucker.
Her fashion is fierce.
- Whoo!
- The theme of tonight's
runway presentation
is country couture,
country glamour,
country realness.
- The only country I know
is my aunt,
and she's, like,
the most country-est person
in the world.
But she has so many
personalities.
So I'm like,
"I want to give
all the versions of my aunt
in one."
But this isn't country,
right?
- Depends on what kind of
country look you're going for.
- The first time that I ever
did drag in front of my friends
in high school was during
this Halloween party.
I thought I looked sexy, girl,
and then I--yeah, no.
I had, like, this afro on,
balloon boobies.
My best friend--
- You did balloon boobies too?
- I sure did.
- Girl, no, I have never done
drag in high school.
- I did drag in middle school.
- Girl, we know.
You came out the womb
putting on makeup.
- I know.
- Do you feel like a woman,
or do you feel
like a drag queen?
- A little bit of both.
I mean, when you're in drag,
don't--
you don't just feel
like a drag queen.
Sometimes you might feel
a little bit more womanly
one day.
You might feel a little bit
more fierce.
- I feel like a drag queen
when I'm in drag.
- I feel like a performer,
and that's it.
- Girl, your cheeks
are really ashy.
- What, right here?
- Yeah.
- Girl, I haven't dust yet.
- Uh, it's obvious.
You cooking?
- It's on slow roast.
Like that chicken we have.
- Best chicken, Granny.
- It's all in this can.
- She like,
"It's all in this can!"
- The reason
why I started doing drag
is because I always thought
I was cute.
I have never in my life
been told I was cute as a guy.
Never.
Mystique is pretty.
Everybody loves Mystique.
- I look around the room.
I see everybody looks like
a country diva.
And then I see
what Mystique is wearing.
She looks like she's a big girl
going out to a club.
I don't think the hat goes
with the outfit...
- Yeah, I know.
- Personally.
But you're a queen yourself,
so you choose.
Mm-mm.
[RuPaul laughing]
[applause]
- Oh, my Lord.
- Hi, everyone.
Santino, how are you, baby?
- What's that flower you got on?
- I feel like an ice-cold glass
of country-style lemonade.
[laughter]
- Pink lemonade.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
we have
Miss Tanya Tucker
in the house tonight.
- Whoo!
- Thank you so much.
- Oh, love it.
Hey, Miss Kathy.
- Hello, my darling.
- This week we asked the ladies
to put the charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
back in country
as two feuding teams
to shoot a TV commercial for
Disco Extra-Greasy Shortening.
Tonight, they come
to the main stage
decked out in their best
denim and diamond couture.
Judges, are you ready to see
what they turned out?
- Ready.
- Whoo-hoo.
- Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Sonique.
- Sonique is everything
that I feel on the inside.
When you feel good
on the inside, it shows.
- Wow.
- She's working it.
A little Tanya Tucker.
- Yeah.
- Ooh.
- The devil went down
to Georgia.
Jujubee.
- During my runway,
all I can think about is,
"Mama, you have to hit this."
- She's popping her cherry
again?
again.
Raven.
- That's so not Raven.
- I know, right?
- Yeah, the Guess girl.
- I've never seen her
so sweet-looking.
- I feel adorable.
Like a cherry
on top of a cupcake.
- The girl next door.
- Well, next door to what?
- Best little whorehouse
in Texas.
[laughter]
- Sahara.
That much leg
should be against the law.
- I'm a dancer, so of course
I'm gonna try
and incorporate that
every chance I get.
A little bootin',
a little shuffle.
- Y'all come back now, ya hear?
All right, Mommy.
- I wanted to do country,
but I wanted it to have
an urban twist.
- It's kind of like Raquel Welch
went to the country.
- Well, you know, it's hard
to keep 'em on the farm
after they've been
to RuPaul's Drag Race.
- That's hard.
- Pandora Boxx.
Cowgirl hall of fame.
- I'm feeling like my outfit
is cute and country.
- This ain't her first time at
the rodeo.
- Even cowgirls get the blues.
- Oh.
Jessica Wild.
- I feel good
because I feel sexy.
I feel that
I am in the country.
- Our little Jessica's
growing up.
She's filling out her jeans.
Her Apple Bottom jeans.
Mystique.
Star Jones before the pilates.
- My strategy in the game
is pretty much to stand out.
To be totally different
from everybody else.
So it can work in my favor.
- Yes, yes.
Uh-huh.
And do-si-do, Mama.
Morgan McMichaels.
The look of today's
country girl.
- Kind of new,
romantic country.
- I think there's just
a one-track mind
about what country is.
You don't have to be Podunk
to be country.
- Aren't they gorgeous,
those boots?
Tyra Sanchez, the other Tyra.
- I try to give the judges
another side of me every week.
- Whoo!
- Flip off that skirt!
- I'll change
at the gas station, Mama.
You won't even know.
- Wow.
Oh, yes.
Now she's Super Tyra.
I'll take one in every color.
Hello, my country queens.
Let's take a look
at the world premiere
of your Disco Extra-Greasy
Shortening commercial.
- Welcome to another
home-fried meal
courtesy of Disco
Extra-Greasy Shortening.
- Howdy, Auntie.
What's for dinner?
- It's your favorite--
Granny McCoy's
famous fried chicken.
- My secret is right in
this can.
- Ain't that Disco Extra-Greasy
Shortening?
- Sure is, Ellie Mae.
- The quickest way to a man's
heart is through his stomach.
- And with Disco
Extra-Greasy Shortening,
you'll get there in no time.
- This is so delicious.
all: And crispy too!
- Put some crispy
in your cock a "doddle" doo
with Disco
Extra-Greasy Shortening!
Whoo!
- Our commercial was hilarious.
I loved it.
- Let's take a look
at the world premiere
of your Disco Extra-Greasy
Shortening commercial.
- Welcome to another
home-fried meal courtesy
of Disco Extra-Greasy
Shortening.
- Oh, Auntie.
It's that mean
Billie Joe McAllister.
He been picking on me all day.
He says I like eating fish.
- Poor dumb Ellie Mae.
Who's gonna tell her that
she smells like fish too?
- That's because
he hasn't tried
Granny Hatfield's
fried fish fillets.
- Especially when I make it
with Disco Extra-Greasy
Shortening.
- Well, if you ask me,
it ain't just the fish
that that McAllister boy's
afraid of.
- The quickest way to a man's
heart is through his stomach.
- It is awful good.
both: And crispy too.
Mmm-mmm.
- Add some crispy
to your fried fish fillet
with Disco Extra-Greasy
Shortening.
Cock a doodle doo!
- So Hatfields, McCoys,
both of your commercials
have highlights
and lowlights.
But I do have a favorite.
And that is...
The McCoys.
Good work.
[applause]
Now this week,
we had you work as teams.
But tonight each of you
will be judged
on your individual performance.
In other words,
no one is safe.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Sonique.
Jujubee.
Morgan McMichaels.
Tatianna.
Sahara Davenport.
You girls, you are safe.
Congratulations.
You may leave the stage.
The five of you represent
the best and the worst
of the week.
Let's begin
our judges' critiques.
Let's start with Raven.
- I did think the performance
was a little
all over the map.
- It was kind of a mixed bag.
I didn't actually know
if you knew
that you were kind of playing
an animal or a chicken.
- Well, when we were practicing,
I didn't realize that
I should do it as a chicken.
- What did you think
you were gonna do it as?
- Well, do the voice
as a chicken.
- Now, Kathy,
you directed Raven in the piece.
- I directed Raven
in the piece.
PS, you look so cute.
I could put you in a smoothie
and drink you.
But I also sense
a real seriousness about you.
Honey, you have to look
around you.
This is just a bowl
full of fun soup.
Lighten up a little bit
and have a good time.
- All right, next up,
Jessica Wild.
Show us your Apple Bottom jeans.
- My Apple Bottom...
- Hey.
- Yeah, I want to mount her.
You are giving thoroughbred
realness today.
[laughter]
- What'd you think of her
as the Disco Critter?
- I thought she did a good job
with your language.
I can barely speak English,
so...
- Put some crispy
in your cock a "doddle" doo!
I love my character
because I love the Muppets,
so I feel like I am a Muppet.
- Thank you, my dear.
Pandora Boxx,
did you make this outfit,
or did you buy it?
- Um, it's bought,
but then I took the fabric
that we had for all the costumes
and added the little lady.
- Ah, crafty.
- I love your outfit.
I love what you did to it.
And it kind of--
kind of reminds me of me.
- Santino.
- Oh.
I'm not gonna be your favorite.
It almost looks like
you're in a child pageant
or something.
I'm thinking, like, you read,
like, 12 or 13,
and then I'm, like--I'm just
kind of creeped out.
- I don't think Pandora
is a fashion girl.
But what I do get all over
from Pandora is comedy.
I thought you were
the funniest person, actually.
- The quickest way
to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
- It was definitely fun to do.
It was kind of my element.
- Very funny.
Mystique Summers Madison.
Are you feeling Southern?
- I went with how my friends
back home dressed as,
since they're country.
- Well, I hear
what you're saying,
but it's not really sort of
the country look.
- I want to stand out
by going as
the normal, mall-wear country.
- [laughs]
- As the country girls--where--
where they still can have on
a nice shirt.
- Isn't this the same top
you wore in the challenge,
though?
- Yes, this is a skirt,
a one-piece skirt.
And I made it more updated
with the gauchos
and everything.
- Why the fuck
did you wear that
and try and make up
some bullshit fucking story?
- I love the way you do
your runway.
I thought your runway
was great.
- It almost seems like
you're twirling even more
because you know that your
outfit is not working today.
- When you walked out just now,
I said,
"I totally forgot
that you're not female."
I just thought, "Well, there's
that gorgeous woman."
It's a bummer about the outfit.
That's a bummer.
- Tyra Sanchez, you tore it up,
Miss Thing.
- I think
some maybe had a hard time
coming up with one outfit.
You came up with three looks
that you gave us.
The only thing
I would ask you is,
when you transform into Tyra,
why doesn't your voice change?
- Well, I can't go higher.
I can try for you.
- What's the highest note
you can hit?
- Happy birthday,
Mr. President.
- Happy birthday, Mr. President.
- That's--that's totally
believable.
- Let's talk about
your commercial.
You played the baby.
- I actually thought about
my own son.
He wakes up
in the middle of the night
out of nowhere and just like,
"Can I have some water?"
And by the time
I get the water
and bring it back to him,
he's asleep again.
- Well, all right.
Ladies, while you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Thank you.
[engine starts]
Let's talk about Mystique.
- She's got that
really pretty face.
The only problem I had
was the outfit.
- Yeah.
- So far off the mark.
- Stood out
in all the wrong ways.
- That outfit--
that was inexcusable.
- Yeah.
- And then having to explain
why...
[laughs]
Not good. Not good.
Okay, so we're gonna go on
over to Tyra.
She's a gorgeous gal.
- Yes.
- She's clearly inventive
with her presentation.
Do you think Tyra's voice
is working against her?
- I think just a little bit.
- She has a very deep voice.
- Because when you look at her,
there's nothing--
I can't see anything wrong.
- Yeah.
Let's talk about Raven.
Didn't do so well
in the commercial.
- I missed the funny.
Obviously
you're in a chicken suit.
That's the first clue
to be funny.
- Raven looked so beautiful
on the runway,
but I thought,
as the Disco Critter,
Jessica did a better job
than Raven did.
- Yes.
Jessica Wild
is from Puerto Rico,
doesn't speak the language
very well,
and she seemed to master
the Disco Critter very well.
- She just went wild.
- I find her really charming
and a great, spicy addition
to this lineup.
- Yes.
- But is she America's
next drag superstar?
That's the question
we have to ask.
- I don't know.
- Pandora Boxx.
Santino had an issue...
- Hate, hate.
- With Pandora Boxx's outfit.
- It's just very just,
uh, pedestrian.
- She is a fantastic comedienne.
- My favorite to work with.
She's got--she's got
some comedy going.
- Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back the girls.
Ladies, welcome back.
Pandora, if you want to win
this race,
you need to step up your style.
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Mystique, you were slow
to make adjustments on set
during the commercial.
When we asked you to give us
your best country couture,
you came up empty-handed.
I'm sorry.
You're up for elimination.
- I knew this was probably
gonna happen this way.
They didn't see me as
their version
of country realness.
You can't please everybody.
- Jessica.
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Raven.
I see flashes of star power
in you.
But as quickly as it comes,
it fades away.
Do you have the consistency
to be the next
drag superstar?
I'm sorry, but you're up for
elimination.
- So once again
I'm in the bottom two.
Honestly, I don't feel like
I belong in the bottom two
with Mystique.
- Tyra Sanchez,
your runway was a hit.
And your Baby Girl
made me laugh out loud.
Congratulations.
You're the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
Which means you have immunity
next week.
Plus you'll receive a collection
of designer bags,
handmade in Italian leather,
from M. Clifford Designs.
Congratulations, Tyra.
You may join the other girls.
- This is the first challenge
that I won,
and I feel great.
I feel amazing.
Because last week they were
making me out
to be a bitch of the group.
And I'm not a bitch.
I'm America's sweetheart.
- Two queens stand before me.
I've consulted with the judges.
But the final decision
is mine to make.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
for you
to lip synch for your life.
Good luck, and remember...
Don't fuck it up.
[country rock music]
-  You went away
and left me long ago
And now you're knocking
on my door
I hear you knocking
- Lip synch area is my stage.
That's my battleground.
And I'm gonna go balls
to the wall.
- I was gonna duke it out.
I don't care
if the wig flew off.
I don't care if I broke a heel.
At that point,
it was do or die,
'cause I was not gonna go home
up against Mystique.
-  Telling me
All your lies
I hear you knocking
But you can't come in
Go back where you've been
[applause]
- Whoo!
- Mystique...
Raven...
I've made my decision.
Raven, you've been
down this road twice.
But you keep pulling through.
And it's that kind of resilience
it takes to win this race.
Shante.
You stay.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
If I was told to sashay away
and Mystique is still standing
up there,
I would have
fucking slit my wrists.
- Mystique Summers Madison,
I want you to believe
in yourself, because I do.
Now sashay away.
[laughter]
- Got it, girl.
Good job.
- I'm not gonna change
who I am
to win a competition.
I'm gonna be Mystique.
Take me as I am
or nothing at all.
So I'm going home
with my head held up high.
- Dolls, like every good
country song,
we will live through
this heartache.
Mystique is gone,
but we will carry on
in the tradition
of all great country queens.
Now remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen.
- Let the music play!
[dance music]