- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
- I'm getting married, y'all.
- Aw!
- This bitch, she was trying
to annoy everyone around her.
- Ugh!
- Just get yourself some manners
so you won't look
so damn stupid.
- [chuckles]
- Shut the fuck up,
or I'll make you shut up.
- Oh!
- We are all in this together.
Tyra Sanchez, congratulations.
You're the winner
of this challenge.
- Sahara Davenport...
shante, you stay.
- Yes.
- Morgan McMichaels,
sashay away.
[applause]
And tonight...
- Ooh, girl!
[laughs]
- Rock on!
A Drag Race first.
- I'm gonna shit myself
on stage.
- Yeah, fuck it!
This is great!
- And it ain't gonna be pretty.
- [shrieking]
- With special guest judges
Terri Nunn and Henry Rollins.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics
and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com,
an exclusive
one-year PR contract
with the leading LGBT firm
Project Publicity,
be featured in L.A. Eyeworks'
legendary designer eyewear
campaign,
and headline
Logo's drag race tour
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks,
and a cash prize of $25,000.
And may the best woman win.
[electronic pop music]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ Ru-Ru-RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman,
best woman win ♪
[alarm clock buzzing]
- Whoo!
One less, girl.
- Wow.
- Oh, Morgan.
- ♪ All you have to do
is dream ♪
- Why did she use
two different reds?
- Because she's deep.
She's colorful and deep.
And her lipstick ran out.
[laughter]
I love you, Morgan.
It sucks that Morgan's gone,
but I feel now that my chances
of being in the bottom two
are a lot less.
While she was here,
I was being too focused
on not only me but her too.
I'm gonna do
what I got to do now.
- I'm still a little shaken
after yesterday's elimination
and being in the bottom two.
I'm nervous.
I don't want to be
in the bottom two again.
- My new nickname.
You want happy ending, honey?
- Not particularly.
[laughter]
- After everything that happened
last night, I feel great.
I don't hold grudges
against anyone,
but I can tell that Tatianna is
sort of holding a grudge.
- Ow!
I don't have any regrets
calling Tyra out.
I hope she took
from the situation
something to work on
in the future,
but that's her deal, not mine.
- Y'all, I was tucked
so fiercely the other day,
I had a blister on you-know-what
and I thought I had an STD.
[laughter]
- Ooh, girl!
You got she-mail.
You want to be
the next drag superstar?
Well, first you better take
a little piece of my heart.
Then you better hit me
with your best shot.
And finally you need
to sing a song
just like a white-winged dove.
So what are you waiting for?
It's time to put another dime
in the jukebox, baby.
Yeah.
- Rock and roll.
They're all titles
of rock and roll songs.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Maybe we have to make
a rock and roll costume?
- That's okay.
- Or maybe we have to be
a rock band with all of us.
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi!
- Oh, what do we have there?
- Oh, wow.
- A great drag queen
is like a rock star.
She pushes it to the limit.
But the one thing that remains
her crowning glory is her hair.
For today's mini challenge,
you'll be styling these wigs,
provided by Wig Pro Collections,
into the biggest, baddest
rocker chick hair
this side of Tina Turner.
You'll have 30 minutes
to turn your wig
into a glam rock piece of art.
And the one who really pumps up
the volume will win.
Your challenge...
starts now!
- Ah!
- Y'all some shady bitches.
So shit.
- It's like vultures
fighting over a dead animal
in the middle of the desert.
- Jeez.
- 30 minutes
is not a lot of time
to put in
a really good hairstyle,
so I'm a little worried.
- Where's my teasing comb?
Where's my teasing comb?
I want to win this challenge.
I haven't won anything.
Everybody else has.
- I have no idea what I'm doing
with this hair.
I don't know how to style hair.
I'm not a hair stylist.
So I'm like,
"Shit, what do I do?"
- I'm thinking in my head,
"Think outside the box.
Pandora, think outside the box."
- I look over and I see Pandora
doing hers, and I'm like,
"It looks like Cindy Lou Who
from a Dr. Seuss book."
I'm like,
"What the hell is she doing?"
- All right, ladies.
Time's up.
That's right.
Rocker chicks,
turn your blow dryers off
and put those rat combs down.
All right,
let's start with Tyra.
Sit it right here.
- Anytime I see a video,
I always see 'em with, like,
a mohawk
and it's just, like, real poofy
and, like, puffed out.
I am happy
with how my hair looked.
It kind of reminded me
of Sasha Fierce.
All the other wigs
were a little trashy.
- My inspiration
was a little Joan Jett
but a little Pat Benatar.
- This is actually a nice cut,
but she's kind of
a conservative rocker chick.
It's more sort of a rocker mom.
Wow.
- She just finished a show with
her band, Thundercunt.
And afterwards,
there was a hotel party
and she got completely trashed.
- You might want to get her
into rehab.
- I don't know much
about rock and roll,
but I do enjoy the music
of Pat Benatar.
So I know her hair is short
and kind of powerful,
so I went--chose to go with,
like, a asymmetrical bob
and a little crimping.
- I'm wondering why
you didn't crimp more.
- Well, she's subtle.
- She's a subtle rocker chick.
- Yeah.
- This is Mustang Sally.
- Oh, is this her?
- This is her.
- I've heard of her.
- Yes.
- Pandora's hairstyle
was a mess.
It was like three Halloween
jack-o'-lanterns
stacked on top of each other.
- She has a guitar on her head.
The strings are right here.
- Oh, she sure does.
- Yes, and if you're lucky,
maybe she'll let you play
her head.
- It's like RuPaul does
Cyndi Lauper, doesn't it?
- My inspiration
is the cartoon from the '80s
Jem and the Holograms.
- Oh, yes,
Jem and the Holograms, yeah.
- The rock band.
You can use tomorrow this.
- I will definitely consider
using that tomorrow.
- Thanks.
- It's always good
to have a backup.
All right, Jujubee.
She's got so much going on here.
- This is kind of like
the end of the week for her,
and she's getting ready
to go shopping for deli meats,
and she decided
to just put everything on.
- So girl to girl...
- Yeah?
- When did you lose control
of this wig?
- When I got the wig.
- [laughs]
Ladies, you all rocked
this challenge,
but there can only be
one winner, and that queen is...
Pandora Boxx.
Congratulations, Pandora.
You'll find out what you've won
in a moment.
For your main challenge,
you're going
to transform yourselves
into hot rocker chicks.
You can use your own drag,
plus materials provided
by Leg Avenue
and Michael Levine Fabrics.
I expect you to take
your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
and amp it up to 11.
But wait.
♪ There's more ♪
For this week's challenge, I'm
going to ask you to do something
that I've never asked any of
my girls to do before.
For the first time ever
on RuPaul's Drag Race,
each of you will be singing live
to a heavy metal version
of my song Ladyboy.
- My heart kind of just dropped.
I just don't want to do it.
- To help you prepare
for your singing debut,
you'll be working with one of
my favorite rocker chicks,
whose monster hits include
No More Words
and Take My Breath Away.
Their latest CD is called
All The Way In.
I'm talking about the amazing
Terri Nunn from Berlin.
- I can't believe Terri Nunn's
gonna be coaching.
I can't believe
we're gonna meet Terri Nunn.
Terri fucking Nunn is here.
- Now, Pandora, since you won
the mini challenge,
you get an extra ten minutes
with Terri.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
Rock on!
- ♪ Hit me up ♪
♪ I'm that chick, you know
that my world won't stop ♪
♪ If you clock me ♪
- Jessica, have you sung live
before?
- Yeah, I sing before
with the rock band Rebeldia.
I want to be a singer,
a drag singer.
If I don't win this challenge,
then what challenge
I'm going to win?
- Girl, I'm in the same boat
as you.
This is the perfect challenge
for me,
because I've heard every other
bitch in that room sing.
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- Ooh, girl!
[laughs]
I can hold a note.
- ♪ This groove is for
my girls ♪
- I have such a big fear of
singing live for an audience.
And I'm really not excited
about it.
I'm gonna shit myself
on stage.
- That's rock.
- The main challenge today
is to make our own
rock and roll outfits.
And we will be performing
RuPaul's Ladyboy live.
- I am so excited.
- I'm nervous.
I'm so glad I have immunity.
- Do you know how to sing?
- The other day,
that was my real singing.
♪ Oh, ooh ♪
I hope the judges don't tell me
to shut the fuck up.
- Does anybody have a pen?
Do you have a pen?
I need to rewrite the lyrics
so that it fits the tempo
that they sing it in,
'cause I can't visualize it
in my head.
This is the challenge
that I'm excited about.
I'm, like, 100% sure
that I'm gonna do fabulously.
I'm very confident about this.
I'm not gonna fuck up.
- Hey, my little runaways.
- Hey, Ru.
- Just checking in.
Looks like the rock shop.
Tyra, tell me about your outfit.
- Because I don't know
too much about rock,
I'm gonna try and go for
a more futuristic rock.
- Have you seen
Tina Turner's videos
or seen her on television?
- The only time
I saw Tina perform
is when she performed
with Beyonce.
- Why did I know
that was the answer?
All right, Tyra,
keep on working.
- Thank you.
- I'm gonna ease on over here
to Miss Raven, who--
something tells me
there is a rocker chick
who lives constantly in you.
- Yes.
- Now, earlier in the run,
you said you don't sing at all.
- No.
- So how are--you feel confident
about doing this challenge?
- Yeah, I do, actually.
Like, I think that when it comes
to rock and roll,
it's about your stage presence.
That's such a good way to say,
"Fuck it."
- That's what rock and roll
is about.
Who do you think is your biggest
competition in this challenge?
- Jujubee.
- Why?
- Jujubee can sing.
She can sing,
and she can sing well.
- Maybe this challenge
is your opportunity
to really step it up.
- Well, I plan on it.
- Rock on.
I'll see you later.
All right.
- Bye.
- Jessica Wild.
- Hi, Ru.
- Look at you.
Are you ready for rock and roll?
- Yeah.
- Do you sing?
- I am not the best singer
of the world.
But I have the personality,
I have the energies,
and I have attitude.
- Yeah. Is this your
rocker chick hair right here?
- Yes, I am going to work
on that wig.
- Because Jessica Wild has
a signature movement,
and it's a hair flip?
- Yes.
- [laughs]
Okay.
Keep working.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Hey, Sahara.
Do you sing at all?
- I do sing,
but I've never done rock before.
- Now, you wound up
in the bottom two twice.
- Girl, don't remind me.
[laughs]
- What are you gonna do
this week to make sure
you don't find yourself
in the bottom two?
- I guess just overcoming myself
and being confident
and letting it out
and not hesitating
or holding back.
My confidence has been an issue
for a lot of my adult life,
and I guess it may be I'm afraid
of disappointing people.
- You ready to rock out?
- I'm ready.
Is that right?
[laughs]
- Tatianna, do you sing at all?
- I used to be in chorus,
but I would even lip-sync that,
'cause there would be
a group of us.
- Really?
- So I just mouthed the words.
- You were lip-synching for your
life in high school chorus?
- Yep, or I'd sing really soft.
- Why?
- Because I was really
made fun of a lot in school,
and so I really thought twice
about everything I did.
I started getting teased
for being gay
when I was in first grade.
I can't count
the amount of times
I was suspended for fighting.
- This is what I do.
And that voice that you're
talking about that says,
"You can't do that,"
that voice will always be there.
Look at me in the eye.
That voice will always be there.
What you have to do--
like muscles,
you have to counteract
that voice with another voice
that says,
"Thank you for sharing.
That was nice, but I'm gonna
do this over here."
This is your opportunity
to put this to the test.
So I want to see you go for it.
- Absolutely.
- All right, Tatianna.
- Thank you.
- Keep working.
- All right.
I think RuPaul
is really looking at me
and wanting to see that I don't
just fall back on my looks.
It definitely makes me want
to make him proud.
- Pandora.
Wow.
Lookit here.
Ooh, that's gonna move
really good.
Have I seen you do this before?
- I don't think
I have done that.
- Do it with me now.
Ow!
- Put it on me, Mister.
- ♪ Put it on me, mister ♪
- Whoo!
[laughter]
- I slipped into Cher.
I don't know how.
- Now, throughout
the competition,
we've actually asked Pandora
to push it more.
- I definitely agree, 'cause
I'm not really a singer either,
so I'm really gonna have to go
out of my box,
which was what I was told
in the last challenge,
to think outside the box.
This is very beyond it, so...
- Yeah.
All right, good luck, Pandora.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Jujubee.
- Hi, mama.
- Hi, baby.
- What's going on?
- When I've spoken
with the other girls,
their main concern is you.
- Why?
- Because they say you can sing.
Now, tell me about that.
- I can hold a note.
- What's surprising to me
is that you have not won
a challenge yet.
- I haven't,
and I want to win this one.
- How are you gonna do that?
How you gonna win
this challenge?
- I know that Ru's there
to challenge me,
and it reminded me
of how my father pushed me.
- This is definitely a chance
for you to come out of the
shadow of the other girls.
- My father died when I was 15,
and because he believed in me,
I believe in myself.
I know that's the reason
I perform.
I'm gonna do it.
And I'm gonna make you happy.
I promise, girl.
[squeaks]
- Thank you, Jujubee.
- Thank you, mama.
This is the time
for me to shine,
and I'm gonna knock
everybody's socks off.
- Okay, ladies, in a moment,
you'll get your chance
to work with Terri Nunn.
And tomorrow,
in addition to Terri Nunn,
we'll be joined
on the main stage
by our extra special
guest judge,
the always sexy and outspoken
rocker Henry Rollins.
[cheers and applause]
Yes.
- He's so, um...
manly.
- He's got these huge hands.
I used to have the biggest crush
on him.
- All right, ladies, good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
All right.
- Bye, Ru!
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Terri Nunn is our coach.
She's the lead singer of Berlin.
- I'm Terri.
What's your name?
- I'm Juju.
- Hi, Juju.
- Very nice to meet you.
You're gorgeous.
- Thank you.
So are you.
- It's insane,
and I'm like, "Wow."
- Cool.
Well, let's see the song.
- Okay, let's do it.
Let's do it.
[RuPaul's Ladyboy plays]
- ♪ This groove is for
my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ This groove is for
my ladyboy ♪
♪ Ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ Hit me up, I'm that chick
with some-- ♪
Ooh, girl.
- Just go!
Just have fun!
- ♪ Ooh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Ladyboy ♪
- All right.
You got the voice.
Your voice is there.
What's important is,
you need to get these words.
How do you relate to that song?
- It's like me and my girls,
we're going out.
We're gonna rock out, and we're
gonna have a lot of fun.
- 'Cause when you're with
your girls,
you're just like,
"Yeah, fuck it!
This is great!"
You know, you're not thinking;
you're just into it.
- This is probably
the first time in my life
where I'm, like, 100% sure
that I'm gonna do fabulously.
Unless I break my leg tonight,
I'm gonna be fierce.
♪ Oh ♪
- Whoo!
- I'm nervous.
- That's okay.
- I can't sing.
- It's okay.
You don't have to be
a great singer.
Just get the feeling across.
- ♪ Take you out ♪
♪ Got chick you know ♪
♪ And the world won't stop
if you clock me ♪
♪ You got me ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- Tyra is very uncomfortable
in this situation
and didn't seem to be able
to get out of that
to just let herself go.
- ♪ Move my feet
'cause the beat-- ♪
- Okay.
Okay.
This is a performance.
We're not in a recording studio.
I mean, it's not just about
the mic and doing the song.
You're performing.
People are watching you,
and you're here,
so there's got to be
some connection.
Hi.
- Hi.
It is such a pleasure
to meet you. I'm Raven.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're gorgeous.
- Thank you.
So are you.
- I'm a huge fan.
- Well, thank you very much.
Yeah, he's, uh--
I'm kind of just a little bit--
he's kind of cute.
[laughs]
- I want to apologize
ahead of time,
'cause I'm not a singer.
- That's okay.
- At all. That's why I lip-sync.
- Well, you don't have to sing
perfectly.
You just have to feel it
and make us feel it.
- You'll feel it, baby.
- Yeah!
All right!
- ♪ One more shot ♪
♪ Got another boogie in me ♪
♪ Move my feet ♪
♪ 'Cause the beat
don't intimidate me ♪
♪ If you want to dance ♪
♪ I'm the girl
with something extra ♪
♪ If you want to dance,
better put it on me, mister ♪
- Oh!
Whoo-hoo!
Very good!
- She loved me.
- I wish you were straight.
You're really cute.
[laughs]
Tomorrow I'm gonna be up there.
I'm gonna be judging your ass.
- I know.
I'll have it hanging out
for you then.
- [laughs]
Just for you, I'm gonna let it
hang out tomorrow.
- I'm in.
- Thank you.
It was so good to meet you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you.
- Great job.
- Thank you. Bye.
Bitch.
- Did you love her?
- No, she loved me.
- Oh, really?
- She was like, "You are so hot,
I wish you were not gay."
- Aw!
- Basically,
I blew her out of her seat.
- Well, all right.
Well, all righty, then.
- ♪ This groove is for
my girls ♪
♪ Little lady boys and girls ♪
♪ This groove is for
my ladyboys ♪
♪ The ladyboys and girls ♪
- He's got a presence.
He's got the communication.
- ♪ Hit me up,
I'm that chick ♪
♪ You know
♪ that my world won't stop ♪
♪ If you clock me ♪
♪ You got me ♪
- Yeah!
- ♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ You got me going ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
I am nervous.
Maybe my voice is not the best.
But the rock and roll is
attitude, and I have that.
Jessica Wild have that.
- ♪ Hit me up,
I'm that chick ♪
♪ You know that my world
won't stop ♪
♪ If you clock me,
you got me ♪
I know I'm not gonna be the
best singer in this challenge,
but I don't think
that's what it's about.
I think it's about going for
that rock star attitude.
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- I don't know if Pandora
can work on his voice.
That's his biggest weakness.
But I think
his confidence level
will overshadow the fact
that he's not really a singer.
[laughs]
[RuPaul's Ladyboy plays]
- I'm nervous, 'cause I'm
definitely not a rocker.
I've done some musical theater.
♪ Oh oh oh oh ow! ♪
♪ This groove is for my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
- I love your softness.
I love your vulnerability.
You've got a good voice.
Right now,
it feels a little like
you don't really know the song
and you're just trying
to get through it.
So just forget about just trying
Just go
with what you're feeling,
even if you mess up the words.
Whatever it feels like
in your body, make it yours.
♪ This groove is for my girls,
little-- ♪
Am I singing with a track?
Are there words with this part?
- Yeah, that's where
you start to sing.
- The moment that I step
on the stage
to work with Terri, I just have
this sinking feeling.
♪ Hit me up,
I'm that chick ♪
I can't, no.
- No?
- Mm-mm.
- Okay.
- This ain't working.
- So what happened?
- I just--I'm not comfortable
at all.
- You're not feeling it?
He's in his head.
He needs to get out of his head.
Go sit there.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- I'll do that.
- Now I'm gonna do
what you just did.
♪ Sitting on a secret ♪
♪ And everybody's in on it ♪
♪ Some girls talk to the boys ♪
♪ In the chat room ♪
I'm just up here,
hoping it's over.
- That's what I'm feeling too.
- I think Tatianna's decided
that she can't sing,
so she's giving up
before she even walks out here.
I just feel
you don't want to be here.
- How was it?
- Don't even ask.
- What did she say?
- It was terrible.
I couldn't even get through it.
- Why?
- I--it's just--I don't know.
- There's two verses
and three choruses.
So learn two verses,
learn a chorus three times,
get over it.
- Maybe tomorrow
when I'm in the whole drag,
it'll come to me
a little bit better.
- I think Tatianna
definitely knows
she's the weakest one here.
- Maybe tomorrow
I can turn it out.
- [rolls tongue]
- Let's rock and roll, bitches.
- How's everyone's nerves?
- I'm nervous.
- They're like, "Just let go."
It's hard to just let go.
They should have had us
bungee jump
before this challenge.
- Isn't it, like,
you'd much rather skydive
than sing live
in front of people?
- And get judged for it?
- They're like,
"Your skydive was horrible."
- Rock and roll, to me,
is just about having
that sense of abandonment
and just going for it
and just rocking out.
That's so the opposite end
of who I am,
because I'm afraid to be messy.
I mean, you guys know me.
I'm not like--
- Rah!
- Right.
I have been messy, and those
were very dark times for me.
The people who I loved
weren't loving me,
and I found solace and comfort
in something else.
When I first came out, there was
some tension between my mother.
I was getting the love
that I needed
from designer drugs
like special K.
I know I'm thankful
for my drag mother
for pulling me aside
and being like,
"Okay, you've become a monster."
- Like, "Calm down."
- "You are doing too much.
This is not who you are."
And it took realizing
that I was in the mess
and that demons can take you
somewhere,
but you don't have to stay
there.
You can come up out
and just move forward.
It's that strength
that got me here.
- Always when I'm going to do
a show, something happen.
- Oh, the zipper's broken.
- When I put my clothes,
boom.
Damn!
My corset explode.
- Hot-glue it.
- Boom, boom, boom, yeah.
- Turn.
- It's open in the back too.
Jessica Wild,
always something happen.
- The closer it gets
to being my turn,
the more
I just don't want to do it.
[laughs]
It's really freaking me out.
[singing scales]
- Everybody thinks
that I'm the one
that's going
to get this challenge,
and I feel great about it,
but if I don't do as great
as they think I am,
it's gonna be an issue.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Hey, Santino.
How you doing?
- Hey, Ru.
It's great to be here again.
- I'm so happy you're here.
Merle, darling,
you look very rock and roll.
- Thank you.
- Henry.
- Hey, Ru. How are you?
- Are you ready to take a walk
on the wild side?
- As wild as you'll let me be.
- I'll let you be real wild.
[laughter]
Terri.
- Hi.
You look fantastic.
- Thank you.
You look amazing.
Now, this week,
we asked our ladies
to transform themselves
into hot rocker chicks...
- Yeah.
- And, in a Drag Race first,
sing live on the main stage.
Hey, judges, are you ready
to rock and roll?
- Yeah!
- Okay.
- We were born ready, baby.
- Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul's Ladyboy plays]
- Oh, yeah.
♪ ♪
Oh, yeah.
- ♪ This groove is for
my girls ♪
♪ Little lady boys and girls ♪
♪ This groove is for
my ladyboys ♪
♪ The lady boys and girls ♪
♪ One more shot ♪
♪ I got another boogie in me ♪
♪ Gotta move my feet ♪
♪ 'Cause the beat
don't intimidate me ♪
♪ If you want to dance ♪
♪ I'm a girl
with something extra ♪
[cheers and laughter]
I love to perform
in front of people.
[cheering]
- This is a headbanger's ball.
- ♪ Uno, dos, tres, cuatro ♪
♪ ♪
[cheering]
- Yeah!
- ♪ This groove is for
my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ This groove is
for my ladyboys ♪
♪ The lady boys and girls ♪
♪ Little lady, ladyboys ♪
♪ Little ladyboy girls ♪
This is a huge fear for me.
I know I am not the best singer,
but I don't think
it's about that.
I think
it's about rock and roll.
- Oh, yeah!
- I hope you like a ladyboy.
- Yeah!
- Put your hands together.
- You do not want
to go home alone.
Put your hands together.
[cheers and applause]
Everybody.
Scream!
[people cheering]
- ♪ Ladyboyyyyyyyy!
Ow! ♪
♪ This groove is for my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ This groove is for my lady ♪
I am definitely channeling
my inner rock goddess,
but I'm a little nervous,
and I fumbled
through some of the words.
♪ Some girls talk ♪
♪ Like them girls
just like I'm running with ♪
♪ Sitting on a secret ♪
♪ And everybody's in on it ♪
- ♪ Ladyboy, ladyboy ♪
- Ow!
- ♪ This groove is for
my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
It felt good to sing in front
of an audience,
which is odd,
because I was freaking out
about it so much.
♪ T-a-t-i ♪
Let me hear you say...
- Y'all ready to rock and roll?
[cheering]
- ♪ Lady ladyboy ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ One more shot ♪
♪ I got another boogie in me ♪
♪ Got to move my feet ♪
♪ 'Cause the beat
don't intimidate me ♪
♪ If you want to dance ♪
♪ I'm the girl
with something extra ♪
[cheering]
I'm feeling, like,
the rocker energy,
like, just the fun, carefree,
fuck-you energy.
You know what, Danny Bonaduce?
You know what, Eddie Murphy?
[cheers and laughter]
You cannot have this ladygirl,
honey.
You cannot afford this ladygirl,
You better work.
- ♪ This groove is for
my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ This groove is for
my ladyboys ♪
♪ The ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ Little lady ladyboy ♪
♪ Lady ladyboys and girls ♪
[muttering]
♪ Move my feet ♪
I enjoy the energy
from the crowd.
I was giving my version of rock,
and I thought that I did great.
♪ This groove is for my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ This groove is for my lady ♪
♪ Little lady ladyboy ♪
♪ Lady ladyboys and girls ♪
[cheering]
- RuPaul: ♪ This groove is for
my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
- ♪ This groove is
for my girls ♪
♪ Little ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ This groove is for my girls ♪
♪ This groove is for my girl ♪
♪ ♪
Right before I get on stage,
I feel wonderful.
And then bam,
I get on stage.
I freeze.
♪ Nobody rocks ♪
♪ Like girls I'm running with ♪
♪ Everybody says ♪
♪ Like everybody's in on it ♪
I am screwing up RuPaul's song
right in front of her face,
and it sucks.
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ Ladyboys ♪
- Ladies, that was
the best concert I have been to
in a long time.
It's time to hear
what our judges think.
Let's start with Jessica Wild.
- Jessica, you're a rock star.
You were into it right away.
You knew the words.
Your outfit's amazing.
- Jessica Wild.
- Yes.
- You killed it.
If there was some critique,
the hair, it's a little wiggy.
- You used your hair as a
weapon, which I quite liked.
And also I truly believe that
you connected with the music,
so I thought you were fantastic.
- Thank you.
- Great.
Okay, Jujubee, you're next.
All the girls said
you were the one to watch
because you could sing.
I was surprised that you...
didn't know the words
to the song.
- It's a pretty simple song,
and I didn't learn it,
and I can't take it back.
I feel like a failure.
- Terri, what'd you think
of Jujubee's performance?
- I have to say, you did
need to know the words,
'cause the words for us singers
are the lines.
We got to know our lines,
and there's no excuse for that.
People come and pay money.
- Oh, Jujubee, today you were
off your game.
When you first came out,
I saw your lips moving,
but I couldn't even hear you.
Like, you almost were afraid
to hear your own voice.
- It occurred to me
during your performance
that the music seemed to be
more like incidental soundtrack.
You went in and out
of connecting with the lyric.
- I think everyone is just
a little disappointed.
- I am so devastated,
because not only
did I let the judges down;
I believe my father was there
watching me,
and I let him down.
- Next up, Pandora Boxx.
- You brought it.
You were a punk rocker
out there.
- Thank you.
- Pandora, I think
your outfit looks great.
It wasn't the best performance,
but I could tell that you
put in a lot of effort.
- I liked the aggressive
punk rock energy you brought,
although, for me,
there was moments
where you kind of got
a little happy,
where you started kind of
hopping around like, "Yay!"
I'm like, "No, no!"
When you're gonna go out
with some attitude,
just remember to stay with it.
- Rock on, bitches.
[laughter]
- Thank you.
- All right, next up,
Sahara Davenport.
Were some of the lyrics
a problem for you?
- Um, no, it was more breathing
and trying to focus
but not be so focused.
- I knew you were nervous.
I knew you were worried
about your voice.
I was like, "Oh, god," you know?
"Maybe she still hasn't
gotten over
being a little afraid of this."
You didn't know the words,
and that is important,
because people notice that.
You know, it's important
to them
that you care about the song,
because usually they're coming
'cause they care
about those songs too.
- You are very elegant
in that dancer, chic,
refined essence.
- But is that rocker chick?
- Well,
that's what I'm wondering.
I know it's probably hard
for you to let go,
because you do have
all that dance--
- Girl, I just did it.
I just let go, baby.
I mean, I don't know what else
you want from me, Merle.
I'm just a girly girl.
- Maybe I just wanted it
a little rougher.
- All right, next up, Tatianna.
- First, you were the biggest
improvement of everybody.
When we finished working
together yesterday,
I was scared for you,
because you were scared.
And you came in,
and you knew the words.
You brought it, and I know
how hard that was for you.
- Being Joey, I felt naked.
But as Tati, I feel like
I can do anything.
- T-a-t-i.
B-o-d-y.
Body, body, body, body.
You're still riding on
this body, and it's amazing.
I just wish you could bring
another element
to this overall look.
Bring it up to rock star level.
- Up next, Rockin' Raven.
Turn around; let's see
what you're working with.
- Oh, my god.
- Rock and roll, baby.
- Raven,
you come out with the ass.
Now I want girls.
You're hot as a girl.
- I've turned you
into a lesbian?
- I'm in.
- Yes!
- Remember at the beginning
of the season,
we were kind of giving you
a hard time about you're cold,
you have too much attitude?
Tonight you took that attitude
and you lit a match under it.
So it was like sneery,
"I'm better than you,"
but it was so perfect
for rock and roll.
- I enjoyed your performance,
because it seemed very much
in the moment.
You sold me completely.
- Thank you.
- Tyra Sanchez,
the other Tyra.
- Instead of doing
kind of hardcore rock,
which everybody else did,
you did glamour.
I think it worked against you.
I felt like you were
more concerned with your look
than your performance.
- I thought the performance was
dominated by your clothing.
It seemed to keep you from
connecting with the music.
I don't think you brought
the rock to it.
- Thank you, for everyone,
for your critiques.
- Thank you.
Ladies, while you're enjoying
an Absolut cocktail
in the interior illusions
lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Thank you, ladies.
This is not gonna be easy.
- No.
- So let's start
with Jessica Wild.
- I thought she was fantastic.
It was ever changing,
yet she kept me with her
the entire time.
- Today I know
why she's still here.
- It was her conviction,
wasn't it?
- Yeah.
- Now, Pandora,
she did a great job too.
- She was unique in all of them,
because she just had a different
attitude than everybody else,
and it made her stand out.
- She came out, and she was
flipping us off and everything.
That, to me,
was a complete turn-on.
- She performed in a way
that I'd never thought, really,
Pandora could perform.
- Now, Sahara Davenport,
I saw her trying really hard,
but I wasn't convinced.
- I felt like she was playing
at being a rock star,
that she had, you know,
read a book about it
and so she was trying out
the moves.
I wasn't feeling
that she was really into it.
- There were great moments
where she lost her considerable
restraint and let loose,
but it wasn't consistent.
- Now Tatianna.
- I loved her look.
I loved that she tried for
something completely different.
You know, everybody thinks
rock is big hair,
and to me, it's about being
an original.
- It just kind of falls
in the middle for me.
I do wish that, you know,
with her youth
and beauty and body,
she would step it up
a little bit more.
- Now, I was very impressed
with Raven.
- Her look is just--
it's really intense.
I like that kind
of confrontation
that isn't necessarily violent
but it does make you deal,
'cause rock and roll
is about confrontation.
- Raven's guts
always win the day.
I thought it was extremely nervy
that she came out
with Terri Nunn hair
in front of Terri Nunn.
- For me, there were
two rock stars in this group,
and they were Jessica and Raven.
She just has that.
- Tyra.
- Tyra has immunity this week,
and if she didn't,
she would be lip-synching
for her life.
- She just kind of did, like,
a weak Beyonce imitation.
- And her twirling around was--
what are you doing, lady?
I don't care
if you don't like rock music.
Your job was to convince me that
you were rocking,
and she wasn't.
- The girl who shocked us all
was Jujubee.
- I had really big expectations
for her.
She's great.
We've all been wanting her
to win a challenge.
I thought
she could win this one.
- I did too.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I thought that Jujubee
was gonna do really well.
When I saw her walk out here,
it's like watching someone
do karaoke really badly.
- And then she didn't know
the words, and, I mean,
that just comes across
as a performer who doesn't care.
- All right.
Silence!
I've made my decision.
Let's bring the girls back
to the main stage.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your rocker chick
challenge,
I've made some decisions.
Tyra Sanchez, fortunately,
you won immunity last week.
So you're safe tonight.
Thank you, Tyra.
Jessica Wild.
Pandora Boxx.
Raven.
As rocker chicks, you ruled.
But one of you
took this challenge
and turned it into
a rock and roll fantasy.
Jessica Wild...
congratulations.
You're the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
- I am disappointed, because
I haven't won any challenges,
but I've been close
to winning each time.
- You have won
a $1,000 shopping spree.
But Jessica?
You have not won immunity
for next week.
Ladies, moving forward,
there will be no more immunity.
From here on in,
every moment counts.
- Of course I feel a little mad.
I win now,
and I don't have immunity.
- Being told that there's
no more immunity left sucks.
That's just going to show you,
"Look, bitches,
it's getting serious."
- Thank you, Jessica.
- Thank you.
Gracias.
Thanks.
[applause]
- Thank you.
- Pandora Boxx, you are the
Susan Lucci of this competition.
- I am.
[laughter]
- But you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Rockin' Raven, your star
continues to rise...
and you're safe.
- Thank you.
Jujubee,
coming into this challenge,
you were the one to beat.
But you proved to be
your own worst enemy.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- Ru is very disappointed in me.
I let her down,
and I let myself down.
- Tatianna, you were lost.
But once again, you channeled
your inner Britney.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Sahara Davenport.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- You know,
before when I was in the bottom,
I was freaking out.
Like I've said
and I'll say it again,
I came here to win,
and I'm not a quitter.
I'm not gonna cry.
I'm gonna fight it out.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourselves
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-sync...
for your life.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[Alannah Myles' Black Velvet]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Mississippi ♪
♪ In the middle
of a dry spell ♪
- This is my moment.
This is my last chance
to show Ru and the other judges
that I deserve to be here.
- ♪ The way he moved ♪
- I love Juju,
but I'm ready to take her down.
I want to be
one of the last ones standing,
and I'll do everything
to ensure that I am.
- ♪ He'd leave you
longing for ♪
♪ Black velvet ♪
♪ and that little boy's smile ♪
- Right away, you see Sahara
going into pirouettes,
and, girl,
that's not what this song is.
- ♪ A new religion
that'll bring you... ♪
- Sahara's kind of doing
the dancer thing
that she did
in the last elimination,
and I just feel like Jujubee
is really capturing
the essence of the song.
- ♪ Black velvet ♪
♪ And that little boy's smile ♪
♪ Black velvet ♪
♪ And that slow
Southern style ♪
♪ A new religion ♪
♪ That'll bring you
to your knees ♪
♪ Black velvet ♪
♪ If you please ♪
♪ ♪
[song ends and applause]
- Ladies, I've made my decision.
Jujubee...
shante, you stay.
- Thank you.
I'm shocked.
Emotions take over me,
and I just can't help
let it all out, you know?
- Sahara Davenport,
it's come to a point
where I must say good-bye
to my best girls.
As you move forward, hold your
head high and stay on your toes.
I know you will.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you all so much.
Thank you.
[applause]
I'm heartbroken
because I didn't win.
I learned so much about myself.
I learned that I got
in my own way sometimes,
but life goes on.
There are big things in store,
so you just watch out.
- Congratulations.
There are six of you left.
I will see you dolls next week.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get a "amen" in here?
all: Amen.
- All right.
Let the music play.