- Previously,
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
Transform these silver daddies
into your drag mamas.
Steven,
you're the mother of Raven.
- She thinks she's being cunty
by giving me someone
who had a full facial beard?
I'm gonna turn it out
and show her,
"No, bitch, you didn't get it."
[laughter]
- I can tell
she's getting tired,
so I grab her
and take her to the back.
[cheers and applause]
- Raven, congratulations.
You're the winner
of this week's challenge.
Two queens stand before me.
Jujubee.
Shante, you stay.
- Thank you.
- Pandora, sashay away.
And tonight...
[feigning tears] I'd to thank
all the members of the Academy,
my personal tucker.
The queens hit the red carpet.
- Oh, my God,
I feel like a cross-dresser.
- I think I did my job.
- Who will be the biggest diva?
The Diva of the Year Award
goes to...
[all gasping]
- Thank you.
- With extra special guest
judges,
Marissa Jaret Winokur
and Tatum O'Neal.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX Cosmetics
and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com;
an exclusive,
one-year P.R. contract
with the leading LGBT firm,
Project Publicity;
be featured in l.a.Eyeworks'
legendary designer
eyewear campaign;
and headline
Logo's Drag Race Tour,
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks;
and a cash prize of $25,000.
And may the best woman win!
[engines revving]
- Oh, my God, it is so empty.
- I know.
- Wow.
- We're down to the final four.
You definitely feel the lack of
other contestants in the room.
- "Lick this Boxx..."
- "Bitch."
- How do you guys feel about me
being in the bottom
last night with Pandora?
Did I deserve to go home?
- Off of just the lip-sync,
I thought
they were gonna choose Pandora.
- But what was
the reason behind that?
- My eyes were going to Pandora.
- I don't look at Pandora
and see a star.
I look at you, and I see a star.
- I think her runway
should have put her
in the bottom two
a long time ago.
- Yes.
- She never, like,
sparkled to me.
- Who cares who Raven
thinks is a star?
I sure don't.
I'm sure she thinks
that she is a star.
And I sure don't.
- I mean, lookit.
This thing
was packed full of shit
and people all up on it.
And now there's four of us here.
I really miss my friends,
though.
- I would talk to my drag mother
every day at, like, 10:00.
- Do you talk
to your drag mother
more than your real mother?
- I don't talk
to my real mother at all.
- You don't?
- No, girl.
She abandoned me.
- My father died when I was 15.
Six months later,
my mother found somebody else,
and she left me to take care of
my two younger sisters
and to just grow up by myself,
and...I just stopped
being a kid.
I just want to thank my mother,
Charisma Jeneva Jackson Taye.
[siren]
- Ooh, girl!
You got shemail.
Hey, dolls, if you still think
Liza robbed Diana
of the Oscar in 1972;
if you look in the mirror
every morning and cry out,
"You like me!
You really like me!"
then maybe, just maybe,
you could be America's
next drag superstar.
[car engine racing]
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hey, Ru.
- Good morning.
- Well, well, well.
You're the fantastic final four.
And you know
the next drag superstar
must possess a unique style,
and she wouldn't be caught dead
wearing the same dress
as another diva.
For today's mini-challenge,
you'll be given
identical outfits
and 30 minutes
to style and accessorize them
in a way to make them your own.
After that, I'll return to
decide which queen wore it best.
No cutting or gluing allowed.
- Oh, God.
- Ladies, make it fabulous
and make it your own.
I'll see you later.
30 minutes.
- Work.
Trabaja.
- Come on, Twila.
It's you and me.
- Are these dresses
all the same size?
I don't even think your tits
can even fit in here.
- Oh, my God,
I feel like a cross-dresser.
- I'm gonna wear this hair.
- I gotta put
some lipstick on, at least.
- I look over and I see Juju
buffing makeup over her stubble.
[laughter]
- You guys laughing?
- Girl, we have on fuckin' wigs.
- [laughing]
And not a stitch of makeup.
- I put some makeup on.
Girl, look at me.
- Ew! You better put lashes on,
you dirty whore.
- I don't need no makeup.
I got fish face.
I'm daytime. I'm real.
- Yeah, girl,
you look like trout, okay?
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Did En Vogue
get back together?
- Yeah!
- You girls work fast.
Look at you.
I can't believe
you got up in full drag.
- Mama.
- And she's
padded and everything.
You've got the leggings on.
Tell me about your decision
to do leggings with this.
- You know what it was?
I didn't have time to really
hide the pad lines,
and I wanted to kind of go
a little bit more R&amp;B with it.
- It does elongate you.
Now, Raven, you chose
all black accessories.
You look like a spy.
Are you a spy, girl?
- I was just going for a
little dark sophistication,
with a little hint
of last year's Rihanna.
- And you went
for scrunch boots.
- Yeah, well,
they came all the way up,
so I pushed them down.
- I've never been
a fan of the scrunch boots,
unless the lady has legs
as long as mine are, you know.
Now, Tatianna, are those
two holes in your ears?
- I have two holes,
so I thought,
why not match it up?
- Tell me about
your silver shoes.
- Well, I didn't want
to do a black shoe,
and I thought,
why not do a silver pump?
Give a little bit
of sparkle down south.
- I think that maybe Tatianna
over-accessorized.
She looks like
a 99 cent store mess.
- All right, now, miss Tyra,
you made yourself a clutch.
- Yeah, I didn't have one.
- Uh-huh, and you decided
to go the classy lady--
ladies who lunch.
From the funeral to the wake
to the after party
and then on to the club.
- And then to pick up
the children to go home.
the children.
It's a very elegant look
that any lady
at home watching
would feel very comfortable in.
- Thank you.
- All right, ladies,
the queen who wore it best is...
Tyra.
Tyra Sanchez, the other Tyra.
Ladies, exciting news.
For your main challenge,
you've all been nominated for
the First Annual Diva Awards!
[all scream]
Yes! Yes!
Now, the Diva Awards
are your chance
to show some serious
awards show realness.
You'll need to pull together
three different outfits
for three different
Diva Award ceremonies.
First up, the Teen Diva Awards,
where you must dress
as a hot teen queen...
using clothes provided by
the House of Infinite Radness.
Then it's the Diva
D.C. Press Awards,
where you'll be serving
some executive realness,
Washington, D.C., Style.
And finally, the Diva
Hollywood Extravaganza Awards,
where you'll be expected
to gag us
with your glamour and eleganza.
I'll be back later
to see how your pre-show
preparations are going.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
Go!
[laughing]
- The first thing I saw
was lime green fur.
So I grabbed
every piece of fur that I saw.
- It's nerve-wracking,
because you don't know what the
others are gonna pull out.
Now, in this competition,
it's getting to,
they're looking for the best.
You don't know
what each person is gonna do.
Our challenge this week is
to create three different looks
at the Diva Awards.
A hot, teen look
for the Teen Diva Awards.
Executive realness
for the D.C. Diva Press Awards.
And a glamorous red carpet look
for the Diva
Hollywood Extravaganza.
- I had something like this
in high school, actually.
- Me too.
- [laughing]
- I felt like the biggest fag.
- Oh, you wore it as a boy?
- I didn't go to school
as a girl, Tatianna.
- [laughing]
- Okay?
Tatianna is stuck
in that realm of, "I am a girl."
I think, as a drag queen,
you should culture yourself.
Maybe I'll go all, like,
Mary Kate on everybody
and just wear 30 things at once.
You should be a chameleon.
If I lose to you...
I'll be fine.
- I want to win this challenge.
- Girl, I want
to win a challenge.
We have to be number one
and number two.
- Them winning is not an option.
- I think that Juju and I
will both help each other out
as much as we can
to make sure
that we make it to the top.
- Is this Hollywood elegance?
- I think so.
- RuPaul keeps repeating,
"Charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent."
I think I have that.
I think Raven has that.
I know the other girls carry
some of those traits,
but I don't think
they have the full package.
- ♪ I don't care ♪
♪ If DJ love the way ♪
♪ I lose my inhibitions ♪
[mumbling]
[falsetto]
♪ Ahh ♪
- Keep on singing, girl.
- I'm sorry.
- No, do it.
You have a beautiful voice.
God gave you a gift, so use it.
[both chuckling]
- Over there trying to read.
- What do you feel about
missing Jeremiah's first day?
- I'm sad
that I'm gonna miss it.
I'm praying that his mom
takes pictures.
My son is starting
preschool today,
and I'm missing out
on his first day of school.
So I'm really gonna, like--
I'm, like, sad about it.
It's been nine weeks
since I've seen my son.
It's just driving me crazy.
I miss Jeremiah so much.
But I know that me being here
and getting a chance
to give him a better life
is all worth it.
Yes. You better do it, Tyra.
Mm-hmm.
- I sat and thought
for a majority of the morning,
thinking of the silhouette
I wanted to work with,
how I was going to utilize
the fabric that I ended up with.
[sewing machine whirring]
You never waste
your time thinking.
- Do I have feathers
all over my face?
'Cause they're
all over the floor.
- I can feel it.
- Sorry, but I want
to be fabulous.
- I just see fuzz flying
all over the fuckin' room.
And I'm like,
"what the fuck Is this?"
Tyra looks like she skinned
all of the Muppets
and is making a gown out of fur.
- I don't know
what the deal with her is.
I don't if she's
just playing a game.
Maybe she's just making this
just to kind of throw us off.
- Fabulous, darling.
Fabulous.
- I've never made
a gown like that before.
It's gonna have
more of a complicated,
more expensive look,
but it's really only, like,
three pieces of fabric
and some hot glue.
- Hello, divas!
- all: Hi.
- Oh, wow, look at this.
You're all busy at work here.
- You better work.
- Yes, mama.
Hey, Tyra.
- Hey, Ru.
- Look at you down there.
Now, which one
of the awards shows is that for?
- Elegant evening gowns.
So I want to be in a gown,
but I want it to stand out.
- Do you feel
that you're the one to beat?
Do you feel that confident?
- I do feel that confident.
I've been challenging myself
and making myself better.
- Yeah,
I've got to mention this.
Now, you're here,
and the fur is flying around,
and it's itching your face.
Now, that may be a red flag
for how it will perform
on the red carpet.
You see what I'm saying?
You might need to vacuum it
before you wear it.
- [laughing]
- Thank you, Tyra.
- Are you ready
for the biggest night
of your psychological life?
- It is pretty psychological.
- It's very psychological.
- So I see three
different ladies over there.
- I'm debating on my executive.
- Uh-huh.
- Most likely, I'm gonna
be going with this one.
- What says D.C. Diplomat
Press Awards to you?
- To me,
it just kind of reminds me
of something
that Sarah Palin would wear.
- 'Cause Sarah Palin
is your idol, and you--
- Oh, yes, I love her.
- Really?
- Please.
[both laughing]
- Everything that you've
learned about drag,
about yourself
up until this moment,
you have to put
into this challenge.
This is the big one,
and you gotta bring it.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Jujubee.
- Hi, mama.
- Wow, what do you
got going on here?
Is this
for your Hollywood eleganza?
- Yes.
- It still seems
a little understated here.
What are you planning to do
to Juju it up?
- You just said it.
I'm just gonna Juju it up.
- Uh-huh.
Last week, you did wind up
in the bottom two,
and the stakes are oh, so high.
- I know.
- Well, listen,
you keep on working it, mama.
Stay down. Stay down.
Stay hood.
- Stay here.
- Stay here, that's right.
All right.
Hey, Tatianna.
- Hello.
- I see you over here
pondering your outfits here.
- Yes.
- What are we looking at?
This is your teen outfit.
- No.
- What is it?
- That is for
the Hollywood red carpet.
- Extravaganza.
I'm just a little worried
about the cha-cha of this here.
What do you think Santino
will say about this?
- I've never done anything
like that before.
- That's not an excuse, is it?
You never--just because you
haven't done it, doesn't mean--
- Well, they haven't seen it,
so they haven't
commented on anything.
- Look, Tatianna,
we're at that place.
You gotta bring it.
You're under double scrutiny.
Triple scrutiny.
- Yeah.
- Because you have three
different looks
and three different
opportunities to be criticized.
- See, I think of it
as the positive:
You have three different chances
to wow the judges
rather than just one.
- Well, listen, I don't want
to throw you off your game,
but I'm telling you, these
bitches are coming for you.
- Yeah.
- If you were ever gonna pull
something out of your ass,
now would be the time to do it.
Thank you, Tatianna.
- Thank you.
- Ladies, gather round.
Tomorrow, at the Diva Awards,
our extra-special guest judges
will be Tony Award-winner
Marissa Jaret Winokur
from Hairspray.
That's right.
And Oscar-winner Tatum O'Neal.
- [gasps]
- Yes, we have people who have
snatched trophies hunting.
- We're having a Tony Award
winner and an Oscar winner
sitting there judging us
on how we maintain ourself
at an awards ceremony.
It's no joke.
- Now, listen, I know you have
a lot on your plate.
But there's just one more
little twist, Tina, darling.
Now, before you hit
the awards show circuit,
the four of you
will need to perform
a Diva Awards opening number.
The song and outfits
have been chosen,
but you need to work together
on the choreography.
Now, Tyra, because you
won the mini challenge,
I'm leaving you in charge
of the opening number.
- I'm in charge of the girls?
- You're in charge
of the opening number.
- Hi, mama.
- Working in a group
wouldn't be my first choice,
but I'm gonna work hard,
'cause there's no way in hell
that I'm gonna let
someone else fail
and put me in the bottom two.
- Now, tomorrow
on the main stage,
I expect you girls to be
dripping with charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent.
[feigning tears]
And finally,
I'd like to thank
all the members of the Academy,
my personal tucker,
and last, but not least,
to my four little darling divas.
I just want to say,
don't fuck it up.
I promised myself
I wouldn't cry.
Good-bye. Good luck.
- Bye, Ru.
- And keep it real.
- What song is it?
- I don't know.
- The last time Tyra
had to work in a group,
she wanted to leave her group.
It's a recipe for disaster.
- I thought it was my name
for a minute.
- The four of us
have to do a number
for the opening
of the Diva Awards.
Am I happy about it? No.
'Cause it takes time away from
me getting my shit together.
- So we're gonna--
okay, so we're gonna
walk out to the intro
and stand by our letter
like you are?
Right to the side of it?
- Do you want us to all
have the same pose,
or do you want us
to all have different poses,
but we just
don't break those poses
until it gets to our line?
- Um...
- So we look at Tyra,
and we're trying to figure out
what the direction is for this.
And she's not really giving
anything,
and then she does,
and we're like...okay...
- We walk out.
When does this happen?
- At the beginning.
- When what happens?
- Right at the beginning?
- This is the end.
- Oh, this is the end.
- I think it showed that Tyra
isn't the best
with choreography,
because there
wasn't choreography.
It was just kind of,
"We're gonna pose
and then we're gonna spin
"and then we're gonna pose.
And then we're gonna
stack letters and pose."
And it was very posey.
- Who's singing this part?
- We'll figure it out later.
- I'm the one with the attitude.
- Oh, I guess
I'll just stay here.
- Our rehearsal was a hot mess.
And so I'm really hoping that we
can pull this off tomorrow.
Thank you.
[alarm beeps]
- Just me.
- You are so shady.
- Bitch, please.
- Is everybody confident with
the things that they have?
- Yeah, I couldn't
sleep last night, though.
I was sitting there thinking,
what the hell?
I wasn't happy with my teen
dream whatever.
- I hope this shirt fits me.
- I'm so scared
about this dress.
I wanted to make a full gown,
completely made out of fur.
But I realize
that I don't like it,
so now I have to change my
entire plans
and come up with a new look.
- So today
determines the top three,
and I'm gonna be there.
- I definitely think
that I deserve to be here.
I think I work very, very hard.
- I know I deserve to.
I worked really hard,
and I've grown a lot
since I've been here.
And I think
that they know it too.
- You know, I may have had
to lip-synch for my life twice,
but it got to the point where
the challenges got harder,
and I won two of them.
- Y'all won two.
You won two.
You got one.
And I have zero.
I do not want to be
in the bottom two again.
You know, this is gonna be
a third time, if I do.
And last I remember,
Sahara did it three times,
and she went home.
- Now, who do you think's
gonna be in the top three?
- Me.
- Name all three people.
- Why don't you start then?
- Okay, I think it's gonna be
me, you and Tyra.
Tyra has shown consistency.
You have brought
a sense of energy.
I have given them
what they are looking for.
And it seems like Tatianna
hasn't done
what they want from her yet.
So, Tatianna, who do you think
is in the top three?
- Um, I hope it's me.
And that's really all
I have to say on the matter.
- Tyra.
- I would have
to agree with you.
But things could change
if she pulls it together today.
I think she, like, would,
like, have to really,
like, wow the judges.
- Jujubee.
- You know, I--I hate
to be like this,
but Tatianna, don't hate me.
- All right.
- But I have to agree
with you, Raven.
Don't be mad at me, girl.
- I've known for a while
that all the girls
don't think I'm competition.
But a lot of those girls who
thought I wasn't competition
have gone home.
In my head, I'm just like...
think that, feel that, own it.
Whatever.
You're not
gonna break my spirit.
- You know I only bring shit up
that I absolutely have to.
- You're such a bitch.
I love it.
[giggles]
[RuPaul laughing]
[applause]
- Hey, judges.
Santino Rice.
Why, you old geezer.
- [laughing]
- Merle, hi, honey.
- Honey,
I don't have to tell you
to gather ye rosebuds
while ye may tonight.
- [laughs]
Marissa!
- Hello.
Your hair is amazing.
- Oh, you know,
I just washed it;
I couldn't do a thing with it.
Tatum O'Neal is here.
So happy to have you.
- Thank you.
- Are you ready to see my girls?
- Hell, yeah.
- Excellent.
This week,
our ladies were challenged
to pull off three
award-winning looks.
Now, to kick things off,
our ladies have prepared
a show-stopping opening number.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
[jazzy music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ "D" is for the discipline ♪
♪ To not give a damn ♪
- ♪ "I" is what
it's all about ♪
♪ Wherever I am ♪
- ♪ "V" is for a vision ♪
♪ that's extraordinary ♪
- ♪ "A" is for the attitude ♪
♪ That's necessary ♪
- The show is going great.
- And then I forget
one of the steps.
- Jujubee was off.
- all: ♪ Every diva
will battle it out tonight ♪
♪ So cover your shins ♪
- ♪ 'Cause only one diva wins ♪
- all:
♪ You're sure to see a bust ♪
- ♪ It's the Diva Awards ♪
- ♪ The Diva Awards ♪
- ♪ Diva Awards ♪
[all singing scales]
- all: Bitch.
♪ D-I-V-A, diva ♪
♪ The Diva Awards ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies and gentlemen,
here come our girls
for the Teen Diva Awards.
Tatianna.
Oh, my God, you guys,
she's so cute.
- Is that from, like, BCBG?
- I'm feeling
like I'm selling it,
and I'm really giving
the aura of hot teen actress.
- Bye.
Oh, my God, that is so Raven.
- That's like teen Chanel.
- It is teen Chanel.
- I feel cute, I feel fun.
I'm just bouncing
down the catwalk.
- I really want
to lose three pounds, Raven.
Yes.
- [laughing]
- Jujubee.
- She's a mean girl.
- Oh, is this the B.E.T.
Teen Awards?
She must be from Baldwin hills.
[laughter]
- I'm so comfortable with this
hip-hop look right now.
I am channeling
miss Mary J. Blige.
- Yeah, MJB, y'all.
Ooh!
[gasps]
Is that Solange Knowles?
No, honey, it is Tyra.
- I felt as if I had turned 16
all over again.
- Oh, my God, Tyra,
you were supposed to text me.
Breaking news.
Let's go live
to the D.C. Diva Press Awards.
Sarah Palin!
She can see Russia
from her house.
I'm feeling super confident.
It's a look that I've
never tried before.
But I still felt sexy.
- Oh, she's got a call.
Hello? Rush Limbaugh?
Why, you fat fuck!
[laughter]
- Oh...Leslie Stahl, yes.
Right?
Well, she's giving
a speaker of the house.
- I'm just gonna give power.
I'm getting an award
for taking care of business.
- Meet you at the Watergate
for lunch.
Jujubee.
Is she a lawyer?
- I think she's getting a call
from the husband.
- He's saying,
"Stop buying all that ESCADA.
It's costing me too much money."
- I'm kind of channeling
a fierce executive.
She refuses to wear skirts.
She wears the pants
in the family.
- She's very Nancy Pelosi.
But, see,
she can move her forehead.
And her ass.
Mary J. Pelosi.
[laughter]
Tyra Sanchez.
Eat your heart out,
Michelle Obama.
- The judges have never seen me
in pants.
And so it's giving them
a different look for me.
But still Tyra--
nice and elegant,
but totally different look.
- Yes, she can.
- I'm James St. James,
author, nightlife dinosaur,
and red carpet perennial,
here at the Diva Awards.
- Here's a young starlet,
Tatianna.
- Come here, come here.
Now tell me what it is
that you're wearing.
- I wanted to show some leg,
but I wanted to still be cute
and not too--too much.
- Gorgeous.
Do you think
she's wearing panties?
- No.
- No Hollywood starlet does.
- [laughs]
- [gasps]
Is that Cher?
Oh, my God, that is Raven.
- You are the spitting image
of Anjelica Huston!
What is it you're wearing?
Give us the ensemble.
- The gown is by Vivian Wallace.
I lost a few beads,
but hopefully they'll end up
on the runaway,
and a couple of the girls
will fall on them.
- That beading is gorgeous.
I want that outfit.
It's very Angelina Jolie, right?
- Without the children.
- Yes, without the kids
or the Mickey D's.
What Bollywood star is this?
[gasps]
Jujubee.
- I feel wonderful, fabulous,
gorgeous, beautiful!
- Keep it coming,
keep it coming.
- You look gorgeous.
You know that.
- [gasps]
Oh!
She's not just dressed
for the red carpet.
She's wearing it.
- Who's--is that Beyonce?
- No. [gasps]
Oh, my goodness, it's Tyra.
- My dear,
how are you feeling tonight?
Are you having a good time?
- I'm feeling fabulous.
- Is there anything you'd like
to say to your fans?
- To my fans,
just keep dreaming,
and remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love anybody else?
- Tyra. Ohh.
- It's kind of Rita Hayworth.
- It's very Rita Hayworth.
Gilda.
- Yes, Gilda!
- Welcome, ladies.
An acceptance speech
is an essential part
of any awards show.
And now, I want each of you
to share yours with the judges.
The Diva of the Year Award
goes to...
Tatianna.
- First off, thank you.
I want to start
by thanking my mother.
Without her,
I wouldn't be here today,
and without her genes,
I might not
have been here today.
I did me to the fullest.
And that is why I'm standing
here today accepting this award.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Tatianna.
- Thank you.
- The Diva of the Year Award
goes to...Raven.
- Oh!
[laughter]
[sniffling]
Thank you so much.
I, first of all,
have to thank God,
for without Him,
I would not be here.
I also have to thank RuPaul
for putting a fire
under my butt.
And I also have to thank
all of my fans
who have gotten me
to where I am today.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Raven.
- The Diva of the Year Award
goes to...
[drum roll]
Jujubee.
- [hyperventilating]
Thank you so much.
First and foremost,
I'd like to thank my Creator,
King Jesus and God Himself.
I'd like to thank my father
for just believing in me
and taking his time to teach me.
Mother, I know you're out there,
and I know you're watching.
It's okay.
One day, we'll be
back together again.
This is my diva moment,
and I am so glad
to share this moment with you.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- [laughing]
- The Diva of the Year Award
goes to...
[drum roll]
Tyra Sanchez.
- Wow, I didn't even know
I was nominated.
[laughter]
First and foremost,
I have to dedicate my award
to my son.
It's you who make me smile.
It's you who keeps me going.
It's you who makes me motivated.
And I just want him to know
that if he believes,
all dreams will come true.
[whispers]
Thank you.
[feigning tears] I promised
myself I wouldn't cry.
[laughter]
[applause]
All right, now it's time
for the judges' critique.
Tatianna,
I want to start with you.
- Hello.
- Did you intentionally
do Sarah Palin?
- No, I wasn't intentionally
going for that,
but I do love her hair.
- Interestingly enough,
I think the sexiest
we've seen you look
was doing
the executive chic in D.C.
The fact that you're
hiding it a little
made you look more beautiful.
- I'm not in love
with the ruffle.
It's a little too big on top.
It's not coming off as,
like, a real garment for me.
- The red carpet, now,
that's where you got me.
Unfortunately, James St. James,
he's been holding a mic
a long time.
Or we don't know what he's
been holding, but what...
- [laughing]
Among other things.
- Among other things.
But he really got into that mic,
and he was like,
"So, what do you think?"
and you were like, "Well..."
- It did seem like you were
soft-spoken
and was lacking confidence.
- Hi, Raven.
- Hi.
- I have to say
I really do love this dress.
- It's actually sheer.
The beads cover your...
naughty parts.
- When you wear it,
you're of course
supposed to be a real woman.
- Oh, you mean
for a biological woman.
- [laughing]
A biological woman.
I'm a psychological woman.
- Oh, okay.
[laughter]
- But...
- You were giving me the first
woman four-star general.
It was very severe
and believable,
and I--I love that.
- I love it--a four-star general
with a pearl necklace.
- Yeah. [laughing]
- That's hot.
- Your backstage was, I think,
the best
out of the girls for me.
You were accessible,
you were funny.
- There are no small people,
just big bitches.
- Funny as that was,
then you turned around
and gave an acceptance speech
that was completely
from the heart.
So we got to see all the
different spectrum of you,
which we saw
in all the outfits too.
- Thank you.
- Jujubee.
- Hi.
- Your Diva Awards presentation.
You missed a few steps.
- Of course, you know, I--
I have two left feet.
- I was like,
"Oh, no, she's messing up."
But then you, like,
camped it up so much
that then I kind of couldn't
keep my eyes off of you.
You really recovered well.
And then this look, I did think,
"Oh, this is a costume.
"This isn't what someone
would really wear
to an awards ceremony."
- I thought what Juju
brought tonight
was nerve.
I thought it was very nervy.
to go with a hip-hop,
urban look
when it's not
what you would expect.
It was really
the only true surprise
that we saw.
- Then we got
your acceptance speech.
- Mother,
I know you're out there,
and I know you're watching.
It's okay.
One day,
we'll be back together again.
We all know I don't have
a relationship with my mother.
But she put me here on earth,
so I have to thank her.
- I can relate.
My dad wasn't there, uh,
for my, uh,
winning the Academy Award.
So--but he was busy and stuff,
so it's not like I
hold it against him.
But, so, but you know, you'd--
I was eight years old,
so you'd want someone there.
So I get it,
you know what I mean?
And--but I love that you had the
presence of mind to say that.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Hi, Tyra.
- Hi.
- I've gotta tell you,
the fact that you've been here
all these weeks,
and you were able
to save this dress till now--
I just want to give you a
standing ovation for that alone.
- Thank you.
- Were there any other times
when you thought,
"Okay, I'm gonna wear
the ice green today?"
- Every time I would get ready
for a challenge,
I would see it,
and I'm thinking,
"It's not time; when it's time,
it'll call my name."
[laughter]
- And you're just
so impressive this week.
I love that plum cocktail dress.
I notice that you
covered the shoes.
You know, you just know
how to wear clothes.
- That was my favorite teen
outfit.
That dress was exactly right.
And then the hair
was so very editorial.
- Your acceptance speech,
it was,
I think, my favorite tonight.
I have seen a lot of growth
in your stage presence.
Your confidence, your calmness,
the way you spoke
was really there.
- Well, thank you, ladies.
While you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior
Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
[car engine starts]
- All right,
here comes the hard part.
Let's start with Tatianna.
There's something about Tatianna
that feels unfinished,
like her dress.
Here's the thing:
when you've got a body
like Tatianna,
you don't have to do much.
If you're asked to bring
red carpet realness,
don't come in something
that's a little too slutty,
a little too obvious--
and homemade.
- But there was a positive about
her Washington, D.C., look.
- I thought that was
her best look,
because she wasn't
leaning on her looks.
She was bringing something else
to the table--
some thought and some fun.
- I think she has a spark.
Even her just
standing there smiling,
like, my eyes are drawn to her.
- Yes.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Like, there's no question
why she made it this far.
- She's gorgeous.
- Yes, she is gorgeous.
- But you've got people
who are dropping into character,
who are like, you know,
have got some,
like, really good,
off-the-cuff repartee,
so it isn't just
about a beautiful face.
- The real question is,
does Tatianna have what it takes
to be America's
next drag superstar?
- She got the beauty,
she got the body;
I don't believe
she has the personality
or the taste level
or the sassy humor.
- Let's go to Jujubee.
You know, Jujubee has this
intellect about her
that feels beyond
any of the girls in the room.
But she sometimes
relies on this sort of
"I perform for you"
type of character
that is sort of one-dimensional.
- No, I totally disagree.
I think she's an actress.
She's got some spunk about her.
Her minus: I think she made
a poor choice on her last dress.
I don't know if that's worth
being sent home for.
- Raven.
- I just was drawn to her,
just because she
seemed like somebody
who's worked very hard, who's--
who sort of gets it,
who is funny.
- Well, I've gotten to be a
bigger fan of Raven's
as the show's gone on.
Every week, the onion peels back
a little more.
- Yeah.
- And what you see
gets more interesting.
- It's so tough, 'cause I--
I mean, the same thing
that I love about Raven
is the thing
that could be her weakness,
and it's that hard edge.
- All right, now, Tyra.
- I loved her from the minute
that she walked on.
She just got me, man.
Like, I just really
looked at her,
and I was like, "Star, winner."
She does need
to work on her voice.
- She's gotten better,
and the speech she gave tonight
was funnier and softer than
anything else she's delivered.
- That's true.
I've never changed my voice.
I think people
hear me differently
when I'm in drag.
But I've never change my voice.
Never have.
- You have a very--
you know,
your voice matches you.
- Yeah.
- He's 21.
I can't imagine going through...
this at 21.
And with a son, to say,
"I'm gonna do this"?
I think that shows more maturity
than anybody else on that stage,
being able to say,
"I have a child,
"I'm bringing him into this
amazing world
"and showing him
you can really do--
this is truly proving
you can do whatever you want."
All right, silence!
I have made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Now, awards are a funny thing.
We lie and say it's an honor
just to be nominated.
But deep down, we all want
to snatch that trophy.
And yet,
what matters in this world
is charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
Based on that criteria,
I've made some decisions.
Raven...
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- You may leave the stage.
- I'm top three.
I'm excited.
But I should have won.
- The winner of this week's
challenge is...
Tyra Sanchez.
[applause]
Congratulations.
You have won a feature photo
spread in Paper magazine.
You may leave the stage.
- I'm not satisfied
being in the top three.
My goal is to win.
- Jujubee...
Tatianna...
the two of you
are up for elimination.
- Once again,
I'm in the bottom two.
I'm so disappointed.
- When I hear
that I'm in the bottom two,
I'm not surprised.
I'm really just trying
to pull this out.
- Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
for you to lip-synch
for your life.
Good luck...
and don't fuck it up.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Shoo ♪
- ♪ Shoo ooh ooh ♪
- ♪ Shoo doo doo doo doo ♪
- ♪ Shoo ooh ♪
- ♪ Ah, shoo doo doo ♪
- ♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Many say ♪
♪ That I'm too young ♪
♪ To let you know just where ♪
♪ I'm coming from ♪
- I definitely had issues
with the lyrics.
The way Aretha Franklin
sings that song
is so difficult to lip-synch to.
- ♪ Hey hey hey hey hey ♪
♪ I'm giving him something ♪
♪ Something he can feel ♪
♪ Yes, I am, baby ♪
♪ To let you know ♪
♪ My love is real ♪
♪ Whoo hoo hoo ♪
♪ So much love ♪
♪ For us to see ♪
♪ So much hope ♪
♪ For material things ♪
♪ Are they only in my dreams? ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Giving him something ♪
♪ He can feel ♪
♪ Oh, ho ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
[RuPaul laughing]
[applause]
- Ladies...
I've made my decision.
Jujubee...
Shante, you stay.
- [whispers]
Thank you.
I am in the final three.
Girl!
I was just like this,
like, gay boy with a dream.
You know?
- Tatianna...
you made this competition
fun and fresh and young.
And we all owe you
a debt of gratitude.
For that, I have just two words.
[tearful]
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Now sashay away.
- Bye.
[applause]
And look at my skirt.
It's short as hell.
[laughter]
Ha ha!
[laughing]
Bye.
You know, to the people who said
that I wasn't drag enough,
just because
I have natural beauty
doesn't mean
I'm not a drag queen.
I didn't have to put on pounds
of makeup to be pretty.
I think that bothered
some people here,
but that's their issue.
I know what I've got.
I know that I am a drag queen,
and one of the top drag queens,
thank you very much.
- And then there were three.
We are fast approaching
the finish line
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Tyra, Jujubee, Raven.
Next week, one of you will be
crowned the next drag superstar.
Until then, remember:
If you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
- all: Amen.
- All right,
now let the music play.
[cheers and applause]
[laughter]