- Previously on
Rupaul's Drag Race...
- The weakest person
in the group is Tatianna.
- No.
- My mom sent me
to a military school
in hopes that she would
get a little soldier.
Needless to say,
she got a drag queen.
- I think I could sell ice
to an Eskimo.
But not dressed as a fucking
Chicken.
Cock-a-doodle do!
- Tyra Sanchez, you tore it up,
miss thing.
Congratulations.
You're the winner of this
challenge.
Raven, I'm sorry, but you're up
for elimination.
You've been down this road
twice...
but you keep pulling through.
Shante.
You stay.
- Thank you.
- Mystique, sashay away.
[laughs and applauds]
And tonight...
hey, squirrel-friends.
Tempers flare...
- I almost just jumped out
this chair at your ass.
- You don't know Beyoncé
personally.
- Are you talking to me?
- And you'll be seeing double.
Rupaul!
Hey, Rupaul!
- Oh, hello, darling.
[laughter]
- With extra special
guest judges
Niecy Nash and Lisa Rinna.
The winner of Rupaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of Nyx cosmetics and be the face
of nyxcosmetics.com...
an exclusive one-year PR
contract with the leading
LGBT firm Project Publicity...
be featured in L.A. Eyeworks's
legendary designer eyewear
campaign
and headline Logo's
Drag Race tour
featuring exceptional
Absolut drinks...
and a cash prize of $25,000.
And may the best woman win.
[electronic pop music]
- ♪ Rupaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ Rupaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ Ru-Ru-Rupaul drag race ♪
- ♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ Rupaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
[alarm clock beeps]
- Oh, Mystique.
- Wow.
Her lipstick is chunky.
- Is that cake icing
or lipstick?
- No, if it was cake icing,
she would have eaten it off.
- Oh, that's cruel.
- Bye-bye, shablam.
- When Raven
wiped the mirror off,
it was almost like
a cleansing for the room.
Like, a new day.
- I don't know,
I feel bad for her.
- Well, we knew from day one
that she was going home soon.
Shit rolls downhill.
- Sonique, she always got that
stink face.
And if she is talking,
it's usually
she's talking mad shit
about people.
- You know, karma is a bitch,
and I think you just get what
you give.
- I just don't feel like she was
this big, horrible thing
that everyone, you know,
has the right
to talk such shit about.
- I pity her.
I don't feel bad for her at all.
- I don't think she needs to be
pitied though.
"She doesn't need your
pity, bitch."
I pity you for the face
that you have.
- I just don't want to have to
lip-sync for my life again.
I don't.
- You better work, bitch.
- I don't want to.
I'm gonna be devastated
if I have to lip-sync
for my life again.
Two weeks on the bottom
is not good.
I won't do it again.
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl!
- You got she-mail.
Good morning, racers.
Sincerity is everything.
And if you can fake that,
you got it made.
Play the game right and you're
gonna leave here
with a whole lot more
than a trash compactor
and a lifetime supply
of turtle wax.
You could snatch the title of
America's next drag superstar.
And please remember to always
spay and neuter your pets.
[laughs]
- You know, there's so many
things that I don't know.
- Hello, hello, hello.
[applause]
Attention, drag race shoppers.
The pit crew and I just got back
from stimulating the economy.
Because for today's
mini challenge,
we're gonna play...
♪ The Queen is Right ♪
In this game,
you'll have to guess
the correct prices of some
drag queen essentials.
There's gonna be three rounds,
and the winner of each round
will advance
to Rupaul's showcase throwdown.
Now since you've been here,
none of you have been able
to contact anyone
from the outside,
but that's about to change.
The big winner of the final
showcase throwdown
will get the chance
to phone home.
- The first thing that pops
into my mind is,
"I'm going to call Chris."
My boyfriend, you know?
I miss him so much.
- All right, ladies.
Are you ready to play
The Queen is Right?
[cheers and applause]
Raven!
- Whoo!
- Swish on down, mommy.
Jujubee!
[laughter]
Sahara Davenport!
[cheering and laughter]
Okay.
Are you queens ready?
- Yes!
- Our first item,
a six-pack of tube socks.
Who needs surgery when you can
stuff your way from flat
to double D?
Raven, what is your guess?
- $9.45.
- Jujubee, what is your guess?
- $5.98.
- Sahara's writing down
her price.
Sahara is guessing--
- $6.00.
- Now, Sahara,
you cock-blocked Jujubee.
- Yes, she did.
- The correct price is...
$10.99.
- Yay, yeah!
- Congratulations, Raven.
- I won something!
- The Queen is Right!
- Winning that made me
feel great.
Like, okay, these bitches
better watch out.
- Our next item...
hemorrhoid cream.
A best-kept beauty secret
to decrease under-eye puffiness
for any queen recovering
from a hard day's night.
Pandora Boxx,
how much do you believe
this hemorrhoid cream
is worth?
- Rupaul, I'm gonna go with
$2.98.
- Jessica Wild?
- It's a cream that I don't
know for what it is.
$4.50.
- Morgan McMichaels?
- $5.85.
- The correct price is...
$5.59.
Congratulations, Jessica Wild.
The Queen is Right!
[applause]
- If I have the opportunity,
I am going to call my mom,
because more than just a mom,
she's my best friend.
- Our next item...
a roll of duct tape.
Not only used for tucking
your tender parts,
but also an essential
for any aspiring
MacGyver of drags.
Tyra, what's your guess?
- $2.98.
- Al right, Sonique?
- I'm gonna say $4.00.
- All right, Tatianna?
- $3.75.
- The correct price is...
$6.98.
Sonique is the winner!
Congratulations, Sonique.
The Queen is Right!
[applause]
- Sonique ended up winning.
Boo.
- All right, ladies,
here we go.
Our showcase throwdown
is designed
for a lady-boy night
on the town.
Starting with a pair of genuine
brass knuckles.
Now what lady-boy
night on the town
would be complete without
a can of...
♪ Pepper spray ♪
With its own cute little
carrying case.
Perfect for the drag queen
on the go.
And finally, a brand-new wig!
And not just any wig,
but a lace front wig
made of real human hair
courtesy of Wig Pro Collections.
Now you need to bid
what you think
all three of these items cost.
Whoever comes closest
without going over
will win the total package.
Let's start with Sonique.
- $225.01.
- Jessica?
- $390.
- Raven, it's come down to you.
- I'm going with $395.
- The correct price is...
$1,283.90.
Raven, you are the winner!
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Raven, you get
the whole package
and a phone call home to mama.
- Yes!
I'm excited to get to call
my mom.
I don't need the wig.
I don't need the pepper spray.
But calling my mom is golden
to me.
- It's time for your
main challenge.
This week, you'll be guest stars
on a game show
I like to call
Snatch Game.
And in the great tradition
of drag,
you'll be asked to appear
doing your best
celebrity impersonations.
- Wow.
That is fierce.
- You'll be judged on your
look, precision, and wit.
And it really helps if you can
make us laugh.
So, gentlemen, start your
engines
and may the best
Liza, terrific win.
[laughs]
[applause]
[phone trilling]
- Hello?
- Mom?
My biggest inspiration for drag
is my mom.
Mom.
- [indistinct]
- Mother?
- Hello?
- Hello, mom.
- Oh, hi.
- How are you?
My mother is the most perfect
person in the world.
And how's church?
- It's fantastic.
Been praying for you every
night, so--
and every day.
- I love you.
Give my love to everyone.
- I will.
Okay, bye-bye.
- Bye.
Being able to talk to her,
it brought me to a place
where I feel confident again.
Mom can always do that.
- So who does everybody think
they're going to impersonate?
Who?
- Who do you--
- I'm doing Beyoncé, so...
- I'm gonna be Bey.
Beyonce is sort of just like me.
Well, I basically have my look
together, I think.
- They didn't give us much time
for this one.
- I know, right?
- I actually have never
impersonated a celebrity before.
So, Jessica...
- Yes?
- Who do you usually, um, do?
- I always perform as myself,
you know, Jessica Wild.
- Same with me.
I just do Tatianna.
Tatianna is the character.
I was like,
"What am I going to do?"
- Our main challenge is the
Snatch Game,
and Rupaul told us to dress up
like our
celebrity impersonations
and get ready to
make people laugh.
Sonique, what made you decide
to do Gaga instead of Madonna?
- I don't have a madonna.
- You look like her.
You could borrow
from every girl.
I guarantee you would
find something.
- My first choice, of course,
would be Pink.
- I'm doing Pink.
Pink is my number one character.
I love her, and I do
a really good, you know,
illusion of it.
- I mean, I love Pink,
but I don't need to do her
every time I go on stage.
- Are you talking to me?
- Yes.
- I did not hear
a word you said.
- I base Sonique off of Pink.
That whole rocker kind of image.
I just--I really like Lady Gaga,
and I want to go for that.
- You better work it out, girl.
- Hello, hello, hello!
- Hi.
- Hey, squirrel-friends.
- Hello.
- Got a nut for another
squirrel-friend?
- There's plenty of nuts to go
around, babe.
- [chuckles]
I bet.
So, Morgan, who are you?
Who have you chosen as your
celebrity impersonation?
- I have chosen Pink
as my celebrity.
She's, like,
the number one for me.
- How would you describe
Pink's personality?
- She stands up
for good things.
Like, she uses her celebrity
for, you know,
PETA and against
animal cruelty
and things like that,
so, you know?
- Well, PETA's sort of a tough
joke to sell in Snatch Game.
- But she's funny.
- I trust you have a plan.
Sonique-ka-nika-nika-nika.
Who are you doing?
- I want to do Lady Gaga.
- Lady Gaga?
- I love her.
- You know, I was on the fence
about her
until she did that
interview where they said,
"What are you looking for
in a boyfriend?"
and she said...
"A big cock."
- [chuckles]
It'll be really easy for me
to channel Lady Gaga
'cause I'll say
what's on my mind
and hopefully
it'll make you laugh.
- [chuckles]
All right, Sonique.
I expect to be gagging
on your Gaga.
Tatianna, now,
who are you gonna be?
- I think I'm doing Britney.
- ♪ Britney ♪
- Britney Spears.
- What does Britney do?
- [smacks gum]
- Chew gum?
- Mm-hmm.
- Ahh.
She does this thing with her--
she'll go...like that,
which is really--
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's it! That's it!
Are we gonna see that?
- Sure. Absolutely.
- Okay.
- And some hair flips?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I want to know who left
my hair out here?
- Me.
I'm gonna be the supermodel
of the world Rupaul.
- [laughs]
You little thief.
Eve Harrington.
Trying to steal my show,
are you?
- [laughs]
- What are some of the
signature Rupaul things?
- You open your eyes like this.
- That's usually a sign
that I have gas, actually.
Now some people would say it's
kind of risky
to do an impersonation
of a person
who's gonna be in the room
with you.
- Yes.
I know, but I can say,
"I did Rupaul
in front of Rupaul."
And you're going to have a lot
of fun
looking that Latina
making you.
- All right, go back to work.
- Yeah, you better work, bitch.
- Pandora Boxx.
Come over here, girl.
I wanna talk to you.
- Okay.
I'm gonna be Carol Channing.
- Carol Channing?
- Carol Channing.
- [dramatic gasp]
Yay!
Thank you, Jesus!
Thank you!
"Corn?
I don't remember eating corn."
- [laughing]
- Are you doing Hello, Dolly!
Carol?
Are you doing Love Boat Carol?
Are you doing "raspberries!"?
- I think I'm doing kind of
like the raspberries era,
because I don't have the big,
crazy glasses.
So, you know,
you can't do, like,
modern Carol without those huge,
like--
- Right.
- Like, saucer glasses.
- Yes.
Thank you, miss channing.
- Thank you.
- Look how gorgeous!
My goodness, the blending.
- Yes, girl.
- It's severe up in here.
Who are you doing?
- I'm gonna do Paris Hilton.
- Why'd you choose her?
- She's fun to make fun of.
- Yes.
Now you've been up for
elimination twice.
- I'm over it.
- You are over it.
- I don't wanna do it again.
- So you're putting
all your eggs
in Paris Hilton's big basket.
- Yes.
I'm trying.
We'll see what happens.
- All right.
Good luck, Paris.
- Thank you.
- All right, I'm gonna scoot
around over here.
Ooh, how "purdy".
And who are you doing today?
- I'm doing Sasha Fierce,
but technically
I'm doing Beyoncé.
- Now, Santino mentioned
the other day
that you should
work on your voice.
- When he said it, I thought
that maybe--
maybe he's right.
If it's a beautiful person,
it should be, like,
a beautiful voice with it.
- Listen, you know, your voice
worked
for Bea Arthur
and Weezy Jefferson.
All right, Tyra.
- Thank you.
- Sahara Davenport.
- Hey, girl, hey.
- Hi, mommy.
- How are you?
- I'm doing great.
- Good, good, good.
- Who are you impersonating?
- Whitney Houston.
- Whitney!
Now, are you gonna be Being
Bobby Brown Whitney Houston,
or are you gonna be Clive Davis'
Whitney Houston?
- I think Being Bobby Brown's
Whitney is a little more fun.
- [laughing]
Bobby Christina!
- Bobby!
- [laughing]
- Well, I'm so glad that
Whitney's back,
and she's on our show.
- [laughing]
Word, so am i.
- Hey, Jujubee.
- Hi, momma.
- Are you preparing for your
Snatch Game?
- Yes, I am.
- Who are you impersonating?
- Kimora Lee.
- You're doing Kimora Lee?
What is she like?
- She's a business woman,
she's a supermodel,
she's a mommy.
So she's kind of like
a chameleon.
- Where do you get your
sense of humor from?
- My father passing away.
You never know when somebody's
gonna leave you.
So you treat every day
like it's your last day.
Amd you just give the best that
you can give, you know?
- And that's why
the sense of humor?
- Yeah, of course.
Why not?
- All right,
you get back to work.
I can't wait to see your
Kimora Lee.
- I can't wait either, girl.
- [laughing]
All right, ladies, the Snatch
Game is about to begin.
Now, this is your opportunity
to steal the spotlight.
Ham it up and make us laugh.
Now the queen with the best
celebrity charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent will win
the challenge.
Oh, and one other thing...
don't fuck it up.
All right, I'll see you all
later, good luck.
all: Bye.
- Bye.
What do I need to do first?
I need to tuck my hoo-hoo away.
I decided I was going to emulate
Britney Spears,
but I had no
idea what I was going to wear.
- What wig are you wearing?
- That one.
Blonde wavy, and then I'm gonna
put a fedora on top of it.
- The wig she was wearing was
just, like, three hairs.
- I have a better blonde wig
if you wanna use it.
It's just fuller.
- It's fuller?
- Yeah.
- Whatever works, definitely.
Thank you.
Morgan, surprisingly enough,
let me borrow one of her wigs.
Is this what you use
for your Britney?
- No, I left my Britney wig
at home.
- I think it might've come
from the fact
that she didn't think
I was going to be a threat.
So might as well let her--
you know, throw her a bone.
Yeah?
Cool.
I think Morgan needs to be
knocked off her high horse,
and I think that that will
happen with this challenge.
Yay!
[laughing]
[applause]
- Hello, everybody!
Welcome to an all-star edition
of Snatch Game 2010.
I'm your host Rupaul.
Let's get to know our
contestants.
She's an actress, model,
and a red carpet favorite.
Phoebe Price is here.
Hello, Phoebe.
- Thank you.
Thank you for having me.
- He's a talented actor,
comedian, and housewife.
Welcome Ugly Betty's Alec Mapa.
Hey, Alec.
- Hi, Ru.
This is a master class in
staying in character.
When you see a really good
queen do it,
you realize that
the clothing and the wig
is the last thing
that has anything to do
with bringing forth
the essence of this person.
- Let's say hello to our
fabulous celebrity panel.
First up, Carol Channing
is here.
- It's great to be here,
wherever I am.
- [laughing]
- All right, next up
we have Pink.
Hey, Pink.
- Rock and roll, baby.
- Now, I've never seen you on
a game show before.
Is this your first one?
- This is my first--well,
it's not my first one,
but it's my
first game show.
- Kimora Lee Simmons.
Now I know that you're not
Simmons anymore.
- We don't wanna talk
about that.
- You don't wanna talk
- It's personal.
- Up next we have Lady Gaga.
Look at your poker face,
darling.
- Trust.
- We have Rupaul.
Hey, Rupaul, how are you?
Rupaul?
Miss Rupaul?
- Oh, hello, darling!
- [laughing]
- How are you?
[laughing]
How are you?
I said I'm going to do Rupaul.
And I'm going to have fun,
and I hope Rupaul will have fun
with my character, too.
- Oh, boy, you look gorgeous.
- Rupaul is very professional
when she's in drag.
Rupaul doesn't just get up
and start walking
and running and singing.
- All right, Paris Hilton
is here.
You have a line of clothing,
you have perfumes,
you have shoes.
- I didn't know that I had
shoes out there.
- Yes, you do.
She's made a big comeback,
Whitney Houston is here.
- I'm so excited to be with all
these lovely divas.
Yes, ma'am.
But let's not forget,
I am the original diva.
- Yes, you are.
Give her a big round
of applause.
- Thank you.
I love you much.
- Whitney's back.
- Ha!
- All right, next to Whitney,
of course...
Britney Spears is here!
- Hey, y'all.
- So happy to have you
on the show.
What's your favorite game?
- Oh, goodness, I like playing
hide the cucumber.
I love that one.
- Oh, yes, one of my
favorites too.
- I always win.
- Next to Britney,
we have Sasha Fierce,
a.k.a. Beyoncé
is in the house.
Hey, Sasha.
- Hi, how are you?
Beyonce's just like me.
All I have to do is
just be myself,
like, just smile,
say nice things--
thank you for having me.
- Tyra is really lucky that she
has immunity this week.
Because her Beyoncé
was not Beyoncé.
It was Tyra talking.
- Here's how the game works.
I'll ask a series of questions,
the celebrities will fill in
the blanks,
and you'll give an answer that
you think will match theirs.
All right, Phoebe,
are you ready to play?
- I'm ready.
- Okay, here we go.
Fat Fanny, the drag queen
is so fat
instead of dollars she prefers
to be tipped with blank.
- Well, I know in the South it
would be pork rinds.
So I would have to say
pork rinds.
- Pork rinds,
that's a good answer.
- She wants to be tipped with
pork rinds.
She's fat, right?
Carol Channing?
- Bingo.
[laughing]
Did I win?
- No, you didn't win.
Actually, we may want to see
your answer.
What did you fill in
the blank with?
Well, I said turkey legs.
- Turkey legs!
She's close.
Pink, what'd you say?
- Well, you know, like, I went
to Britney's concert,
and it's just, like, you know,
a drag show.
So I--and I tipped her
with slices of lunchmeat.
- Slices of lunchmeat.
Good answer.
- Paris Hilton,
you have pork rinds?
- No, I don't know too many
fat people.
- Oh, okay,I see.
- So I don't know what they
like to eat or be tipped with,
but I would think that
they would want something
that could fit
in their tight clothing...
- Yes, of course.
- And that they could eat.
So I put beef jerky.
- Beef jerky.
- When I was fat...
- Yeah?
- Kevin liked to tip me in
what he liked to call
his man butter.
- Man butter!
- Mm-hmm, it was really good.
- Sasha Fierce, what do you have
for Fat Fanny,
the drag queen?
What'd she like to be
tipped with?
- Well, ru, I never met
Fat Fanny,
but during my worldwide tour
I stopped in Texas,
and I did meet Mystique.
- Uh-huh.
- And she wanted to be tipped
with a two-piece and a biscuit.
- Two-piece and a biscuit.
Mystique gone but not forgotten.
[cheers and applause]
Okay, you ready for
the next question, Alec?
- Yes, I am.
- Okay.
Slutty Sally is so slutty,
last time I took a ride on
her disco stick, I got blank.
- I'm gonna cast a wide net here
and say the last time I
took a ride on her disco stick,
I got an STD.
- What do you think Slutty
Sally gave to people
with her disco stick?
- Scurvy.
Scurvy, yeah.
- I'm the national spokesperson
for Broadway Actresses
Against Scurvy.
- [laughing]
- We deliver limes and lemons
to all the people around
in the neighborhood.
And raspberries.
- And raspberries.
Is that a deterrent for scurvy,
raspberries?
- Well, they tell me it is.
I don't really know anything
except what they tell me,
you know.
Carol Channing,
hysterically funny.
I love that she was completely
out of it the entire time.
- Let's go to Kimora Lee
and see what she says.
- Scabies.
- Scabies is not sexually
transmitted, is it?
- It can be, I've had it.
- [laughing]
- Let's go to Lady Gaga.
- Yes.
- Last time I took a ride on
her disco stick, I got...
- Money, honey.
- Lady Gaga, I didn't really
feel like
there was any
characteristic "Gaga-ish-ness".
- Okay, Rupaul--is Rupaul
asleep down there?
Is she okay?
Do we--seriously, is she okay--
oh, she's okay.
- The time has come now for you
to lip-sync for your life!
- [laughing]
- To impersonate somebody
who's standing
ten feet from you
takes gigantic balls.
- ♪ I will always love ♪
♪ Shoes! ♪
- She got shoes
from the disco stick.
From Whitney to Britney.
Slutty Sally is so slutty,
last time I took a ride on her
disco stick, I got...
- I got lost.
- You got lost?
[laughing]
Am I wrong?
- Britney...
eerily accurate.
Kinda spooky.
- Thank you.
- All right, darling.
Dumb deedee is so dumb,
last night she got arrested
for driving without a blank.
- Let's go to Phoebe price
here, Phoebe price?
- I would have to say driving
without a car.
- Driving without a car.
- I've done that before.
- Where did you go?
- I don't even--
I was just driving around,
and then I realized, like,
I'm walking, y'all.
[laughter]
I'm walking.
- When one queen gets laughs,
everybody scrambles to get just
as many laughs,
but I think once
the scrambling began,
they lost the plot of the game.
- I'm a little embarrassed, Ru.
- Are you embarrassed?
- I'm a little embarrassed,
'cause I just wrote,
"I've got a lovely bunch
of coconuts".
[laughing]
- Great minds think alike.
I said car.
- Thank you, girl!
- I broke you in, girl.
I broke you in.
- She looked like Pink,
and the clothes and the wig
and the makeup were hooked up,
but the mannerisms
weren't there for me.
- Wonderful, okay.
Lady Gaga.
Well, my first answer
was spaceship.
- Uh-huh.
- But the one I put down
was car.
- Two points!
Paris Hilton.
- Well, because you're so hot,
I knew that we would get this
right so I said car, too.
- Car!
[applause]
Wonderful!
- The voice wasn't even close
to being Paris Hilton.
- Britney, Dumb Deedee's so
dumb last night she got arrested
for driving without a...
- A baby in her lap.
- A baby...
[laughing]
- Because every time I do it,
I don't get arrested.
- Yes, that's right.
- Dumb.
- Before I say my answer,
can I say one thing?
- Yes.
- To Britney and Whitney.
- Because I love them much.
Whitney, you're such an
inspiration to me.
- I love you too, baby girl.
- But I notice
they keep twitching.
And I know that they're
survivors,
but the only way
they're gonna keep survivin'
if they stop sniffin'
these markers next to them.
- Am I the only one
who's doin' it?
- Uh, I--apparently.
- It smells like home.
[laughing]
- So right now, the score
stands at five for Alec,
three for Phoebe.
Alec has won this game.
- Thanks, stars!
Thank you, ladies.
Thank you.
- All right, until then
we love you,
keep coming back
on Snatch Game 2010.
All right, stars,
see you next time.
- I'll be really surprised
to see
who's in the bottom two
tomorrow.
Yeah, it'll be
a sleepless night.
- Good morning.
- Good morning,
morning glories.
- It's lip-sync day.
- Here goes.
- Who feel like they're gonna
be on the bottom tonight?
- Just as long as it's not me.
- The bottom is not bad.
[laughing]
- I do wish all of you luck.
Can you win a challenge
two weeks in a row?
- Do you think you're gonna win
- I'm praying I do.
- I don't know why Tyra
was asking
if anyone's ever won
two challenges in a row.
Because she's totally
not gonna win.
- What did you guys think
about me?
- Picking Beyoncé's
a difficult thing to pick.
Like, because she's not
that funny.
- But I don't think Britney
is funny,
but you made her funny.
- No, Britney is funny.
- But there are a lot of things
that B does
that are funny to me.
- The only thing she's done
funny is fall.
- Well, that's funny to you
and that's crude.
And like, I almost just jumped
out this chair at your ass.
That was insulting to Beyoncé.
This is something that she may
have been embarrassed about.
- You gotta get over this whole
Beyoncé thing.
- No, just drop it, please
just drop it, girl.
- Beyoncé fell,
and it was funny.
It tickled me pink.
- I thought it was funny, too.
- It was funny!
You don't know Beyoncé
personally.
- Tyra, she believes
that she's Beyoncé.
And she doesn't wanna hurt
Beyoncé's feelings,
because somehow Beyoncé
pays her bills.
- Well, we'll see
on the main stage.
I'm just gonna shut up.
- [laughing]
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the base in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And what? ♪
[applause]
- Hello, hello.
Santino, how are you?
- Ru, I'm great, how are you?
- Are you jealous of my boogie?
- I am so jealous.
- Today you are just
boogielicious.
- [laughing]
Niecy Nash, thank you for
joining us.
- Thank you for having me.
And thank you for letting me
have that flower!
[laughing]
- Lisa Rinna.
- Hello.
- You are gorgeous.
- Oh, no, you are.
Stop it. Thank you.
- This week, the ladies
were challenged
to a celebrity impersonation.
Tonight, I asked them
to knock us out
with their own
personal style.
Judges, are you ready
for what's coming?
- Ready!
- Oh, yeah.
- Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Pandora Boxx...
- I'm feeling really good
about the choice I made
with the dress.
I'm listening to what
all the judges have said,
and I'm trying to incorporate
that into my runway.
- She's like
a hollywood starlet
looking for a casting couch.
Tyra sanchez,
ladies and gentlemen.
It's the other Tyra.
- What recession?
[laughter]
- The concept of my costume,
I was thinking,
for a rich, couture woman,
and she has endless
amounts of money.
- Just buried the husband.
- And out spending his money.
- What do the bags say?
They say "Santino."
[laughter]
Oh, my god.
Santino, I didn't know you had
a boutique.
Okay, Morgan McMichaels.
Oh, honey, the circus
is in town.
- My personal style
is funky and fun,
and, you know,
drag is a circus,
and I want to be the director.
- It's the greatest show
on earth, Morgan McMichaels.
Jujubee.
Or should I say Lil' Kim?
- I feel like I'm
a superhero diva,
and my power is glitter.
- Is that Lil' Kim
or Lil' Kimchi?
Yes.
- Wow.
- Oh.
Sonique's in the house,
ladies and gentlemen.
Julie Newmar,
eat your heart out.
- My style was dominatrix,
feline, sex kitten.
- Faster pussycat, kill, kill.
Tatianna Porizkova.
- As I'm walking further down
the runway,
I'm noticing that my skirt
is rising and rising
and rising.
- Honey, if that skirt
were any shorter,
we'd have to arrest you
for dealing crack.
Jessica Wild.
Puerto Rico, okay.
- I feel great.
I feel very good.
I'm very happy with my outfit.
- She gonna party like
it's 1999, hunty.
High fashion.
Parisian.
- Ohh.
- Don't go out and blend in
with the rest of them.
Every time you go out there,
look your best.
Don't save something for later
because you may not have later.
- Ooh, yes, honey.
- These ruffles have not
any ridges.
- No, I bet you can't take
just one bite.
Ooh, girl!
Sahara Davenport.
What will people say?
- I'm feeling very powerful
and strong.
They need to see
this side of me.
- Little Grace Jones.
- Yes, gorgeous.
Ladies, your fate
is in your hands.
Inside there's either
a heel or no heel.
If it's a heel,
you can walk away safe.
No heel, and you stay,
which means you're one of
the best or worst of the week.
Tyra Sanchez, heel or no heel?
She's got a heel.
Congratulations, you're safe.
- Thank you.
- You may join Sasha Fierce
backstage with the dancers.
Tatianna.
No heel.
You stay.
Raven.
- Please just let there be
a fucking heel in this briefcase
so I can leave the stage.
- Heel.
- Yes! Thank you, Jesus!
[laughter]
- Jujubee.
No heel.
Jessica Wild.
Heel.
Sahara Davenport.
Sonique.
No heel.
Pandora Boxx.
Morgan McMichaels.
No heel.
You stay.
The five of you represent
the top and bottom of the week.
It's time for
the judges' critique.
Jujubee, the challenge
yesterday, you were Kimora Lee.
- I think I would have liked to
have seen you to be even bigger.
- We don't want to
talk about that.
- You don't want to talk
about that?
- It's personal.
- When you do characters,
and you only have
a short amount of time,
you want to do the biggest thing
about them
that makes people go,
"That's Kimora."
- Thank you, Jujubee.
Sonique, yesterday you portrayed
Lady Gaga.
- I think what Lady Gaga
was missing was comedy.
- Trust.
I didn't want to embarrass
my character.
It's all about the fashion.
I focused a lot
on the way I looked.
- I want you to come out
from behind the mask.
I feel like you might be hiding
a little bit.
- Would you like me
to take my mask off?
- Would you, please?
Can we see?
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Sonique.
- There we go, okay.
- Yay!
- There's a lot of fabulousness
in there,
and I think we just need to see
more of it.
- All right, Sonique,
thank you.
Pandora Boxx.
- Hello.
- I think you give great camp,
because instead of doing camp
that's, like, cheesy,
you do camp that's funny.
- I just wrote "I've got
a lovely bunch of coconuts."
[laughter]
- I think you nailed it.
You so nailed it, girl.
I just think you own it.
- Thank you.
- Tatianna.
How do you think you did on
the Snatch Game?
- I felt really proud
of myself.
- Last time I took a ride
on her disco stick, I got...
- I got lost.
- She used to live around
the corner from us,
and so I saw her a lot,
and you nailed her.
- I think you've got
a million-dollar face
and a $5 million body,
and you've got a $20 outfit on.
But I want to see more charm
and less hooker.
- Morgan McMichaels.
Tell me about your Pink
during snatch game.
Now, I've never seen you
on a game show before.
Is this your first one?
- This is my first--
it's not my first one,
but it's my first
game show.
- Your Pink,
I didn't necessarily get.
I think you could have been
way more obvious,
way more butch.
- It wasn't very effervescent.
- I felt like it went over
like a fart in a space suit.
And it was a risk.
And I knew by doing Pink,
I would be here.
- Thank you, ladies.
While you wait in the
Interior Illusions lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Thank you, ladies.
This is the time when we have
to break this shit down.
Sonique, I was not gagging over
her Lady Gaga.
- Yeah.
- Even if we don't know
who Lady Gaga is.
She could have done anything.
Make something up.
- Great on the pole dancing.
Like, unbelievable.
- When she hit the pole,
she was on fire.
She has to take that
pole performance
and put it in her
Lady Gaga.
She has to be more out there.
Tatianna.
- She needs to go home
and read 20 Vogues
and get back to us.
- Her Britney was amazing.
- Oh, the Britney, genius.
Her Britney blew me away.
I think it was
the best character
on the Snatch panel.
- Pandora Boxx.
- Pandora Boxx has got
great comedic timing.
I don't love her personal style.
I mean, it's almost easier
for her
to play a character than
be herself as Pandora Boxx.
It's not all, like, linking up.
- She's a drag queen
for Christ's sake.
She giving us lightness
and comedy and old movie star,
and I think she does it
really well.
- Okay.
Morgan McMichaels.
Her Pink impersonation was not
very strong.
- She did say that she knew
that she may have that problem
with not being able to go for it
because of her reverence.
Now, if this is a competition,
and you're trying to win,
you need to take a risk,
but that's the wrong risk
to take.
- Jujubee.
- She was not in the most
fabulous outfit.
Merle, I'm surprised you didn't
pick her apart.
- I would have if it was
on somebody else,
but something
about her comedy
and her wink-wink, nudge-nudge.
- Let's talk about her
performance as Kimora.
- As a comedian, that makeup
on her neck--what?
- That was a good detail.
- You know, the performance
could have just been okay,
but that attention to detail--
- Yes, and it's those
little things
that make a character
come to life.
- It's so true.
- Okay, silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Pandora Boxx, you delivered
another standout performance,
but you were overshadowed
by one of your competitors.
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Tatianna, you may have looked
a little cheap on the runway,
but in the challenge
you displayed a level of
confidence and professionalism
that is worthy of the next
drag superstar.
Congratulations, you're
the winner of this challenge.
[applause]
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- You've won immunity
for next week,
plus a $1,000 shopping spree
from billiondollarbabes.com.
- It's just validating.
I really am meant to be here,
and there really is something
special in me.
- Congratulations, Tatianna.
You earned this one.
- Thank you so much.
[sniffling]
- Sonique,
you're a beautiful doll,
but we were not gagging
on the eleganza of your Gaga.
It was a risky choice and one
that did not pay off.
I'm sorry, my dear,
you're up for elimination.
- Being in the bottom was just
so fucking nerve-racking.
- Morgan McMichaels,
you were pretty in pink.
- Thank you.
- But your performance left us
a little blue.
You're up for elimination.
- First time in the bottom two
sucks.
I knew I was going to be there,
and I knew I deserved
to be there.
- Jujubee, I've saved you
for last,
because I want to light
a fire under you.
You keep landing in the middle
of the pack.
Turn up the heat,
or you could go down in flames.
- I won't.
- You are safe.
Please join the other girls.
Two queens stand before me.
I've consulted with the judges,
but the final decision is mine
to make.
This is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourselves
from elimination.
The time has come for you to
lip-sync for your life.
And remember, good luck
and don't fuck it up.
[music begins]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I-I-I-I need ♪
♪ I need you ♪
♪ I-I-I-I need ♪
♪ I never said I wasn't gonna ♪
♪ Tell nobody ♪
♪ No baby ♪
♪ My body's burning ♪
♪ So come on heat my desire ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ Two of hearts ♪
♪ Two hearts that beat as one ♪
♪ I need you, I need you ♪
♪ Two of hearts ♪
♪ Two hearts ♪
- I was telling myself,
"You're gonna have to do
whatever it takes to get you
out of this hole."
- ♪ I-I-I-I need ♪
♪ I need you ♪
♪ I-I-I-I need ♪
- It's a lip-syncing
competition.
It's not a gymnastics
- ♪ Two of hearts ♪
- Wow.
- Wow, ladies.
Whoo-hoo!
- Sonique, Morgan McMichaels,
you both approached this with
two completely different styles.
Morgan, the precision of your
lip-sync
was one of the tightest
we've ever seen.
Sonique, you pulled out
all the stops
and worked every inch
of this stage.
This choice has never been
so difficult.
But I've made my decision.
Morgan McMichaels.
- Yes?
- Shante, you stay.
- Thank you.
- Sonique, sashay away.
[applause]
- I guess the hardest part of
this whole contest
was trying to find
the beauty in yourself.
Maybe I shoulda just stopped
being so serious.
There's more to life than just
being better than everyone,
and I definitely feel
more humble now.
- Ladies, you're all-stars,
but only one of you can be
the next drag superstar.
Remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen.
- All right,
let the music play.
- ♪ Don't be jealous ♪
♪ Of my boogie ♪
♪ Don't be jealous ♪
♪ You can say that you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you looking ♪
♪ Don't be jealous ♪
♪ Of my boogie ♪