- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
It's time to make
some her-story.
- How you doing?
- Yee-haw.
- Change for the Ritz.
- Everyone needs
peace with Latrice.
- I am of the people
and for the people.
I'm Sharon Needles
for sharing responsibilities.
- Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
Latrice Royale,
shantay, you stay.
Dida Ritz, sashay away.
- Thank you.
- Once again,
I've been criticized
for sending some of my queens
home too soon.
Michelle, I want you
to confer with Santino
to decide which one
of the eliminated queens...
deserves to return.
- No, bitch, top four.
No mo' hos.
- And tonight...
the dolls meet their mamas.
- Whoa.
- Man.
- And it ain't pretty.
- You okay?
- With extra-special
guest judges
Jesse Tyler Ferguson
and Jennifer love Hewitt.
[cheers and applause]
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime
supply of NYX cosmetics,
a one-of-a-kind trip
courtesy of ALandCHUCK.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race Tour
featuring Absolut Vodka,
cocktails perfected,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And may the best woman win.
- God.
- What?
- Oh.
- Don't what me.
Cluck-cluck, top four.
- What does it say?
- "Stay true.
Chad, Needles, Latrice."
- Dida's gone, but she left
a little piece of herself
for us to remember her.
- all: Cheesecake!
- I'm gonna miss Dida.
She was fierce!
- She was fierce.
- [indistinct]
- Love her.
- I had so much fun
getting to know her.
- We--yeah,
me and Dida connected.
It's a bittersweet situation.
Yeah, one more bitch
is out the door,
but Dida was my girl.
- Were you nervous?
- You know, I thought
I was gonna be really nervous,
but after, like,
the first beat kicked in,
bitch, I was craving
for some show action.
- You were good.
You put Dida straight to bed.
You took us to church, she
took us to a Beyoncé concert.
- Which is fine, but not
for Gladys Knight.
- Sometimes girls
give too much energy
for a song that just needs
some delicate, soulful moves.
- That's it.
- You gave it.
- So congratulations, Needles.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, your third win.
- Oh, stop!
- Okay, so let's say this right
now so it's really official.
We are...
- all: The top four.
- So some shit's gonna go down.
- No.
- There will be a departed queen
returning to the competition
this morning.
Who do you think it's gonna be?
- Bringing anyone back
isn't fair in my opinion.
- We should make up some
shirts or some shit.
- Shirts, or, like, signs.
- Signs.
- Yes.
- Top four. Add no more.
- Let's do this, honey.
Let's get it all going.
This sucks,
and we're protesting.
Top four. Add no more.
[siren wails]
- Oh, let's go.
- Ooh, girl.
You got she-mail.
Ladies, this competition
is still pregnant
with possibilities.
And soon a star will be born.
But will it be a labor of love
or a bastard of disaster?
Time to push, ladies.
Push!
'Cause I'm about to crown...
[moans]
America's next drag superstar.
I hope it's a queen.
[giggles]
Hello, hello, hello.
- all: [chanting]
Top four. Add no more.
- Whoo!
- Nice try, Norma Rae.
But this week we are celebrating
the modern drag family,
starting with the return
of one of your soul sisters.
Ladies, please welcome back...
Oh, the suspense is killing me.
[cheers]
- Kenya Michaels is back.
- She's a force
to be reckoned with.
She can dance, and she's pretty.
And that's exactly
what we don't need right now.
- Welcome home, mama.
- Yeah, I'm ready.
I'm back in the building.
I'm ready to compete.
So let's prepare, ladies.
- Oh, pit crew.
For today's mini challenge,
you need to get crafty
and turn these papa bears
into mama bears.
You'll have 20 minutes
to drag out your teddy bear.
The one queen with the most
unbearably beautiful critter
will win.
Ready, set, growl.
Whoo-hoo.
- Better make
your spook bear, bitch.
Spoo...kity.
- Sorry, Kenya, we've lost
our fucking minds.
- Look what you left me with.
Now I'm not the youngest or
the shortest or the fishiest.
- And you never will be,
Blanche.
And you never were.
[laughs]
- Okay, ladies, time's up.
Let's take a look
at your lady bears.
- RuPaul, meet Malibu Bearbie.
- She's very Jiggly Caliente.
- Yes.
[laughter]
- May I call you Jiggly?
Next up, Sharon Needles.
The bride of Chucky wore black.
- She's part
of the Scare Bear collection.
I let her borrow my contacts.
- So who do we have here?
- We have La Transbear.
- Are those pasties
she has there?
- Yeah, her pasties are sexy.
- She is a fishy bear,
and bears love fish.
- This is Portia the Pooh.
- I see that her face
is bejeweled.
- Like mother, like daughter.
- This is Princess Bitch Bear.
She comes complete
with a set of accessories.
- Booger Bear.
- Those are all
jealous bears over there.
- Ladies, one bear
is creating a panda-monium.
The winner of today's
mini challenge is...
Lil' Kenya Michaels.
- Yay.
- Yes, I win.
La Transbear.
- But, ladies, you can all
be proud of your work,
because all
of your dragged-out bears
will be auctioned off
by the Bear to Make
a Difference Project...
- all: Aww.
- Which supports
the Matthew Shepard Foundation's
effort to erase hate.
Can I get a amen in here?
- all: Amen.
- ["elderly" voice] Ladies,
when I was growing up,
a man went to work...
[normal] And left his wife
at home to raise the children.
But in today's modern families,
we expect a lot more
from our father figures.
Now, to prove my point,
I want you to meet some DILFs.
Or dads I'd like to frock.
[laughter]
- Whoa.
Truck-driving, burly men, like,
for real, for real.
[chuckles]
- Ladies, for today's
main challenge,
you need to transform
these handsome daddies
into sexy drag queen mamas.
All right, dads,
please introduce yourselves.
- I'm Leland,
the father of six.
- Six?
- Yes.
- Damn, Leland.
- Hi, I'm Rick, and I have
a beautiful daughter.
She's six years old.
And a beautiful son.
He's four years old.
- My name's James.
I have a beautiful
two-year-old daughter.
- My name's Chris.
I'm a proud father
of two beautiful girls.
- My name is Mike.
I have six children
and five grandchildren.
- Wow, so you're a grandfather
I'd like to frock.
- I am.
- All right, Lil' Kenya.
Since you won the mini
challenge,
you get to pick a daddy
for each of the other girls.
- You go with Chad Michaels.
- I'm looking at Kenya,
and I'm kind of doing,
like, the eye thing,
so that way she knows,
like, to send the guy
this way or this way.
- You're gonna go...
- When she comes
to pick out my guy,
I just give her,
like, a little nod,
so that way she just comes
and gives me my guy.
- With Phi Phi.
Um...
You're gonna be spooky.
- Okay.
- Hi.
Sharon Needles.
- The guy that I have been given
has the brickest face
in the bunch.
He's too manly to be pretty.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Leland is with Latrice.
So, Lil' Kenya,
who's your daddy?
- This is my daddy.
- [giggles]
- My guy is the most
beautiful woman.
Because he's gonna look
like Jessica Wild something.
- Now you can use your own drag,
plus extra materials and hair,
courtesy of Risque Wigs.
Now I'm expecting to see
a strong family resemblance.
And tomorrow, on the main stage,
to keep things in a family way,
you and your daddy mama
will be carrying
a bun in the oven.
- [laughs]
- That's right.
The category is...
baby bump realness.
- It's one thing
to put these dads in drag.
But now it got to be
maternity clothes?
You gonna be pregnant?
Ugh.
- Okay, little mamas,
your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
got you into this situation.
Now you need to use it
to turn it out.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best mother win.
- All right, come on.
- How do you call--
what do you call 'em?
- These are sequins.
- Sequins.
- I didn't even know
they made stuff like this.
- Is that your cell phone in
your pants
or are you just happy to see me?
- Nope.
- Okay.
Didn't told me I was
in the movie Anaconda.
What's going on here?
- Oh, my God.
This one's a freak.
Mike-o the Psycho is so weird.
- Ooh, baby.
- [chuckles]
- He makes me want to run
and take a shower immediately.
- You single?
- Not today.
- Sharon's DILF
looks freakin' insane.
He's like the
Silence of the Lambs killer.
- So we got to get you pregnant.
- Why do we have to be pregnant?
Today we have to turn DILFs
into MILFs--
pregnant, glamorous MILFs.
- Man.
Ugh.
- You have to get rid
of your manhood.
- But that will hurt.
- No, it doesn't hurt.
- If you push 'em
up inside you--
- Nah, it's--
that's where they go.
- Ooh!
- It's either that or you can
sit on 'em, and that's not--
- Sit on--oh, shit, no!
- Exactly, so...
- You can't--you tape it to your
leg or something like that?
[laughing]
- You gonna be serving
moose knuckles.
- So they want to see,
like, the transformation,
like, the difference.
And you'd look like a dude.
- Pretty manly man.
- I get paired up with Chris,
and I'm super excited,
because he's really
getting into this.
- I'm down to go all the way.
- Awesome.
- I want to win this shit.
- It's kind of fun
teaching a straight guy
how to be me.
- How you doing?
- Pretty good, you?
- Good.
- Don't talk to my dad.
- I can talk to your dad
if I want.
- All right?
Maybe your dad likes me better.
- He wants to be on the winning
team, so I doubt it.
- Yeah.
'Cause we're gonna win.
- You like that?
He even talks like Phi Phi.
- I was like,
"You're just like me."
That's what I like, 'cause
that way I can school these hos.
- Phi Phi loves to come for me,
and she can come for me
all she wants.
Come for me, baby.
However,
I have to stay focused.
What I'm producing
has to be perfect.
- No, that's way too bright.
I don't like the fact
that it's so long.
- 'Cause I'm thinking,
like, right about here.
Show some hip.
- He could chill out
just a little bit,
'cause I do know
what I'm doing,
and I don't need
too much direction.
- I want, like, a four-inch...
Bam!
- Walk.
Come on, walk.
Okay.
Okay, don't bounce.
Don't do that.
No, don't do that.
Okay, come on.
Walk, walk.
How you feel?
- Like, it--
it just--
Is that how they usually feel?
Like, hurting here?
- Yeah.
All the time.
- All the time?
- Yeah, all the time.
- My toes are
like this right now.
[laughs]
Yeah, I know,
because you have a men feet.
[laughing]
- Ah, fuck,
these shoes fucking hurt.
- Walk in the fucking heels
and then shut up!
- I might as well
level with you.
- Yeah.
- All these girls here
are like classic beauty queens.
I like to look kind of, like,
half dead most of the time.
- Who am I to judge anybody?
- Do you have both your shoes?
- The way I look at it,
go big or stay home.
- Right.
- Right?
- Agreed.
- Sharon Needles' DILF
is really, really
rough in the face.
- Well, what do you
do for a living?
What makes you so strong?
- I was a sheriff's deputy.
- Oh! I see.
Law enforcement?
- So don't step out of line
or I'm gonna throw
the handcuffs on you.
- Oh, got it, got it.
Challenges either
go two ways with me:
I either feel
ridiculously confident...
- No, no.
Don't be so out.
- Yeah, you don't want
to walk like that.
- Or I know I'm up the shit
crick without a paddle.
Feel your ass
going back and forth.
- Wow.
Sharon, mama,
you may be in trouble.
- Foot in front of foot,
crossing over.
- Sharon, he walks
just like you already, girl.
[laughing]
- Hello, hello, hello!
- Hey, Ru.
- Oh, Ru!
- Well, hello, Phi Phi.
- Hi, Ru.
- And Chris.
Apparently you're
making your outfits?
- We want to be,
like, sexy moms.
We're gonna have, like, fun,
flirty little pregnant dresses.
- You've been criticized
for proportions.
- I'll be fine.
It'll work.
I get worried when you do that,
"Oh, it's gonna be fine."
- I know you do.
- "It'll work. It'll work.
It'll be fine."
Remember, there have been times
when you've done that
and it didn't work.
Now, do you think
you have enough time
to finish sewing these outfits?
- Yeah.
It's not gonna take long.
There's that thing again.
"It'll be fine."
- Stop it!
No, we're gonna be good.
- Get to sewing.
- All righty.
Thank you, Ru.
- All right.
- Hi, Leland.
Hi, Latrice.
- Hello, Ru.
- Will you be wearing
matching gowns?
- Um, well...
- We're looking
for a family resemblance.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
- But it's gonna
work out, I think.
- So, Leland,
what are you most nervous about?
- Walking in them shoes.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
- You play sports at all?
- I used to.
- Yeah, well, because, honestly,
it has to do with
your center of gravity
and knowing your body
and your hand-eye coordination.
- Still ain't got no
coordination for basketball
with dribbling and--no, no.
- Right. Hmm.
All right, Royale sisters,
you have a lot of work to do.
I'm gonna leave you to it.
- Thank you, Ru.
- All right.
- Hey, Rick.
- Hi.
- Hey, Lil' Kenya.
You look like Elvis.
Do people tell you that?
- My mom told me I look
like a young Elvis, yeah.
- Now you're gonna look
like Lisa Marie Presley.
Have you picked
a drag name for Rick?
- She gonna be my Lil' Mama.
- Lil' Mama.
- Because I'm Lil' Kenya.
[laughs]
- How do you feel
about that, Lil' Mama?
- Uh...I don't feel
like a little mama.
- Well, listen,
you got a lot of work to do.
Let them have it.
- Bye.
- Hey, Chad.
- Hey, RuPaul.
- Wow, look at this.
- Isn't that fun?
- Yeah, it was both our idea.
We're both very technical people
when we start out--
"Is it off? It is doing this?
Doing that?"
- He's taking a very
active role in this,
and he's very assertive.
- Now you've been doing this
for a long time.
Can you look at James' face
and tell what he's
gonna look like
just based on bone structure?
- Yeah, he's gonna be pretty.
- Really?
- We'll see.
- I'm gonna let you get
back to it, okay?
- Thank you.
- Mike and Sharon Needles.
- Hello.
- How are you two kids
getting along?
Mike, you're getting into it
early, aren't you?
- Oh.
I'm embarrassed by Mike
because he seems
to have no filter.
- Why'd you decide to do this?
- 'Cause I want to bring out
my inner diva.
The only problem I have
with this outfit
is I think I'm having a baby
elephant.
You want to see his trunk?
- You kids have your work
cut out for you.
I'm gonna let you
get back to it.
Good luck taming Mike.
- Thank you so much, Ru.
- Gather round.
Ladies and gentlemen,
tomorrow night we'll be joined
by our extra-special
guest judges,
one of TV's favorite dads...
Modern Family's
Jesse Tyler Ferguson.
- Yeah!
- He's cute as a button.
- And the always lovely
Miss Jennifer Love Hewitt.
[gasps and exclamations]
But before you have a baby...
there needs to be
a little seduction.
So tomorrow, prior to your baby
bump runway presentation,
each couple needs
to get us in the mood
with a sexy striptease.
- What?
- Insane.
- And, in the words
of my sainted mother...
God damn it, you pussy-mouthed
motherfuckers...
Don't fuck it up.
- Welcome to the runway.
- Awesome.
- It's time for me and James
to do our striptease,
and I'm a little apprehensive.
- We just have to figure out
how to make it sexy,
'cause it's supposed to be
like a striptease.
That's not turning me on yet,
dude.
- I figured, with James,
since he doesn't have
a lot of experience,
you keep it simple.
Walk out, looking at each other.
Then let's hit.
So your arm's gonna go up on--
your right arm.
And you know how I like
to be perfect, darling.
Boom, and then throw it.
You've never stripped before,
I'm sure.
- No.
- You've been
to a strip joint, though.
- Yeah.
- Lap dance?
- Oh, yeah.
- Tipping?
- Yeah.
- Poles?
- All of it. All right.
Hold right, and then boom.
Perfect.
Real sexy, hands on hips.
Right to the X right here.
Pose. Perfect.
Just work your sexiness.
Like this. Look.
Ah.
- Okay.
- Perfect.
Just up. Perfect.
Give me five, brother.
- Got it.
- That's my man.
- You're gonna win.
- I hope so.
- So cross out.
- Wait, wait,
I didn't even cross.
I think I feel like
I'm walking off the stage.
- One, two, three, four.
Five, six...
- Oh, fuck.
That's all right, I got to
get used to the spin.
- It's kind of difficult
to transform, like,
a big, old, macho straight guy
into, like,
a real feminine woman.
Five, six, grab it.
Seven, eight.
- Five, six.
Oh, no, wait.
- No, that's clearly a dude.
- I feel like I'm
doing the Hulkamania.
Rrr!
[chuckles]
- Do you know what fishy means?
Like a girl.
Like, "ay!"
- Yeah!
- Kiss. Boom.
- Boom.
- No, you said boom after me.
That means you're
not timing with me.
- Uh...
back?
I know I should have saved my
brain cells when I was a kid.
- That's no excuse.
Turning. Now what?
- I'm fucking brain-dead, dude.
- I want to kill him,
because I have created
the most simplest,
cheapest routine
that Helen Keller could do
on the first try.
Can you skip?
- Nope.
- I'm panicking.
- I suck. It is what it is.
- Don't say, "it is what it is,"
'cause it's my 100,000
fucking dollars.
I need to make sure
that he's giving 100%.
But I don't think
I'm going to get it.
- You okay?
- It's coming alive now.
There she go.
You know who you look like
right now?
Rick James.
[laughter]
- You're trying to make me look
like Teena Marie, though.
[laughter]
- Hold on.
I dropped my bush.
- Sharon's DILF
is a cross-dressing,
support-group-needing dad.
- Mm.
[inhales]
- No, no, no, no.
We don't fetishize the clothes.
- He's a little bit
too comfortable,
if you know what I mean.
- What if one of your daughters
grew up to be gay?
What would you tell them?
- I wouldn't care.
- You wouldn't care at all?
- No.
Even if I had a son.
- That's good.
- It is what it is.
- But that's good
that you wouldn't
shun your kids or anything.
My dad, he didn't
like it at all.
- That sucks.
- I haven't talked to him
since I was, like, 18.
- One day he'll realize
what he's not being part of.
- It's really cool to talk
to someone that, you know,
they're straight but they see
how my lifestyle is
and it's okay to be who I am.
If you had a son,
would you have him audition
for RuPaul's Drag Race?
- No, 'cause he'll probably do
a better job than I do.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- I do. Yeah.
- How long?
- Eight years, and I was here
during our anniversary.
- On our eighth-year
anniversary,
we renewed our vows.
- Well, we might renew our vows
if we can ever get married.
- Why call it a marriage
if you're gonna
offend so many people?
- It's making everybody equal.
Say I've been together
with somebody for 40 years.
Say I get sick.
I go into the hospital.
They can't come visit me,
because they're not
related to me in any way.
So that's what
we're fighting for.
- That's what you're
standing up and saying.
- That would kill me to know,
if I was sick,
laying in a bed somewhere,
that Adam couldn't come see me.
No, it's cool.
I just, you know.
It just comes up, you know.
It's like--just to know that,
God, he would be locked out
and that he would be
left with nothing.
- I don't believe
that's fair at all.
I support you guys.
Everybody should have the right
to love who they want
to love, you know?
- You expect me to walk up
on this thing in these?
- Yeah.
Put on them shoes, boo-boo.
- [groans]
I can't even
walk on it barefoot.
Ooh. [laughs]
[exhales]
Okay.
- Tell me you got some rhythm.
- I got some rhythm, but I don't
know if I got any sexiness.
Oh!
- I need sexy swagger.
I need hips and ass,
and he don't have
none of that going.
- Whoa.
- You're okay with your shoes?
- Yeah.
Do I need 'em right now?
- You have to practice.
Come on.
One and two, the chair.
The legs.
Ha, ha, ha.
I do the split.
He need to be sexy.
Come on.
One more time.
Five, six, seven.
[speaks indistinctly]
Rick is a hot guy,
but he's not a dancer.
- That's it?
- Oh, my god.
- Pfft!
- One, two, three, four.
It's the end of the day,
and I'm panicking,
because we have
a short window of time
to get something so simple done.
Since you're strong,
what if I turned around
and you caught me?
- Yeah, let's make it
more difficult.
- Yeah.
- Ladies, can you vacate
our runway, please?
- "Vacate our runway."
- Get the fuck off our runway.
- We're better off than them.
- Don't make up excuses why
you guys are inferior to us.
- Well, their dance techniques
are bitchin'.
- Not really.
- A little bit
too much testosterone
running around here, sunshine.
- Why are you getting
such a bad attitude right now?
- Because I got
my diva bitch attitude,
and we're gonna win it,
and you guys
need to just stay home.
- Oh, I get it,
it's your diva bitch attitude.
- Yeah, just stay home.
- Bitch, I didn't come here
to stay home, "ossifer".
What?
What are you gonna do to me?
Beat my skinny ass up?
Go for it.
I don't give a shit.
I'll fucking put you
in jail too.
- Know what's funny, is nobody
laughs at your shit but you.
Can't take it, huh?
- Mike's in our space.
It's not the locker room.
I don't need all that,
like, macho bullsh--crap.
It's completely out of line
and I'm not having it.
- I hope it isn't your last day
here tomorrow.
- But you know what,
you're not gonna fucking come up
in my motherfucking workroom
and talk to me like this, sir.
- I just did, didn't I?
- Well, you know what, maybe you
need to be fucking removed
with your badass
motherfucking attitude.
Fuck that shit.
Sharon.
- You're gonna let this
bitch talk to me like this?
- Oh, I'm a bitch now?
- Do not call my sister a bitch.
I'm working with a DILK--
a dad I'd like to kill.
- Cluck-cluck, ladies.
- Good morning, everybody.
- Y'all are gonna be women.
- We're back
in the workroom today,
and I have to get myself
in drag, my dad in drag,
and we have to get
ready for the runway.
- I stirred
the shit up yesterday.
I wanted to give 'em
something to think about.
A little drag queen drama.
- Inescapable.
- So let me ask you a question.
Were you ever bullied in school?
- Oh, my God,
are you kidding me?
It was terrible.
You know, they'd wait for me
after school
and, like, beat me up.
- I mean, is this anything
you could report to the police?
- I never wanted to report it,
'cause I was embarrassed.
- Man, I'm sorry.
That's got to be
so frickin' hard, man.
You know, I'm learning
a lot about the world.
- As much as I rag on Mike,
he certainly was sympathetic
to the fact that I went through
a lot of hell growing up.
Still doesn't know
how to fucking dance.
- Dude, it's already squashed.
- Yeah, yeah.
I need to put tape.
Let me finish.
- No, I'm not taping my dick.
- Just tuck it back.
It don't feel that bad.
It's okay.
- I remember a friend
in high school tucking
after he saw
Silence of the Lambs.
Ugh!
- Let me see.
Rick can't tuck himself.
I have to...
- What about the balls?
- You can take your dick
from the back and pull up.
- Like that?
- No. More.
- It's gonna look like a tail.
- [laughs]
- Put it on the side
of the balls?
- It's from back.
- I think the balls are too big.
- [laughs]
I'm sorry.
- I'm really glad I didn't have
to kick your ass yesterday.
- It was all in a good time,
you know.
I just--I may have pushed the
envelope a little too far,
but I was totally joking.
- It's all right.
I needed to blow
some steam off anyway.
- Well, it's good.
You can use me for that.
I have a really good poker face.
I was cracking up inside.
- I'm sure you were.
- Ain't no fun
if there ain't no drama.
That's the way I look at it.
- [giggles maniacally]
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
Hey, guys.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hey, gorgeous.
- Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage. Hi, mami.
- How are you, baby?
We match tonight.
- And we're all eating
at red lobster.
- Mm-mm.
- Santino Rice.
- Great to be here, Ru.
- And look who
the stork brought.
It's Jesse Tyler Ferguson.
- Hi, Ru.
- Are you ready
to meet my modern family?
- Bring 'em on. All of 'em.
- [laughs]
Jennifer Love Hewitt,
welcome to our blessed event.
- Thank you for having me. Hi.
- Will you be
our drag whisperer?
- Yes.
[laughter]
- This week,
the queens were challenged
to transform real-life daddies
into sexy drag mamas.
They'll perform
a seductive striptease
before they rock-a-bye
the runway
wearing their best
baby bump eleganza.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Oh, yeah!
- We're doing the choreography.
Rick know the choreography,
but Rick's not sexy.
- It's like dancing with
Leslie Nielsen in Airplane!
That's what I thought
he looked like.
- [laughs]
- Leland's missing
a couple of cues,
but I'm not worried about it.
We're working it out
the best way we can.
- Oh, yeah.
- It's top five,
so the judges
are gonna look for anything
to put us in the bottom,
so I hope that our routine
was good enough to get us by.
[cheers and applause]
- Let the baby
bump parade begin.
- Sharelle and Latrice Royale.
- The water has broken, honey.
- Oh, Lord.
- You better get
Lamaze over here.
- Nine months later.
- If you're part
of the Royale family,
you're definitely
gonna be a glamour girl.
So Leland's looking
very elegant, very lady.
He's looking gorgeous.
- She didn't know
she was pregnant.
Gi Gi and Phi Phi O'Hara.
Ladies, the auditions
for 16 and Pregnant
are down the hall.
[laughter]
- Chris and I are basically
just trying to serve
sexy, pregnant MILF realness.
I kind of feel like he was
a drag queen in a past life,
because he's
doing this too good.
- It's a boy.
It's a girl.
It's both.
[laughter]
- Best friends and pregnant.
- Lil' Mama
and Lil' Kenya Michaels.
- Being pregnant's hard.
- Macabre too apparently.
- Yeah.
- We're in this together, mom.
- I know that Rick
gonna be a man,
and I think, okay,
if Rick gonna be a man,
gonna be a beautiful man.
- Khloe and Kourtney Kardashian.
- It is.
- Next up, Robin Mansions
and Sharon Needles.
Honey, they're having
Rosemary's Baby.
- My other eye
is my good judgment eye.
- Me and Robin are serving up
filthy-ass bad girls.
Who slept with Robin?
Who got her pregnant?
- Is this morning sickness
or is she gagging on her beauty?
- Apparently, Marilyn Manson
does have a uterus.
- Lady Samantha
and Chad Michaels.
Now, that is an immaculate
misconception.
- Paris Hilton,
meet your future.
- We are serving Carnaval
pregnancy realness.
We're so happy to be pregnant,
and we're glowing
with anticipation.
- There's a couple
of baby boomers.
- It's a very long child.
- It is a tall one.
My cervix is softening
just watching.
- Is it?
Mwah.
Welcome, ladies.
First up, Chad Michaels
and Lady Samantha.
- How are you?
- Hi, judges.
- Let's take a look at Lady
Samantha's before pictures.
That's James.
And, baby, look at you now.
Did you tuck?
- A little bit, yes.
- Oh.
- How do you tuck
just a little bit?
- Yeah, just push things around.
- Like, just between
your cheek and gums?
- Yes, sir.
[laughter]
- Yes, ma'am. It's yes, ma'am.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I have to say, James,
Lady Samantha if you're nasty,
I think you're wearing
the highest heels
on the catwalk here,
which I think
should not go unrecognized.
Very impressive.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- James, I love that you
were almost, like,
put out with how hot you were.
[laughs]
I thought that was really great.
I'd like to adopt that quality.
- So, James,
would you schtup you?
- Oh, yeah.
[laughter]
- Next up, Sharon Needles
and Robin Mansions.
That's Mike.
And now look at you.
What's your favorite part
of the drag getup?
- He seemed to be very occupied
by my breast plate.
- Oh.
- Liked it.
- Is Mike wearing it now?
- No.
- I swallowed half of it.
[laughter]
- I'm getting, like,
an Al Pacino in drag thing,
and not in a good way.
[laughter]
- Robin Mansions' face
repels beauty.
And I love that.
Nothing makes
a woman feel prettier
than standing
next to this one over here.
- Well, that's why I hang out
with Michelle Visage.
[laughter]
All right, next up,
Phi Phi O'Hara and Gi Gi.
Wow, that's Chris.
Now you are Gi Gi.
You're gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- What was the hardest part
of the striptease?
- Being fully tucked
and walking in high heels.
- So you were fully tucked?
- I had the elephant all the way
back towards the waterhole.
- Oh, really?
- I liked seeing
the resemblance.
- You look like you share DNA.
You look fantastic.
Great job there.
- I have such a girl crush
on both of you.
- What was the most
difficult part
of working with your daddy mama?
- We really worked
well together.
He's like an inspiration
of what everybody should be.
He's an open-minded,
heterosexual male
that just values people
for who they are,
doesn't judge a book
by its cover.
My dad's not like that.
If I could have a dad like him,
my life would probably
be a lot easier,
and, you know,
I wish I had that bond,
so it's nice to have
a friend like this.
- It'll happen one day.
- Do you think your father
will watch this show?
- Probably not.
And that's okay.
[crying] I'm fine with that.
I just--I hope he values...
like, who I am.
If I can get anything from this,
I'm just--I'm happy he was here
to see that I'm a good person.
That feels so good.
Thank you.
- Thanks, kids.
- Thank you.
- Next up, Latrice Royale
and Sharelle Royale.
That's Leland.
Girl, you come a long way.
- Sharelle is a ho.
She can't even get enough
of herself in the mirror.
- Really?
- Trust.
Look at that.
Do you see this?
- Yes.
- That's gorgeousness.
Gorgeousness.
- The family resemblance,
though,
it ain't up in there.
- You don't see none?
- Well, I...[mumbling]
- I'm different.
- Okay.
- See? There it is.
Now what? See.
- I will follow suit and say
that I'm not seeing
the family resemblance.
It's sort of more of like
here's two friends
in a Tyler Perry movie.
[laughter]
- Next up, Lil' Kenya Michaels
and Lil' Mama Michaels.
That's Rick.
- Wow.
- And this
is Lil' Mama Michaels.
- Rick, I feel like you and I
could be related.
I feel like we look a little bit
alike if I straighten my hair.
And I'm digging it.
- I don't love the dresses
that I'm seeing here.
I think they could have used
a little more flash,
so I would have liked to see
a little more sparkle.
- Lil' Mama, was this
an unwanted pregnancy?
- Uh, yeah.
- 'Cause it was the most
somber, macabre,
fricking death walk
I've ever seen.
I was like, oh.
This poor baby.
- [laughs]
- I'm ready to have this baby.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
I have, like,
four underwears right now
and, like, two pantyhose.
Even these shoes,
they don't even fit me.
They're glued to my feet
right now.
- Literally glued to your feet?
- They're glued to my feet,
so I can't take it off--
[laughter]
- He can't even kick 'em off.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Now while you untuck in the
Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, kids.
Just between us "goils"...
let's start with Chad Michaels
and Lady Samantha.
- I loved the striptease.
I loved the walk.
- The runway presentation
was very basic.
Nothing sexy about it at all.
Because Chad doesn't take risks,
it brings Chad down.
- Well, I was enamored with him.
I thought she did a remarkable
job with Lady Samantha.
- Sharon Needles
with Robin Mansions.
- I love Sharon Needles.
I love her energy,
I love her humor,
I love her look.
However, I really thought
Robin Mansions
was a dog of a lady on stage.
- I just feel like she
left her sister out to hang.
- Phi Phi O'Hara
and her sister Gi Gi.
- Phi Phi is
absolutely adorable.
- I-I heart Phi Phi O'Hara.
Love the shoes, love the bag,
love everything.
Love it.
- There was really
an uncanny resemblance.
- Yeah.
- Latrice Royale and Sharelle.
- Oh, the Royale sisters.
- [giggles]
- We're sisters,
but we look nothing alike.
I just felt like they had
a different baby daddy.
- I wasn't a huge fan
of the striptease.
For me, a little lackluster.
- Lil' Kenya Michaels
and Lil' Mama Michaels.
- I thought little Eva Longoria
was just adorable.
So much charisma,
and I can totally see why
you'd want to bring her back.
- Their pregnancy dresses with
the fur coming out of the top,
the sweater set,
and the marabou trim,
it was all a little bit wrong.
- Kenya Michaels
is a fierce queen.
It's unfortunate that she's
just off her game.
- Silence.
Now bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Chad Michaels...
You're safe.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Awesome.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
you babied your daddy mama
and carried this challenge
to full term.
- Damn straight.
- Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
- Whoo! Yeah, girls!
Whoo! Yeah!
- You and your daddy mama
have each won a trip for two
to Las Vegas,
courtesy of ALandCHUCK.travel.
- Ha-ha-ha!
Vegas, Vegas, Vegas,
Vegas, Vegas, Vegas.
- Thank you. Mwah.
- And all of our daddy mamas
will receive a $1,000
gift certificate
from Moods of Norway.
Kenya Michaels,
your daddy mama presentation
gave us a case
of the baby blues.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you
are up for elimination.
- Ooh.
- Oh, not again.
I don't want to do Carmen.
I don't want to go home today.
- Sharon Needles...
- You got this.
- You gave your daddy mama
a face only a mother could love.
Latrice Royale,
your daddy mama looked like
a sister from another mister.
Sharon Needles...
you're safe.
- Yes! Yes!
Yes!
- Latrice Royale,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- That's all right, mama.
- I didn't expect
to be in the bottom two,
but I'm gonna turn it out.
It's do or die.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last
chance to impress me...
And save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-synch for your life.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Looking out ♪
♪ On the morning rain ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I used to feel ♪
♪ So uninspired ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Before the day I met you ♪
♪ Life was so unkind ♪
♪ You're the key ♪
♪ To my peace of mind ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel ♪
♪ You make me feel ♪
♪ Like a natural woman ♪
- ♪ Woman ♪
- ♪ When my soul ♪
♪ Was in the lost and found ♪
♪ You came along ♪
♪ To claim it ♪
♪ Now I'm no longer doubtful ♪
♪ Of what I'm living for ♪
♪ And if I make you happy ♪
♪ I don't need to do more ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel ♪
♪ You make me feel ♪
♪ Like a natural woman ♪
- ♪ Woman ♪
- ♪ You make me feel ♪
[applause]
[cheers]
- Ladies,
I have made my decision.
Latrice Royale...
Shantay, you stay.
- Thank you.
- Lil' Kenya Michaels,
it's hard to say good-bye
to a queen like you.
Till we meet again.
Now, sashay away.
[laughter]
- I feel sad because
all the girls have the dream
to win this competition,
and maybe it's not my time.
Don't stop dreaming
'cause all the dreams come true.
- Wow.
The fantastic four.
The future of drag
rests in your hands.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- all: Amen.
- All right.
Now let the music play.