- Tonight all the queens are
back to dish the dirt
as we prepare to crown
America's next drag superstar.
Plus we'll find out:
What did Willam do?
From the El Portal Theatre
in Los Angeles,
give it up for the gorgeous
glamazons
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul's Glamazon plays]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- A queen for all seasons,
Alisa Summers.
[cheers and applause]
The apopaloptic
Lashauwn Beyond.
[cheers and applause]
Drag Race royalty The Princess.
Eww, look who's here.
It's Madame LaQueer.
[cheers and applause]
London, Paris, Milan.
Next up, may I call you Jiggly?
Jiggly Caliente.
[cheers and applause]
Category is cheesecake.
It's Dida Ritz.
[cheers and applause]
Serving you fish,
it's little Kenya Michaels.
[cheers and applause]
Large and in charge,
chunky but funky,
Latrice Royale.
[cheers and applause]
And our top three.
Chad Michaels.
[cheers and applause]
The spooktacular
Sharon Needles.
[cheers and applause]
And the unstoppable
Phi Phi O'Hara.
[cheers and applause]
[sassy pop music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- And now the star of our show,
the original supermodel
of the world,
the one, the only RuPaul!
[cheers and applause]
Ladies and gentlemen...
RuPaul!
[cheers and applause]
- I am so sorry I can't be
with you in person tonight.
I'm stuck here on the set
of my new feature film,
Drag Queens in Outer Space 4:
Uranus is burning.
[laughter]
But thanks to the miracle
of modern technology,
I'll be hosting tonight's show
via satellite.
So to get things started
I have one thing to say.
You better--
[static]
Excuse me.
Excuse my beauty.
Bitches better beware!
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl playing]
♪ ♪
Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
Hello and welcome
to the new main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
This season you've been there
for every twist and turn,
and tonight we're here together
reunited.
- Yes.
- Thank you for that.
Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
The race for the crown
has never been this tight.
So you better be careful,
ladies,
and don't slip because
the stage is dripping with
charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
[cheers and applause]
[moans]
So, gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
[energetic pop music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
Welcome.
RuPaul's Drag Race fans
are the best fans in the world.
[cheers and applause]
Well, tonight
the stars have come out.
We have Drag Race royalty
with us.
Hey, pork chop!
Hey, girl.
[cheers and applause]
And it wouldn't be Drag Race
without my squirrel friends.
Michelle visage, Santino,
Billy B are in the house.
Give a big round of applause.
[cheers and applause]
Working with America's
fiercest drag queens
is bittersweet.
I'm thrilled when they're here,
but it kills me
when they sashay away.
Let's take a look
at some of the queens
who were gone too soon.
[cheers and applause]
[somber piano music]
♪ ♪
- Eww!
- Welcome.
First up, Alisa Summers.
Now, were you surprised
that Jiggly sent you packing
with her sickening
lip sync and split?
- Did you see that outfit
she was wearing, honey?
When she was creating that
thing,
I was like, there is no way,
there is no way,
even if I'm bottom two.
Honey, but she turned it out.
But then again,
if I was wearing sneakers
I could have turned it out too.
[laughter and boos]
- Now, Lashauwn
and The Princess,
both of you were criticized
for being too low-key.
Do you regret not speaking out?
- I regret not speaking out
because I don't think
people got the chance
to really know who I was
and what I'm about.
So, yeah, most definitely
I regret it.
- Yeah?
And what about you, Princess?
- The only thing that I regret
is that the rest of America
didn't get to see what else
I had to show.
If I was more of a character,
say like Willam,
I probably could have
stuck around longer,
because, uh, I had more to show,
and frankly what came after me,
after I got kicked off
down the runway,
it was kind of lame.
[audience oohs]
- All right, now--
[laughter]
Madame LaQueer,
you won challenges,
and yet you were repeatedly
picked last
by your fellow queens.
How did that make you feel?
- Well, for a second
that made me feel bad
but in the moment that
made me feel in high school.
I get picked last
for the basketball team,
but, bitch,
I was a maid of honor.
Okay?
- Now, all of you
left the competition
before one of our favorite
mini challenges.
So I'm gonna give you a chance
to prove that
reading is fundamental.
[cheers and applause]
Madame LaQueer,
the library is open, darling.
[cheers]
- Jiggly Caliente.
I know I can call you Jiggly.
But, mama, where's your teeth?
I know, hanging out
with your good taste.
[audience oohs]
[applause]
- Ladies, stick around
because we've got
a lot more shade thrown
before we crown
America's next drag superstar.
[cheers and applause]
[techno music]
Welcome back to RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited.
Tonight all my girls are back
to help me crown
America's next drag superstar.
Now while our top three
are getting ready backstage,
I wanna talk to a queen
who became famous,
or should I say infamous,
for flipping her wig.
Let's take a look.
- That's a desperate
cry for attention.
- A little I am what I am,
La Cage.
- ♪ Gay straight or bi ♪
♪ Lesbian transgender life ♪
- Milan, girl,
that's clearly a dude.
[cheers and applause]
- London, Paris, Milan.
You look great.
Now, have you done something
different with your hair?
Oh, no--oh, you're wearing it.
[laughter]
Now, I gotta ask,
I gotta ask,
now, were you surprised
by the uproar
over all the hair flipping?
- You know, to be honest,
I was a bit surprised.
I, um--I think that people
sometimes misinterpret
what I do as an artist.
At times you'll disagree,
and I respect that.
- So do you feel like
flipping your wig right now?
Let's do it together.
You first.
Ready?
Come on, come on, let's do it.
Come on, Milan.
Come on.
- For real?
- No!
- No, thank you, Milan.
- Thank you, guys.
- Next up, when it came time
to put an outfit together,
this queen got Jiggly with it.
Let's take a look.
- The thing is,
I don't need to sew
to become
the next drag superstar.
- I don't see a real dress.
- I'm finishing that up
with some more...
garbage.
- Baked potato couture.
- Girl, right now you're a mess.
Things are falling off.
Fix your tutu.
- Where the fuck are my tits?
- It ain't the school for drag.
Let's face it,
she just took a bunch of pom-pom
and she just threw it on top.
It just looks horrible.
It looks horrible.
- Beyoncé don't be sewing
her shit.
[laughter]
- Hello, Jiggly Caliente.
May I call you Jiggly?
- Of course, darling.
Everybody does.
- [laughs]
Now--now listen.
Now, your struggles with sewing
and design brought you down.
Have you been working on this?
- My brother gave me a gift.
Like, after his tax return check
came,
he decided--he decided to get me
sewing lessons.
So in a couple weeks I'm gonna
start my sewing classes,
and then I'm gonna turn it
the fuck out.
[laughter and applause]
- All right, so all right.
Let's talk about
your temper tantrums.
- I mean,
like I said on the show,
I kept it 100 all day every day.
- You kept it 100?
- All day--
- Not 95?
- Not 95.
100 all day every day.
And some people
just didn't like it.
And sometimes they took
my temper or my anger,
and there was just
so many issues I had
also coming onto the show.
When I got home,
I went to go get--
went to go see therapy.
I have serious daddy issues
and--
- Honey, don't we all?
Right?
- Well--
[laughter]
- Um, so the therapist told me
to write a letter, and I did.
- You wrote a letter to daddy?
- Yeah, I did.
But she didn't tell me that,
you know, to really mail it.
I mailed it,
and the right address.
So whoever gets it--
- Well, actually, I have
the letter right here, Jiggly.
- Oh, shit!
- No.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- All right, next up Dida Ritz.
Dida, during your time
on Drag Race,
you had a breakthrough
with your family.
Let's take a look.
- Surprise, Dida.
- [gasps]
- It's your mom.
- That's my mommy.
- Say hi, dad.
- Hi.
- We just wanted to let you know
how much we love you
and we miss you.
And we're really proud of you
for pursuing your dreams.
Love you!
See you soon.
Bye-bye.
- So, Dida, what's happened
since the show?
- Since the show, you know,
before my parents
never saw me in drag,
they'd never been to a show,
and now they watch the show.
My family is, like,
the biggest fans.
My mom calls me so much,
and she's always telling me
how my grandparents
watch the show
every time it comes on reruns.
And my mom's actually here.
- Is she here?
Your mother's here?
Oh, there--
may I call you Mama Ritz?
- Yes, you may.
- Now, in the clip we heard
your husband in the background.
What does he think about Dida
on television in drag?
- He's proud of him.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm, and he loves him.
- How does it feel
to get this acceptance
from your father
and your mother?
- It feels amazing.
You know,
every time I've seen you
I've said thank you
a million times
because you're bringing
happy homes together
and especially religious homes
together.
So I guess for me
it's a blessing,
and it's something
I feel very happy to have
because I know that there
are people out there
who don't have that, you know?
My mom's sitting here right now,
so...
- Yeah, yeah.
[cheers and applause]
Your parents are proud of you,
and so am I.
And like I always say,
RuPaul's Drag Race:
Bringing families together.
[laughter]
It's true.
Up next, little Kenya Michaels.
She had the looks, the moves,
but what the hell
was she talking about?
[laughter]
I mean, let's take a look.
- Mama, it's not what you say.
It's what you do.
[roars]
Hmm, I kind of
like the smell!
- Kenya, you like the smell
of the beaver,
so don't hold your nose.
- This is a challenge
that you can go and kick ass,
because go, girl, smoke that.
That's my time, you know?
And it's more easy for you
than for me
that I don't speak more English.
It's the only thing that I say.
That's all.
- I understood
about four words of that.
- Whoo!
[cheers and applause]
- Hello, little Kenya.
Hello.
Now, my dear, sometimes it was
difficult to understand...
- I know.
- But tonight
we don't want to miss a thing.
So we've invited
an extra special translator.
Please welcome our biggest
drag professor, Charo.
[cheers and applause]
- Hola.
- Hello, Charo.
Now, Charo,
I need you to ask Kenya
how has everyone in Puerto Rico
responded
to her appearance on our show.
[laughter]
- Right.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- [speaking Spanish]
[both speaking Spanish]
- Si?
- Ah, yeah.
- [speaking Spanish]
[cheers and applause]
[continues speaking Spanish]
[both speaking Spanish]
- Si, si.
- [continues speaking Spanish]
Um...
[laughter]
Well, I tell you what, Charo.
Let's ask her one more question.
Please ask her
if she was surprised
that we brought her back
to the show.
- Right.
[speaking Spanish]
- Jodera...
I'm so excited, girl.
[speaking Spanish]
Baby, it's not what you say.
It's what you do.
[cheers and applause]
- Right, I kinda understood
the last part, but could you--
could you translate the first
part of that, Charo?
What'd she say?
- RuPaul, I'm very confused.
I cannot understand
a word that bitch say.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- Well, Kenya,
you are a fierce queen
in any language.
And, professor Charo,
so are you.
[cheers and applause]
Kenya, do you cuchi-cuchi?
- No, can you show me, please?
- [speaking Spanish]
- Actually, let's everybody
cuchi-cuchi out to commercial.
[upbeat music]
[cheers and applause]
Welcome back to
RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited.
Now, before we crown
America's next drag superstar,
there's an important
piece of business
that we need to attend to.
This season, for the first time
in Drag Race history,
a queen was disqualified
from the competition.
Now, rumors have been flying,
but there's one thing
for certain.
There's never been
a more controversial queen.
Let's take a look.
Willam,
it has come to my attention
that you have broken the rules.
Willam, I have to ask you
to leave the competition
immediately.
[cheers and applause]
Ladies and gentlemen,
to set the record straight
about Willam...
you'll have to tune in
to this season's premiere
of RuPaul's Drag U,
coming this summer on Logo.
[audience groans]
Just kidding.
J.K., Miss Thing.
[laughter]
Please welcome back Willam.
[cheers and applause]
Now, Willam, I want the answer
to the question
everyone is dying to know.
Audience, let's say it together.
all: What did Willam do?
What did Willam do?
- What didn't I do?
[laughter]
- No, seriously,
I want you to take a deep breath
and break it down for me, okay?
- When you go away to Drag Race,
you can't tell anybody.
It's top secret.
And I told my husband
I was doing
a non-union horror movie
in Europe,
which I've done before,
and they suck,
so don't watch them.
And he didn't believe me.
He's like, "Why you gotta
take all this drag?"
So I lied, and he followed me
to the hotel.
And then the first night
he knocked on my door,
and it was a delivery.
- So in other words,
you were receiving
conjugal visits
from your husband,
and unfortunately
that was a violation
of the rules.
- Visiting makes it sound like
we were visiting.
There wasn't no talking.
- [laughs]
- But they were
very long visits.
He's 6'6".
- Oh, yes, yes.
Listen, I was disappointed
to see you go
and so were your fans.
[cheering]
- Thank you.
- I want you to know that
I really, really believe in you.
And actually I thought you had
a chance to go all the way.
[cheers and applause]
Do you have any regrets?
- Um...
I was gonna be flippant,
but after hearing you say that,
um...I regret that...
I maybe--
I should win next time.
- [laughs]
- Well, Willam, I have one
last question to ask.
- Sure.
- And this is
a serious question.
- All right.
- Do you have anything to plug?
- I have my new single,
the WDWD Doot-Doot Trouble mix
on iTunes.
And here's a little sticker.
- Oh, great, thank you.
- Yeah, and they're scented too.
They smell like a sticker.
- Oh, yeah, they do.
Yeah, yeah.
Willam, I expect great things
from you in the future,
so keep breaking the rules,
mama.
Just don't break my rules, okay?
- No, your show, your rules.
- That's right.
This next queen won our hearts
and made us cry
and redefined
the meaning of the word "bitch,"
being in total control
of herself.
I'm talking about
Latrice motherfucking Royale.
Let's take a look.
[cheers and applause]
- You have changed my life
forever.
You have changed the world
of drag forever.
Thank you for seeing
something special in me.
Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
- [laughs]
Now, I wanna ask you, Latrice,
how has RuPaul's Drag Race
changed your life?
- I am not the same.
I mean, the overwhelming
response that I'm getting,
the outpour of love
that I'm getting,
I never expected
to get all this.
I mean, really.
But I truly am humbled by it.
I thank you so much.
I definitely feel that, um,
I'm inspired
to keep on keeping on
because doing me works.
[cheers and applause]
- Now, you were very open
about your prison background.
Do you regret letting the world
know about that?
- No, that was the most
liberating thing
that I ever coulda done.
I want people to realize that
it's okay to make mistakes.
It's okay to fall down.
Get up, look sickening,
and make them eat it.
[cheers and applause]
- I hear that you brought
a letter from a fan.
- I did.
I did it just so--
if it's not all wet.
- Oh.
- Moist.
- Ew, dear.
- Delicious.
- Oh, okay.
- Says, "Hi, Latrice.
"I just wanted to tell you
what a role model you have been
"for my ten-year-old daughter
Katherine.
"We get in bed
every Monday night together
"and watch the Drag Race.
"She's been dealing with
some bullying issues,
"but lately she's been
channeling her inner Latrice
and showing those bitches
the door."
[cheers and applause]
"When I drop her off at school
in the morning,
"I tell her,
'You be fierce, mama.'
"Much love.
Rock on.
Gina from Florida."
- That is lovely.
I love it.
Well, of course you haven't
seen the last of Latrice.
I'm very excited to announce
that she's joining the faculty
of Drag U this summer
right here on Logo TV
and logotv.com.
Give it up for
Latrice motherfucking Royale.
[cheers and applause]
The shade, the shade of it all.
The shade, the shade, the shade.
Ha, it's fabulous.
Gorgeous.
[cheers and applause]
Welcome back to
RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited.
Last week, our top three queens
were lip syncing for their lives
to my single Glamazon,
available on iTunes and Amazon.
[cheers and applause]
Tonight they're dying
to find out
who will be crowned
America's next drag superstar.
Please welcome back to the stage
the top three.
[cheers and applause]
My girls, my girls.
Can you feel the love tonight?
- Oh, it's incredible.
- Fabulous.
- It's "phierce" with a "p-h".
- Yes.
- Sharon, Phi Phi,
for most of the season
the two of you hated each other.
Why?
- Well, who first?
- It's really hard
for me to hate someone,
and it's really easy for me
just to get along with anyone
when I can just find
a redeeming quality.
Unfortunately,
it was really hard for me
to find a redeeming quality.
I mean, that's--
[cheers and applause]
- And Phi Phi, uh, why did you
hate Sharon so much?
- I did feel that a lot of times
instead of talking to me
as a person,
she was talking down to me
or at me,
and I don't take that very well.
But, I mean, I love her and
I respect what she does and--
- Bullshit.
[cheers and applause]
- Now, Chad,
you defended Phi Phi
for most of the season.
- I did.
- How do you feel about her now?
- As I watched the season
from home,
I realized that there were times
when I wasn't around that
Phi Phi really
let her ass hang out,
and, um, a lot happened
when I wasn't there.
And I literally felt like I was
walking around in a cloud.
Specifically setting up
Jiggly to fail.
Um, well, trying to set up
Willam to go home
by having Latrice
throw the contest.
And then the thing that just
left me really unsettled,
Phi Phi, in the Gold Bar,
when you came for Willam
it wasn't an attack
on his talent,
and it wasn't an attack on
what he was doing at the show.
It was a personal attack.
And I just--
I just felt as though
you could have behaved
a little bit better.
But that's my opinion, baby.
- And I complete--
I completely understand
where you're coming from,
and I do--
I watch the show now
and I see that--
watching, I'm like,
oh, I'm insane.
[laughter]
And, um, I just felt sometimes
that you guys were attacking me,
and so maybe that was
my defense mechanism.
- I wanna hear from
some of the other queens.
Do you have anything to say
to any of our top three queens?
Jiggly?
- This hurts a lot.
Phi Phi, me and you,
we supposed to be road dogs.
We supposed to be sisters.
You came to my crib.
You chilled with me.
And for me to see that
like that at--
damn, girl, I swear to god.
Ooh, I just felt betrayed.
And you always were like,
"You can lean on me
and you can lean on me,"
and then that.
I felt like a sucker.
And I'm supposed to be
your sister?
That shit ain't cool with me.
- You know,
I completely apologize
if that hurt you in any way,
but when I signed on
to this show--
and people might not
agree to it--
I signed in to win $100,000
and a crown.
- Honestly, like, I think--
I'm an egomaniac.
Everybody knows that.
But, like, she should be studied
down there.
I don't understand it.
It's almost sociopathic the way
she'll tell people, um,
"It was just a character.
I was just playing it up."
And then she'll sign autographs,
"Fuck Willam, fuck Sharon."
It's not cool.
And I understand
that it's a game.
I never retaliated on the show
because I didn't care
and indifference
is worse than hate.
And I'm not gonna "RuPaulogize"
for anything that I'm doing now.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, bitch.
Oh, bitch.
Consider that word stolen,
honey.
[cheers and applause]
My new album will be called
"RuPaulogize" on iTunes.
[cheers and applause]
All right, ladies,
it's time to find out
which one of you bitches
will be named Miss Congeniality.
Oh, pit crew.
[cheers and applause]
The fans have spoken.
And this year's
Miss Congeniality is...
[audience shouting, cheering]
Latrice Royale.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Condragulations, Latrice.
You've won a round trip
first class flight
and legendary
hotel accommodations
anywhere in the U.S.A.
courtesy of orbitz.com.
[cheers and applause]
Welcome back to
RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited.
My girls, Chad Michaels,
Sharon Needles,
and Phi Phi O'Hara,
in a moment
one of you will be crowned
America's next drag superstar.
First up, Chad Michaels.
Now, you've impressed everyone
with your grace
and professionalism.
Chad, I want to know
how you're feeling right now.
- This has meant a lot to me,
and just to be here with this
incredible group of friends
and with you, Ru,
I'm galvanized, I'm focused,
and I'm ready to
take home the crown tonight.
[cheers and applause]
- Now, do you have
someone special
here tonight rooting for you?
- You know I do.
I have my partner, Adam Magee.
He's right over here.
- Hi.
[cheers and applause]
- So, Adam.
- Yes?
- Now, you design out--
did you design this outfit?
- From head to toe, sweetheart.
- Really?
[cheers and applause]
Gorgeous.
I'll have one in every color.
[laughter]
Now, Chad, I want to ask you:
What would it mean for you
to become America's
next drag superstar?
- It would be a personal test
that I put on myself
that I passed.
It would be showing me
what I'm made of.
It would be justifying
all the support that I have had
over the last 20 years of--
basically I get to
play dress up for a living
and walk around the stage
and move my lips.
I think lastly, Ru, for me
and for so many entertainers
across the country
it would be my honor
and my privilege
to represent RuPaul's Drag Race
and to work for you, mama.
[cheers and applause]
- Chad Michaels,
I want to thank you
for elevating this
beautiful race to the highest.
You are a class act.
- Thank you, Ru.
Thank you, thank you.
[cheers and applause]
- All right, up next,
Sharon Needles.
[cheers and applause]
Now, Sharon, you've become
quite the cult figure.
How does it feel?
- It's humbling
because, you know,
I came here, you know, to show,
you know, the underbelly
and the underground outsider
art side of drag
and try and get $100,000
doing it,
and now it's become
a full-time job
and a responsibility
to so many young people.
I get hundreds of letters
a week.
I never thought I would
touch people like that.
[cheers and applause]
- Now, you have
some special people
here tonight to cheer you on.
- I do.
I have my girlfriend
with a penis, Alaska.
[cheers and applause]
And I also have my
mommy dearest, Joan craw--
or excuse me,
Joan Coady right there.
[cheers and applause]
- Was he a spooky child?
- Well, he's always been a fan
of horror movies
and Halloween in general.
In our house, Halloween costumes
didn't come out of a box.
And the last unspooky costume
I remember was the scarecrow
from The Wizard of Oz.
So from then on it's just been
zombies and bloody things.
- [laughs]
What would it mean for you
to be America's
next drag superstar?
- Well, first it would be
such a great honor.
Being the holder of the crown
would show that you don't
have to fit a certain mold
to make it in any industry
or in any desire that you want.
And for any gay kid out there
or just weird kid
that gets picked on,
just know, you know,
when in doubt, freak them out.
Do whatever the fuck
you wanna do, and--
[cheers and applause]
And if anyone
ever boos you offstage,
that is simply
applause from ghosts.
You remember that.
- [laughs]
[audience boos]
- I love it.
[cheers and applause]
- Up next, Phi Phi O'Hara.
No one has been in it to win it
more than you have,
and that drive has propelled you
into the top three.
Now, what's the best thing
to come out of the experience?
- As many haters as I have,
I would definitely have to say
that the fans,
the fans that I do have,
because, granted I came in here
to win the $100,000,
a crown, title of
America's next drag superstar,
but I wanted to be the backbone
and strength
for a lot of those kids
that had to go through,
like, a child abuse past
and stuff like that
and just have that person
that they could look up to
that I didn't have as a child.
- Right,
now you've been very honest
about your relationship
with your father.
And have things improved
since the show aired?
- No.
- Does he know
you've done the show?
- Yeah.
Um...
I know he watches it, and, um,
and I know he doesn't like it.
But I love me.
And, um--
[cheers and applause]
If I can show any kids out there
to be strong
and, um, live life for yourself
and just be happy,
make sure that at the end of the
day when you go to bed,
as long as you love yourself
and you're proud
of everything that you did,
fuck what everybody else says.
[cheers and applause]
- So, Phi Phi, who's here
rooting for you tonight?
- The person
I look up to the most,
um, my beautiful mother.
[applause]
- And what's your mom's name?
- That's Rhonda.
- Hi, Rhonda.
What do you think of Phi Phi?
- I think he's beautiful.
I just think that the judges
made a call right
when they said he may of wore
a little bit too much makeup.
[laughter]
- Shut up.
- But he toned it down,
and he looks great.
He looks just like me.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- Phi Phi,
what would it mean to you
to be crowned
America's next drag superstar?
- Money in the bank.
[laughter]
And, um, like I said, a voice.
I just want to show people that
you can fight for anything that
you want,
and never let anybody stop you
because if you want it,
you can make it happen.
- Thank you, Phi Phi.
And I just want to say,
watching you
in this competition grow
and be such a fighter has just
really been amazing.
And no matter what anybody says,
you are fantastic,
and you deserve
to be in this race, okay?
Let's give
a big round of applause
for our top three.
[cheers and applause]
Welcome back to RuPaul's
Drag Race: Reunited.
Chad Michaels, Sharon Needles,
and Phi Phi O'Hara, one of you
is just moments away
from being crowned
America's next drag superstar.
Before I announce the winner,
I'd like to hear from our judges
one last time.
Michelle visage,
what do you think?
- I can tell you
from the bottom of my heart
any one of these queens
will represent you
and your show flawlessly.
- Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
All right, Santino and Billy B,
what do you think?
- We have just one more thing
to say.
both: Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
[cheers and applause]
- Thank you, judges.
I want you to know
from the bottom of my heart
you are the air beneath my foot.
[laughter]
Now, being America's
next drag superstar rocks.
Take a look at this.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics,
a one-of-a-kind trip
courtesy of alandchuck.travel,
headline logo's Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut vodka,
cocktails perfected,
a custom crown designed by
Marianna Harutunian,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
The time has come
to crown our queen.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Chad Michaels...
Sharon Needles...
Phi Phi O'Hara...
as always, I have consulted
with the judges,
and for the first time ever
I've consulted with you,
the fans,
but the final decision
is mine to make.
♪ ♪
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race...
America's next drag superstar...
is...
♪ ♪
Sharon Needles.
[cheers and applause]
- Love you.
- Thank you, that's so sweet.
- I love you so much.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Here you are, darling.
[cheers and applause]
- Can I hold the train?
- I love you, Ru.
[cheering continues]
- My queen.
Sharon, is there anything
you'd like to say?
- Happy Halloween, everybody.
[cheers and applause]
- Listen,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
all: Amen!
- All right, let the music play.
[RuPaul's Champion plays]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]