- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
My top three,
the best of the best.
- Morning, bitches.
- Chad Michaels,
Lady Chadderly.
- You want some of this?
We got plenty for you too!
- She's serving
the deadliest catch.
- Snapper.
I love the peek-a-boos.
They're sayin' hi.
- We gotta get back to
the sprinkler.
We gotta get back to
the running man.
- Excuse my beauty.
- I don't know why they book me
on these chicken shit gigs.
- [laughing]
- I'm a fucking oscar-winner.
[cheers and applause]
- Sharon Needles.
- This is my kinda ghoul.
- I might not be
the biggest star here,
but I got
the biggest knockers, okay?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[laughter]
- Take me to your leader.
- Yes, just a little prick
in the mouth.
- Oh, you nasty bitch.
[laughter]
- I'm the fucking
future of drag!
Why?
Because I'm sickening, bitch!
[laughs]
I'm Sharon Needles,
sharing responsibility.
- Well, hello, hello.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
survivor of the Rupocalypse.
Va-va-voom.
Her legs are like
peanut butter--easy to spread.
- You're me.
- That's what I was channeling.
- I loved it.
- Now I'm gonna show you how to
really beat a mug, bitch!
- Well, poo-poo-pi-doo!
Phi Phi's the shit.
- [laughing]
- Have three words for you--
fab-u-lous.
- Thank you.
- And tonight, the winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race,
America's
next drag superstar, is...
- The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race will receive
a lifetime supply
of Nyx cosmetics.
A one-of-a-kind trip, courtesy
of alandchuck.travel.
Headline logo's Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut vodka--
cocktails perfected.
A custom crown designed by
Marianna Harutunian.
And a cash prize of $100,000.
And may the best woman win!
- ♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen ♪
♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ Ru-Ru-RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen ♪
♪ Start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
- [monotone] I am one of three.
- [monotone]I am two of three.
- I am three of three.
all: Resistance is futile.
- This is the top three,
and I feel really, really good
that I'm finally here.
I'm so excited.
- We bow to you,
fierceness diva.
- You are our ebony goddess.
And we will see you again soon.
- Bye, sister.
- ♪ Latrice! ♪
Coming down the runway,
400 pounds.
Coming down the runway
in a velvet gown.
It don't matter.
- Our sister Latrice
had a lot of spirit.
And I'll miss her.
- Remember the first day here,
just walking in here
and not knowing anyone?
It's like the first day
in prison, you know?
- Like the first day of school.
- It has been kind of like a
long therapy session.
- Almost.
It's therapy, rehab,
prison, school.
- This is the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
- Girl, we've done some shit.
- First we got chased
by zombies.
- Drag queen zombies.
- I was so scraped up
and bruised from all of that.
- Just battered.
- We've walked down that runway
pregnant, with a dog,
and in a boat.
- What about
the wet T-shirt contest?
- Oh, I hated it.
- My mother's gonna be
so proud of that one.
- This is actually
who I thought
would make the top three.
- Well, I'll be honest,
I'm shocked
that I'm in the top
three.
I can't even win a pageant
in a bar in Pittsburgh.
And here I am.
- So, you guys, the runway was
pretty rough last week.
- Which one of these bitches
does not deserve to be
in the top three?
- I would say Phi Phi.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Bullshit.
- Are you guys feeling okay
about everything, or...
- Oh, I still hate both
of y'all.
- I think there was
a misunderstanding.
- We basically can agree
to disagree.
When it boils down to it,
we like each other.
I like you, Phi Phi.
Now, go home.
[alarm whirring]
- Ooh...girl!
You got shemail.
My queens, the chosen three,
you have survived
the end of the world,
bitch fights,
pregnant daddies,
and boatloads
of proud seamen.
Damn!
But your biggest test
is yet to come.
Which one of my girls will take
a giant step
and join me
in my elite squadron
of fighting glamazons.
Today, RuPaul's Drag Race.
Tomorrow, the world.
[cackling]
[laughter]
- Hello, hello, hello, ladies.
- Hey, Ru.
- [laughing] Wow.
My girls.
Now, your resilient charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent
earned you your place
in the top three.
But now it's time for
the ultimate test.
For your final challenge...
you'll be starring with me
in my new music video,
the fashion adventure
extravaganza,
Glamazon.
[laughter and cheers]
- Ah, it's so exciting.
- You'll have to dance, act,
style, and lip-synch
for your life...
as you work with director
Mathu Anderssen
and choreographer Candis Cayne.
- All right!
- Awesome.
- Now, I said it before,
and I'll say it again.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- Hello, girls.
Congratulations.
both: Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Miss Candis Cayne.
She's a famous superstar,
and is a fantastic dancer.
- Do any of you guys have
any dance experience?
- I do.
- Um, a little.
- A little.
Okay.
Well, you know, this is your
final challenge.
So it is super important that
you guys bring it.
- Okay.
- The concept of my
choreography
is high fashion
dragzilla primal glamour.
You turn, two, three.
Four and five.
Six, and then you repeat that,
but going back.
One, two...Sharon,
you wanna go this way.
- Okay.
Yes, right.
- Six, seven, eight!
Okay, stop.
You're spinning twice.
- Okay.
- So you should only spin
once there.
- Got it. Sorry.
Can you tell I'm shaking?
- It's okay.
It's all right.
- So why don't we start
one by one.
We'll start with you, Phi Phi.
- Okay.
- One, two, three, and four.
Five, stop, hit, hit.
Phi Phi, she's great;
she has the steps,
but she's also
a little cha-cha.
Let's try you, Chad.
One, two, three, and four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
It's a little too, uh, girly.
Let's try you.
- All right.
- It doesn't have to be pretty.
- Mm-hmm.
Thank God.
No.
[laughing] I'm teasing.
I'm joking, I'm joking.
One, two, three, and four.
Okay, let me just go over it
with you.
So just look at my feet.
I'm most worried about Sharon.
If you don't get the steps down,
you can't perform the video.
And then on this leg, you go,
step, step, step.
- Step, step...
Oh, goodness.
It's just so fast.
I am intimidated
that the other girls
are picking this up
a lot quicker than me.
This is just far too difficult.
- I just want you guys to do
the best you can do, okay?
- It's hard.
- Let's beat this face, ladies.
- Now it's time to
change into our
beautiful monster outfits
for the Glamazon video.
- And this really is gonna be
the coolest video.
- Our looks for the music video
are kind of a mixture between
1950s B-horror films
meets an issue of Italian Vogue.
Work.
You know what those monster
costumes remind me of?
- What?
- GWAR.
- Uh-huh.
- What's GWAR?
- "What's GWAR?"
- Talk about edgy.
- GWAR is, like, some crazy
'80s, like,
pop punk metal band,
but they wear
all latex monster costumes.
- Oh, why would I know that,
though?
- Because it's drag.
- Yeah, well...
- Oh.
- Coming from "never seen
Paris is Burning."
- I fell asleep.
- Ah!
As drag queens, I think of
ourselves as funhouse mirrors.
We reflect pop culture
back to the world,
and I think to be America's
next drag superstar,
you have to be exactly that.
- Fell asleep during
Paris is Burning.
- I was tired.
Chad and Sharon, they're old.
Screw them.
Let them watch their TV.
I have better things to do,
like become America's
next drag superstar.
- Candis Cayne
was an amazing instructor.
- I love that dance.
I thought the dance was fun.
- I hate it.
I just don't dance like that.
It freaks me out.
- Yeah, 'cause, I mean,
at this point,
we have to be perfect.
At this point, I kind of hope
Sharon messes up.
I want to win this.
- See, that's the shot.
- It is time,
ladies and gentlemen.
We're gonna start serving
Godzilla realness.
- And cue.
- ♪ Female phenomenon ♪
♪ Glamazon, ah ah ah ♪
♪ She's so wild, so animal ♪
- And cut.
Honey, help that girl.
Sharon needs to stay
on her line.
- Huh?
- You're drifting in to Chad.
Try your best to stay straight.
- If you drift out of it,
the shot's kind of fucked
for everyone.
- All right.
- One, two, three, four.
Five, stop, hit, hit.
♪ Do it, do it ♪
- Pose.
- Was I a little better?
- It was only one "wah" as
opposed to two "wah."
♪ Wah wah ♪
- It's just one song, Sharon.
- It needs to be together.
- We cannot
drop the ball on this.
- Action.
- ♪ She's so wild ♪
♪ So animal, she... ♪
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- We're jumping ship.
You're supposed to go
in the front,
she goes in the back,
I cut through the middle.
So it's that easy.
- I feel like I'm on
Candid Camera,
and I'm the butt of the joke.
- Let's get through
the fucking dance
in the half an hour that
we've got to do it in.
- [whispering] Jesus Christ.
Sharon needs to get this,
and she needs to get it now.
- Oh, fuck, fuck me.
- This is gonna be
a crap video.
- Hi, Phi Phi.
- Hi, Chad.
- After the choreography
debacle yesterday,
it's important for me to do well
in the rest of
the music video.
- What's on the mirror?
- It says, "Meet us
in the ladies' room."
- Who's "us"?
- Could it be, like, some of
the departed girls?
- [feigns sobbing]
- What do you think it is?
- I don't even know.
- Let's go.
- Let's go check it out.
Oh, god.
- [chuckling]
- [gasps]
both: Surprise!
[laughter]
- It's Tyra and Raja,
winners of season two
and three.
- Hi, mama.
- Hi, baby.
I'm gonna cry.
Hold on.
- Raja and I,
we've worked together
for ten-plus years.
And I just have
a lot of love for Raja.
- Hello, ladies.
- Hello.
- We've got one more little
twist to share with you.
- You'll be acting with
Miss RuPaul herself.
- Cool.
- In a face-slapping,
gut-punching, kick-ass scene.
- Work.
- Oh...and you'll be having
a one-on-one lunch with Ru.
So a little piece of
sisterly advice.
both: Don't fuck it up.
- Oh, I'm starving, Ru.
- Oh, good.
- How are you?
- I'm terrific.
- You look so beautiful.
- Now you get to see me
up close and personal.
- [laughs]
And, by the way,
if you're hungry,
just have a bite.
- Well, actually, I haven't
eaten since 1972, Ru.
That's how I stay thin.
- Oh, good for you.
- Isn't that great?
- I want to ask you,
over the course of your time
here,
people, Michelle,
talked about, um,
you being so perfect.
- Right.
- Because you're very poised,
and you say
all the right things.
And I think she just
wanted to see
that vulnerable edge
that every superstar has.
- I'm me all the time.
And if it's not edgy enough,
then so be it.
- Now, are your parents
still with us?
- Yes, my parents are with us.
I actually live with my mom.
My father is nearby,
but, um, still a little bit
estranged.
- Why is that?
- It's been a long 25 years of,
um, me not forgiving.
I felt like my father really
chose another family over--
over me and my mom.
And it's just recently that...
I'm realizing how much it
affected me.
- How does it manifest?
- Sometimes, it's easy for me
to disconnect from things.
And not...
really face my own feelings
about my father.
- Is it possible that
the invulnerability
that Michelle
is talking about
is exactly what
you're describing?
- Could be.
- I bet that's what it is.
I'm just wondering if that is
your breakthrough moment
in terms of
not only this contest,
but, you know, in your life.
- It could very well be.
- Thank you so much, Chad.
- Thank you, Ru,
it's been an honor to be here.
- Take these for the road.
- Thank you, darling.
I'll see you on the runway.
- All right.
- All right, mama.
- What's going on?
- Oh, other than
losing my mind?
I'm having a hell of a time.
- All you need to remember
is that right now,
you're in the heat
of the competition,
there's only three of you left,
but once this is all done,
regardless if you win
and get that prize
and the crown
and so on,
your life is about to
absolutely fucking change.
- Right.
- Of course it's better to win.
- Yes.
- Yeah, it's better to win.
- Yes, yes.
- Well, you know,
I'm used to being a loser,
but I really hope that I do win.
I want to let every loser
out there know
that there can be a giant crown
on their head.
There are so many of me's,
all around the world.
People who want to
express themselves
in unconventional ways.
If I win RuPaul's Drag race,
it will definitely show them
that anything is possible.
- Let's just go over
some of it.
- All I ever wanted was to be
a female phenomenon.
- [laughing]
I like the fact that you can
modify your voice,
'cause I've never
had that talent.
- I modify my voice
all the time.
- Yeah.
[laughs]
- Girl.
- I'll be Ru.
You ready?
- Uh-huh.
- You sure?
- Punch her! Hit her! Get her!
- Ohh!
- Hey! Yes!
- Uhh! Oh!
- Damn bitch knocked
my bracelet off.
- Work!
That was awesome.
- ♪ Legendary ♪
Ohh!
- Phi Phi, darling!
- You look amazing.
- Oh, you're just saying that.
- No, for real.
- Are you hungry?
- I'm hungry.
- Well, that's what
everyone says--
you're so hungry and
ambitious.
- I have a drive,
and I have a strong drive,
and I really
wanted to prove to you guys
and show you guys,
especially you,
that I can do whatever it takes.
- Does that come from having
an army dad,
where you feel like,
"I want daddy's approval"?
- I mean, I haven't talked to
him for seven years now.
- What was the last thing
you said to him?
- It was a fight, actually.
I-I don't even remember.
I was put in the hospital.
- By him?
- By him, on my 18th birthday,
so I haven't--
there wasn't many words.
[laughs] So...
- Wow.
- But I'm here!
So--so it's okay.
If anything, it taught me to be,
you know, a fighter and stay
strong and...
I guess, because I grew up in
such a situation,
I feel like maybe
it felt like
it was normal at times, but...
I shouldn't have felt that way.
- I want you to walk away
from this luncheon
and remember this idea
that you would deserve
to be abused
or not thought of
as absolutely beautiful,
never think that again.
- I really feel like
we connected,
and she understands
a lot more of the heart
of who I am.
- So, um, what's it been like
so far?
Who's your biggest competition?
- Sharon Needles.
We're like kindred spirits.
- Yeah.
- And, um...
- Have you guys ki-kied?
- [laughing] No, we have not
ki-kied.
- What's your relationship like
with Phi Phi?
- She's definitely comin'
after me.
But it's okay!
You know, we got a big age
difference between us.
And I've commented on Phi Phi's
maturity level,
but I also have
to remember she's 25,
and I remember when I was 25.
- Well, I'm 23.
- You're that young?
- Yeah.
- Jesus Christ.
- Only 23.
- And look at your position.
- Though we've had our spats,
maybe I'm not tolerating
that amazing kid
for who she is.
- So really just go for it
and be larger than life
about it.
You know?
- You promised to make me
a panther on the runway.
- Well, stand in line, girly.
- Slap her!
Uhh! Yeah!
Ohh! There you go.
Woooork.
- If I knew it was so formal,
I would have changed.
- [laughing]
- You look absolutely stunning.
- Why, thank you.
- Even from this close,
you can't clock a lace-front,
girl.
You gotta love that.
I'm just--I'm looking
for a problem.
- Well, there are several.
So, now, Sharon, I know you have
people back in Pittsburgh
that you love
and that you're worried about
what this experience would
do to the relationship.
- Oh, most definitely.
- We're talking about Alaska,
aren't we?
- Alaska has tried out for this
competition all four years.
I've tried out for this
competition once--this year.
I just wish I could
speak to him,
you know, and just see
if it was okay.
- What would you say?
I'm Alaska.
What would you say?
- I love you so much
and, in my eyes,
you're the biggest
superstar in the universe.
I just pray this doesn't
do any damage.
- I'm gonna tell you what
Alaska would say.
It's fine.
I would never stand in the way
of your success,
which is your destiny.
- Hmm.
- And Alaska has a destiny.
We all have a journey,
and it is up to you
to see it through.
- RuPaul gives nothing more
than good advice.
But I definitely have a fear of
success and fame.
It intimidates me.
- All right, see you later.
- [mouth full] Yes, ma'am.
- Needles.
How'd it go, mama?
What's wrong, baby?
Aww.
[chuckles]
It's okay. It's okay.
- Touching little witch.
- [laughs]
- God!
I knew this was all
coming to an end,
and it was the first time
I really realized
that everything truly
is going to be different.
And this is a big deal.
Oh, jeez, Louise.
- What's goin' on?
- Not much. Top three.
- Yeah!
Whoo hoo hoo!
- I know, it's crazy.
- Do you think
that you being young
has been a challenge for you
in this competition?
- Well, I'm 25.
I think a lot of people use that
as kind of like a...
like an excuse, really.
And I don't let that--
- Well, when I did the show,
I was 21.
So don't let anyone, like,
hold you back.
- Oh, I haven't.
- Being young is being fun.
- Just like me, everybody was
ganging up on Tyra
because she was the baby,
or they felt like she had
too much attitude.
So the fact that someone can win
at a young age
and still be a great role model
and America's next drag
superstar,
why can't I?
- Now sashay!
- Uhh!
- Shante!
- Ohh!
- Shante! Shante! Shante!
- Aah!
- ♪ Oscar ♪
- Why does the little one
get beat up?
Uhh!
- Wonder how ol'
Phi Phi's doing.
- Disneying it up somewhere.
- In a way,
I feel bad about, like,
saying some of the shit
I said to her.
I feel bad.
- Yeah, I know.
- Who the fuck am I
to tell her to grow up?
- [humming]
- How was it?
- It went really, really well.
- I just want to say something
to you.
- To me?
- [crying] I'm sorry for saying
for you to grow up, because...
I know that you're just a kid,
and you deserve to be 25
and have fun and be stupid
and flippant and crazy
and blow it out, because,
before you know it,
you're gonna be 40.
And I love you for who you are.
- [tearful chuckle]
- And everything you aren't.
I'm sorry.
- Don't cry.
Ah, give me a hug.
Mmm.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry
I'm annoying sometimes.
- You're not, though.
You're not.
- I'm not sorry,
but I like you.
- [laughing] Shut up.
We really are sisters.
No matter how different we are,
as much as we probably
don't want to admit it,
we're a family.
[clapper snaps]
- Gorgeous.
- It's time to shoot our scenes
with RuPaul.
It's very exciting.
- Here we go.
First positions, please.
If you don't do it properly,
the dog's going to die.
- [laughs]
- Action.
[triumphant music]
When you hit your marks,
defiant.
- Not so fast, "Rude Paul."
- Yeah, get a load of us,
stupid-model of the world.
- Yeah, grandpa!
We're here to throw a wrench
in your plans.
Uhh!
[clang]
- Bitch, that wrench came
awful close to this face.
- [laughs]
Try not to hit RuPaul.
Action.
- You had no intention
of giving up your crown.
- You'd love to replace me,
wouldn't you?
Well, take a number
and stand in line!
- Uhh!
- And cut.
Slap her.
I didn't believe that
for a second.
[beep]
- Chad Michaels
is a little prissy.
- Ouch!
- But she takes direction well.
She's slapping you.
That's gotta hurt.
- Ohh! Oh!
Oh! Uhh...
Oh! Ooh!
- Beautiful!
- Uhh!
- I very much appreciate
Chad's efforts.
- Are you all right, darling?
- I love it.
- [laughing]
- Okay.
Which brings us along
to Sharon Needles.
- Uh-huh.
- Sell it to me.
- Whatever happened to,
"Everybody say love"?
[gasps]
[thud]
- Sharon, you should
probably go, "uhh," forward.
- Got it.
Whatever happened to,
"Everybody say love"?
[gasps]
Hyuh!
Ah! Ugh!
Agh!
- Everybody say love.
- Anyone who gets
the opportunity
to have RuPaul kick
the shit out of them
should consider themselves
a very lucky individual.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Yes, sir.
- It's your turn to shine.
- This is my last time that
I can really impress Ru,
so I don't want to mess this up.
I wanna win this.
- Action.
- And you, my pretty?
- RuPaul, what happened
to that innocent kid
from the Brewster projects
with the pair of heels
and--and a dream?
- And cut.
Can we ratchet that back
just a few notches?
It was a little Dorothy,
Wizard of Oz on crack.
- [chuckles] Okay.
What happened to that
supermodel of the world?
Ohh! Aah! Ohh!
[groaning]
- Good girl, Phi Phi.
Let's do it one more time.
On your marks...
get set...
action!
- Well, take a number
and stand in line.
- Ohh!
This competition, it's like
graduating high school
and going to Yale.
- Ohh!
- It's taken 18 years
to get here,
and it's validation
and redemption.
- I looked up to you.
- I've never worked on
something this hard
in my entire life.
There's just been ups and downs.
I've made enemies.
I've made best friends
for a lifetime.
I just feel like I could
conquer anything now.
Anything.
- Sashay.
- Oww!
- Shante!
- Ohh!
To be here and be able
to share my story
and grow as an entertainer,
I'm just super happy.
And I wouldn't trade that
for the world.
- May the best glamazon win!
- I am America's next drag
superstar.
- [laughing]
- My name is Chad Michaels,
and I'm America's next drag
superstar.
- [laughing]
- Oh, no, you didn't.
I am America's next drag
superstar.
- [laughing]
[coughing]
- And cut.
It's a wrap.
So thank you, ladies.
Great job.
- Thank you, ladies.
- And RuPaul will be available
for actual beatings later.
[laughter]
- Guys, it's the last day!
- I'm gonna miss this place.
- Me too.
- It's the big day.
It's the last day here.
And someone's gonna be
crowned today.
- One of us is going to be
America's next drag superstar.
- Isn't that insane?
- How do you feel you did
on your video?
- I feel good about it.
- Consistently throughout
this entire challenge,
I felt like I did really well,
with the dancing and everything.
- I found the dancing
challenging.
Structured choreography
is just hard on me.
- From day one till now,
starring in Ru's new video,
Glamazon,
this has been
the journey of a lifetime.
- So how do you think
it's gonna feel
to be on the main stage
for the last time?
- It's gonna feel amazing.
- I'm nervous.
- I'm nervous too.
- I worked so hard, and...
to be told I'm not gonna win,
it would just kill me.
- I'm, like, seriously shaking.
Ah!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- So who do you think
is lip-synching
for the win tonight, girls?
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Sharon Needles.
- Chad Michaels.
- One of you guys is correct.
[laughter]
- Only two will be lip-synching
for the crown.
And, oh, I hope
I'm one of them.
- [laughing]
- ♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what ♪
- Hey, guys!
- Hi.
- Hey, Ru.
- Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag race.
This evening is extra-special.
Because tonight,
it's just family.
Michelle Visage!
- Hot mama!
- [laughs]
- Our little girls have
all grown up.
- It makes me weep.
- Shake the dice
and steal the rice!
Hey, Santino.
- Whew! I want a taste
of that honey!
- Anytime, honey.
Now, are you ready to crown
a champion?
- He's crowning as we speak.
- [laughs]
- This week, our queens
were challenged
to star as rompin',
stompin' glamazons
in my new music video.
Tonight, they're ready to pummel
the runway one last time.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win!
- ♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
- Chad Michaels!
Wow.
- That's Donatella Michaels.
- Ver-sassy.
- My look is Versace-inspired,
but it's also a little bit of
Jane Fonda Barbarella.
It's a power costume.
- Who knew she was
a bondage queen?
- Ah.
- Strap it on, baby.
- Super hero.
Sharon Needles.
- Ah, oh, yes.
- I'm hungry for some calamari.
- Sharon Scissorhands.
- You're squiddin' me,
Michelle.
- I squid you not, girl.
- I am giving them straight up
Sharon Needles fierceness.
Fashion forward
to the dark side.
- I think she's opening a can
of worms, if you ask me.
- [laughs]
- Touch all of this octopussy,
honey.
[laughter]
Phi Phi O'Hara!
Ooh!
Leopard on the runway.
- Flintstones 2012.
- Yabba dabba do me.
- [laughs]
- I wanted to give that
Wilma Flintstone realness.
I'm feelin' sexy
and I'm showin' body.
I'm just having a great time.
- She's the side piece Fred was
knockin' boots with.
- [laughs]
Phi Phi Flintstone.
She's gonna make your bed rock.
Welcome, ladies.
My top three girls.
Let's begin by watching
the world television premiere
of your acting scene.
[thunder crashing]
[electronic blooping]
Now that I've perfected my super
size queen glamazon spray,
my sinister plan for world
domination is nearly complete!
[laughing]
Ohh.
- Not so fast, "Rude Paul"!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Get a load of us,
stupid-model of the world.
- Yeah, grandpa!
We're here to throw a wrench
in your plans!
Uhh!
- Nice try, ladies.
But you lose.
Again.
[clang]
- You promised to make me
a panther on the runway!
But all you did was lock me up
in that smelly old workroom.
You had no intention of
giving up your crown.
- You'd love to replace me,
wouldn't you?
Well, take a number
and stand in line.
- Uhh!
Ohh!
Uhh!
Oh! Agh! Uhh!
[whimpers]
- You love to make me hit you.
- [whimpers]
- All I ever wanted to do was
to be a female phenomenon.
I looked up to you.
We all looked up to you.
Whatever happened to,
"Everybody say love"?
- Love. Ah, yes.
I was in love once.
It was the worst 20 minutes
of my life.
- [gasps]
Hyuh! Ah!
Uhh! Hyuh!
Ohh!
[groans]
- Everybody say love.
And you, my pretty?
- RuPaul, what happened to that
innocent kid from
the Brewster projects
who became a shining example
for dreamers everywhere?
What happened to that supermodel
of the world?
- You're right.
I am that supermodel
of the world.
- Ohh! Aah!
Oww! Oww! Uhh! Ahh!
- Now...sashay...
- Ohh!
- Shante!
- Shante, shante, shante!
- Aah!
- My super size queen
glamazon spray
should take effect any moment.
First, you'll destroy the world.
Then you'll destroy each other.
[laughing]
May the best glamazon win.
[cackling]
[laughter]
- All right.
- Chad Michaels,
Phi Phi O'Hara,
Sharon Needles...
it's time for your performances
in the Glamazon video.
[upbeat music]
- [screaming]
- ♪ Oh, oh, she's a glamazon ♪
♪ Sashay, shante ♪
♪ Panther on the runway ♪
♪ Do it, do it, oh oh ♪
♪ All the girls say ♪
♪ Sashay, shante ♪
♪ Panther on the runway ♪
♪ Do it, do it, oh oh ♪
♪ All the boys say ♪
- She's so bloody tall.
- ♪ She's so wild ♪
♪ So animal ♪
♪ She's gonna work that ♪
♪ Sexy body, so sexual ♪
♪ She's like a female ♪
♪ Phenomenon ♪
♪ She's a glamazon ♪
♪ Female phenomenon ♪
♪ Glamazon, ah ah ah ♪
[laughter]
- Wow, beautiful.
- The one thing I can count on
Chad doing well is,
you do this thing where
everything has a flourish.
- It's all this, girl.
- Yes! Oh, my god!
I could watch you do that
forever!
- It's old-school.
- Don't ever stop doing that.
- I don't think I can,
'cause it's, like,
one of three tricks
that I have.
[laughter]
- Old-school or not,
it's really refreshing
to watch you.
- Oh! Ohh!
- You played well with Ru.
I thought you were
very convincing.
It was funny, and I actually
wish some of that
lightheartedness
and your sense of humor
would have been
in your monster stomping.
- Next up, Sharon Needles.
- I'm so glad that you came out
tonight
for the finale in your
California natural look.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, this is succubus
ready to wear.
- I love your stomping monster.
Very campy.
- But the choreography
and the dancing,
it was a little rough.
It looked a little shaky
in parts.
- When dancing
isn't your thing,
you can either own it,
or you can really fail.
You gotta be ready for
any challenge, you know?
- All right, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- I'll start with your
runway look tonight,
because I love it.
- Oh, thank you.
- Your stomping, that was
probably
your weakest thing,
'cause it looked more like
you were doing a runway.
I just got like, "I'm cute,
I'm fierce, let me walk."
- But I think your dance moves
were very tight and on beat.
Your range of energy was really
unbelievable in that video.
- Thank you, Phi Phi.
While you
and the other girls untuck
in the Interior Illusions
lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, just between us
"goils," what do you think?
- Oh, Ru.
- This is it, and they all
represent
three different
factions of drag.
Phi Phi is the ingénue newcomer.
Chad, the professional diva.
And Sharon Needles,
the little monster.
They could all represent this
competition so brilliantly.
- This is a tough one, baby.
- Let's start with
Sharon Needles.
- Sharon needles was
an underdog.
She came out here looking like
Nosferatu on the first show.
- She won that challenge.
- I know she did,
because she did it fiercely.
- Sharon always came out here,
week after week,
with something
conceptual and creative.
And I think that sometimes
people are scared of things
that are unconventional.
- I like the goth,
but I feel like,
"Do you have to do it
all the time?"
I don't know if the entire world
is ready
for somebody to win
this competition
like a Sharon Needles.
- Well, listen,
Lady Gaga's done it.
- Sharon's even beyond
Lady Gaga, I think.
- All right, kids.
Chad Michaels.
- There is nobody more
qualified than Chad Michaels.
The bitch is a professional.
Her representing your show
would be executed perfectly.
- It's great that Chad probably
had those
Versace dresses
in her closet from
the early '90s.
- Yes, a little old-school,
but Chad grew up in a different
time period
where drag was
what Chad does.
- It's not so much
the age thing,
'cause Chad is ageless.
- Age ain't nothin'.
- It's about
evolving constantly
and looking at what's next
and what's new.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
At one point,
I thought she was too green,
but, boy, has she grown,
faster than any other competitor
we have ever seen.
- And what she lacks
in experience,
she makes up for with drive.
- If you remember,
she's gotten some heat
for being too ambitious.
Do you think that's a bad thing?
- No, it probably is what's
driving her creativity.
You know, you see it in the way
that she's evolved.
- And I feel like with Phi Phi,
she's the new
generation of drag.
- Silence!
This ain't over...
till they lip-synch
for their lives.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
The moment of truth is upon us.
Based on your performance
in the Glamazon music video
and your body of work
throughout this competition,
I've made some decisions.
Chad Michaels...
you are a seasoned queen.
But do you represent
the future of drag?
Phi Phi O'Hara,
my beautiful queen...
in this competition, no one
has ever grown so fast.
But are you fully prepared
for the responsibilities
that come with the crown?
Sharon Needles, you are
as charming as you are scary.
And you shake drag to its core.
But do you have the right stuff
to be America's next drag
superstar?
For the first time
in Drag Race history,
we are breaking
all the rules.
- What?
- Chad, Sharon, Phi Phi.
The three of you
will lip-synch for your lives.
Three queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and prove to the world
that you are America's
next drag superstar.
- This is everything
I've worked for,
all coming to
a head in one moment,
and I'm gonna give it
all I've got.
- The time has come...
for you to lip-synch
for your life.
- It's just a tornado
of emotions.
But I've never been afraid
of an audience,
and I'm not gonna
start now.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Everybody wants her ♪
♪ Miss sexy in the city ♪
♪ She's on the prowl ♪
♪ She rocked this town ♪
♪ Who's that girl ♪
♪ A fly, ferocious lady ♪
♪ Get up and dance ♪
♪ Get up, get up and ♪
♪ Sashay, shante ♪
♪ Panther on the runway ♪
- I am giving them
a little bit of spook,
a little bit of laugh,
and a whole lot of diva action.
- ♪ She's so wild, so animal ♪
- I want to show the judges
that I'm a true entertainer.
I am America's next
drag superstar.
- ♪ Glamazon, ah ah ah ♪
♪ Ladyboys and girls ♪
♪ And those who dream ♪
♪ To rule the world ♪
♪ Smoky eyes, cherry lips ♪
♪ Stilettos on ♪
♪ Now break it down ♪
♪ Oh oh, oh ho ♪
♪ Oh oh, she's a glamazon ♪
♪ Get up there ♪
♪ Sashay, shante ♪
- This is my time
in the spotlight.
I'm feeling pretty powerful
right now.
- ♪ All the boys say ♪
- She's so bloody tall.
- ♪ She's so wild ♪
♪ So animal ♪
♪ She's gonna work that ♪
♪ Sexy body, so sexual ♪
♪ She's like a female ♪
♪ Phenomenon ♪
♪ She's a glamazon ♪
♪ Female phenomenon ♪
♪ Glamazon, ah ah ah ♪
- Hoo hoo!
[cheers and applause]
[laughing]
- I love you bitches.
- Love you too.
- Brava! Brava!
Ladies...
I've made my decision.
- Chad Michaels...
Phi Phi O'Hara...
Sharon Needles...
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race...
America's next drag superstar...
is...
Going to be announced
next week...
On RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited.
- Is this a joke?
- RuPaul, you crafty
little witch.
- And I want to hear from you,
the viewers.
Who should be America's next
drag superstar?
Should it be Chad Michaels?
Sharon Needles?
Or Phi Phi O'Hara?
Let your voice be heard.
Tweet your thoughts to
#dragrace.
Ladies, I'll see you and your
drag sisters next week,
where, together,
we will celebrate our new queen.
- No matter what, I'm still
gonna win that crown.
- This is uncharted territory.
This has never been done.
I don't know
what's gonna happen.
- Any one of us deserve
that crown.
Maybe me a little more.
- Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen!
- All right,
now let the music play.
- ♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ Of the record you like ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ G-g-get it, get it right ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ This is the beginning of ♪
♪ The rest of your life ♪