- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race....
You'll be launching
your very own dragazine.
- Sex sells, people, sex sells.
- Ha ha.
I'm a successful drag queen.
I'm not like some club queen
who has to show for a dollar.
- You have to spot me.
- That looks like a man.
I look like Sharon in that one.
- Ouch.
- Your dragazine cover
is possibly the worst one.
I hate the font.
- Me too.
- The eyes scare me.
- They're my trademark.
- It creeps me out.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
- [laughs]
Ah, finally!
- Willam, shante, you stay.
Jiggly Caliente--
may I call you Jiggly?
- Yes.
- Sashay away.
And tonight, you'll be competing
as a couple...
of frenemies.
The jig is up.
If Phi Phi O'Hara was the last
ladyboy on earth,
would you kai kai with her?
And a shocking twist...
- [vomiting]
- It's really not cute.
- With extra-special
guest judges
Pamela Anderson
and Jennifer Tilly.
[cheers and applause]
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics,
a one-of-a-kind trip
courtesy of alandchuck.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring Absolut vodka--
cocktails perfected--
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And may the best woman win.
[tires squealing]
- ♪ Jesus is a biscuit ♪
- ♪ That'll stop you up ♪
- ♪ Hey ♪
Walking in today
to Jiggly being gone
is obviously mind-boggling,
'cause there's only
six people left.
- [singing]
- Yo, that's a lot of lipstick.
- "To my bitches, love you all
to death, Jiggly Caliente."
At least the lipstick's
on the mirror
and not on her teeth for once.
Bye, girl, bye.
That was my first time
in the bottom two.
I wasn't happy to be up there,
and I know I was trying
to be pretty at least.
- Did it humble you?
- It didn't add
any humility to me.
- Humble pie is what
Willam should be.
If it was anybody else
other than Jiggly,
she would have went home
last night.
- Girl, you were so pissy
and fussy up there, girl.
Ooh!
- Any way to keep
my dress moving
and to keep me
sparkling a little bit.
- Mew mew doesn't make
talent, honey.
- My last performance
wasn't my best,
but it was enough
to keep me here.
- You girls told me to take
those damn white contacts
out of my eyes before Runway,
and I didn't.
I said I wanted 'em.
They looked pretty.
And they totally got me.
So now I have to, like, serve up
some girly-girl nonsense.
- Like, can you leave your
gothic and your vampire,
like, that type of look aside,
and just do, like,
glamorous, pretty?
- But I think I am glamorous.
Can I do a lemming look?
Sure, I can throw myself
off of a cliff with you,
but I don't want to.
I am no longer justifying
my personal beauty
to these girls.
No one remembers the girl with
the tan skin and the blond hair.
They remember the girl coughing
up blood with white eyes.
- What I read in my makeup
and everything,
I want the judges to know
that I am listening
and I want to be here--
- You did a great job.
- And I want to take
all their critiques in.
- Like, standing next to you
when you won,
you, like, kind of
threw your head back
and I saw, like,
the square sideburn.
- Oh, picking straws, dude.
- Hold on, I'm still
complimenting you
in your appearance
that was like--
- That's, like,
a backhanded compliment.
I'm tired of her
and I want her to go home.
I thought it looked gorgeous,
and if I can rock a sideburns
and win a challenge,
then I'm gonna rock a sideburn
and win a challenge.
They liked it.
- Everybody want Willam
to go home.
She is completely annoying.
- Well, congratulations, whore.
- Yeah.
- Phi Phi.
- Two challenges ago,
I was in the bottom three,
and now I'm in the top.
- So, Phi Phi,
what took you so long?
[alarm wails]
- Ooh!
- Girl, you've got shemail.
You know, there are two things
I don't like about you.
What?
Your face.
[gasps]
Ladies, keep your friends close
and you frenemies even closer,
'cause in this competition,
even the mirror has two faces.
Yeah, and one of 'em is
cracked.
Shut up!
Oh, you shut up!
I'm not listening to you.
La la la la la la la.
Bitch, I'll be waiting for
your ass in the parking lot.
Bitch.
[laughter]
Hello, hello, hello.
- Hi, Ru!
- RuPaul!
- Ladies, in a competition,
people can say one thing
to your face
and then talk smack
behind your back.
Sometimes it's hard to know
who your real friends are.
For today's mini challenge,
I'm not looking
for a winner or a loser.
I'm looking for the truth,
and you can't handle
the truth, girl.
One by one,
you'll be hooked
to a lie detector,
a little lady go by the name
of "Polly Graph."
Know her?
I thought you did.
- I'm worried she's gonna ask me
some questions
I don't want to answer.
- Time to spill it, girls.
[laughter]
Welcome, darling.
Now, I'm going to ask you
a series of questions.
You answer each
with a simple yes or a no.
Is that clear?
- Yes.
- John, are you all set?
- I am.
- Are you now
or have you ever been
a biological woman?
- No.
- Have you ever worn
women's clothing?
- Yes.
- Do you sleep in the nude?
- No.
- Just as I suspected.
- If Sharon Needles were
the last ladyboy on earth,
would you kai kai with her?
- No.
- If Phi Phi O'Hara was
the last ladyboy on earth,
would you kai kai with her?
- Yes.
- If Willam were the last
ladyboy on earth,
would you kai kai with her?
- No.
- If Latrice were the last
ladyboy on earth,
would you kai kai with her?
- Yes.
- Interesting.
[beeping]
Do you think Willam
is prettier than you?
- Yes.
- No.
- Have you ever talked shade
behind Chad Michaels' back?
- No.
- Do you think you could win
a lip-sync for your life
against Sharon Needles?
- Yes.
- Have you ever lied
about your age?
- Yes.
- Fascinating.
- Do you think Willam
is annoying?
- Yes.
- Have you ever
looked at the pit crew
with lust in your heart?
- No.
- Yes.
- Do you like my line
of iron fist shoes?
- Yes.
- Last question:
Are you the future of drag?
- Yes.
- Your questioning is over.
I will supply the FBI with
a copy of your transcripts.
Ladies, the results are in.
In addition to the truth,
your answers revealed to me
a lot about your different
personality types.
Now, I've arranged you
in two lines.
Look at the queen directly
across from you.
That's the person you have
the least in common with,
someone you might not even
like very much,
but that queen possesses skills
and traits you don't have,
and in a crisis,
she could save your ass.
That means, Dida Ritz, you're
paired with Chad Michaels.
Willam, you're paired
with Latrice Royale.
- Oh, evil.
- Phi Phi O'Hara, you're paired
with Sharon Needles.
- Party City.
- Busted showgirl.
- For this week's
main challenge,
you need to put together
a nightclub act
sponsored by NYX cosmetics,
and you'll be competing
as a couple...
of frenemies.
Now, each pair will create
costumes, choreography,
and specialty lyrics
to the original song,
Better Than You.
Oh, and tomorrow
on the main stage,
you'll be singing it live...
- What?
[laughs] What?
- No lip-syncing.
- I don't sing live, boo-boo.
There's a reason
why I lip-sync.
- In the tradition
of famous frenemies
like Joan Crawford
and Bette Davis.
Time to make nice,
girls, or just fake it,
you know,
like I'm always doing.
[laughter]
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
See ya.
[laughs]
- Bye, Ru.
- Bye.
- O-m-g.
- Have you listened to it yet?
- No.
- It seems like the mindset
amongst the queens is that
you're only as good
as your last performance,
but I'm a singer,
I have a band,
and I plan to win
this challenge,
and I want to prove that I'm
not just some lip-syncing queen.
I think it's kind of
natural too,
because my voice is probably
an octave higher
than yours,
so it'll sound good.
♪ At least my dresses ♪
♪ Don't make 'em blind ♪
♪ I do ♪
- [laughs]
Okay.
- Why don't we do,
like, the elphaba--
like, a Wicked thing.
- Ooh, I like devil and angel.
It's better,
and it's how people see us.
- I'm not sure how Phi Phi and
Sharon are gonna work together.
They're the most opposite,
and they've also had
a little tiff.
Should we rewind that back?
- Tired-ass showgirl.
Fuck you.
- "Tired-ass showgirl"?
At least I am a showgirl, bitch!
Go back to Party City,
where you belong!
- If the chemistry's not there,
then it shows through on stage.
- Okay.
- We can play off that
showgirl/Party City thing.
- We can just write
Party City/busted showgirl,
as who you are.
[laughs]
Busted showgirl,
which I'm sure you don't want
to say about yourself.
- The only thing I'm really
nervous about
on this challenge is,
I can't stand Sharon,
and that probably won't change.
- Do you want to call me
post-mortem glam
or Party City spook?
- I think
Party City spook is good,
'cause I don't want
to call you glamorous.
- I wouldn't consider
Phi Phi a frenemy.
I'd consider her an enemy.
- And that's it.
♪ I wear heels ♪
♪ That heighten the mood ♪
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much ♪
- ♪ I do it much better ♪
♪ Than you ♪
Shit.
- This challenge is so tough
because we basically have
to create a nightclub act,
and we're singing it live.
♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much ♪
- Neither Dida nor myself sing,
and it was hard.
both: ♪ I do ♪
- We sound like two sick cats.
both: ♪ I do it
so much better than you ♪
- I've been waiting
for this challenge,
because I love to sing, I've
been singing since I was little,
so we'll see how this goes.
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
♪ But I do it
so much better ♪
- Hot mess.
Oh, my God. What?
both: ♪ So much better
than you ♪
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hi, Ru.
- Chad Michaels and Dida Ritz.
So what's your plan?
- Well, our plan
is a classic sister act,
truly reading each other down
the Runway.
- Listen, there are
two other teams,
and you've got to have something
that's gonna stand out.
Dida, what do you think that
Chad has that you don't have?
- I have a bit more
of a kind of younger,
around the way
type of look with my drag.
- Chad, what about you?
What do you think that Dida has
that you don't?
- She's not afraid to,
you know,
fall on her face or to fail.
- I want to be surprised.
I want to be entertained.
Trust me,
they're coming for you.
- Thanks, RuPaul.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Sharon Needles,
Phi Phi O'Hara, how's it going?
- I've been working
with my frenemy.
I guess it's going okay.
- Why do you think you two
were paired up?
- We kind of hate each other.
- Really?
A lot of co-stars don't
particularly like each other,
but somehow it creates
a sort of chemistry on-screen
that actually works.
Are either of you singers?
- I am.
- Yeah, we both
are kind of singers.
- Wow. All right, so do
a little preview act for me.
Okay. Ready?
- All right, so,
you want to do--
do you want to put our
choreography with it as well?
- Let's sing it right now.
- Okay, okay,
we'll just sing it,
'cause choreography,
we're working on real hard.
- Okay.
- I'm white, girl.
- Oh, dear.
- Ready? Here we go.
- Uh-huh.
- ♪ My heels ♪
♪ Always heighten the mood ♪
- [off-key shouting]
♪ My balloons have attitude ♪
- ♪ People never think ♪
♪ I'm a dude ♪
- [off-key shouting]
♪ You're right ♪
- Wow, was that harmony there?
There's a lot of stuff
going on there.
- Sharon really wants to do
this, like, heavy metal voice,
and I'm like,
oh, hell no.
- I'm gonna let you
get back to work.
- Okay, thank you.
- Good, can't wait to show you.
I know I'm gonna do a good job.
Sharon better not fuck it up,
'cause I'm gonna be pissed.
- Willam and Latrice.
- Hello.
- Do either of you sing
in your acts?
- I regularly do.
Most of my act
is with a live band.
- Now, Latrice,
what do you think Willam has
that you don't have?
- When I first met
little Willam,
I was not featuring
her at all, right?
She was not the feature
presentation.
But I'm a quiet confident, where
she's very vocal about it.
- What does Latrice have
that you don't have?
- I would love to have
some of that quiet confidence
instead of my confidence
that some people mistake
for cockiness.
- I'm gonna help ground
Willam a little bit more.
We're gonna calm her down.
Pss-pss, pss-pss.
- Yeah.
- Let your work
speak for itself.
- So what is the gimmick
for your outfits?
- We're gonna be pretty in pink.
[laughs]
- Oh, pretty in pink.
Is that enough of a gimmick?
- Oh, I'm gonna turn her out.
- Oh, yeah?
- Basically,
she's gonna be a whore.
- You kids have your work
cut out for you.
I'm gonna let you
get back to it.
- Okeydoke.
- All right, wonderful.
- Fuck it, let's just do what
we want to do and do it well.
- [groans]
- All right, ladies,
gather around.
Later today, you'll have
a chance to work on your acts
with the composer
of Better Than You,
my songwriting partner
and producer Lucian Piane.
- Very cool.
- And tomorrow
on the main stage,
you'll be making your
NYX cosmetics nightclub debut
in front of our
extra-special guest judges,
the wonderful actress and
poker champion Jennifer Tilly.
- [gasps]
- Wow!
- I love Jennifer Tilly!
- Academy award nominee
Jennifer Tilly.
It doesn't get better than that.
- And the always fabulous
Pamela Anderson will be here.
- Shut up!
[laughter]
- Honey, I grew up watching
Pamela Anderson.
She's sickening.
She's the blond bombshell.
- And you'll be judged
as a team.
That means one pair
will be the winner
and one pair will have
to lip-sync for their lives.
- Why?
RuPaul, why are you
doing this to us?
- All right, frenemies.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- Thanks, Ru.
- Bye, Ru.
- This is crazy.
The first time in history
we all have to lip-sync
against each other.
Like, that could be
an emotional lip-sync.
What do you guys think
about, like,
having to lip-sync against
your teammate?
- Uh, well, that's a wrench
in the program, but--
- I'm not making plans to do it.
- [laughs]
- If Willam and Latrice
get in the bottom together,
bye, Willam.
- Honey, 'cause Latrice
know how to buck.
- Girl, Latrice
is gonna wear her out.
- Phi Phi's rolling her eyes
and talking about me,
and everybody's
saying I suck,
but they can fuck themselves.
I mean, Phi Phi--
I feel like in her eyes
I'm only as good
as my last performance,
and she thinks I'm just,
like, worthless now.
- Well, what was her
last performance?
- She's never done anything.
- No.
- Her's seems to be
a lot of the,
"Up here, dumb character!"
Voice, voice voice!
That's all I'm seeing
right now.
- Our accessories
sell our dresses.
You know, we'll have halos
and devil horns, devil tail.
- Yeah. It just has to look
really showgirl-y.
- You know, Phi Phi just wants
things so "perfect."
And then they'll say,
"Ooh, your tutu's legs."
- The only thing with
a minidress I'm scared about
is that it's gonna rise up.
- Well, we don't do anything
upside down.
- I'm not gonna go on-stage
and get read
for having my panties show.
Like, that's why.
Sharon's look is never polished.
I just don't feel like her drag
should be even critiqued
side-by-side with mine.
This is stressing me out.
- Hi, I'm Willam.
- Latrice.
How are you?
- Hi, nice to meet you.
I'm Lucian.
- Lucian is RuPaul's producer.
Like, he's the man
behind the magic.
- So are you guys ready
to perform for me,
and then we'll
take it from there?
- Sure.
- We'll come out to here,
do the first lines.
We'll move on to the whole show,
and then on the,
"I'm so much better than,"
we'll start walking.
- Oh, I thought--
- You walk in with me.
What, what?
- Yeah, I thought we were gonna
do our lines as we walk.
- Oh, okay, that's even--
- 'Cause that--yeah.
- That's fine.
- I think that's better.
- Okay.
- Are you guys ready?
- We're ready.
- Cue playback.
- ♪ I'm Latrice ♪
♪ And I'm the whole show ♪
- ♪ Um, it's a competition ♪
♪ I thought you'd know ♪
- ♪ I'm legendary ♪
- ♪ Makeup abuser ♪
- All right, make sure you say,
"I'm a legendary," and then--
- I'm a legendary.
- Yeah, just make it clear
that you're being interrupted.
- Okay, got you.
- ♪ I'm a legendary ♪
- Wait.
- ♪ Makeup abuser ♪
♪ But I'm the best at being ♪
- ♪ No, you're a loser ♪
- ♪ So ♪
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
♪ Than ♪
It's every man for themselves.
If Latrice misses a line,
I'm gonna steamroll through it
with my next line.
♪ I do it so much ♪
- ♪ I do it so much ♪
both: ♪ Better than ♪
♪ Than you ♪
- To be late is to be left.
- Boom.
Yeah.
- I would just say, like,
the more, like, vindictive
you can be with each other--
- Oh, well,
we've got that going.
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so ♪
both: ♪ Much better ♪
♪ Than you ♪
- Yeah, you almost had it.
I don't know what happened
right there.
- Can we do it again
from the top, please?
- Willam is scrambling,
and she's not in
the right head space.
If either one of us screws up,
we're both screwed.
- Do you have any notes for us,
like, other than--
- Yeah, you guys just have
to practice and practice.
- Thanks.
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ Much better ♪
- ♪ So--better than-- ♪
I know that, in his head,
Lucian is reading.
He's like, these bitches are
fucking my song up right now.
♪ Better than you ♪
- A little rough
on some of the cues there.
If you don't get
the lines across
and you guys are just doing
physical comedy,
it'll be like, why did she
fall down on the stage?
Or why did this happen?
Really concentrate on the lyrics
and getting those down,
and then, like, have fun.
- There's a certain level
of expectation for me
because I've been in
the business for 20 years.
I don't want to look like an
idiot in front of America.
- Cue playback.
- ♪ Cheesecake, fake it ♪
♪ Please don't break it ♪
- ♪ I'm a legendary ♪
- Wait.
Ready?
- ♪ I'm a legendary ♪
- ♪ Makeup abuser ♪
- Chad and Dida seemed
a little less prepared.
They struggled a little bit
with the timing of the lyrics.
- ♪ A loser ♪
- Okay, okay.
In a performance like this,
you guys have really
got to, like, step it up.
- The stress point of
the rehearsal was vocalization.
You throw the choreography
in there with it,
it's getting a little hairy.
♪ Than you ♪
- ♪ Than you ♪
- We have a little work
to do here.
- ♪ I wear heels ♪
♪ That heighten the mood ♪
- ♪ My balloons ♪
♪ Have attitude ♪
- ♪ I'm a legendary ♪
- ♪ Makeup abuser ♪
♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- Yeah, we need a little work.
Um, uh, I'm a--
I guess I'm a little confused
by the opera stuff.
- 'Cause I'm an angel,
and I want to do, like,
a Disney character type of look.
- And I'm a devil.
I'm supposed to scream one of
my, "I do it so much better."
- Okay.
- Like...
I do it so much better!
- Yeah, we'll see.
- And then back to our normal.
- Oh, okay. Okay.
But why don't we Run it again,
and you--you guys--
- Could we just sing--
just do it normal
with no gimmicks
or anything right now?
- ♪ I wear heels ♪
♪ That heighten the mood ♪
- ♪ My balloons ♪
♪ Have an attitude ♪
both: ♪ I do it ♪
♪ So much better than you ♪
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much ♪
- Okay, okay.
I feel like you guys
are just trying to sing this
a little too much.
The vocals are upstaging
the lyrics.
You don't have to do the vocal
stuff a little bit.
- Don't Christina it out.
♪ Whoa-oh-oh-oh ♪
- Bitch, shut up.
That's fine.
We'll talk it.
- Let's just, like, go,
uh, through the end part.
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much ♪
- ♪ I do it so much
better than ♪
- Fucking shit!
- Let's try that again.
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much ♪
- [groans]
Fucking shit!
Sharon has no rhythm,
and if our rhythm is off,
then the music's off,
and then our beats are off,
and then it's just
all gonna be off,
and I'm not gonna be
in the bottom two
because Sharon is off.
- It doesn't even
fully seem like
you're totally present
right now.
I don't even know what that is.
- There'll always be tension
between me and Phi Phi.
She's that squeaky princess
that just needs to be
whapped over the head
with a two-by-four.
- You guys have to bring
your A game.
- Down the rabbit hole, darling.
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
♪ Than you ♪
- No, you don't.
- It is showtime,
ladies and gentlemen!
We have to perform duets.
Not lip-syncing.
Not recorded in a studio.
Live, bitches.
- Do you notice that Willam
is low energy today?
- She seems really quiet, girl.
- Usually Willam
has these one-liners
that she just shoots out
and throws,
but she's not speaking
to anyone and...
she just doesn't
seem like herself.
- How are you feeling today?
You all right?
- What?
- You know, you feelin' okay?
- Um, yeah.
It has nothing to do with this.
- Nothin'?
I'm a little worried because
we're being judged as a couple.
This definitely could
affect our performance.
I think you seem really
distracted today.
- No, I'm not.
I'm fine.
Once--once the red light's on,
I'm there.
- Okay, all right.
- Don't worry.
- [clears throat]
- ♪ Let's state facts,
you're orange, not tan ♪
- Wait, what?
♪ This coming from
Miss Marilyn Manson ♪
- ♪ Well, I'd rather be pale
than have a tan in a can ♪
both: ♪ I do it so much better
than you ♪
- [laughs]
- I'm glad I wore double
deodorant today.
I'm just gonna
ham it up onstage.
When Ru says, "You guys are
the winner of this challenge"--
- I'll like you permanently
if we win this together.
- Yeah, we fumbled yesterday
on the Runway,
but we understand that this
is an important challenge,
so put all differences aside.
Let's win this challenge.
Oh, my god,
you're a showgirl now.
- Oh, my--
- You're like me!
- Phi Phi and Sharon,
surprisingly, are getting along.
Is this for real?
- Sharon is a showgirl!
- I'm just temporarily playing
the role of a Phi Phi.
I'm getting to like Phi Phi
a little more,
but now it's just
upgraded to hate.
[clatter]
- Who is slamming the fucking
counter while I'm doing liquid?
- Girl, the counter moves.
- No, someone just slammed
something shut twice.
- Well, everyone tiptoe
around Willam's liquid.
- Shut the fuck up.
- ♪ La la la la la la la ♪
♪ Latrice ♪
- ♪ Trice ♪
- ♪ La la la la la la la ♪
♪ Latrice ♪
- I miss my drag family
now so bad.
I work with
some of the weirdest,
most interesting performers,
I think, in America.
If we're not freaking 'em out,
we're not working it out.
That is just the name of the
game in the house of haunt.
- If we go too long without
seeing and talking
with each other,
we have a potluck dinner
at my house and everybody
comes over for drinks.
- I want to come over
to dinner at your house.
- Me too, bitch.
- Absolutely.
'Cause we cook
the house down, honey.
- I always thought
I was so fucking interesting
before I came here but, like,
your guys' lives sound
like so much more fun.
I haven't come
from a drag family
because I didn't come up
through the club system
like most people have.
I've been on TV most of my life
for the past ten years.
I am a little weak in the friend
department because of it.
- I can't believe
you don't have,
like, a strong drag family.
- No.
- I need them.
- I couldn't live without them.
- [laughs]
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, baby.
- Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
It's my evil twin,
Michelle Visage.
- Yes, and a big
domo arigato to you.
- [laughs]
Lucian Piane,
my partner in crime.
- Hey, it's so good to see you.
- How are my girls?
- They're really amazing.
- Did you sleep
with any of them?
- Two of them.
- [laughs]
Jennifer Tilly.
You're looking
beautiful tonight.
- Well, thank you.
The monkey glands are working.
- [laughs]
And Pamela Anderson.
Hey, soul sister.
- I finally made it.
Thanks for having me.
You look gorgeous.
- This old thing.
- [laughs]
- This week,
the queens were challenged
to perform a duet
with their best frenemies.
Tonight, on the main stage,
they're gonna make their
live nightclub debut.
Are you ready
for some double trouble?
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
First up, Latrice and Willam.
- ♪ I'm Latrice ♪
♪ And I'm the whole show ♪
- ♪ Uh-uh,
it's a competition ♪
♪ I thought you'd know ♪
- ♪ Well, at least
my mustache don't show ♪
both: ♪ I do it so much ♪
♪ Better than you ♪
- ♪ Excuse me, sir ♪
- ♪ Uh-huh ♪
I feel good vibes
coming from this.
both: ♪ I do ♪
- Willam is in it to win it.
I'm in it to win it.
Let's do this damn thing.
♪ Your lip-sync ♪
♪ Is always behind ♪
- [laughs]
- ♪ At least my dresses ♪
♪ Don't make them blind ♪
both: ♪ I do it so much ♪
♪ Better than you ♪
- ♪ Ooh ♪
[laughter]
- ♪ I'm a legendary ♪
- ♪ Makeup abuser ♪
♪ I'm the best ♪
- Oh!
- ♪ At being a loser ♪
- [laughs]
- All the jokes land,
but any chance to be onstage
is a chance to shine.
♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- Whoo!
- ♪ I do it so much ♪
both: ♪ Better than ♪
♪ Than you ♪
- [laughs]
both: ♪ So much better ♪
♪ Than you ♪
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Phi Phi O'Hara
and Sharon Needles.
- ♪ I wear heels ♪
♪ That heighten the mood ♪
- ♪ My balloons have attitude ♪
- ♪ People never think ♪
♪ That I'm a dude ♪
- ♪ Yeah, right ♪
both: ♪ I do it so much ♪
♪ Better than you ♪
- ♪ You little devil, you ♪
- ♪ I do ♪
♪ Let's state facts ♪
♪ You're orange, not tan ♪
- ♪ This coming from ♪
♪ Miss Marilyn Manson? ♪
- ♪ Well, I'd rather be pale ♪
♪ Than have a tan in a can ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
both: ♪ I do it so much ♪
♪ Better than you ♪
- I think she added
a teaspoon or two
of Christina "Agliera,"
but that's another matter.
- ♪ I'm a legendary ♪
- ♪ Makeup abuser ♪
♪ I'm the best at ♪
- ♪ Being a loser ♪
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
both: ♪ I do it so much ♪
♪ Better than ♪
♪ Than you ♪
- I could tell that the judges
looked a little bored.
I'm going to be so pissed if
this cheesy song and dance
number sends me out of here.
both: ♪ So much better ♪
♪ Than you ♪
- Whoo!
- Chad Michaels, Dida Ritz.
- Hello, Dida, darling.
- Hello, Chad.
How are you?
- I'm a legend.
- Well, that's debatable.
- I never.
- ♪ I wear heels ♪
♪ That heighten the mood ♪
- ♪ My balloons have attitude ♪
- ♪ People never think ♪
♪ That I'm a dude ♪
I could hear my voice
kind of shaking a little bit.
RuPaul is right in front of you.
Don't fuck it up!
- ♪ When I do Cher ♪
♪ You can't take it ♪
- ♪ With all this cheesecake ♪
♪ I can't fake it ♪
- ♪ Cheesecake, fake it ♪
♪ Please don't break it ♪
- [gasps]
both: ♪ I do it so much ♪
♪ Better than you ♪
- But at least my face moves
when I frown.
♪ I'm a legendary ♪
- ♪ Makeup abuser ♪
- Oh! Skag!
- ♪ I'm the best ♪
- ♪ At being the loser ♪
- Oh!
♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much better ♪
- ♪ I do it so much ♪
- ♪ I do it so ♪
both: ♪ I do it so much ♪
♪ Better than ♪
♪ Than you ♪
- ♪ So much ♪
- ♪ Better than you ♪
- Oh!
Dida, you bitch! Oh!
[laughter]
- Thank you.
- Welcome, ladies.
This week, we asked you
to combine your strengths
and weaknesses to create
one dynamic duo,
so tonight,
you'll be judged as a couple.
First up, Willam
and Latrice Royale.
Tell us about your performance.
- She has definitely gotten me
out of my comfort zone
a little bit.
[laughter]
This is not exactly what
I would do normally,
but absolutely loving
that I'm showcasing
the curves and swerves
I represent for the big girls.
- [laughs]
Do you feel that this outfit
compromises your Christianity?
- Jesus is a biscuit,
and I let him sop me up, so--
- Yes!
[laughter]
- You guys look amazing.
I love the lingerie,
the stockings.
Your shoes are killer.
- Oh, they're Versace.
- And that pratfall.
I'm using that trick.
That was some Vegas shit.
- But sometimes too much shtick
can get in the way.
- You two were sort of
like a Laurel and Hardy
or a Jane Russell/Marilyn Monroe
sort of combination.
You're really different,
but you worked so well together
and I really enjoyed it.
- Thank you, ladies.
- I just have to say one thing.
- What's that?
- America's Got Talent
has nothing on this show.
- Uh, hear, hear.
- This is a great show,
and there's so much talent
on the stage,
it's fun to see.
- Thanks, Pamela.
- Next up, Chad Michaels
and Dida Ritz.
- Hi, Ru.
- Hi.
- So, Dida, who did it better?
- Uh...
- Just say it, bitch.
- I will say me.
- That's right.
[laughter]
- What about you, Chad?
- Of course, darling, it was me.
[laughter]
- Sorry.
- I was getting a cavity,
listening to you two.
[laughter]
It was so Roxie and Velma.
It was very Chicago,
which I love.
- Well, I feel a little
like Paula Abdul,
'cause I loved everything.
[laughter]
- Dida, sometimes when you get
really, really excited
and you're singing
and you have so much energy,
you kind of lose
a little bit of the vocals.
- I think the jokes may have
fallen a little flat
because you couldn't hear
what you were saying.
- Next up, Sharon Needles
and Phi Phi O'Hara.
How did it feel up there?
- Me and Phi Phi have had
some bad blood here.
I've always found it
kind of hard to be accepted
by glamorous pageant-y queens,
and I took a little bit
of that mindset
into this competition.
- Calling her a pageant queen,
is that a read?
- Sharon, you could learn
something from pageant queens.
You're not losing Sharon Needles
in this glam look.
- I love this hair.
- It's gorgeous on you.
- I should have
done this a long--
this is some country crock hair.
- I think you guys were great,
and you look a little Janice
Dickinson and you're me.
- That's what I was channeling.
- I loved it.
- When you came down
to the bottom of the stage,
I loved that you were
trying the harmonies,
but they're a little bit off.
- I do feel like the comedy
was underplayed.
I think you guys
should have been funnier.
- Y'all were almost too nice.
It's a frenemies type of thing.
You know, it's kind of like, uh,
you're cutting on each other.
It was hard to even hear
if there was any shade in there.
- Thank you, ladies.
While you untuck in
the Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
Just between us girls...
- [sighs]
- What do you think?
Willam and Latrice Royale.
- Latrice stepped out
of her comfort zone,
and it looked great.
Vocally, I thought Willam
could really sing.
I did love their shtick
that they did,
but it kind of
took over the song.
- A little less might have been
a little bit more in this case.
- Well, I thought that their act
was very polished.
I really liked the choreography.
I thought it was very smooth
and it was very worked out.
- Now, would you have them open
for you in Vegas?
- Yes!
Especially with that little--
that thing at the end,
when they threw the purse
and she tripped or whatever.
- Yeah, that was good.
- The pratfall was great.
- Chad Michaels and Dida Ritz,
the ingenue and the veteran.
- The duo felt a little lopsided
with Dida's energy
being over the top.
- She was so energized,
and that's a great thing,
but that can also be
detrimental sometimes.
The microphone was a bit close,
like she gonna swallow it.
- Now, is that a bad thing?
- [laughs]
Not normally.
- All right, let's move on
to Sharon Needles
and Phi Phi O'Hara,
the devil and the angel.
- They started with the
harmonies, and I was like,
oh, my God, I'm so impressed.
They're singing in harmo--uh-oh.
Oh.
[laughter]
- I loved their voices together,
but then, I'm tone deaf.
[laughter]
And I thought there
could have been used
a little more choreography
at the beginning,
but I have no rhythm, so--
- Oh!
[laughs]
- Yesterday, there was some
undercurrent of tension
between them and then, today,
they seemed like
they had their shtick together.
They knew exactly what they were
doing, but unfortunately,
their shtick
didn't have a lot of shtick.
- I did like their outfits.
I thought that the angel
and devil thing was a good idea,
but it didn't really deliver,
because you couldn't even tell
any jabs were being thrown.
- All right.
Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your frenemies
nightclub act
and your presentations
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Now, you are all troupers,
but tonight,
one duo did it so much better.
The winner of this week's
main challenge is...
Willam and Latrice Royale.
[applause]
You each win a custom corset
skirt and brassiere
of versatilecorsets.Com.
- I didn't expect to win
this challenge.
I'm really glad I didn't let
my partner down.
It's pretty fucking cool.
- That leaves Chad and Dida,
and Phi Phi and Sharon.
- [groans]
- Ladies, it's come to
a point in the competition
where every decision
is a painful one.
Phi Phi O'Hara
and Sharon Needles...
- [vomiting]
I feel kind of, like,
gut bubbles,
and I feel really sick.
I didn't want
to make RuPaul wait.
I didn't want to make
any of the guest judges wait.
I'm sorry.
So I tried to throw up
off the stage.
- It's really not cute.
- Willam, are you okay
to continue?
All right.
Phi Phi O'Hara
and Sharon Needles,
you are up for elimination.
Chad Michaels, Dida Ritz,
you may join the other girls.
- I was nice to Sharon,
and it backfired.
You know what?
I'm done.
I'm not playing nice
with you anymore.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourselves
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip-sync for your life.
- I don't want to go home,
plain and simple.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- This is RuPaul.
- And this is Martha Wash.
- We are reporting
to you live...
- From our weather center.
Honey, just when
you thought it was safe
to go back outside...
both: Bam, the sequel!
- ♪ Tonight
for the first time ♪
- ♪ The first time ♪
- ♪ Just about half past ten ♪
- ♪ Half past ten ♪
- ♪ Uh-huh ♪
- ♪ For the first time ♪
♪ In history ♪
- ♪ Say what? ♪
- ♪ It's gonna start ♪
♪ Raining men ♪
- ♪ All right, girl ♪
- ♪ It's raining men ♪
- Hey!
- ♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ It's raining men ♪
♪ Amen ♪
- Oh, crap.
My wig was hanging on
by one freakin' bobby pin.
I'm not keeping
that bitch on my head.
It might as well go.
It's in my way.
- ♪ Rough and tough ♪
♪ And strong and lean ♪
♪ God bless Mother Nature ♪
- That's right, honey.
♪ And she did ♪
♪ What she had to do now ♪
- I've worked too hard
and I've gone too far
into this competition,
and I'm not gonna get kicked off
because of some showgirl
Barbie doll.
- ♪ It's raining men ♪
- ♪ What you talkin' 'bout ♪
- I know how Phi Phi
dances and performs.
I was shocked to see
that Sharon is keeping up.
This is tough to watch,
because you don't know
who is gonna go home.
- ♪ Rip off the roof ♪
♪ And stay in bed ♪
- ♪ It's raining men ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ It's raining men ♪
♪ Amen ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ It's raining men ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies, I have made
my decision.
- I'm very fucking nervous.
It was my first time
having my fate
dangled in front of my face.
- Willam, will you please
step forward.
- What the hell is happening?
- Willam, you won tonight
because you are a beautiful
and talented queen,
but it has come to my attention
that you have broken the Rules--
Rules that are in place
to protect the fairness
of this competition.
Your actions have consequences,
and I'm afraid
you leave me no choice.
Willam, I have to ask you
to leave the competition
immediately.
Now, sashay away.
- I broke the Rules,
but I'm a big boy
dressed in big girl's clothes,
so regret's kind of like
a fool's game.
I can't change anything
that I did,
and there's no use spending
any time dwelling on it.
I stood on stage, sick,
with a 24-inch-waist,
and I'm proud of myself.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
Sharon Needles,
in light of tonight's events,
you got lucky.
You are both safe.
Shante, you stay.
[applause]
You may join the other girls.
My fierce five, let this
be a warning to all of you,
in the race to become
America's next drag superstar,
sometimes a queen's worst enemy
can be herself.
Now remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen.
- All right.
Now let the music play.