- Ladies and gentlemen,
the one, the only...
RuPaul.
- ♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
♪ Better get it, get it ♪
♪ Ge-ge-get it, get it ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ Ge-ge-get it, get it ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
- This is the Glamazon edition
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Stuffed and tucked with
everything you love and more.
- There's a hole in my stomach!
- Plus, never-before-seen
footage
from the you better work room.
- Yes, I know how
to sop it up, girl!
- Then it's celebrities
caught on tape,
with exclusive outtakes
from the judges' panel.
- I felt like I was maybe
about to watch
some sort of an adult,
erotic film of sorts.
- Oh, dear.
- And watch out,
fashion police.
We're counting down the most
sickening fits and fashions
with the arresting Chanel,
Mariah, and Pandora Boxx.
- ♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
- So don't go anywhere.
The Glamazon edition
of RuPaul's Drag Race
is ready to let you have it,
Auntie.
Can I get an amen up in here?
Cameroon?
[weakly] Anybody?
Helloo?
- Are you making fun of me,
Michelle?
- Some drag queens
can be so touchy.
[slap]
- Welcome to the Glamazon
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Thanks to you, this season has
been the biggest drag ever.
Let's flash back and share
some extra-special footage
that no one's seen.
Take a look at the casting tapes
that tried to snatch
my attention,
including some familiar faces.
♪ I'm in your arms ♪
♪ Champion ♪
♪ Greatest of 'em all ♪
- Oh, shit,
that's the wrong song!
- Can you believe I walk around
with no eyebrows, child?
- Gah! Eat it, bitch! Aah!
- ♪ Everybody wants her ♪
♪ Miss sexy in the city ♪
♪ She's on the prowl ♪
- Why do you want me?
Um...look at me.
- I split, my butt cheeks
hit the floor.
Who does that?
This bitch.
- ♪ Sashay, chante ♪
♪ Panther on the runway ♪
♪ Do it, do it, oh oh ♪
♪ All the girls say ♪
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
- Miss Phi Phi
does not like to lose.
- What is this? I don't even
know what this means.
Why am I even here today?
- You said you come in for Chad
Michaels in RuPaul's Drag Race.
- The first Latin
Puertorriquena that win!
- I...will...
take my Vaseline out.
- Oh, I see, so this is some
sort of free
public service announcement
for some drag queen.
You know what? I don't
have time for this shit.
- I will take my earrings off.
- I'm gonna do
whatever it takes.
- I don't give up.
- Get rid of the pretty
and knock a bitch out.
- The Princess.
Now, when you hear that name,
you're thinking, well,
she thinks pretty
damn highly of herself.
- My friend wanna be
on RuPaul's Drag Race
'cause she this friend name
Willam who's hella cool.
- I got charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
And as far as I'm concerned,
I'm pretty sure that's what
you're looking for, Ru.
- I think that,
in this business,
we all should be sisters,
we all should be friends.
We're one of a kind,
so we all should have our backs
and support everybody, and
that's my philosophy on that.
- ♪ Female phenomena ♪
♪ A Glamazon ♪
♪ She's so wild, so animal ♪
♪ She's gonna work that ♪
♪ Sexy body, so sexual ♪
♪ She's like a female... ♪
- I'm gonna win of this
competition!
- Win the competition.
- I came to win.
- ♪ Amazon na na na ♪
- I'm a fucking Oscar-winner!
I'm out of here!
- Oh! Hi.
I didn't see you come in there.
Welcome to my home.
- This one's my favorite
that I made.
I actually just made it.
Pins on just like this.
- Hairpieces that I make.
I do big hair too, but you--oh.
It's coming apart
like Shangela hair,
something to do with this.
- This, believe it or not,
is a shower curtain.
And, believe me,
it has many, many uses.
- I made this little
piece right here.
This is from white party.
- I definitely see,
like, Britney Spears
wearing something like this.
- You'll see my Dolly Parton
hair over here.
- Well, here we have a drag
queen's best friend--sequins.
Oh, that just bounces off of my
face, and it's just making me
just so sickening.
- There's a hole in my stomach!
I'm a big fan of, like, punk
rock,
and I'm not talking, like,
Pat Benatar punk rock, honey.
I'm talking like Jane Wayne
County punk rock.
[glass shatters]
- I'll send her home, girl.
- You--
- I can lip-sync the shit
out of you, girl.
- I mean--oh...
- Girl.
- Well, that's because you do
songs that everyone knows.
- Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
- I love him more than
anything.
And I do really mean that,
baby.
- I love you too, sweetheart.
- Let's go on TV and be famous.
- I know.
Mm, mm.
- 13 exceptional queens were
invited to join the race.
And when they received
the good news,
their reactions
were truly touching.
[Thus Spake Zarathustra]
♪ ♪
- Huh?
I made it?
What--what--like,
I'm on the show?
- Whoo!
- Aah! Ha!
- [laughing]
- [gasps]
- Shut your mouth.
- Oh, my God!
This is it. This is it!
This is it!
- So I think you guys
should do this:
You guys should probably
fit me for the crown,
'cause I plan
on taking it home.
- It's gonna be an honor to be
a part of this part
of drag history.
- I'm so grateful, so,
so grateful to you guys.
- Whew! Oh, my God.
I'm going to be on fucking
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Season 4.
- So how does that
make you feel?
- Yay. Ooh,
my teeth look good too.
- Once they arrived,
these girls wasted no time
doing what drag queens do best--
ki ki!
Now, I proudly present the world
premiere of...
Shit My Girls Say.
- The library is now open.
- No sale, no search, no shade.
- No shade.
- No shade, no tea.
- Work.
- No tea.
- No tea, no shade.
- Girl...
- No, but no shade, no tea.
- Ooh!
- Oww!
- The category is cheesecake.
- Cheesecake.
- Eat it!
- I will never be late
for dinner.
- Eat it!
- Bella!
- Are you upset because you
can't handle all this fishiness?
- Bitch, you are a fish!
- Gorgeous fish.
- Eat it. Eat it!
- I'm probably gonna get read
for Phil...for Phil...for Phil.
- Beat that wig!
- Beating the face, girl.
- Yeah, but not literally
beating my face.
- I am trying!
- A post-apocolake--apocolake.
A post-apocolake.
Apocolake.
That's all I--
that's how I say it.
- I love being a woman.
- I love pussy.
- Yes, who doesn't?
- They all assume that
I want to be a woman,
like, and I don't.
- You gotta find the inner diva.
- Lookin' fabulous!
- Work it, girl.
- Put some foam around that ass.
- When making your ass, always
draw the shape of Africa.
- This is gonna look a hot mess.
- Should I tuck?
- All you have to do is dip it
in some apple cider vinegar
and it tightens right back up.
[kiss]
- Daylight is no friend
of the dragoon.
- Dry those tears and powder
those cheekbones, okay?
- This is called
cutting a cheek.
- You know how much garbage
comes out of these
over-painted lips.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Girl, no.
- My moustache
is gonna start showing.
- People don't even know how
much of a man
it takes to be a drag queen.
- Where the fuck are my tits?
- If you have a cameltoe,
that's perfect.
- This season, with all
the backstage conflama--
that's "conflict" and "drama"--
we couldn't fit it all
into the series.
So let's start
with some sassy outtakes
from the You Better Work room.
- If we had to imitate
somebody in here,
- Okay, but Willam--
- I would do Willam.
- Willam, 'cause, you know--
[laughter]
- Hold on, hold on.
I'm actressing.
You can catch me
on Sex and the City and--
[laughter]
Extras for--
- Oh, my God!
- Any extra that they ever
needed a gay prostitute.
- Willam.
- And the category is?
- Oh, my God!
[laughs]
- People must just look at you
and be like,
"Oh, my God, Jujubee!"
- That's the Lane Bryant
Jujubee.
- She went to a buffet before
she entered the race.
- Wow.
- Really, bitch?
- She is a bitch.
I'm a bitch. You're a bitch.
What does "bitch" mean?
both: Being In Total
Control Of Herself.
- Bitch!
[laughter]
- Does anyone know any good
drag toasts for drinks?
- Here's to women,
women divine,
they bloom every month,
they bear every nine,
the only of God's creatures
this side of hell
that they could get juice from
a nut without cracking a shell.
- Oh!
- I got one too.
Here's to the girl
in the little brown shoes.
She'll eat your man
and drink your booze.
She'll eat your cherry
and drink your gin,
but thank God I got my deep
brown box my cherry came in.
- Cheers!
- Michelle,
you look fantastic.
- Thank--Sharon, thank you,
thank you.
- Say, you know,
the thing about me and RuPaul--
when we go down to a gay bar,
we both get mistaken
for drag queens.
[laughter]
I don't know!
It's crazy.
It's just me.
- You know what,
Cher, I like you,
and I'm gonna tell you why.
- Tell me.
- You don't give a fuck.
- I don't give a rat's ass.
- And that's what I like
about you.
- I don't give a rat's ass.
You know, I'm every
gay man's best friend.
And that's a lot of holes
to fill.
- [laughs]
Now, I created
RuPaul's Drag Race
to elevate the art of drag.
But I know you all love it
when these bitches get shady.
Roll the tape.
- Y'all got enough sewing
machines over there?
Y'all look like a sweatshop.
- Jiggly too--she talkin'
about she saw this thing.
- Who?
- Her.
- This bitch is shady.
- That smelly bitch,
she got nerve.
- Who, me?
- Yeah, you, you monster.
- Me? I'm monster?
- Yeah, you.
- Who's the big one in here?
- Girl, you look like a horse.
- Roar.
- You look like a horse.
- You wanna call me a horse,
honey, that's fine.
Horses have gorgeous legs,
and these legs will kick.
- You look like you've been
kicking, all right--
kicking flour.
Put some lotion on them
ashy-ass knees.
- Bitch, bye, boo!
- You ugly,
and I'm at peace with it.
[laughter]
- Willam's school for bitches
is now opening,
accepting enrollments
for the 2011--
- I already graduated.
- Nurse. Like, "Oh, nurse."
- Nurse.
- Yeah, 'cause she needs help.
And nurses help people.
Nurse.
- Did this bitch really
just come for me?
- Ooh, nurse!
- All that venom inside you,
mama.
We need to do an extraction.
- Out of me?
- Yeah.
- You think I'm evil?
- Didn't Sharon look pretty
yesterday?
- What?
- Sharon. I was shocked.
- [laughs]
- Don't think about it.
What makes you happy? Food?
Food makes you happy, right?
- I know you have low
self-esteem,
so I'll let you think you won.
- Thank you.
- Your attitude sucks.
It sucks, and you suck.
- I can't hear you.
- What did you read me about
now, you bitch?
- Girl, you're so insecure.
Nobody was even
talking about you.
Paint your face.
- You're such a rude bitch,
Phi Phi.
- Oh, well.
You might not have to deal
with it for long.
- [chuckling]
- Just like Glee,
there's something
about RuPaul's Drag Race
that makes a queen just
break out in song.
- ♪ Comin' down the runway
in a velvet gown ♪
♪ I pound down the runway,
400 pounds ♪
♪ I'm Latrice ♪
- ♪ She's Latrice ♪
- I'm Latrice!
- Cover girl!
Why your base look like chalk?
[all howling with laughter]
- ♪ Crunchy toes, busted pose ♪
You can't walk!
- You better do it, bitch!
- Walk.
Don't walk.
Walk!
- She is so stupid.
- Don't walk!
[laughter]
- ♪ Sharon Needles ♪
♪ Don't share your needles ♪
♪ With Sharon Needles ♪
- ♪ Don't share your needle ♪
♪ You'll get the ♪
[claps]
- [laughs]
- ♪ Or the butt flu ♪
♪ You will, [cough cough] ♪
♪ Or maybe ah-choo ♪
- ♪ Jesus is a biscuit ♪
all: ♪ Sop you up ♪
- There you go!
♪ Jesus is a biscuit ♪
♪ Won't let him sop you up ♪
- Did she just say "A biscuit"?
- Yeah.
- What's that mean,
"Jesus is a biscuit"?
- Let him sop you up.
- Sop you up?
- Sop up stuff with a biscuit.
- You do?
- Y'all so white
and Anglo-Saxon and shit.
Y'all never heard of
sopping it up with a biscuit?
- No.
- No, seriously, what's sop up?
- Sopping it up means you, like,
take your syrup
and your biscuit or whatever,
and you sop it up.
- Yeah, I do eat that.
- You know about sopping it up--
- Oh, you take
the biscuit after--
when it's on your plate,
and you go...
- That's soppin' it up!
- That's soppin' it--
yes, I know how to sop it up,
girl!
- Now, a lot of what happens
during filming
is just too hot to air, so label
these next clips N.S.F.W.--
Not safe for the workroom.
- There's a bunch of booties
back here.
- Mama, somebody left, like,
a dirty Kotex in my station.
- Aah! I think Phi Phi
might be in heat.
- Guys, my butt hurts.
- [trilling]
- If you fart, bitch, I swear.
'cause you's a gassy ho.
- [laughing] I can't.
- You never know which end
it's gonna come out of.
- [burps]
- Rick Santorum is,
if you google his name,
there is a filthy, filthy
definition that comes up,
because a gay man
was smart enough to make it
an urban dictionary word
or something.
And he hates gay people.
So I'm glad that
it's called that.
- Oh...my God.
I did not know all this.
- The queens just love to sit
around the table
debating hot topics.
It's like The View,
only more ladylike.
Hey, Miss Hasselbeck,
no tea, no shade.
Word up, girl.
- What president do you think
or have you found to be
the best or good-looking?
You know, like, the hottest
president we've had?
- Oh, my Mr. Obama.
- You think he's hot?
- Absolutely, he's so handsome.
- You do him? Yeah?
- Absolutely, and then I think--
- Bill Clinton.
- That's who I got my vote.
- Eww.
- When he first started,
he was hot.
- But President Obama, he's--
I've always thought he was just
so handsome and so charismatic.
- Lincoln was kind of cute.
He was really, really--
he was really tall and--
- In like a woodsman
kind of way.
- Yeah, and he wore, like,
a steampunk's top hat.
He looked really punk.
- Didn't George Washington
wear wigs?
- He did.
- So he could
double our collection.
- And Taft, if you're
a chubby chaser.
He was all right.
He's the one that got stuck
in the tub.
- Huh.
- Wow.
- Doing what?
- The one thing I didn't get is,
what is with the wig wars
when drag queens snatch off
their wigs during a lip-sync?
- Well, I mean--
- Like, you took off
a sequined dress,
and your wig stayed on.
And then, all of a sudden,
she just pulls her off.
- Well, you know, I felt like
you're in the moment,
and that song has so much
angst going on in it,
and I literally couldn't, like,
the hair was in my face.
- Well, that's one thing.
- So I was like,
"I gotta get rid of this hair,
so they can see my lips."
- But why did she
pull off her wig?
- It just--y'all,
they got down, girl.
They got down.
- It's lip sync for your life.
You know?
- If the wig falls off,
it falls off,
but I am not personally
taking that bitch off.
- It's all staying on, bitch,
when I do it.
- All those pins in there--
bitch, I had, like,
40 pins in my head.
- That's a desperate cry
for attention.
- A little I Am What I am,
La Cage.
- You know? Yeah.
But it's, like, unnecessary.
I understand you're born
this way, but...
- Right.
- Yeah, right now, you gotta be
a woman and stay a woman.
And you're killing my illusion.
- Where do you stand on these
very important issues?
Tweet your thoughts
to #DragRace,
and I will retweet my favorites.
Welcome back to the Glamazon
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
It's time to flashback to the
queens' most memorable moments.
All right, boys.
Let me see what you got.
Now the first queen to leave us
was Shangela Laquifa Wadley.
- Hallelu!
I'm back, bitches.
[group groans]
Hallelu is in the building.
- After trying to crash
the party one more time,
I had her removed
from the competition...
[cheering]
And sent some place where
they'd really appreciate
her style and humor.
- [screaming]
- Let's just say
the zombies ate her up.
- Aah, hallelu!
Hallelu!
- Hello, how y'all doing?
- Alisa Summers experienced
quite a lot
in her short time here.
She braved exposure
to toxic waste.
- Do we get a barf bag?
- Aah!
- And a zombie attack.
But her post-apocalyptic runway
couture
didn't devastate our judges...
and Alisa Summers
did not survive.
Now, Lashauwn Beyond
was something unique
to this competition...
a shy drag queen.
- Hi, queen one.
- Hi.
- Now, her apocalyp--
her--her [indistinct]
- "Post-apocolake."
- Her couture was
out of this world.
But Lashauwn lacked nerve.
And it do take nerve.
What can't you believe?
- That I'm here.
- Bitch, you're here.
- Yeah, honey,
you better snap out of it.
But in week two, Lashauwn
was sent to the great beyond.
all: Whoa.
- Hi.
- The Princess,
a reserved extrovert,
struggled to let
her sparkle shine.
- [singing]
Do you feel like you've come
to the end of your road?
- After lackluster performances,
the judges felt The Princess
didn't have enough
zing in her Zen.
But she'll live forever
as Drag Race royalty.
- Hi, y'all.
- [screaming]
- What's the Spanish word
for roller coaster?
I bet Madame Laqueer knows,
because that was her ride
on Drag Race.
She won the wrestling
competition...
- Jiggly, get your butt
over here.
- [chuckles]
- But was always the last person
picked for teams.
- I wouldn't want to choose
Madame for my team
because I don't want her.
- She was team captain
for the sitcom challenge.
- [screams]
- But after a Razzie-worthy
performance,
Madame Laqueer
had to sashay away.
- Hey,
there's a new girl in town.
Let's get to business.
- Next stop, Paris, London,
Milan.
- Mahogany.
- This queen brought Broadway
experience to the competition.
- That young man look pretty
mature enough
to handle a beaver on his own.
- Um, Milan.
You're kind of
playing this stuff out here.
Look at the person
that you're talking to.
- Sorry.
- Her fierce lip sync helped her
stay in the game.
But the third time
was not a charm.
And Milan was sent back
to Broadway.
- Hi.
- What's good, ladies?
- Next up,
Miss Jiggly Caliente.
- [singing]
- And yes,
you may call her Jiggly.
She started strong, by winning
the toxic photo shoot.
- Yeah!
[cheering]
- But her hoarding couture
put her up for elimination.
- I'm getting
my eyeballs assaulted.
- Her tough New York
attitude...
do you take the train and drive?
- Yes, mama,
I have to get to work.
- Jiggly will cut a bitch.
- Thank you.
- Soon gave way to self-doubt.
- What the hell
would I write about
how to eat a pound of chicken?
- Exactly, that's funny.
- Oh.
Damn.
- She fought hard
in the lip syncs.
But the third and final face off
was the last for this
plus-sized Barbie.
- Deuces.
[laughter]
- Willam's rare combination
of sexy and funny
made her the queen to beat.
- Ooh, a 26, damn.
We got some big girls.
I hope they don't have diabetes.
- Already a successful
working actor...
- You look really familiar, Ma.
- Me?
You must have a television.
- She never let us forget it.
- I was on Boston Public
with you.
I was the best friend
of Candace Kane when she died.
I died on Nip/Tuck.
CSI: New York,
Women's Murder Club.
- Is that Willam
dropping names over there?
- Her acting experience served
her well in the challenges...
- Willam, you're funny.
- Thank you, hire me.
[laughter]
And so did her sickening body.
- I hope that lotion's
waterproof.
- But when I discovered
that off-screen,
Willam had violated show rules,
I had no choice but to give
this sexy drag queen
the heave-ho.
Willam, it has come to my
attention
that you have broken the rules.
Willam, I have to ask you
to leave the competition
immediately.
Now, sashay away.
- Category is...
all: Cheesecake!
- Our next queen was a tasty
slice of cheesecake.
Dida Ritz.
[cheering]
- Bonjour, ladies.
- Feisty and lovable...
- How you doing?
- It's nice to see you again.
- Dida won fans on the runway.
- Supermodel.
- The judges lived for her long
legs and catwalk stomping,
but felt her fashion sense
was a bit pedestrian.
- Outfit-wise, I wasn't moved
one way or the other.
- My name is Dida Ritz,
I'm here representing--
or running for Wig Party.
- Her presidential debate did
not win her any supporters...
- I thought you were
the weakest debater.
- And she was voted
off the show.
But had there been
a wig-whipping challenge,
Dida may just have gone
all the way.
- Hi, girls.
[cheering]
- Little Kenya Michaels
was a tiny queen
who posed a big threat
to the other girls.
- [laughs]
- She's cute.
- Fuck.
- Kenya was a spicy firebird
on the runway...
- Bella!
- And in the wrestling ring.
- Praise God!
[indistinct yelling]
- What did you just do?
- In the snatch game,
we weren't Crazy In Love
with her Beyonce impression.
Oh!
And Kenya was sent packing.
[kisses]
- Ay!
[cheering]
- But the judges felt Kenya
had more to offer,
and invited her back.
But when her makeover of a dad
turned into a dud...
- Being pregnant's hard.
- Macabre too, apparently.
- Yeah.
- It was hasta la vista
for this sexy senorita.
[kisses]
[cheering]
- Ow!
Eat it!
- Sit back, relax, and pour
yourself an ice cold glass
of miss Latrice Royale.
- The shade,
the shade of it all.
- Her curves and swerves had the
judges captivated,
and so did her body slams.
- Aah!
- Mmm.
Well, hello, gorgeous.
- As Large Marge, she killed it
in the sitcom challenge.
- Get those nuts
away from my face.
- Her full-bodied grace
and soul made her a contender
to win it all.
But when her canine couture
went to the dogs,
Latrice was sent home.
- I am Latrice Royale.
- Bitches better beware.
all: ♪ Latrice! ♪
- Royale!
[applause]
- All my queens
are sickening, no?
But which one is your favorite?
Go to newnownext.com
and vote for Miss Congeniality.
Do it for your lips.
Welcome back to the Glamazon
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
The best seat in town
is the judges' table.
With my best squirrel friend,
Michelle Visage,
and my Judge Judys,
Santino Rice and Billy "V"
by my side--
well, things can get
a little bit stupid.
- If you do the research,
you won't have those
deer-in-headlights moments.
It's all the help.
- Did you just call her
the help?
- No, I said I'm here to help.
So I called myself the help.
- I see.
- It's okay because
I called myself the help,
and I am a black man...
dressed as a white woman.
- Yes.
- Sound familiar?
- Mm-hmm.
[laughter]
- I did think of Grey Gardens,
that smell of cat piss.
- I thought that was me, so--
[laughter]
- When I look at you, it almost
looks like an Austin Powers
kind of joke or something.
If clothes looked like a couch,
or an ottoman, or a loveseat,
you just wanna stay away
from it, you know?
[barking]
- What did you just call me?
- And no matter where I am
in this studio,
I can hear her laughs.
And it's just the most beautiful
thing I've ever heard.
- [laughing]
- Every time she laughs,
her nuts get bigger.
- This season,
the judges' panel
was more star-studded than ever.
They were looking good
and feeling gorgeous.
- With the tattoos,
I felt like I was maybe about
to watch some sort of an adult,
erotic film of sorts...
- Oh, dear.
- Which, not opposed to at all.
- Hello.
Well, welcome to the jungle.
- America's got talent
has nothing on this show.
- She looks like Divine Brown,
but we're trying to excite
America, not Hugh Grant.
- She was going for
Sex and the City,
and it was more like
"Sex in the Alley."
- Well, I'm not gonna
turn that down either.
- I really want a drag name.
- Jennifer Love Hewitt
is the best drag name
I have ever heard.
I'm changing my name
to RuPaul Love Hewitt.
- [laughs]
[thunder]
- The judges provided the queens
with constructive criticism,
but I swear, some of them was
jealous of they boogie.
- I appreciate those
hair and pants.
- You can have them
when I'm done.
- Okay, girl. They're mine.
- They're yours.
- 'Cause I love them.
- May I borrow
that hairpiece you had?
- The red one?
- Yes.
- I would like to borrow
your dress.
- You can have it.
- From your neck up,
I would decapitate you
and wear your head.
And I'm living for that ring.
- This is actually a broach.
I just threw a ring on it.
- Bitch.
- And PS, fuck you for having
the most amazing body ever.
- Your body is possibly
the sickest I've ever seen
on a queen in any season.
It's the legs, then she
turns around, it's the ass,
and that face--
my God.
- Your legs are really
something major,
and that is amazing.
- How dare they have better
legs than me?
How very dare they?
- Now, the celebrities weren't
just here to look fierce.
Once I scanned
their library cards,
those bitches
were ready to read.
- If we were gonna
go out on the town,
I'd pull you aside and say,
"Let's go look in your closet
closet and find something else."
- The wig looked like a litter
of kittens had sucked on it,
and she found it in the garbage.
- I would love to have
a cocktail with you.
Whether or not I would
get up to use the bathroom
and never come back,
I don't know.
[laughter]
- Is that a pot scrubber
on your head,
or are you just happy to see me?
- I was wondering,
after I painted my room,
where the drop cloth went.
- Yeah, there it is, right.
- That's where it was.
- Last night, my leftovers were
in the shape of aluminum foil
with a swan, you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- And somebody
put your leftovers
in the shape of Jiggly.
- [laughs]
- You know, that was a little
Jonbenet Ramsey.
That was a little creepy for me.
- You know, before,
I had a problem
with the makeup
every single time.
Today was the best
that it's been.
- Now, is that a read?
- A little bit.
- Uh-huh.
The celebrities also revealed
plenty of personal information
that we tastefully chose not
to include in the show...
until now.
I need more energy on the panel.
So I need about five hamsters.
Are there any in the building?
- Including her tits.
- [laughs]
- All right, Wy.
Winner of the challenge?
- This is very hard for me.
I feel like they should all
win something.
I'd rather go to the
gynecologist than do this.
- I'm gonna go
to the gynecologist
with you after this.
- I like a pap smear.
Count me in.
- I love ex-cons, but that's
a whole nother show.
- I've gotten in trouble
with a couple of those.
- I think it cheapens
you a little bit,
like a hooker in the Bronx.
- They're expensive.
- Oh. Oh, are they?
John said they're expensive.
- I have seen larger queens
turn it out.
- Yes, miss perky.
- Are you talking about
my chest?
- You've been talking about it
all day, you're so cute.
Go forward.
- I want her fondle me.
- I'll fondle you.
- There you go.
- Phone call for RuPaul?
Okay, yeah, all right.
Obama's calling me
real quick, hold on.
Somebody said you'd bumped your
head earlier.
How is your head?
- Haven't had
any complaints yet.
[laughter]
Welcome back to the Glamazon
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Now, this season the runway was
a fashion phenomenon.
And to help me rate
the ra sha sha,
I've invited back
queens from all seasons.
Welcome the sensational Chanel,
that funny fox Pandora Boxx,
and last, but not least,
we call this queen Mariah.
Hello, ladies.
- Hello.
- Hi, Ru.
- Are you ready to countdown
the top ten most sickening
fits and fashions of the runway?
- Uh, my tuck is on fire.
- Literally.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Coming in at number ten,
Milan serving disco harem chic.
Burn, baby, burn.
- T.G.I.F.
She came out like
that was her last dance.
- [laughs]
- When she was dancing around,
it definitely took some flight
with the air into it.
It was hot, love it.
- Yes, is it something
you would wear?
- No, but I liked it, yeah.
- No? [laughs]
At number nine,
it's Jiggly Caliente
working her '80s retro look.
- Grey Jell-O never looked
so good.
[laughter]
There was the Missy Elliot
video where they, like,
pumped her full of air.
- Right, right.
- Sickening, and that gave me,
very much, that sort of feel.
I live for Jiggly.
I think she's amazing.
In the number eight spot,
it's Latrice Royale
in royal blue.
Ooh, now I love that dress.
I love the color of that blue
with the color of her skin.
And was living for
an asymmetrical silhouette.
- True, true goddess.
Voluptuous, beautiful.
I love that her eye shadow
matched the gown.
She wore it impeccably.
- I just can't believe
how beautiful
Michael Clarke Duncan
looks...gorgeous.
- He's done really well
for himself.
- He really has.
- Yes, he has.
At number seven,
Phi Phi O'Hara,
survivor of the RuPocalypse.
Very [indistinct].
- It was like Waterworld
meets, like,
Xena: Warrior Princess.
And I loved that when she
walked,
it was very much, like,
"I know I'm the shit.
It's cool."
- Bushmeat
never looked so good.
- [laughs]
- I live for the attitude,
the confidence, the silhouette.
It had a purpose.
And she executed it very well.
- You didn't think it was
a little too roadkill?
- It gave me beaver
on the side of the road.
But, you know,
who doesn't love a good beaver?
- That's true.
- Especially
on the side of the road.
- You're absolutely right.
Number six, Dida Ritz...
serving gold and gams.
Very Fritz Lang Metropolis.
- The Walmart version.
I wouldn't personally wear it,
because I'm not that cheeky.
With her skin tone,
gold is absolutely amazing.
Her having legs for days,
she can really pull off
a look like that.
- Coming in at number five,
Chad Michaels'
renaissance realness.
Lady Chatterley.
- Gorgeous,
the dog days are gone.
- I think she was Joan Of Arc
in her former life.
- [laughs]
At number four,
little Kenya Michaels
is pretty in pink.
Oh, look at her.
- If Nicki had a my size Barbie,
that would be her.
- [laughs]
- Definitely.
- She's so adorable.
She's just, like, a little doll.
I wanna pick her up
and squeeze her till she pees.
- [laughs]
- I still have to question if
everything is down there still.
She is true, true Walmart fish.
She really is.
- [laughs]
At number three,
it's Sharon Needles,
serving drastic plastic chic.
- What drag queen does not love
a good battery acid
chemical peel?
- I love the "Madonna two weeks
before the Super Bowl" look.
- [laughs]
- Sharon has such
an incredible ability
to me to take something so odd
and make it so chic
and ugly-beautiful.
- The number two fits in fashion
is Willam's tummy troubles.
- [vomiting]
- I say, "Bitch, that's what you
get for eating solid food."
- Agreed.
- It's obvious somebody still
has their gag reflex.
She's giving blonde trash
everywhere a bad name.
- [laughs]
- Tara Reid
would be proud though.
- Tara Reid would be proud.
- You're absolutely right
about that.
- And now, if I may, Ru,
the number one most sickening
fits and fashion belongs to--
oh, you know, it's not just one.
It's 11 timeless looks.
- I think I know
where this is going.
- And the winner is...
RuPaul!
Roll tape.
[growling]
Oops, uh-oh,
I think I just got fired.
Roll the other tape.
- Chanel,
which one of my outfits
was your favorite?
- I have to say with the
feathers--the blue feathers.
Like, May West had
a RuPaul drag baby.
- I, of course,
love absolutely all of them.
- Yes, that goes with saying.
- It's a toss-up between
the best little Ruhouse
in Texas look.
- Yes, yes.
- Or the very flowing, like,
Barbie meets Mrs. Roper look.
- Yes, yes, I love that.
- Gorgeous.
- Gorgeous, gorgeous.
I'm not gonna
leave you out, Mariah.
- I have to pick
the emerald green.
I wanted to
ease on down the road,
and snatch it right out
of your closet.
- Oh, my goodness.
I'd give it you, but I just
don't want to see it on eBay.
[laughter]
All right,
just between us girls,
who do you think should be
crowned
America's next drag superstar?
Chanel?
- Chad Michaels.
He's so seasoned.
And he's so professional.
And he's a perfectionist
in every single thing he does.
- Pandora?
- I would really love to see
Sharon Needles take the title.
Because I think
she's so different
than any of the previous winners
that she would really
just take it to a whole,
different, crazy, spooky level.
And I love it.
- Mariah?
- My pick has to be
Phi Phi O'Hara.
She's definitely hungry.
She has the fire.
The attitude is channeled
the right way.
She can just sear
right through the competition.
- Well, ladies,
you'll have to wait
just like everyone else
to find out
who's crowned America's
next drag superstar.
Now, before you go,
there's a little thank you gift
under your seat.
- [gasps]
Look it.
- It's RuPaul's Drag Race
Iron Fist shoes.
- It's a petite size 12,
just like me.
- I just want
to make love to it.
- I love that.
- Cute little kitten heel
to go play around in.
- [meows]
- Strap on some attitude, girls.
Welcome back to the Glamazon
edition of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Next week,
it's attack of the Glamazons,
as Chad Michaels,
Phi Phi O'Hara,
and Sharon Needles
battle it out
for the title of America's
next drag superstar,
and walk away with a lifetime
supply of NYX cosmetics,
and a one of a kind trip
courtesy of alandchuck.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring cocktails
perfected by Absolut,
and a cash prize of $100,000
in the over-the-top extravaganza
that you won't want to miss.
The time has come for us to take
an up and close personal look
at the final three.
- Well, hello, hello.
all: Hi.
- How are y'all doing?
- A Chicago showgirl,
Phi Phi O'Hara is a feisty
firecracker...
- Don't be jealous of my boogie.
With the will to win...
- I want to look like a hot
Miami piece of ass.
- You look like it to me.
- Good.
- Hungry and ambitious...
- You're damn right I'm hungry.
You all should be hungry.
- She always brings
her A game.
- If the final say-so happened
today, you would win.
- Oh, hell no!
- Phi phi fierce
ruled the wrestling ring.
[cheering]
- Now, I'm gonna show you how
to really beat a mug, bitch.
- And her fighting spirit
caused a few rumbles
in the workroom as well.
- At least I am
a showgirl, bitch.
Go back to Party City,
where you belong.
But Phi Phi also revealed
a softer side.
- I wish I had a dad
like him to accept me
for everything that I am.
- Do you think your father
will watch this show?
- Probably not.
And that's okay.
I'm fine with that.
I hope he values...
like, who I am.
I'm a good person.
- I really want you
to have my phone call.
I really wanted to win it
for you.
- Honey, thank you so much.
- Yeah.
- Phi Phi O'Hara has a magic
combination of talent,
beauty, and ambition.
But, is it enough
to take her to the very top?
- Morning, bitches.
- What's up?
- Hi, everybody.
- Let's turn back time
on Miss Chad Michaels.
A world-class Cher impersonator.
- Cher comes to her for tips.
- This is one of many natural
hair colors
that I'll be wearing tonight.
[laughter]
I'm Cher, bitch.
- Throughout the competition...
- You want some of this?
We got plenty for you too.
- This dark lady has proven...
- Oh, oh, drop it like it's hot.
- That she's much more
than a gypsy.
- I am from California.
More specifically, the Shady
Acres Trailer Park on Doheny
between Weho and Beverly Hills.
- Tramp...
- What a jerk.
- And a thief.
- What made you think that
we could get away with
sneaking into a nut farm
in the middle of the night?
- Having accomplished
so much in her career,
will the next feather
in this half-breed's headdress
be the title of America's
next drag superstar?
[cheering]
- Sharon Needles arrived
as the freaky underdog.
- I look spooky,
but I'm really not.
- And her spooky-drag persona
set her apart from the start.
- Oh, she's bleeding.
- Goodness.
- Somebody call a dentist.
- She didn't hit off
with the other girls initially.
- I think a lot of the girls
here think I'm a one-trick pony.
You know, I'm just a spook,
monster girl.
- Just put some white powder
on your face and look gothic.
That's all we need you to do.
- But Sharon soon won over the
judges with her edgy aesthetic.
- I didn't even get the name
right away.
- All in the past, Miss Cole.
- Okay?
You know, so I'm right there
with you, but anyway.
- All right, well, yes.
- But she was plagued
by nagging guilt
over her boyfriend back home.
- She's auditioned
all four years,
and then I try out one time
and, you know, here I am.
I feel guilty about it
all the time.
- But Sharon rose above
and kept on winning.
- Condragulations.
Condragulations.
- Yes.
- You are the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
She showed the judges
that she could diversify
her dark-sided drag.
But always stayed true
to her own unique style.
- You look like you
came out of Italian Vogue.
- Ooh.
- From spooky to unspookable,
does Sharon Needles
have the fright stuff
to be America's
next drag superstar?
The top three girls,
the best of the best.
So which of these amazing queens
has the charisma,
uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
to be America's
next drag superstar?
Let's consult the stars.
Tell us what the future holds,
Madame Visage.
- Chad Michaels.
Chad Michaels is a Pisces,
and fish always do well
in this competition.
I predict Chad Michaels will be
America's next drag superstar.
- Oh, spoil alert.
Well, what's the story
for the others?
- Sharon Needles is a Leo
with Scorpio rising
and panties dropping.
I see it now.
Sharon Needles
will win this competition.
- Wait a minute,
I thought you said
Chad Michaels was gonna win.
- What, you--what?
You don't question
Madame Visage, girl.
Hold the celestial phone.
Phi Phi O'Hara
is a double-jointed Virgo.
As see it as clear
as a Lucite hooker-heel.
Phi Phi O'Hara is the winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
- Don't quit your day job,
Madame Visage.
What you say about my boob job?
- Well, what is crystal clear
is this competition
has never been so close.
And, with a cash prize
of $100,000,
next week's final challenge
promises to be the most
pressure-filled
and surprising
in Drag Race history.
You won't want to miss a moment.
Until next week...
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- Amen.
- All right.
Let the music play.