- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
the theme for this year's Pride
is hope floats.
[cheers and applause]
- Jiggly is a hot mess.
- Where the fuck are my
tits?
- Ahoy.
Orange Jigglius.
- Does her snake have one eye
or two?
- I'm giving you maritime
realness with the starship
Willam.
- Milan.
- Her body language is totally
"dude in a dress."
- Willam, condragulations.
You are the winner of this
challenge.
- Jiggly Caliente...
shantay, you stay.
Milan, sashay away.
And tonight...
get out your library cards,
girls.
The library is open.
- You're such a fat slut,
after sex you smoke hams.
[laughter]
- And the dolls go glossy.
- You have to spot me.
- With extra special guest
judges Regina King
and Pam Tillis.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX Cosmetics,
a one-of-a-kind trip courtesy of
alandchuck.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut Vodka...
cocktails perfected...
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And may the best woman win.
[tires screeching]
- Cluck, cluck, ladies.
- Where's our hangers?
- Wha-wha!
- Milan's gone, and now it's
down to the lucky seven.
- "Colored girl, why yo base
look like chalk?"
- I loved Milan, you guys.
Milan was a class act.
How did it feel to lip sync
against your mama?
Were you scared?
- No, 'cause I know Milan is
good, but then I know I'm good
too.
- Well...
- Do you think you're gonna
win the show?
- At least--
- That was an awkwardly long
pause.
- Yeah.
- I was at the bottom two
twice, so the girls are just
kinda, like, assuming that
I ain't shit.
- You went from a baked potato
to a sweet potato.
- Sweet potatoes have
antioxidants.
- But they're better.
- It's a good fat,
as they say.
- Dumbass bitches, I'm gonna
fight till the end.
I just wanna see her do what I
did with our without shoes.
- You wanna see me do a split?
- Go ahead, jump into a split.
- I can't jump into a split.
- Thank you, then shut the
fuck up, bitch.
- Bye, Milan.
We'll see you in New York City.
She as really defensive,
though, a lot.
- It's hard to come here and,
like,
people tell you
that you're not good
at what you've been doing.
- Oh, trust me, I get it.
I think the trick with dealing
with the judging panel
is just get them to tell you
that they have no notes
and that you're perfect.
[laughs]
Yeah, I won.
I was stunned.
I'm like,
"This is the best review
I've ever gotten in my life.
- You had your moment,
and you done had your shine.
Now, can we let it go, girl?
Because, boo-boo,
it's a new week
and a new challenge.
And you're in one week,
and you can slip the next.
No tea, no shade.
- I was fucking stunned
that they said that.
- Well, they upped
the smoke machine last night,
so they couldn't see your beard
coming through.
[laughter]
[alarm sounds]
- Ooh, girl!
You got shemail.
Extra, extra!
Tweet all about it!
Like a rolling stone, today's
queen on the down low needs to
be a real hustler on time and
always in style.
So start spreading the news,
'cause you're gonna wake up in
a cyber city that never sleeps.
Hello, hello, hello.
[together]
Good morning.
- My legendary children.
In the great tradition of
Paris is Burning...
[deep voice] Get out your
library cards, girls.
- Ooh!
- Yes!
- Because reading is what?
all: Fundamental!
- Oh, God.
- Now for today's mini
challenge, you'll take turns
throwing shade.
Hashtag "thelibraryisopen."
21st-century reading, darlings.
All right, ladies, first up
Dida Ritz.
- I'm gonna try.
I don't know how to really read
that well, so...
does someone smell that?
- What? What is it?
- Oh, that's just
Sharon Needles.
- Oh!
- Jiggly Caliente, you should
feel honored.
The first contestant in
RuPaul's Drag Race history
with child.
- Oh!
- [laughs]
- Latrice Royale,
you're free now.
You don't have to rock the yard
sandals anymore.
[laughter]
- Jiggly Caliente.
Darling, what do you see?
- Bitches.
- Oh-oh.
- Dida, let me start with you,
boo.
- There's lotion in my purse.
You need to use them on your
elbows and your knees.
You look like you've been
driving through flour, baby.
- Oh!
Phi Phi O'Hara,
India called.
She wants her look back,
boo.
- [chuckles]
- Mama Chad, it's called
Forever 21, not Forever 41.
- [laughs]
- Willam, honey, your face
is made out of marble.
Shit don't move.
- Oh-oh.
Dida, you know,
I always think it's cute
to rock your mother's
two-piece sweater set
on the runway.
Oh-oh.
- Oh, jujubee, you know,
helium's for balloons,
not your stomach.
Oh, and, you know, Willam,
I know you're talented at,
you know, buying shoes,
but are you talented at,
you know, drag?
You know, uh, Sharon, I love how
you rock the party city.
- That's where I got your
Lady Gaga wig.
[laughter]
Phi Phi sucked.
- Dida Ritz, I don't know if
that is hot couture or hot
"coutorn," 'cause there's holes
in that shirt.
There are holes in the garment.
Ooh, Jiggly.
Jiggly, uh, 31--yeah,
there should be 32.
- Ooh.
Phi Phi, you are gorgeous.
You catch the camera's eye
from the right.
But from the left, you snag it.
- Ohh!
Crawlin' out the tar pits with
your relative the saber-tooth.
Visit it while you're in
Los Angeles.
- [laughs]
- Chad Michaels, you so old,
you still on
myspace.Com/chadmichaels.
- I was gonna take that down.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the RuPaul ball.
Tonight in the category
of butch queen, Dida Ritz.
- Oh!
- Jiggly, I love you.
Come to mother dust.
Come here, come to me.
Come to me, I won't hurt you.
Here's my dentist's card.
Use it.
Willam Belli.
Willam Belli loves to live his
life and think that he's
Carrie Bradshaw.
But in the sequel, she'll be
playing Scary Bradshaw.
- Oh-oh.
- Latrice.
Latrice's feet are so big,
she will be starring
in the remake
of the beloved family favorite
Flipper.
[laughter]
- Jiggly Caliente, B.M.W.
Body Made Wrong.
[laughter]
Phi Phi O'Hara, although reading
is fundamental, darling, you
might learn how to spell first,
you illiterate fuck.
[laughter]
Willam, Miss Industry,
congratulations on your new role
as the big bad wolf by the hair
on your chinny, chin, chin.
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Sharon Needles, two words...
sideshow freak.
[laughter]
- Dida Ritz, a lot of you girls
like to clock me for painting
my skin on the gray side, but
I was inspired by your knees.
- Oh!
- They're the same color
as Willam's chin.
- Oh-oh-oh!
- Phi Phi O'Hara, what brand
of makeup do you wear?
Sherman Williams?
- Uh-oh, uh-oh.
- That was a weak one.
Latrice Royale, you know,
a lot of us have done
great work in bars.
You've done your best
behind them.
[laughter]
Jiggly Caliente, you're such
a fat slut,
after sex you smoke hams.
[laughter]
- [deep voice] The library is
permanently shut down.
Ooh, no tea, no shade.
And the winner is...
Latrice Royale.
[cheering]
- Yes.
- Condragulations, darling.
- Thank you, Mama.
- My girls.
For this week's main challenge,
I need you to conquer the world
of publishing.
You'll be launching your very
own dragazine.
Oh, pit crew!
As editor-in-chief, you'll each
be assigned a different title.
And then it's up to you to
create a cover, choose the
articles, and really make it
your own.
Now, Latrice, since you won
the mini challenge, you get to
assign the dragazines.
- Oh.
- She's picking
Battle of the Bulge,
health and fitness.
Jiggly Caliente.
Wow.
- Tastes Like Chicken.
For food lovers.
Dida Ritz.
Uh-oh, Sugar Walls.
Now, this is home decor.
Willam, editor-in-chief.
Kitty Cats.
Meow! For cat lovers.
Meow!
Kitty Cats!
[laughter]
- I love pussy.
- Yes, who doesn't?
Sashay Away.
Travel.
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Are you trying to say
something?
- Please do.
[laughter]
- And last but not least,
for fashion, Eleganza goes to...
Chad Michaels,
which leaves What's the T?
Celebrity gossip
for Latrice Royale.
All right, ladies, you are on
a tight deadline,
so get to work.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- I think what makes this
challenge so hard is we've not
had to do anything like this.
It kinds separates the
intellectual people from
the not-so-intellectual people.
- Jiggly does go right for that
snack bin, honey.
It helps her think, I think.
Crunch, crunch.
"Oh, yeah, I got an idea."
Health and fitness.
Ha!
- Jiggly.
- [belches]
- Any complaints?
- What the fuck do I know
about working out?
- I know, right!
- Shit.
- See, I'm helping you out,
girl.
- Did they say we have to make
these comedy?
- Never hurts.
- You gotta grab your
attention--do like
the headlines that are on your
back to front cover.
- The thing is, like, me and
comedy obviously doesn't mix.
I think I'm just gonna be real
about it.
- I do not suggest you do this
for real.
I'm sorry.
I think you should make it
funny.
Everybody likes to laugh.
That's my advice to you.
- My only advice with that is
that if you feel like you can
get more with the serious route,
I'd rather you have a consistent
magazine that you can follow
by.
- Phi Phi...shady.
- 'Cause if you fuck up funny,
then it's gonna fuck up bad.
- Exactly.
For me, it's hard to find
the funny in weight loss.
Hell, no, no.
I'm gonna be serious, and I'm
gonna do this the right way
emotionally.
- He's doing a serious one
for his.
- What?
Are you kidding?
- No.
- His humor is, like,
his strongest thing.
- I know that he's gonna mess
up if he does, like, serious.
So I was like, "No,
you should do serious."
I'm tired of Jiggly.
She doesn't belong here.
Send her ass home.
Did you wanna help pack his
bags?
[laughs maniacally]
Ahh, you stupid bitch.
- Today we get to be
editors-in-chief
of our own dragazine.
- I have Tastes Like Chicken.
- We have to design a cover,
pose for it,
and come up with
eye-catching headlines.
"How to stop over-salting
your food,"
'cause I always hear people
talk about that.
Like, people always salt
their food too much, you know.
I really want to, like, almost
class this up a little bit.
It can easily come off as
offensive.
You know, a black woman on
the cover of a magazine saying--
with a title like that.
- [laughs]
Girl, go on.
- It's like, I don't even like
to really eat chicken in public.
- Girl, really?
- I don't eat watermelon in
public, because people are
ignorant and people make
comments.
- I know, girl, but--
- It's disrespectful and rude.
- 5 Gs, please.
Good God, get a grip, girl.
'Cause it's not that serious.
Really, you're a dude in a wig.
[laughs]
- Latrice, she set you up.
- She set me up.
Latrice was trying
to gook a bitch.
- [laughs]
- Can I please win a challenge?
Hopefully, I could exchange my
mini challenges for a win.
- You should step up your game,
girl.
Win a big one.
- So far in this competition,
I haven't won a main challenge.
Doing graphic and web design,
this is what I do
in my day job,
so if I lose this challenge,
it's gonna make me upset.
Honestly,
I don't want Sugar Walls.
- This is the one I wanted.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Well, I'm glad for you,
but I did not want that.
You're a sarcastic little bitch,
so you'll come up
with something.
- Where there's a Willam,
there's a way.
The only problem I'm having
in the workroom today is,
I just want to tell
the others girls,
"You can stop.
I'm gonna win."
- Hello, hello, hello.
[together]
Hi, Ru.
Hi.
- How are my future media
moguls doing?
- Fabulous.
- Well, well,
busy at work here.
Tastes Like Chicken.
How are you gonna convey Dida
in "Chicken of the Month?
- Well, "Chicken of the Month,"
I mean,
there's so many different ways
you can cook chicken.
- Seriously?
I would've took that whole
chicken thing into
a whole
different direction.
- You can broil it,
you can fry it.
- But how will we know this
is Dida?
- It's me.
Who else would think of
"Chicken of the month"?
I haven't heard Oprah come up
with it yet.
I mean,
you're fascinated by that.
You want to pick up the magazine
and look at it.
- Well...
- "Chicken of the Month" for me.
- Uh-huh, okay.
- I believe in my idea, and if
it makes me have to lip sync
for my life, then so be it.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
Sashay Away.
So tell me about the cover.
- Well, I'm channeling
the horny gay, like 69 hot spots
for hookups.
- You know, the challenge is
to combine travel and Phi Phi
O'Hara's esthetic.
How are you gonna do that?
- Well, Phi Phi's sexy.
I'm just gonna, you know,
showcase my sexiness.
- This reminds me of when you
told me you were going to make
Lady Gaga really pop.
Do you remember that
conversation?
- She popped;
it might not have been in a
good way,
but she popped.
- All right, get to work.
- All righty, thanks, Ru.
- Sharon Needles.
- Hi.
- Kitty Cat magazine.
Who is this magazine for?
- Well, you know,
I see the cat magazines
at the pet store,
and they're always geared to,
like, grandmas and, like,
sad ladies that never
fell in love and stuff.
So this is more for, like,
Edie Beale,
that, you know, have cats,
because they're cheaper
than boyfriends.
- So, now, what does
Kitty Cats magazine say
about Sharon Needles?
- [meows]
- Now, listen.
I want you to make
your dragazine appeal to me.
Even though I don't have a cat.
I want you to make me want
to get a cat.
- Okay.
- And just knock 'em dead,
kiddo.
- I will.
Thanks a lot.
- Willam.
- Hi.
- Editrix-in-chief of
Sugar Walls magazine.
- I prefer editor-in-queef.
- [laughs]
So now who would you say is your
target audience for Sugar Walls?
- Um...
women.
Men.
- All of the above.
- Uh-huh.
- It's a little broad to just
do men and women.
And, you know, there is
a certain esthetic that you have
that's very clear-cut.
That's what we wanna see in this
magazine.
- Yes, ma'am.
- All right.
Jiggly Caliente.
- Hey, Mama.
- May I call you Jiggly?
- Oh, Mama,
you can call me Jiggly anytime.
- Oh. Battle of the Bulge.
- Yeah.
- Were you insulted by being
assigned that magazine?
- Yes, I've done some bad
things to lose weight.
- Well, what kind of things
have you done?
- I decided to binge and eat
a lot and throw it all up.
And I would say that it's not
the smartest thing to do.
And I just think that when it
comes to weight loss, it's not
a joking matter.
- You've been able to process
what people think of you through
your humor.
I mean, you're Jiggly Caliente.
That's your name.
Embrace the Jiggly.
- I am, I'm--
- Do you hear what I'm saying
to you?
- Yeah.
- You're funny.
Do that.
It's not rocket science.
- I'm going to stick to my guns,
because this,
I'm not questioning this.
This is the right way for me.
- Okay, all right.
Well, you got your work cut out
for you, Jiggly.
- Yes, I do.
- Think about it.
Chad Michaels.
- RuPaul.
- Editor-in-chief
of Eleganza dragazine.
- Finally.
- [laughs]
- I've been waiting.
Eleganza magazine is going
to be geared toward drags
and the women who love drags.
Sort of the major is gonna be,
"Dusted or Busted?
The Fashion and Runway Trashin'
of RuPaul's Drag Race: Season 4.
- Oh, so this is an inside look
at some of the fashion
we've seen so far
in this season.
- And the inside scoop.
- I want to know that.
- It's gonna be fantastic.
- I can't wait to see
what the Eleganza woman
is wearing next season.
[roaring]
- I'd like to show you.
Drag cougar, honey.
- [laughs]
Them old girls still have it.
- Yes. All right, kiddo.
See you later.
- Thanks, Ru.
Thank you.
Well, Latrice Royale.
Girl, What's the T?
- What's the T, Ru?
- How are you gonna make your
dragazine something that is
relevant in the 21st century?
- You're gonna wanna buy it
once you see me on the cover
because everyone knows that
Latrice is the true "T".
- Well, the publications at
the grocery have stars on
the cover, and they have star
names in their articles.
- Oh.
So I'm gonna go back to my
research department.
- Yes.
- I'll get it there.
- You get to it.
- Thank you.
- All right, dolls,
gather round.
Tomorrow night is the launch
of your dragazines.
We'll be joined by our extra
special guest judges.
platinum-selling country artist
Pam Tillis will be here.
- Yee-haw!
- Pam Tillis, old-school
country diva, honey.
- And an actress I've loved
since she was a child on 227.
The star TV's Southland,
Regina King will be here.
[cheering]
- I love Regina King.
She's on a show called
Southland.
Oh, wait, I was on a show called
- Oh, and one last thing.
Don't fuck it up.
All right, bye.
- Bye, Ru.
- Hi, gorgeous.
- Hi.
Ooh, hi. How are you?
- Good,
I'm Jonathan Clay Harris.
So what are we doing today?
- Our challenge this week is,
we have to develop our own
dragazine.
So now we're gonna pose for our
fabulous cover.
My magazine
is Tastes Like Chicken.
I want it to be a sexy magazine
but with chicken.
- Yeah, give me some sexy.
Sex appeal with that one.
Oh, my God, chicken?
Chicken?
- Chicken.
- Yeah, work that chicken.
Show me a little hunger
in those eyes.
- What drag queen do you know
that has taken a head shot
with chicken?
Chicken!
- And what are you serving
for dinner tonight?
- Look at you.
You look gorgeous.
- Yeah, you too.
- Oh, thank you.
- Have you done porn?
- Not recently.
- Well, you should really
consider it.
Thought it would be a genius
idea mounting the cat climber,
channeling my inner kitty cat.
- Just be careful.
- I can trust myself.
- All right, Sharon, I don't
think this is working.
Let's go back.
- God, you don't know anything
about fashion.
Okay, we're gonna just do
chairs.
- There you go.
- Work that hand...
Eleganza.
- I wanted to seem like
a powerful bitchy mogul woman.
- Let's get a little more of
that pussy in there.
There you are.
Beautiful, right there.
- I was totally giving
the camera nothing but legs,
and I was giving them pure
cunt face.
- Beautiful.
- I feel sexy in anything,
even a body bag.
- Hello.
How are you?
- Oh, wow.
- So what's your magazine cover
that you're doing today?
- I'm doing, uh...
what was it?
Bulge of--
Battle of the Bulge.
- Battle of the Bulge, okay.
Are those RuPaul's
Iron Fist shoes?
- Yeah, these are RuPaul
Iron Fist shoes.
- Those are amazing.
- Aren't they sickening?
- They're sickening.
- This is the most exercise I'm
gonna get for the rest
of my life.
- Oh, no.
Here we go.
Little Kill Bill action.
- God, if Phi Phi was just in
front of me, I could've knocked
her ass out for all that shit
she be running her mouth with.
Please don't trip me.
- We won't.
- One, two, three.
- Okay, once more, here we go.
[laughs]
- Doesn't matter, as long as
it looks like
it's in the air.
- Let's do it again.
Loosen a little bit.
Just mind your face
when you're jumping.
- Okay, I'm cool.
One, two...
- I just didn't think that
it kind of worked with Jiggly.
She just seemed so completely
uncomfortable with the camera.
- And you have to spot me.
- Point your eyes at me just
for a couple frames.
Gorgeous.
Look at those eyes.
- So my final wardrobe for
the photograph is really kind
of a '40s glam red carpet dress.
I could see someone like
Veronica Lake wearing it to
a movie premiere.
- And what do the goggles say
about your outfit?
- The goggles say,
"she's an adventurer and she's
fashion-forward."
- She looks like it.
- Right now it is important for
me to get out there and give
the judges some variety to be
a little bit less polished,
to be avant-garde.
I think I'm good.
I think we got it.
- I wanna look like--like--
like a hot Miami piece of ass.
Like you wanna visit me.
- Work, here we go.
You look like it to me.
- Good.
- Let's do it.
Miami, honey.
I wanna go for a more sexier
side of Phi Phi, something that
I haven't showed yet, and, you
know, I wanna be, like, a whore
on this magazine and have whore
headlines.
- Let's see some sex
in those eyes.
Here we go.
- I'm throwing you, like,
a Farrah Fawcett sexy look,
and, you know, I had the drink
in my hand.
I'm holding the umbrella.
Hold on, I don't want
my muscles showing.
I gotta look like a woman.
- You wanna look at 'em?
- Yeah, I feel sexy already.
So let's look at 'em.
I'm prettier than the other
girls, aren't I?
You can say it.
- I'm not going to.
- You should.
Delete that one.
That looks like a man.
I look like Sharon in that one.
- Okay.
[laughter]
Ouch.
- Yes, Mama, right there.
Good.
Beautiful.
Boys, I want you touching her.
- So What's the T? is a gossip
column magazine.
Of course I'm featured on the
cover with my boys.
The boys.
Always helps when you have boys.
Come and join me on the couch.
Let's have a ménage à trois.
The boys, of course, is just for
my sheer amusement and pleasure.
Come do something.
Come rub on me.
Let me rub on you.
- Latrice, look at me.
Eyes at me, everyone.
Eyes at me.
Sex in the face.
Look at me.
- I love my boys,
and that's the "T".
- Sex sells, people.
Sex sells.
My overall concept is
stripped-down design.
Mama needs some tape.
Your head is so unprofessional.
- [chuckling]
- I tried to dress the pit crew
as lamps and put lamp shades on
their head, but their heads
aren't even.
And they wouldn't let me put
nails in them.
And remember to flex, boys.
I don't want you looking puny.
[laughter]
No faces, you don't exist.
- Willam was beautiful and
definitely knew her body.
- [laughing]
♪ I'm the prettiest one ♪
♪ Now that Kenya's gone ♪
- I thought she was a little
bitchy.
You guys look amazing.
- Please don't address them.
- Right.
- You can't fuck me.
[laughs]
I'm gonna fall.
- Good.
Let's take a look at these.
- I'm naked, I'm tan,
and I have boys around me.
I'm happy with the photo shoot.
All right, now clean this
shit up.
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chatter]
- Good morning,
mother cluckers.
- We're back.
- We're back!
- We're back in the workroom
today,
and we're getting ready
to present our magazines on
the runway in our glossy glamour
looks.
- How did your challenge go
for you guys?
- Mine went well.
- I liked mine.
- Well, you have a health and
fitness magazine.
Why would you go serious
on that?
Obviously you were assigned
that magazine to, you know,
ham it up.
[laughter]
- There's more to me than just
being funny and goofy.
1240 on the SATs.
I need to show that I have
intelligence.
Girl.
- Latrice, does your family
still live--where are you from
again?
- Atlanta.
- Have you ever been, like,
bullied or whatever by family?
- From my brother, yeah.
He didn't want no punk for
a brother.
- My dad did that in front of,
like,
his fucking drinking
buddies.
I grew up in a house where
I was beat and made fun of for
being gay.
It was hell.
Family's supposed to love you
no matter what.
And if that's love,
I don't want it.
- You couldn't hold hands,
kiss, look at each other in
Texas without getting called
a faggot or anything.
- What kills me is that they
wanna say that we're the ones
destroying the institution
of marriage.
Please.
- You know, I've met gay people,
though,
that don't agree with
gay marriage.
- I--okay, here we go.
Since y'all brought it up.
- Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
- I just don't want it to be
called marriage.
For me, marriage describes
a straight relationship.
And I think we should be called
something else.
Call it something more fabulous.
- As a gay man, it's just hard
for me to believe that you don't
want equal rights for yourself.
- I did not say that.
- But if it's all the same
thing as marriage,
why not call it that?
- Because it's not the same
thing to me.
- Yes, it is.
- I will be pissed if Latrice
is gonna be the first one that
gets married too, bitch.
- Hell to the no.
- I fully support gay divorce.
- [laughing]
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, gorgeous.
- Hey, Ru.
- Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, you old tool.
- What you talking 'bout, tool?
- On newsstands everywhere,
it's Santino Rice.
- Lookin' beautiful
as a fresh bruise.
Black and blue.
- Grammy award-winner
Pam Tillis.
I am so excited you're here.
- You are like a song.
I'm telling you.
[trills tongue]
- [laughs]
And Regina King.
Hey, girl, you look like
a cover girl.
- Oh, thank you.
So do you.
You have to show me how you
create the hair blowing without
the fan look.
- [laughs]
This week, our queens went to
the presses to launch a new
dragazine, and now they're ready
to pump up your circulation.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
First up, Sharon Needles in
black and white, editorial.
- She's black and white and
fierce all over.
- This is a glamorous look for
Sharon Needles.
- It is.
- I'm feeling like
the Tim Burton
vintage sci-fi glamazon.
I feel stunning.
- Her booty looks awesome
in that dress.
- Yes, thanks, DuPont.
Very Valley of the Dolls.
- I was thinking
Jackie Collins.
- Kind of like a possessed
- Yes, yes.
Up next, Dida Ritz.
- Not just a cracker.
- No.
- What'd you call me?
- I love the little "S" walk.
- Yes, it's a strategic walk
so a sniper can't get her.
[laughter]
- I'm serving you
editor-in-chief realness.
Old Hollywood glamour.
I feel sexy.
- Tastes like chicken.
Looks like fish.
- Uh-uh.
- Chad Michaels.
Rock and roll.
- Lita Ford.
- Pat Benatar.
- Tonight I'm wearing something
more dangerous.
My paint is much darker
than usual.
I'm loving my short hair.
I'm feeling fantastic.
- Guns &amp; Ammo magazine.
Cover of Rolling Stone.
- Where is her Stratocaster?
- Yes.
- It's hidden.
- Latrice Royale.
Ebony magazine.
- Foldout.
- Yes, honey, this is
a two-page spread.
- I walk out giving my Gothy
glam, very Nubian princess,
lots of jewels and cleavage,
and I feel gorgeous.
- She makes glamour look
real simple.
- I love the jewels down the
back.
- Yes, gorgeous.
- Like a character from
The Wiz.
- Uh-huh.
- Up next, Willam.
Red carpet ready.
- Kylie Minogue.
- Kylie min-yes.
- Just the whole body, jeez.
- Uh-huh.
- I feel confident
on the runway.
I'm just giving them cute girl,
fish salad realness with a side
of Teddy.
- Hollywood starlet.
- Back action and everything.
- I want a lifetime
subscription.
- Jiggly Caliente.
- Venus de Brooklyn.
- Build me up, buttercup.
- Uh-huh.
- I want the judges to take it
all in, catch it.
Look at all the Swarovskis.
I want them to try to count how
many Swarovski there are on
this gown.
I look like a fucking
lemon drop.
A blinging lemon drop.
- That's a pretty dress.
- It is gorgeous.
I love me a train.
- Mm.
I'm gonna leave that alone.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Ooh.
- Wow.
Serving body and turquoise.
- I love the proportion.
- Yeah.
- Love all that leg.
Beautiful.
- Go on and take
the center stage.
- Walking down the runway,
I'm feeling super sexy and
flirty, and I'm just having
a good time out there.
It's a fishy outfit,
I look really pretty in it.
I look glamorous.
- This is the best Phi Phi
has ever looked.
Very Cosmo girl.
No Photoshop necessary.
Hello, dolls.
Let's find out whose dragazines
are fresh and fabulous, and
whose are just conde nasty.
Up first, Chad Michaels.
Eleganza.
- Yes.
- I wanted to take the theme
of Eleganza, which was style,
and gear it toward drag cougars
and the women who love them.
- I didn't know what type of
magazine it was.
It's just all over the place.
- It looks like something that
you would pick up for free at
the grocery store.
You look beautiful tonight.
Love the one-shoulder.
You look great in black.
- You guys challenged me to
dirty it up a little bit,
and I feel fantastic.
- I love that Chad thinks
this is dirty.
I guess it is for Chad.
- All right, up next,
Dida Ritz.
Tastes Like Chicken.
- Yeah, that's what they say.
- I wanted to add a little bit
of, you know, glamour to it,
and my inspiration was really
the type of women you see on
the Food Network.
- I saw "stop."
It kind of is at odds with your
fun look and your fun colors,
and then this negative message.
- I like black hair on you.
It looks very pretty.
Just next time think more
volume.
I keep telling you more volume.
It's all about the silhouette.
- All right, next up,
Sharon Needles.
Kitty Cats.
Meow.
- I wanted to create a hip cat
magazine for, like, young
hipsters that love cats.
- Oh, you nasty bitch.
You--oh, my God, I love
the headlines.
I just wanna read it.
I wanna know how many is too
many.
- Well, I'm talking about cats.
You're a pervert.
- Oh, I know, I know,
I know.
But the eyes scare me.
- They're my trademark.
- But everything else is just
so pretty and elegant.
It, like, creeps me out.
- I am still waiting to see
full-on glam, no eyes,
no Goth Sharon Needles.
Just once.
I don't think you'll lose you.
- Next up, Latrice Royale.
What's the T?
- If my magazine was on the
newsstand, if you're not picking
it up for me, you're definitely
gonna pick it up for the hot
boys that are lusting after me,
so...
- I sort of expected your
magazine to be like, "Shh!"
- It looks like the name of the
magazine is "Hollywood."
It looks more like a club flyer.
- You don't need the pit crew
boys on there at all.
It really looks like you got
some hookers somewhere.
- This gown that you came out
in, it's like, ugh,
that's so heavy.
It looks like a couch from
Rent-A-Center.
- I think there's a little too
much jewelry; I don't know.
- Oh, Lord, Jesus.
- Showgirls.
[laughter]
- Oh, oh.
- Oh.
My bracelet breaks.
Oh, fuck.
In front of everybody.
- But already that looks
better.
It does.
- Next up, Willam.
Sugar Walls.
- I love home design, and I
made one of the pillows
on the cover.
I'm a power bottom like that.
- I love what you look like
tonight, but in the beard area,
we see the shadow again tonight.
- Touch this.
Touch all of this.
- I'm trying to help because
you're the only one that has it.
So it really hits hard when it's
out there.
- Your dragazine cover is
possibly the worst one.
I hate the font.
- Me too.
- Okay.
- This looks like a porn thing
about to happen.
I'm getting anything but
decorating from this.
- Yeah, I wouldn't have hired
myself to be that designer.
I love the ideas that I had.
I wish I had more time to
execute them and a better staff.
- See, my career I've had to do
every single part of
show business.
You know, edit, produce,
you name it.
And that's what we're really
looking for.
Next up, Jiggly Caliente.
May I call you Jiggly?
- No.
- [laughs]
Battle of the Bulge.
- I found the funny, and I
found the silly humor in it.
Battle of the Bulge,
ya, ya, ya!
- I think with Battle of the
Bulge you could have really
taken it anywhere.
- Yeah, because when we spoke
in the workroom, I was going on
and on about you should approach
it with more humor.
- I chose to play with words
instead of the humor because
I don't know anything about
fitness.
What the hell would I write
about, how to eat a pound
of chicken?
- Exactly, that's funny.
- Oh, damn.
[laughter]
- Next up, Phi Phi O'Hara.
You got Sashay Away,
the travel dragazine.
Wow, va-va-voom.
- This is the best I've ever
seen you look so far.
- Yeah, all the proportions
are right.
Cute little outfit.
Your makeup looks lovely.
- Thank you.
- What happened?
[laughing]
- You look gorgeous on
the cover.
The color makes me wanna go
wherever you are.
This looks like an actual
magazine.
- You picked all the key words
to highlight.
Bathhouse, 69, virginity.
I would read this inside
and out.
- All right, ladies, while you
enjoy an Absolut cocktail in
the Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
All right, just between us
girls, what do you think?
Chad Michaels.
- The runway really made up for
the look that's on the cover
of Eleganza magazine,
which is horrible.
- And it's just not modern
or hip.
- If you're looking for hip,
young, and trendy, you ain't
gonna find it in Chad Michaels.
- Dida Ritz.
- I'm just kind of thinking
she's somewhere in the middle
today.
She was cute on the cover.
- I never equate fabulous drag
queens and cute.
- Right.
- I wanna be devastated.
- She comes out like a straight
line with these big football
player shoulders with flat hair.
She's a pretty girl, but it
seems like we're getting stuck
here a little bit with Dida.
- All right, let's move on to
Sharon Needles.
- I really like her sense of
comedy.
There's something really cool
about her.
- Yeah, her dragazine,
very funny, tongue in cheek.
And it looks like it reeks of
cat piss in there.
- I did like her dragazine.
- Do I think it's the best?
No.
- Latrice Royale.
- The dragazine cover was like
Sydney Biddle Barrows, you know?
It was like a madam's calling
card.
- Willam and Sugar Walls
dragazine.
- She totally missed the mark,
and I really feel like this was
probably one of the easiest
ones to do.
And there's something about her
on stage that's a bit robotic.
It's like she stood there with
the same exact smile.
It was kind of creepy.
I kept, like, looking over to
see, all right, okay, 20 minutes
has passed by, and she was
still...
- Yeah, that don't move.
- She's got a major attitude,
and I like that, though.
Good news, bad news.
Good news, she's a diva.
Bad news, she's a diva.
- Jiggly Caliente and
Battle of the Bulge.
- You know, Jiggly seems to be
some sort of self-sabotage.
- Yes.
- Maybe she doesn't feel like
she deserves to be here.
- Right.
- And if you don't believe it,
nobody else will.
- Moving on to Phi Phi O'Hara
and Sashay Away magazine.
This looked like the most
professional magazine of
the whole bunch.
- It did, but as we're going
through all of these I'm
wondering did it look like
the most professional because
everything else was so bad?
- [laughs]
- I had a problem with the fact
that she wore
a blonde cap with
blonde hair.
She looked like she had a dead
baby lamb on her head.
- And who wants that?
- Nobody.
- Sharon Needles.
- There'd be blood coming out.
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your dragazines and
your presentations on the main
stage, I've made some decisions.
[suspenseful music]
Phi Phi O'Hara, your travel
dragazine was a real trip.
And we're excited that you keep
taking us to new places.
You are the winner of this
week's challenge.
[applause]
- Ah, thank God.
- You've won a cruise to
the Bahamas courtesy of
alandchuck.travel.
- Oh, man.
[laughs]
Oh, finally.
This is my first win, and I'm
really excited because it's nice
to know that my hard work has
paid off.
Those girls better watch out.
- Sharon Needles, you're safe.
Dida Ritz...
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Chad Michaels.
- Yes, ma'am?
- This week the judges were not
gagging on your Eleganza.
You...
are safe.
- [exhales]
Thank you.
- Jiggly Caliente, once again
you left us hungry for more.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- Again?
Seriously?
That's just straight-up jank.
- Latrice Royale...
you're safe.
Willam, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- When Ru tells me about being
in the bottom two,
I feel shaken,
and it's a little scary.
- Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight you were asked
to prepare a lip sync
performance of Mi Vida Loca
by Pam Tillis.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you to
lip sync...for your life.
- I'm gonna fight till the end.
No way I'm gonna let this skinny
Botox bitch send my ass home.
- Good luck and don't fuck
it up.
- ♪ If you're coming with me ♪
♪ You need nerves of steel ♪
♪ 'Cause I take corners ♪
♪ On two wheels ♪
♪ Well it's a never-ending ♪
♪ Circus ride ♪
♪ The faint of heart ♪
♪ Need not apply ♪
♪ Mi vida loca ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ Destiny turns on a dime ♪
- I mean, I hate to say it,
but I think Willam did good.
She looked very much a young
country pop star.
- ♪ Welcome to my crazy life ♪
♪ ♪
- God damn, you couldn't give
me a Lil' Kim song?
- I really, really wished
I had panties on.
But I didn't think I'd have
to lip sync.
- ♪ Mi vida loca ♪
- Jiggly is pretty much
standing in one spot.
Not good.
- ♪ Over and over ♪
♪ Welcome to my crazy life ♪
♪ ♪
[applause]
- Bravo.
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Willam...
shantay, you stay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
And I'll always try to do
my best.
If I fall short, I'm sorry.
- Jiggly Caliente,
may I call you Jiggly?
- Yes.
- Good, because after your time
here, you'll be on a first-name
basis with millions of fans.
Now, sashay away.
- Thank you so much.
I love you.
Deuces.
- [laughs]
- I'm disappointed, but I know
my mom would be so proud of me.
I fucking fought my way.
And it just didn't happen.
But life goes on.
It's all good.
- My sensational six.
The race to become America's
next drag superstar is still
wide open.
Now remember, if you can't love
yourself how in the hell are you
gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen.
- All right,
now let the music play.