- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
I want you to meet some dilfs.
- Whoa!
- Or...
"Dads I'd like to frock."
- [chuckling]
You know who you look like
right now?
Rick James.
[laughter]
- How you doing?
- Pretty good, you?
- Good.
Don't talk to my dad.
That's what I like, 'cause that
way I can school these hoes.
- Phi Phi loves to come for me.
Come for me, baby.
[cabaret music]
♪ ♪
- Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
- Whoo! Yeah, girl!
- Latrice Royale...
shante, you stay.
- Thank you.
Lil' Kenya Michaels.
Sashay away.
[inaudible]
And tonight,
the queens get catty.
- ♪ Coming down the runway ♪
♪ 400 pounds ♪
♪ I'm Latrice ♪
- And it's any bitch's game.
- You're on stage, lying,
is what you're doing.
- I'm not lying.
- Bullshit.
- With extra special
guest judges
Rose McGowan and Wynonna Judd.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive
a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics,
a one-of-a-kind trip,
courtesy of alandchuck.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring Absolut vodka--
cocktails perfected--
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And may the best woman win!
- We are back in the workroom
this morning.
Kenya's gone again,
and we're sad, but we're kinda
glad that she didn't knock
any of the fantastic four
out of the running.
- [imitating Kenya]
"Girl, I say bye again."
[laughter]
- Read the whole thing in
that voice.
- "When I left this competition,
I feel loved.
"I love you and the winner is...
I don't know."
- Yes.
[laughter]
- I'm pretty sure she just
forgot to write my name.
- Well, we talk about
consistency,
and I consistently wear some
nonsense on that runway.
- It makes total sense to them.
- I think they're just holding
us to our own personal standard,
and they want to see
that you are...
- [sighs]
- Completely pushing yourself,
but that you are yourself.
- I want to go out as
Sharon Needles just one time
and see what happens.
- Yeah, and get read.
They're gonna be like, "You"--
- Ohh--
- Hey, it's all about risks.
- I come out as a freak too.
I used to do Club Kids.
But this is about being
America's next drag superstar.
And a superstar should have some
finished hems on their garments.
Oh, um, I won a trip to Vegas,
just in case y'all missed that
on the stage.
- Bitch, you gonna be
on vacation a lot, bitch.
- Where's my vacation?
All I wanted was a cruise.
- Shut up, stupid,
you're not getting one.
- It's your second time
in the bottom.
- Yeah, second time
But you know what?
If you're not on the top at this
point, you're on the bottom.
But some of us
have not lip-synched--
- Girl, I can't help it
if I'm consistent.
- Oh, "I'm consistently
perfect."
- I brought my A game
to this competition.
If perfection is the worst thing
that people can call me,
then call it.
- Well, they don't want you
breaking a hip up there, girl.
[siren blares]
- Ooh, girl!
You got shemail.
Hello, my pets.
- Hi, baby.
- If life's a ball,
I say go fetch it, girl.
Because it's a drag-eat-drag
world out there.
And sometimes,
a queen's best friend
can be a real bitch!
[barking, panting]
[all laughing]
Hello, hello, hello!
- Good morning.
- For today's mini challenge,
we're gonna have a good
old-fashioned bitchfest!
- Ooh.
- And we're gonna do it
with puppets!
- Everyone loves puppets.
- Everyone loves puppets!
First, you pick a puppet
that represents
one of your competitors.
Second, you drag it up.
Third, you and the puppet
have a bitchfest.
First up, Sharon Needles.
Reach inside that black hole
and pick your puppet.
- [chuckling]
- Careful, there might be
teeth in there.
- [gasp]
Ms. Chad Michaels.
- The resemblance is uncanny.
Next up, Latrice Royale.
- Oh, of course!
I got Sharon Needles.
- Next up, Chad Michaels.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- You better get some spray tan.
- He needs glasses.
I don't think my puppet
really looks like me.
He's, like, albino,
and then he has black hair.
I don't have black hair,
and I have a mohawk.
That was not my puppet.
- So Chad has Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Wah, wah.
- "I'm old."
[laughter]
- Last but not least...
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- A little black baby.
♪ Latrice ♪
[laughter]
- You have 20 minutes
to drag up your puppet.
On your mark, get set, go!
- Ah!
Gimme some black,
and some black,
and then gimme some more black
'cause that's Sharon
Needles, down!
[giggling]
- I'm gonna kick your ass, Chad.
- Why? What did I do?
- Bitch, I'm not that orange.
- What the hell?
Sharon's doll look like
a burn victim.
I guess it's plastic surgery
gone wrong.
- All right.
Time's up.
Let the bitchfest begin!
- Hi, Ms. Michaels.
"Oh, hi, Sharon."
You're just a vision
of perfection.
"But Michelle Visage
wants me to show
"some rough and tough looks
looks on the runway.
What does that bitch
want out of me?"
I think you look perfect,
especially your silicone work.
"Sweetie, getting silicone
removed from your face
"is about as hard as getting
a cigarette around here.
Can I get a fucking cigarette?"
[laughter]
- Hey, Sharon, good to see you.
"Fuck off."
No, really, girl,
what's going on?
"I don't strive for perfection.
I can just basically--
"you know, you see this dress?
I made this dress,
"and it's basically shit.
"And they just love it.
They love it. They eat it up.
"But you know what?
"I didn't get
my fucking cruise.
Where's my fucking cruise?"
Well, girl, just calm down
because you're kinda spooky.
"Well, thank you, Latrice.
Fuck off."
Okay, thanks.
- I certainly never tell anyone
to fuck off.
- Hi, Phi Phi,
how are you doing today?
"Um, I just wanna say
that I love everybody.
[giggling]"
You know, I'm always afraid
I'm gonna snag my costume
on your tooth, girl.
"[gasp] Oh, my God,
"I can't believe you went there,
Chad Michaels.
I'll get you later."
And what about your wig,
Phi Phi?
It's really pretty,
but haven't you worn that
like three times already?
- My snaggle tooth
is not that big,
and that puppet
looked nothing like me.
- Well, maybe you
could get the help
to help you out
next time, Phi Phi.
"I am not a racist.
I do not know why you guys
keep harping on that."
Yes, you're right, Phi Phi.
You're absolutely right.
I'm sure America's
just gonna love you.
[laughter]
- Oh, it's on, bitch.
Nah-ah.
- Chad got some shade
that lies deep within, honey.
- Hey, Latrice,
how are you doing?
♪ "Coming down the runway
in a velvet gown ♪
♪ "Coming down the runway,
400 pounds ♪
♪ I'm Latrice! ♪
Oh, is that your new single?
"Yeah, I'm the
Barry White of drag."
Oh, and that's, like,
a real beautiful necklace.
Where'd you get that from?
"Well, my friend
Lashauwn Beyon--"
[bracelet breaks, falls]
[all cackling]
- Oh, Lord Jesus.
- Oh, girl, this is awkward.
We should probably go.
- Yay!
[laughs]
- Ladies, you let it all
hang out.
The winner of today's
mini challenge is...
Chad Michaels.
- Phi Phi, we won, I love you.
- Condragulations.
You're the baddest bitch
in town.
- Thanks, Ru.
- All right, ladies,
in the great tradition
of Paris Is Burning,
for this week's main challenge,
we're throwing
our first-ever Bitch Ball.
- Oh.
- What?
- And you'll be doing it...
doggie style.
[dog barking]
First category,
daytime dog park realness.
[dog yaps]
- Oh.
- Second category is...
pooch in a purse party girl.
[dog yips, whines]
Third category is...
canine couture.
[dog barks]
A high-fashion look
inspired by a real-life dog.
[all gasp]
- Puppy!
- Babies!
How cute.
- Oh!
- Meet your fashion inspiration
and runway partners--
Filan, a Chinese crested.
Cali, a standard poodle.
Babyface, a Pomeranian.
And Hunter, a bloodhound.
Chad, since you won the mini
challenge,
you get to match each queen
with her dog.
- Hi, Hunter.
We're gonna do
opposites attract.
- I knew you were gonna
do that to me.
Bitch!
Ugh!
- Little baby!
- Oh, a little baby.
- So Babyface is with Latrice.
- You're beautiful,
but you're kinda edgy and crazy.
- Come here, Cali.
- Cali goes with
Sharon Needles.
- And I'm gonna take you,
you little beauty.
- Chad is partnered with Filan.
Ladies, you can use
your own drag,
plus furry fixin's
we have provided, and...
RuPaul's Drag Race
iron fist shoes.
[dog barks]
I think Phi Phi might be
in heat.
- Wow, Phi Phi.
- Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best bitch win!
- [barking]
- Whoa!
[laughing]
- [sigh] I'm already tired.
- See, this is a mess.
This is how you steal my heart
right here.
- We're all just bonding
with our dogs,
and I'm noticing that Phi Phi's
dog is a real handful.
- [sigh]
You're impossible.
Stay here for like five seconds.
Ah! Ooh!
- You know, Hunter seemed
to take a liking to Phi Phi.
- Ugh, you're drooling
on my artwork.
- Phi Phi's dog
is helping her draw.
- I definitely got
the worst dog.
I mean, who really wants
to fashion their clothes
after a bloodhound?
- Are you mad at me?
- No, Chad,
why would I be mad at you?
This is a competition.
- Well, you're the only one
that really looks at it that way
right now.
- Sharon, I don't need
your two cents.
- I didn't do it
to fuck you over.
- I didn't say you did, did I?
- I know, but you
just seem, like, mad.
- Chad--she's full of crap.
She knows that I'm one of
the strongest competitors here,
and so she's trying to get me
out of the game.
[dog growling]
- Don't be mad, girl.
- Girl, shut up.
- She just told me to shut up.
[dog barks]
- Get inspired.
Tell me what I should use.
You like this?
Do you like this fabric?
- Mwah!
[dog whining]
For today's challenge,
we need to create
three distinct looks
for the Bitch Ball--
dog park realness,
puppy in a purse,
and canine couture
inspired by a dog.
[dog yips]
Who's yappin'?
- Is that Willam
dropping names over there?
[dog yips]
- Shut your yapper.
You guys, I think Phi Phi
might be pissed off at me...
for giving her that bloodhound.
- Well, she's not happy
about it.
- If the shoe was on
the other foot,
she would have tried to get us
with her dog decisions.
- I didn't do it
to fuck anybody over,
but it's also I fucking won the
challenge, so it's up to me.
- True that.
- This is a competition.
I can't be preoccupied
with how Phi Phi's feeling.
- I know you're excited
I'm back.
- Sss!
[dogs whimpers, yips]
- I know he had a plan.
He can deny it as much
as he wants, but I mean,
in the end, I'm still
gonna win this challenge.
- [laughs]
- Oh, how did you get off?
Come here.
Oh.
Come on, let's go back.
- Oh, girl.
- Did she step on your
white fabric, girl?
- Yeah, she got paw prints
on everything.
- It's gonna be an adventure.
Get into it.
- Sharon, how do you feel
about this challenge,
like, are you glad you got
the standard poodle?
- To be honest, I did kind of
want Miss Michaels' dog,
just because there's so many
beautiful shades of...
- So pretty.
- Beige and gray and mauve.
I mean--
- That's why I got it.
- That dog's wearing
all my colors.
- This is gonna be so different
to see you in white, bitch.
- In white.
Well, I mean, you usually
don't see a dark lady
in the dog park during the day.
- White's not really my color.
Like I always say,
"Send me to hell.
I don't look good in white."
It definitely
is making me nervous.
And I'm not gonna be able to,
like, rely on my shocking makeup
because it's gonna have to work
with three separate looks.
This will be somewhat
of a challenge.
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hello.
- You look like you could use
a little pup talk.
- Ha.
- Ha ha.
- Hey, Latrice.
- Hey, Ru.
- Hey, Babyface.
Now, you've gotten heat in the
past from the judges--Santino--
- I have.
- About your styling
and your fashion sense.
- Yeah.
- Are you worried
about that at all?
- No, not really, because the
things that I have sewn myself,
people have raved about.
- Good, 'cause you are in
the final four!
- Oooohhh!
- But I gotta say...
there's no room for excuses
or mistakes at this point.
100,000 coins, darling.
- Yeah. And I need every bit
of all of that.
Because my life has been
such a roller coaster
and I've been so unstable
for so long, this is going to,
like, put me where
I'm supposed to be.
Being in prison,
I lost everything.
And it was hard.
But that 100 grand, baby...
that can buy some stuff.
- Remember, we wanna see
a storyline on the runway.
I'm gonna let you get
back to it.
Bye, Babyface.
[laughs]
That bitch is ignoring me.
- [laughs] Thank you, Ru.
- Well, hello, there.
- Hi.
- Are you making love to Filan?
- I've got puppy love.
- [laughing]
The judges in the past--
Michelle--
have said, you know,
that you're...
sometimes too polished.
What does that mean to you?
- I don't know what that means,
Ru, honestly.
I didn't come here
not to be perfect.
- I think she wants
more depth from you,
and this is the perfect
challenge for that.
What are you gonna do for your
daytime dog park realness?
- It's going to be
almost a little bit
Little House On the Prairie.
- Well, that's not particularly
a modern look.
- You'll--it's gonna work out
really well.
- We're asking you to be
fashion forward.
You've got a lot of work to do.
I'm gonna let you and Filan
get to it.
See you in a minute.
- Okay.
- Sharon Needles and Cali.
- Yeah, hi.
- Hi. So tell us about
your canine couture
inspired by Cali.
- I guess I'm kind of going
for a tight body suit
and then use the fur
as maybe like a big bolero.
- That's interesting.
- I think I am going to be
gold and tan tomorrow.
I'm running out of pale
foundation, so...
[both laughing]
- Are you transforming into
someone we don't know?
- Well, you know, um...
we'll have to see.
- That's interesting to hear.
We're down to the best
of the best.
You and Cali have
a lot of work cut out for you.
So I'll let you get
back to it, okay?
- No problem, thanks.
- Well, Phi Phi and Hunter.
How are you kids getting along?
- Well, I mean,
it was difficult at first,
but he's calmed down and he's
allowed me to work, so...
- [laughing]
Right.
So have you controlled
his saliva?
- Oh. Oh, no.
- Is that your inspiration?
- Absolutely.
A sticky, wet mess.
- Tell me about your
dog park realness.
- I really wanna take you,
like, to Paris...
- Ooh!
- And like poodle skirt
type of look, so...
[hunter whines]
- But the poodle skirts
are from the '50s,
and you've got a bloodhound.
- I'm gonna intertwine
both of those, like, styles
to make one look.
- Well, you know,
we really want the costumes
to speak for themselves.
We don't really want
a lot of explanation.
- Okay.
- Now, have you seen
Paris Is Burning?
- I've seen parts of it.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Oh, you've got you homework
to do, don't you, young lady?
You know what the ball scene
is all about, right?
- Oh, yeah.
I'm familiar with it.
- Have you ever walked a ball?
- No, but I've been asked
many times to do it.
- In what category?
- Face--
- But you didn't do it.
- I haven't done it yet, no.
- Ah.
- All right.
You get back to work.
- I have a lot to do.
- Bond with hunter.
- We have.
He's taking a nap.
[both laughing]
So...thank you, Ru.
- All right, ladies,
gather round.
Tomorrow on the main stage,
we'll be joined by our
extra-special guest judges.
She's no bitch, but she plays
one on TV and in the movies.
Rose McGowan will be here.
- [gasps]
- I love Rose!
- Yes!
- Really.
- And the platinum-selling
country superstar
who's always best in show...
Wynonna Judd will be here.
- Wow!
- I love the Judds.
I love Wynonna's music.
She's a kickass
rock and roll chick.
- In addition to modeling your
three doggy-style outfits,
there's just one more
little thing.
[dog yaps]
[dramatic chords]
You'll need to perform a
Broadway-style opening number.
- Bitch, I ain't got time
to do this.
We're trying to pull these
three looks together.
- Think Cats, but,
you know, with dogs.
Chad, since you won the mini
challenge, you're in charge.
- Shit! Is Ru serious?
Is he trying to kill me?
- Ladies,
the dog days aren't over.
In fact...
they're just beginning.
So don't fuck it up.
All right, bye.
[dog whimpers]
- All right, bitches.
It is time to rehearse the dance
routine for the Bitch Ball.
Let's do some blocking.
Kind of my idea's for Phi Phi
to start, like, maybe...
center?
- And maybe we should
kind of be in hidden pose
until we're supposed to animate.
- Or maybe you're just
sitting there like...
- Yeah, scratching fleas
or you know how theater,
how things are completely still?
- I kind of like the idea of
everyone being animated.
Maybe we could do--
- Well, you're in charge, so
just pick, and let's get to it.
- I would like you to do a pose.
- All righty, go.
- Or sideways.
As we get up on our first line,
move up with Phi Phi.
- So maybe we just crawl up
to one point for our line,
and then we...
- Okay, this is how
it really should go,
like a real show.
Because this makes no sense.
So when we're singing our lines,
all of us should get
into our four spots,
and we should land here,
just like we're in a musical.
Or else it's gonna
look like crap.
I'm kinda not having it,
because I really just want
to get all my stuff done,
and I really just
wanna make sure that this
rehearsal goes fast.
♪ I can turn around ♪
- ♪ I can lie on the ground ♪
- ♪ Look what I found ♪
- ♪ I got laid at the pound ♪
all: Whoo!
- ♪ Ruff ruff uh uh uh ♪
all: ♪ The Bitch Ball ♪
- ♪ I'm a sucker for meat ♪
[dramatic chords]
- You're traveling this way,
and then you can just,
like, slide in--
♪ I'm a sucker for meat ♪
- I was the one
that was chosen to lead,
so girlfriend really needs
to calm down
and let me
get a word in edgewise.
You can stay where you are,
but we'll come in front
and then you can, like,
bust through to the front.
- No, that's too long, Mary.
- We're talking about the first
part before we move.
- Why are we talking
about that
when we were just discussing
the second part?
- So that we can get
our transitions
all clear for everybody.
- But we're not transitioning
right there.
That's what we just practiced.
- It is so tense right now.
I can't take too much
more of this,
so let's clear it on up.
Here we go--five, six,
seven, eight, bitches.
♪ Woot uh uh uh ♪
- ♪ At the Bitch Ball ♪
- ♪ Ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ♪
- And to...
- ♪ The Bitch Ball ♪
- Ah.
- Does everybody
feel good about this?
- Ow!
[dog whining]
- Don't eat it!
- So much to do.
- Yeah. The house down.
- This challenge is
a little bit intimidating
just by the sheer volume of
the work that we have to do.
I mean, that's three looks.
That's a lot of styling
and sewing and hair.
[dog whining]
- It's gonna be quite
interesting
on that runway tomorrow.
I'm just thinking about how much
I'm gonna whoop Chad's ass
in this challenge.
- You're hungry, honey.
- You're damn right, I'm hungry.
I don't understand what makes me
so much more hungry
than you guys, though.
- We feel you behind us
pushing us down the stairs.
I saw that movie, girl.
- Yeah, I'm a hungry bitch.
I mean, this is a competition.
There's so much at stake.
There's so many opportunities
form this.
They are just concerned because
they know that I'm here to win.
I love everybody.
- Famous last words.
- I do!
- That's what
the puppet head said.
- [laughing] Shut up.
[Latrice laughing]
- What do you think, Needles?
- Diva!
It's fantastic.
- What do you think?
- Gorgeous, darling.
Turn around.
Let me see it.
Work!
Work.
I still have to sew
a complete dress tonight.
- Ha.
- My original concept was to
create a bolero on a leotard.
Then I realized
I've never sewn a bolero.
Feel like I need some
methamphetamines
to get this project done.
- Just say no, Needles.
- One down.
What do you think
of this boot, Phi?
- [laughs]
Um, it's very much a poodle.
We've been working on our
outfits for a while,
and the only thing
that Sharon has accomplished
is he glued some fur on a boot.
- Phi Phi, can I steal you
for a minute?
Mama, come here for a minute.
- Me?
- Yeah.
- I'm exhausted!
[whispers]
I've never done a hem.
Do I just fold it?
- Yes.
- I know I have three looks
to put together
and on top of that,
sewing a new outfit.
It's just the straw
on the camel's back.
God damn it, my fabric got
caught in my machine.
- Sharon's in trouble.
I think that top four
is her stop.
This is where you get off,
Sharon Needles.
- [grunts] Uh!
[alarm buzzing]
[razor whirring]
- And back to work.
- Poomp!
- It's a dog-eat-dog world.
- Today, we're getting ready
for RuPaul's Bitch Ball.
We know that one of us
has got to go today,
so everybody's
a little bit up in arms,
and trying to pull it out
real quick.
- It's gonna be top three
after this.
- I know.
The stakes are really high
right now, you guys.
- [sighs]
I'm gonna lose my damn mind.
- Well, we don't want
to spin off the board.
I'm feeling not so confident.
I'm not sure, this time,
if it's gonna be enough
to keep me
out of the bottom two.
- Miss Michaels,
remember how psychic I was
when we first got here?
- Oh, my God!
- It was so creepy.
- You guys, this bitch
literally predicted
the whole sitcom
and mug shot challenge
before it happened.
- Told ya I was a witch.
- [laughs]
- Sharon.
- Uh-huh?
- Since you're miss clairvoyant,
who's the top three?
- I predict it will be Latrice,
and Miss Michaels...
and...
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- And you're saying this
based on...
- Off you know, my energies...
- Oh, whatever!
- That I am collecting deep
into my, uh, subconscious.
- Are you sure that's not
because you don't feel
so confident?
- I'm probably the most worried,
but do I want to be in
that top three?
Absolutely.
- [laughing]
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Ru.
- Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, well,
you look well-groomed tonight.
- Bitch, please.
- [laughs]
Santino Rice, you dirty dog.
- [barks]
- [laughs]
- Rose McGowan,
you look beautiful.
- Thank you, darling.
I love your roses.
- Black roses.
- The best kind.
- And one of my doggone
favorite singers,
Wynonna Judd is here.
How you doin', mama?
- I like it rrrough.
- [laughs]
[imitates scooby-doo]
- This week, our queens
unleashed their talents
and created three
doggy-inspired looks.
Are you ready to get this
Bitch Ball rolling?
- Ready.
- Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- ♪ Once a year ♪
♪ We're called together ♪
- ♪ To a castle in the fog ♪
- ♪ Where we recognize ♪
♪ The very best ♪
- ♪ And the diva is top dog ♪
- ♪ Diva is top dog... ♪
- ♪ She's top dog ♪
- ♪ And all the girls say ♪
♪ Ruff, ruff, ruff-ruff, ruff ♪
♪ At the Bitch Ball ♪
♪ Ruff, ruff, ruff-ruff-ruff ♪
- ♪ I can turn around ♪
- ♪ I can lie on the ground ♪
- ♪ Look what I found ♪
- ♪ I got laid at the pound ♪
- ♪ Ooh! ♪
- ♪ Ruff, ruff ♪
♪ At the Bitch Ball ♪
♪ Ruff, ruff, ruff-ruff, ruff ♪
- ♪ I'm a sucker for meat ♪
- ♪ I'm always in heat ♪
- ♪ Can I get a treat? ♪
- ♪ I peed in the street ♪
- Ooh...
- Ugh.
- Ew.
- Girl.
- ♪ So, welcome one and all ♪
- ♪ Welcome one and all ♪
- ♪ One and all ♪
all: ♪ To the Bitch Ball ♪
[laugher]
- Let the Bitch Ball begin.
Category is...
daytime dog park realness.
Latrice Royale.
Hey, girl.
Give a dog a bone.
- [laughs]
- I made a little, fun skirt,
a little slinky top,
and some cute pumps.
Bitch, honey, this is what I'd
wear out to the dog park.
- She's a real tail wagger.
- [laughs]
- Next up, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Oh, she's brought
her own pooper scooper.
- Oh, my gosh.
- I'm loving my daytime
dog park realness look.
I'm Nicki Minaj meets Barbie.
- Well, poo-poo-pee-doo.
Phi Phi's the shit.
- [laughs]
- Up next, Sharon Needles.
Just another dog day afternoon.
- Is this another
Simpson sister?
- I'm serving true dog park
realness.
It's kind of inspired by
late '60s
Italian fashion photographs.
- She looks fetching.
That's right,
clean up after your dog.
Chad Michaels.
Uh-oh, she lost her doggie.
- I'm really loving my daytime
dog park realness.
It's light, it's flowy,
and I feel beautiful in it.
- I told you to keep your dog
on its leash.
Oh, you'll find it.
Category is: Pooch in a purse.
Party girl realness.
Latrice Royale.
Hey!
- Well...
- She is on the VIP list.
- Uh-huh.
- My party girl look is very
chic,
very "Let's go cha cha,
boo boo,
I'll meet you at the club."
- She's all up in the club.
The kennel club.
- [laughs]
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Oh!
Can I borrow that wig?
- That's her hair, Wynonna.
- Oh, I am so sorry.
- Oh, my goodness.
Look at those heels.
Her dogs must be barking.
- My "it" girl looks like
Rihanna
if Rihanna had a dog.
It's edgy.
- She carries her poochie
in her Gucci.
- Sharon Needles.
Oh...
- Rock and roll party girl.
- If Courtney and Lindsay
had a baby?
- Yes.
- What's she got
around her ankle?
Uh-oh.
- Oh, it's a scram bracelet.
- Yes, it is.
- I'm serving heroin chic,
hung-over, party girl realness.
Like the celebrities I see
in my tabloids.
- Uh-oh, uh-oh.
- [laughs]
- Eat a sandwich.
Chad Michaels.
- Posh party girl.
- Ready for the paparazzi.
- I am serving structured
Kardashian realness.
I'm feeling very confident,
I'm feeling a little
bitchy in it.
- She has a big diamond
from her rich man.
- Yes.
- And she's got a big behind
right now, too.
- Mm-hmm.
- Very Kardashian.
Category is...
canine couture eleganza.
Latrice Royale,
and her dog Babyface.
- It's very Mahogany.
- Yes.
Look at that furry muff.
- [laughs]
- I'm giving them sleek,
sophisticated, simple, clean
silhouette,
and I'm feeling good,
and looking gorgeous.
- She's dressed to the canines.
Phi Phi O'Hara,
and her dog Hunter.
Ladyboy and the tramp.
- Oh, look at Hunter's bow tie.
- I'm a hound dog.
- I'm just trying to serve
the judges glamorous fish,
and they couldn't take
their eyes off me.
- Oh, yeah.
- You know what he smells.
- What does he smell?
- Pussy willows?
- Oh, of course.
- [laughs]
- Sharon Needles,
and her dog Cali.
- Cali caliente.
- That bitch is in heat.
Her poodle's on fire!
- It looks like
I'm walking three Calis.
I kept all the fur on the lower
half of me,
and her height
matched up perfectly
to my canine couture boots.
- Do the boots match the dog,
or does the dog match the boots?
- [laughs]
Chad Michaels,
and her dog London Paris Filan.
- [laughs]
- Every dog has
its De La Renta.
- My canine couture
is just a slight nod
to Cruella Deville
on vacation in Aspen.
- It's a little 101 Dalmatians.
- Cruella.
- Yes, very Cruella.
- Kinkyella.
See you on the slopes.
- Welcome, ladies.
Let's go straight to
the judges' critiques.
First up, Latrice Royale.
- I'm loving the whole
Mahogany thing.
- Thank you.
- I just think you've got a lot
of sass and a lot of class.
- And a lot of ass.
- Pow!
- [laughs]
- Eat it.
- Some men like a little meat
with their potatoes.
- [laughs]
- Out of all three looks,
I think the daytime was your
least successful.
Glitter navy skirt going
to the dog park--a little much.
- Your canine couture, simple.
I would've liked
a little bit more.
- Thank you, Latrice.
Next up, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Because I worked with my
prissy-butt mom for ten years,
I'm always looking
for the head-to-toe.
I think makeup-wise, flawless.
Your sparkles are aplenty.
Your boots, oh, my gosh.
- The dogs production,
you stole the show.
You were fully into, like,
the cute little ditzy dog role.
Your Japanime, over-the-top
daytime realness
was not realness.
- I have no interest in real.
- [laughing]
- I find real people boring.
I'd be far happier to see you
at my dog park any day
than to see somebody in
sweatpants and tennis shoes.
- She would hate us
at the dog park, Wy.
- I don't go to the dog park.
I have people
that do that for me.
[laughter]
- Next up, Chad Michaels.
- The only thing I would say
is in the opening,
the lip sync was a bit off.
- Ooh, okay.
- Your canine couture really
shocked me when you came out.
It doesn't have to be so...
old lady.
- There's something about
that look that just...
is less diva-ish.
- Thank you, Chad.
Next up, Sharon Needles.
- Love this look tonight.
You look like you
came out of an editorial
out of Italian Vogue.
- [gasps] Ooh!
- I'm sure you
made those boots.
- 5-1/2 hours
and a hot glue gun.
- If somehow Liza Minnelli
in Cabaret
and Jean Harlow had a baby,
and threw it
in white puffy boots
with the perfect poodle,
it would be you.
That poodle could not have
worked the boots harder
with you.
- And it was good to see you
as a blonde-blonde,
not like an evil zombie blonde.
It was nice to see that
different side of you.
You continue to inspire.
- Ah!
- Thank you, Sharon.
Ladies, one final question.
Which of these bitches
does not deserve
to be in the top three?
Let's start with Sharon Needles.
[dramatic music]
- I'm going to say
Phi Phi O'Hara.
She has a very cutthroat
attitude.
To be America's
next drag superstar,
we need a sweetheart.
As drag queens, I think
we need to show as much heart
and family morals
amongst sisters--
- Bullshit.
What you said right now
is a complete lie.
I value family morals.
You're on stage lying,
is what you're doing.
- I'm not lying.
- But you are.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
same question.
- I would definitely
have to say Sharon.
For him to stand on this stage
and tell...
that I don't value family
is bullshit.
If I'm, you know, cutthroat,
then so be it.
I'm a fierce competitor,
and I deserve to be here.
- Thank you, Phi Phi.
- Chad Michaels, same question.
- I would say Phi Phi.
She has...a lot maturing to do.
At times, she has acted her age,
and she's made no qualms about
wanting to win this contest,
hands down, whatever it is
that she needs to do.
- Latrice Royale.
- [exhales]
- I feel Sharon Needles.
She has gotten through this
competition being imperfect.
On the runway,
we strive for perfection.
If I was to come out here
with unfinished seams
and a ripped up this
and a ripped up that,
my ass would be handed to me.
- All right, ladies,
I think we've heard enough.
While you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior
Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
[engine starts]
All right,
just between us girls,
let's start with Latrice Royale.
- Party girl was her best.
That was cute-ish.
But it wasn't enough
compared to the other divas.
She was just too flat
for me tonight.
- When she picked Sharon Needles
and was critiquing her
for her unfinished hemlines,
and then I looked down
and Latrice has, like,
something that is clearly
an unfinished hemline,
it was little like
kettle, pot, black.
- Right.
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- I was counting Phi Phi out
for a few weeks in a row,
and she's really
done the Phoenix
and risen from the ashes.
- Yeah.
- I was very impressed
in all facets
of her performance tonight.
- What did you think of what
Sharon had to say about her...
ambition in the competition.
- Even if someone
is extremely ambitious,
I don't hold that as a fault.
- The blessing is she's,
you know, fierce.
The burden is she's fierce.
- I totally understand
that burden.
- [laughs]
Me too, Rose.
- Little miss attitude
down there.
- [laughs]
Chad Michaels.
- She's so elegant, and she
really has the "it" factor.
- She's got the beauty and this
classy look to her
that the clothes
did not live up to.
- Tonight was the first night
that I was like "meh" with Chad.
- Sharon Needles.
- She really turned it out.
She really gave us ball
day realness, like, down.
Boots!
Party girl chic
was the winner for me.
- She looked like an Olsen twin.
- [laughs]
The canine couture,
the boots that she hot-glued
together,
I want to eat that shit up.
- She owned it.
It's very, very hard
for me right now
to go between Phi Phi
and her for the night.
- Silence.
I've made my decision.
Now bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your performance
in the Bitch Ball,
I've made some decisions.
[dog whining]
Sharon Needles,
you are a lone wolf
who barks to the beat
of a different drummer.
And tonight, you are top dog.
Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
[applause]
[dog barks]
You've won crystal flower
body jewelry
made by Marianna Harutunian.
- Thank you so much.
[dog barks]
Winning this challenge
means so much to me,
'cause I just never thought
I would be in the top three,
and it's awesome.
- Chad Michaels...
- Yes, Ru.
- Throughout this competition,
you have been
a leader of the pack.
But tonight, you didn't leave us
begging for more.
[dog whimpers]
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- It's tough to hear
those infamous words,
but I'm ready to fight for my
place in this competition.
- [exhales]
- Phi Phi O'Hara, you started
out as the runt of this litter,
but tonight, you've proven that
you can teach a young dog
new tricks.
Phi Phi O'Hara...
you are safe.
[dog howls]
- Thank you.
- Latrice Royale...
I'm sorry, my dear, but you
are up for elimination.
[dog whimpering]
- Child, honey.
Let's shine on, boo boo.
Let's shine.
Let's shine on.
- Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of No One Else On Earth
by Wynonna.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lip sync
for your life.
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
[No One Else On Earth playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I've been a rock ♪
♪ And I've got my fences ♪
♪ I never let them down ♪
♪ When it comes to love ♪
♪ I keep my senses ♪
♪ I don't get kicked around ♪
- I've never done
a country song ever,
and my plan is to just attack it
Latrice Royale style.
- ♪ The damage is done now ♪
♪ I'm out of control ♪
♪ How did you get to me? ♪
♪ No one else on earth ♪
♪ Could ever hurt me ♪
- I don't want to go home,
not after coming this far,
so I'm gonna turn it out.
- ♪ 'Cause when the night ♪
♪ Falls ♪
♪ You make me forget ♪
♪ Your love is killing me ♪
♪ And it ain't over yet ♪
♪ How did you get to me? ♪
♪ No one else on earth ♪
♪ Could ever hurt me ♪
- Latrice always gives that
great soul energy.
Unfortunately, I just don't
think that synced up
with this song.
- ♪ No one can love me like ♪
♪ No one like you ♪
- [laughing]
- Oh...my...God.
[applause]
- Work, bitches!
- Ladies...
I've made my decision.
Chad Michaels...
shante, you stay.
You may join the other girls.
- Thank you, Ru.
Thank you, judges.
- Latrice Royale...my queen.
I bow to you.
And I have one thing to say:
Bitches better beware.
- You have changed my life
forever.
You have changed the world
of drag forever.
I love you and respect you
so much.
And thank you for seeing
something special in me.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Now...
sashay away.
- [sobbing]
She is large, in charge,
chunky, yet funky,
the bold and beautiful,
I am Latrice Royale.
- ♪ Latrice ♪
- ♪ Royale ♪
[dog barks, whines]
- Dream and dream big.
It doesn't matter
where you come from,
what color you are,
what shape you are.
Be the best you can be.
- My top three,
the best of the best.
And there's only one way
to go from here,
and that's up.
So remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I an amen up in here.
all: Amen!
- All right,
now let the music play.