- Charisma.
Uniqueness.
Nerve.
Talent.
We've raised the bar on grace
and beauty so high
that now there's
only one place to go...
[drum roll]
[cheering]
[yelping]
Over...
the motherfucking...
top.
- Let's not get it twisted.
- Hold on, bitch.
[camera clicking]
- More booty.
- Welcome to Tuckahoe Prison
for Ladies.
- Hello.
[dog barking]
- More sassy stars.
- I don't know why they book me
on these chicken-shit Gigs.
[laughter]
- More drama.
- [speaking Spanish ]
- Get out.
- Your fake-ass hoe.
- All right,
you tired-ass showgirl.
- At least
I am a showgirl, bitch.
Go back to Party City,
where you belong.
- For the first time
in Drag Race history,
and a finale,
we are breaking all the rules...
- Oh, my god.
- That will be the most
sickening ever.
- [gagging]
- Hey!
- ♪ Jesus is a biscuit ♪
♪ Let him sop you up ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
- RuPaul's Drag Race...
[laughter]
Is about to spin out of control.
- Pew, pew.
- In three...two...one...
- [snarls]
- [laughs]
My name's Willam.
I'm 29.
Ooh, a 26.
Damn, we got some big girls.
I hope they don't have diabetes.
I didn't come up
through the club system.
I'm an actor.
I've done TV, I've done film.
Sex in the City, The District,
Criminal Minds,
and a show that was, like,
a multi-story arc.
I think I'm
the skinniest one; yay!
I'm a successful drag queen,
and not some bitch
who has to show for a dollar.
Now no one else can have it.
- My name's Lashauwn Beyond.
I'm 21 years old.
Hi, queen one.
- Hi.
- Lashauwn Beyond is the main
attraction for the circus.
She just has a lot of fun.
- Your hair's too big
for the frickin' door.
- I know, right?
- Hi.
- What's good, ladies?
My name is Jiggly Caliente.
I'm 30 years old from Queens,
New York, baby.
Wow.
Jiggly Caliente is New York
City's plus-size Barbie.
She got swag for your nerve.
You can't take her.
You look really familiar, Mom.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Oh, now I know who you is.
- You must have a television.
- Oh, hell no, you didn't.
- Well, hello, hello.
- Hi.
- How are y'all doing?
- How are you?
- Good, wow.
- My name is Phi Phi O'Hara.
I am 25 years old.
Are you guys excited
for the first challenge?
- No, we're not.
- You're not excited?
- Duh, yeah.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- Hiya.
- [shrieks]
- I am Madame LaQueer.
I'm 29 years old.
- Your lips are amazing.
- Perra.
- Thank you.
- Give 'em here.
"Per--"
What does that mean?
- "Perra" is like saying,
"Oh, bitch."
- Sickening.
- Oh.
I'm gonna learn Spanish
by the time I win.
- What?
- Huh?
- Hey, there's a new girl
in town.
Let's get to business.
- Broadway just hit our stage.
That, or they picked up
a pimp off the street.
- Cash or credit card?
- My name is Milan,
I'm 36 years old,
and I'm from New York City.
Hey! Oh, my gosh.
Milan is fierce.
She is fabulous, she's a diva,
she can act, sing, dance,
produce, and you don't want it
from her.
[laughs]
- Hi.
- Hello.
How y'all trannies doing?
- Hi.
- Hi, wow.
- My name is Alisa Summers,
I'm 23 years old,
and I'm from Tampa, Florida.
I am definitely a fishy queen.
I can walk down a street.
You know, I don't really
get clocked.
People are looking more so
at how big my titties
and ass are.
I'm ready, girl.
[cheering]
- Bonjour, ladies.
I'm Dida Ritz, I'm 25 years old,
and I'm from Chicago.
[screams]
Oh, my god, you're here!
Oh, my god.
Dida Ritz is--if you
think about Beyonce
and Carrie Bradshaw
and Kimora Simmons
and they all three got together
and somehow had a baby.
- Dida Ritz look a mess.
That dry-ass wig
and that awful-ass make up.
- Oh, my god.
- So we don't have any
backwoods girls yet, huh?
- Hello. Hi.
I'm the princess.
I'm 32 years old.
- You look sickening.
- Thank you.
I'm a reserved extrovert,
and I think
putting on the makeup
and the wig and the costume
unleashes her.
This is crazy.
It is so insane.
Wow, wow, wow.
- Hi, girls.
My name is Kenya Michaels.
I have 21.
I am from the island
of enchantment, Puerto Rico.
We are two Puerto Ricans.
- [laughs]
- Mama.
I'm a little person,
but I'm a fierce...bitch.
- What's her name?
- Huh?
Kenya.
- Kenya?
She's cute. Fuck.
Kenya looks fishy.
I was like,
"Crap, now I'm gonna have to be
the funny one
and not the pretty one."
- Morning, bitches.
Hey, everybody.
How y'all doing?
- Good.
- My name is Chad Michaels.
I am 40 years old.
- Shut the Cher show down.
Don't nobody do anything Cher
or Cher-adjacent.
- Yeah, 'cause
we're gonna have to row.
- Hi.
- Hi, baby.
Chad Michaels
is first and foremost
a celebrity impersonator.
That's my passion.
Cher has been what I'm most
well-known for.
This is my work outfit, baby.
- Cher comes to her for tips.
- [laughs]
I really do my best
to impersonate her with reality.
Like, you'll never see "ho!"
I will never do that
because she doesn't do that.
- How you doing?
- I'm doing all right.
- I immediately saw Cher,
so I want to see what else Chad
has to offer.
[cheers and laughter]
- My name is Sharon Needles,
I'm 29 years old,
and I'm from Pittsburgh,
Pennsylvania.
I look spooky,
but I'm really nice.
At least for now.
- My first impression
of Sharon Needles
was "Wow, what a whack job."
- Yes, the princess.
I'm the queen.
- The three words that would
describe Sharon Needles
are "beautiful," "spooky,"
and "stupid."
- Ow!
Eat it.
My name is Latrice Royale.
39 years of age.
- Hi, I'm Willam.
- Latrice.
- I'll hold your bag for you.
- Oh, I know you will.
[whoops]
Home team, home team.
- Miss thing came painted.
She had stones on her face,
and she was giving me all that.
- [delighted exclamation]
Latrice Royale is large
and in charge.
Chunky yet funky.
Wow.
Bold and beautiful, baby.
Mm-hmm.
Girl, the shade,
the shade of it all.
- The season four family.
- Look at this here, honey.
[cheers and applause]
- I want to know if I'm
the oldest bitch in the cut.
- You have to be.
[laughter]
[sirens]
[exclaiming variously]
- Girl, you've got she-mail.
[electronic sizzle]
We are living
in desperate times.
Birds falling from the sky,
dead fish fouling the sea,
once-fertile areas becoming
dusty, dried-up wastelands...
and that was just my last visit
to the lady doctor.
[laughter]
This is a test...
this is only a test...
to find out which one
of my girls
has the charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
to snatch the title of America's
next drag superstar.
You are the hope
for future generations
of glamazons everywhere.
Ladies, tighten your tucks.
This is the beginning
of the rest of your life.
[progressively quieter]
Life... life...life...life...
life... life...life...life...
life...
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- Hello, hello, hello!
Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race.
[cheers and applause]
Now, enjoy this moment.
Because it won't last for long.
Now, you've signed on
for a competition
that requires severe stamina
and devastating acts of beauty.
But if you dream big
and play to win,
it will all be worth it.
In addition to winning the title
of America's
next drag superstar,
the champion
of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics,
a one-of-a-kind trip
courtesy of ALandCHUCK.travel,
and headline
Logo's Drag Race Tour,
featuring Absolut Vodka:
cocktails perfected.
But wait, there's more.
- More?
- America's next drag superstar
will walk away
with a cash prize of...
$100,000.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my god.
- When I heard $100,000,
I just wanted
to just pee on the floor
and start doing flip-flops.
- That's the good news.
But here's the bad news.
- Oh, here we go.
- Okay.
- You may need to spend
that prize money quickly
because, according
to the Mayan calendar,
2012 is the year the world ends.
This week,
you'll need to survive
the biggest drag disaster
of all time.
[distorted voice]
The Rupocalypse.
[cheers and applause]
- Bring it on, bring it on!
- Oh, wait a minute.
Somebody's missing.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Somebody is missing.
- 13, 13.
- 13, it's complete.
- I know.
Oh, pit crew.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my god.
- I'm sitting on that box,
it ain't opening.
- I'm going to kick that box.
- All right, boys,
let me see what you got.
- Hallelu, I'm back, bitches!
[scattered groans and applause]
Yes!
I'm back, bitches.
- Oh, hell to the no.
It's time to make room
for new queens.
- New queens?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Well, what about you, Ru?
- Oh, bitch.
Oh, you know what...
[laughter and chatter]
Pit crew,
take this box out back,
throw in a rabid honey badger...
- Yes!
- Work!
- And set it on fire!
[cheers and applause]
- What about my money!
Hallelu!
- Bye.
- Hallelu. Hallelu.
Hallelu, love you, Hallelu.
Let that be a lesson
to all of you.
My show, my rules.
Now, are you ready
for your close-up?
[cheers and applause]
- Today we have
our photo challenge,
and RuPaul said that we should
be ready for the Rupocalypse.
I'm really, really excited
to see what's gonna happen.
- Hello, Chad Michaels.
- Hi, Ru.
- I want you to meet
our favorite photographer,
Mike Ruiz.
Now, he's here to shoot
your totally toxic photo spread.
- Okay.
- Now, the pit crew
will be using their hoses
to spray you
with hazardous waste.
All of this while you spin
around in this toxic dump.
- I'm a soldier and I'm ready.
- All right.
- I want the queens
to embody the apocalypse,
but maintaining,
like, a lot of beauty
and fashion sensibility.
- Think Karen Silkwood, darling.
[camera flashes]
- Uh-oh.
- Electric storm.
- Find your li--
- Careful.
- Today just threw me
off balance.
And I was a little bit wobbly,
but I got through it,
got my bearings.
- Play to the camera.
- That queen is poison.
Dida Ritz.
- Beautiful, yes.
Give me, like,
crazy body shapes.
- You are a survivor, darling.
Grace Jones, darling.
- Beautiful.
- Give us toxic shock. Yes.
- Oh, beautiful.
To the camera, to the camera.
- Whoa!
- Oh.
You're traveling back in time.
- Back in time, darling.
- Kenya has such
a beautiful face,
but she does this really weird
thing with her mouth.
Her mouth is, like, wide open,
like she's trapping flies.
- Give it to Puerto Rico!
Beautiful.
Milan, find the camera.
- Don't cover your face.
Don't cover your face too much,
thank you--hold on!
- Ooh!
- You're spinning
out of control, girl!
- Yes.
Mahogany 2012, darling.
Sharon Needles.
- Hi, Ru.
- Did I meet you
at the free clinic?
- I think so.
I quit going.
It's so expensive.
- [laughs]
- Give me Chernobyl chic.
- Shocking beauty.
Give us some body.
- [yelps]
- Okay, now find the camera.
[yelping in slo-mo]
- Uh-oh.
- Topsy-turvy, topple over,
fatty.
And I'm like, "damn."
- Queen down!
- I couldn't let my fall
be the death of me.
- End of the world glamour.
That's right.
- Pucker your apoca-lips.
- We got it.
- ♪ Fabulous ♪
Alisa Summers,
give us the drama now.
- Yeah, just slide your hair
out of your face a little bit.
I want to see
that gorgeous face.
Yes, but beautiful.
You're not afraid,
you're giving me beauty.
- Aftershock.
Glow, baby, glow.
- How'd it go, mama?
- [sighs]
Spinning me all crazy.
- I've got get
out of my undergarments.
You're going to see
that I'm really
a 300-pound Latino here
in a second.
- Oh, man,
she said "300-pound Latino."
Sharon Needles.
She creeps me the fuck out.
- Oh, Lord.
- Oh, my God.
I feel like I need
to pray the rosary
when I'm talking to you.
It was hard to have
a conversation and not cringe.
- Girl, look what this duct tape
did to me.
- Ooh, you did get
a little rug burn there,
didn't you, mama?
- The duct tape for what?
- I taped my titties up today...
- Oh.
- And because I
was in it for so long,
and it was pain--
I just ripped it off.
- Oh, my god, wait, come here.
- Look.
- You know, the stakes are high,
but damn.
- Give me all
of your Princess fierceness.
- I think the pit crew
just shot on your chest.
Princess of the apocalypse.
- Yes, tortured!
Make it severe.
- Yes.
- Like angry?
- No, not angry, beautiful,
gorgeous.
Uh-huh.
- Hello, vanity.
- Ooh.
- Only your beauty will survive
the apocalypse.
- That's right.
Make love to the camera
for the very last time.
- Beautiful.
- Tina Turner,
Lashauwn Beyond Thunderdome.
Madame LaQueer.
There's a hole in your ozone.
Now fill it.
- [panicked sounds]
- Give me beauty face.
Madame LaQueer
was giving me comedy face
when I really wanted
high-fashion face.
Give me beauty.
- The last cover of O Magazine.
It burns so good.
Let them have it, Latrice.
- [squawks]
- Oh, ooh, work it.
Yes, back to the camera.
A little sexier.
- I don't do photo shoots.
I don't like 'em.
I don't never know what to do.
I feel awkward and just, like,
"What do you want me to do?"
- Face-fuck the camera, Latrice.
- What?
- Cue the aftershock.
- Electroshock.
- [yelping and laughing]
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Queen down, queen down.
- Ooh.
[laughs]
- Were those your underwear?
- Wait a minute,
are those your panties?
- Ooh, yes.
- Keep spraying her.
- They're artificially
inseminating her
with that toxic waste.
Dr. Schwartz at your cervix.
Willam.
- Hi.
As soon as I walked in
and saw some body splatters
like a crime scene,
I'm like,
"Yes!
Some of these bitches fell."
Shoot me.
- Release the kraken.
- Remember to always--
- Ooh, careful.
all: Ohh!
- It ain't happenin'!
- Good save. Yes.
- There you go.
- You've saved the world.
- Go home.
Go home.
- [laughs]
- It was a total shocker
to see how these girls looked
as boys.
- Oh, my god, the princess.
I was like,
"Dude, you look
like a construction worker."
Latrice...she went from looking
like Aretha Franklin
to Biggie Smalls.
- Everybody's so tiny
without shoes and hair.
Y'all don't look
like such a threat no more.
- [laughs]
- Kiss my ass.
- Ooh!
Now, wait a minute,
let's all get along.
There's no fighting.
- Willam is getting
on my nerves.
Shut up, bitch,
and just go back in that box
where Shangela
popped out of and...leave.
- I just want to say
that I love everyone,
and can we all just get along?
- Shut up.
- Oh, what?
- She wants to get along
with everybody.
I don't know.
- Oh.
- Every one of you.
I love you all.
The first day,
at least just try to get along.
And wait till a bitch
steals something of yours
or sabotages you,
and then you can wreak.
But let's not walk in here
like you own the shit.
[cheers and applause]
Ooh, I'm not a virgin.
I don't want a virgin cocktail.
- Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and greetings]
I don't know
who these people are.
- We're robbing you.
- Now, ladies, Mike and I
went over your totally
toxic photos.
One of you
was truly drop-dead gorgeous.
The winner of your very first
challenge is...
Jiggly Caliente.
- Yeah!
Yes!
Fat girl win the first
challenge!
- Con-drag-ulations, Jiggly.
- Thank you, mama.
- I love your totally
toxic photo so much,
I'm gonna tweet it tonight.
Hashtag Rupocalypse.
- [taunting singsong sound]
- Now, my queens,
I wish you sweet dreams
because tomorrow
is gonna be a living nightmare.
- Oh, shit.
She's going to put us
through something,
and it's not gonna be pretty.
- All right.
- Bye.
all: Bye!
- You won the first challenge.
- Whoo!
- Good job, boo, good job.
- Thank you.
- They brought us
to this old hotel
in the middle of a sketchy area.
And I'm like,
"What are they gonna do?"
- Ladies, I've invited you
to this godforsaken place
for this week's main challenge.
It's here that you will scavenge
among the ruins
to put together
a fabulous outfit
that screams
post-apocalyptic couture.
Now, you can use your own wigs,
undergarments, and shoes,
but the rest has to be looted.
Now, you're probably wondering,
"Ru, where am I going to get
all these materials?"
[laughs]
Well, you know what they say...
only three things will survive
the Rupocalypse:
Cockroaches,
Cher...
- Amen.
[laughter]
- And drag queen zombies!
- What?
[doors creaking ominously]
[snarling and groaning]
- The zombies
were scary as hell.
They got, like, guts coming out
and eyes popping out.
I'm like, mm-mmm, no, ma'am.
- When I saw the zombies comin'
after me,
I was about to hit it.
- [snarls]
- All right, you've got three
minutes to grab what you can.
And avoid being eaten alive.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman live.
[whimpers]
[zombies groaning]
- Give it, bitch!
- So I'm running around
in between these zombies
and I realize that they're
former competitors
from competitions past.
Shannel, Venus,
Morgan McMichael's, Delta Work.
- I got to see Akashia, Raven,
Pandora Boxx, Ongina.
- Drop it, bitch.
- Oh, maybe some--oh, oh, yeah,
you're not a zombie.
For a quick second, I thought
Chad Michaels was a zombie.
It's just that Halloween mask
of a face that she has.
- Mine.
- Give me that, give me that,
give me that.
No, no, no, no, no.
Bitch, bitch, you crazy.
I'm from new York, motherfucker.
- Oh, well, of course, a corset.
- Girl!
- I'm looking
for anything sparkly,
anything structured,
anything that I can glue
onto a costume that I create,
and then, after that,
I just start
grabbing everything.
- Sorry, girls.
- [screeches]
- Oh! Hi.
Oh, you're drop dead gorgeous.
Ooh, I dig the look.
Oh, no, honey, I'm on your side.
- When I saw the zombies
and then Sharon Needles,
I thought she probably felt
like she was at home.
- God, it's like
a family reunion.
Hey, sorry, sis.
- [screams]
Black people don't stand there
while zombies
are coming at them.
They run, bitch.
[screaming]
[snarling and growling]
[indistinct yelling]
[objects clattering]
- [screaming]
No, no!
[screams]
Oh, Hallelu!
[munching sounds]
[emergency alarms sounding]
- Welcome back, girls.
[cheering]
- We get back to the workroom,
and there's more supplies
to help us with our outfits.
And everybody just went off.
- Can we flip this over?
- Uh-uh-uh.
- I grabbed it.
- We're like drag queen savages
who've been locked up.
We were just tearing each other
apart to get in these boxes.
- That shit's mine!
Everything in here is mine.
- Oh.
- Oh, fuck.
- Thank god I'm good at math.
One small corset
plus another small corset
equals one fat-ass
corset, bitch.
[laughter]
[hammering]
- Get it, Lashauwn, get it.
- Going to break
that motherfucker.
- So Ru tells us
that we have to make
a "post-apopaloctic" outfit,
and I don't know
what that means.
It's the end of the world.
I sew for a living.
And I can't go down the runway
lookin' a fool.
- Yay, I got it.
- Lashauwn thinks he's Magellan,
splitting the earth in half
or something.
- I don't think art historians
would appreciate that.
- I don't know what she's doing.
Lashauwn might be going home.
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi.
- Let's get this
end-of-the-world party started.
Hi, Princess.
Wow, what do we have here?
- I'm kind of going
for Rupocalypse
meets Black Swan
meets the princess.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, yeah.
- How does this say
"end of the world"?
- Well, it's
kind of armor.
Like, if a ballerina
were preparing
for, you know, a comet.
- Mmm.
But I'm looking
for post-apocalyptic couture,
Mad Max Beyond Thunderdome.
- So after the comet
has landed, then?
- Yes.
- Okay, I got you.
I'm definitely nervous
about how much time
we have left.
I just need to rethink and redo.
- I'm gonna let you get to it.
- Okay, cool.
- I can't wait.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Well, Sharon Needles.
- Hi, Ru.
- Wow. Tell me about this.
- I'm kind of going
for a Linda Hamilton,
Beauty and the Beast,
trapped under the city
because of an impending
nuclear dust cloud, and--
- Now, I love all that,
but how are you
going to make that read
on the main stage?
- I am a little nervous.
I'm worried that the judges
aren't going to quite
get the look, but...
to get anywhere
in this competition,
you got to take a risk.
- I noticed you have a Tammy
Faye Bakker tattoo on your arm.
- I do.
She was a huge idol to me
as a kid.
I didn't even know
she was selling Christianity.
I thought
she was selling me makeup.
- [laughs]
All right, I'm going to let you
get back to work, okay?
- Okay, thank you.
- Lashauwn Beyond.
- Hi, Ru.
- What do we have here?
- Well, this is just a top.
And that's my hair.
I'm gonna make it
look explosive.
- That's your hair?
- Yes.
- Wow.
- I want to dye it,
but I'm still trying
to be couture and pretty.
- So the silhouette is gonna
be a traditional silhouette,
where it's a bustier
and a full bottom.
- I'm not too sure yet.
- You're not sure yet?
You know, there's $100,000
at stake here.
- I know.
- And you don't seem too worried
about the time here.
- I am, I am, I am.
- Huh.
Well, time is running out...
- You're right.
- For all of us.
- I know.
- You've got
a lot of work to do,
and there's $100,000
on the line.
- Stop reminding me. Oh, my god.
- Yeah, so...
- It's making me sweat.
- I'm not finished,
so I'm really feeling a certain
type of way.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, Lord.
- You have got
to make it happen.
- I will.
- All right, thanks, Lashauwn.
- Take care.
- Jiggly Caliente.
- Hey, mama.
- May I call you Jiggly?
- Of course, mama,
everything jiggles.
- [laughs]
Now, tell me about this
post-apocalyptic couture.
- This is my Escape from New
York post-apocalyptic outfit.
- Ah.
- So I need my solar panel
pieces
to make my lights light up.
- I don't see a real dress.
- I'm gonna wear a corset.
And I'm finishing that up
with some more...
garbage.
- All right, listen.
I'm gonna let you
get back to work.
- Yes, mama.
- So you just bring it.
- I will, definitely.
- Alisa.
- Hi, Ru, how are you?
- Hey, mami.
Now, what do we have here?
- This is what I will be wearing
after the Rupocalypse.
- [laughs]
You are a breastplate girl,
aren't you?
- It's basically a swimsuit
with some titties on it.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Now, you know
that the judges are...
let's just say they're
a bunch of bitches.
- Yeah.
- Are you ready for that?
- Oh, I'm so ready.
I'm sure that they're gonna
love it.
- Listen, you've got to bring
your game.
- Oh, I'm doing it, Ru.
- All right, get back to work.
- All right, Ru.
See you later.
- Latrice Royale.
- Well, hello, Ru.
- Sounds like a gorgeous
after-dinner cocktail, yes.
- Sweet and delicious.
- All right, honey.
Ooh, you're making me thirsty.
Now, listen, I've lived
a long time,
and I've had those years
where it felt like
it was the end of the world
as we know it today.
- Yes.
- What was your end-of-the-world
moment?
- Really, you really
want to know?
- Mm-hmm.
- Um...when I went to prison.
I went to prison.
Um, I made some stupid mistakes,
and I got 18 months in, uh--
in the hole.
And during that period,
I lost my mom.
- Mmm.
- And those were my worst two
fears come true.
That was a dreadful,
tragic year for me.
I couldn't even go to my
mother's funeral.
It was the most
degrading experience
I've ever had in my life.
But I'm a survivor,
I'm a fighter,
and I persevered
through triumph,
you know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- I had a plan when I got out.
And my community
came to my rescue.
They had a "Get Latrice Royale
back on her feet
and on the stage" benefit.
- Wow.
- And it worked.
Now I'm on RuPaul's Drag Race,
living my dream.
- I love it.
All right, kiddo.
Get back to work.
- Thank you, sweetie.
- All right.
All right, ladies, gather
'round.
Now, tomorrow, you'll make your
doomsday debut
on the main stage,
where we'll be joined
by our extra-special guest
judge,
one of my best girlfriends...
the mistress of the dark,
Elvira, will be here.
[cheers and applause]
- I'm so excited, I can't even
put it into words.
She's my idol since I was five
years old.
- Ladies, the human race
depends on you for the survival
of drag.
But if you fail, it's not the
end of the world.
Oh, wait a minute, it is.
So don't fuck it up. Bye.
all: Bye.
- Good morning.
Yay.
- Mama, what a mess.
- This is a freakin'
disaster area.
- Today is runway day.
It is elimination day.
It is all getting very real,
bitches.
- Someone's going home
today, girls.
- So, Lashauwn, how you feeling
about your look?
Is it coming along?
- To be honest with you,
I really don't know.
- What was Ru's feedback?
- I think she was really...
hinting that it wasn't enough.
- Uh-huh.
- You want to impress her.
- Absolutely.
- And I don't feel like I did.
- It's coming together.
It's gonna be fine.
Lashauwn is a little bit
on edge.
But you got to put the rooter
to the tooter at this point.
You've got to just sell it.
You crazy and creative
and outside the box.
You're always "beyond."
- I know you trying to let me
have it, too.
- No, well, as far as the looks
and the way you look,
it doesn't get any better
than this.
- Thank you.
- Okay, you better do it, honey.
- Talk to me, boo.
How you feeling?
- About the challenge?
- Yeah.
- Feel like everything
will be fine.
I just got to work it out.
- Well, you know, I'm a little
nervous,
but I think it's going
to be fine,
and I think that my mom
is going to be really happy
to see this, so...
- In 2007, I lost my mom,
and it was a rough year.
- If you don't mind me asking,
um, how did she pass away?
- My mom had an aortic aneurysm.
She had complications after
surgery.
And...she just...went down.
- What was your relationship
like with your mom?
- My mom was always there.
But me being a drag queen was,
like, one of the biggest
arguments we've had, 'cause she
never understood why I wanted
to do it so much.
The last few months that she
was alive, she did understand.
I was able to tell my mom
everything.
I'm angry.
When everything was
on the table,
I had three months with my mom
and...three months?
Like, damn.
- Your mother is here.
She's here...you know, and
just--just do what you need
to do and bring it.
- Are you nervous at all?
- Wait, are you trying
to read me
and tell me I should be nervous?
- Nah, it's cute for, like,
pirate couture.
- I changed my outfit last
night,
but today I'm feeling really
nervous about it.
- Are you upset that you had to
change your outfit?
- Ru just didn't like it.
She wasn't feeling it,
so I had to go more
post-apocalypse with it.
I was just so in my head about
it, about her being like...
"Nope," so I was like, "I'm just
"gonna--fuck it, I'm just
gonna change it all."
I took a risk in my look and I'm
freaking out, because if you
mess up, you go home.
- Okay, I'm going in on this
bitch.
- All right.
- You got an instant facelift
with this, dahling.
- What the fuck is that
on her head?
- I don't know what that is,
girl.
- The weakest out of everybody,
I would say, is Sharon Needles.
Sharon's outfit looks more like
a brown tube sock that she just
stretched out.
Looks like she got it at a
discount costume store.
She's not at that point, right
now, to compete, so, if
anything, I feel like she's
gonna be the first one
to go home.
- Can I just tell you, like,
I'm so glad that you're here?
- I'm so glad you're here, too.
- No, because I don't know
anybody else who does your drag.
- Right.
- You know, and I know that
some of the other queens are
just like, "Why is she here,
she's a freak."
- Really?
Well, they can think all they
want.
There's a million kinds of drag.
And it's not just being a fishy,
annoying girl.
- Yep.
- I think some of the girls
here, particularly the beauty
queens, might be looking at me
as just a freak.
And I want to show them that I
have everything that it takes
to win this competition.
And more.
- You are exactly the type
of guy that I go for too.
- Oh, stop it.
- Like, that whole, like, meth
look, like, that's...
- "Meth look."
- [laughs]
- Only I could take that
as a compliment.
- Have either of you ever been,
like, arrested or...?
- No, ma'am.
- Oh, yeah.
Um, I have a DUI.
The day I got my call to come
here is the--my last day that I
was--I was on probation.
- Really?
- Uh-huh, so it was like--that
was such a blessed day.
Over the last year I've been
dealing with a DUI.
It's just been such a struggle
for 15 months.
I've been without being able to
drive.
It's hard for me to keep a
regular job.
They arrested me in drag.
- No!
- Biggest fear ever.
- Oh, okay, I thought--
- In handcuffs, in full paint,
full body, everything.
- I kind of would like that,
though.
- No.
They made me undress in front of
a room full of people
they had arrested.
Like, nobody would touch me.
They ruined my life
for 15 months,
but it's over now, and my life
is about to change.
I'm ready for the whole country
to know who Alisa Summers is,
and I hope they're ready for me.
- I just feel like my stuff
needs more.
- I'm worried that they're not
gonna get it.
Honestly, I think you better
create a really good story
for it.
- Okay, what I'm gonna say is,
"Escape from New York--"
ooh, shit, it's falling apart.
- Yeah, that's not good, either.
- Yeah.
- Jiggly's costume is a hot
mess.
It's all hot glue and scissor
work.
It's just like an explosion
of aluminum foil.
- Baked potato couture.
- You look like you're ready to
bake at 350.
[laughter]
[applause]
- Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Well, look what the zombies
dragged in.
Michelle Visage, you're back and
better than ever.
- Don't you know it, my lovely
lady in red.
- Mike Ruiz, I'd stop the world
and melt with you, darlin'.
- Oh, here we go again, Ru.
- [laughs]
Sometimes it's champagne,
sometimes it's pretzels
and beer,
but Santino's still here.
[laughter]
- And the eternal beauty,
mistress of the dark, Elvira.
- [gasps] Me?
- Hey, girl, you're gonna put
somebody's eyes out
with those things.
- [gasps] I hope it's not yours.
- [laughs]
Now, this week I asked our
queens to rise from the glittery
ashes and blow us away with
their post-apocalyptic couture.
Are you ready to see what's on
the other side?
- Bring it.
- Yeah.
- Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- First up, Willam.
- Not Willem Dafoe.
- No, not Willem Dafoe.
- And not Will.I.Am.
- Not Will.I.Am.
- Very Westwood, too.
Only one boob, though.
- Yeah, the other one got lost
in the apocalypse.
- As I'm walking down
the runway,
I'm trying to give them some 90s
supermodel.
Ass, ass, titties, hair, hair,
gas mask.
- Cloudy with a chance of acid
rain.
- I like the gas mask on the
back of her head, it's very
two-faced.
- Willam's a real gas.
[laughter]
- Up next, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Two queens enter,
one queen leave.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Is that a dream catcher
covering her private parts?
- Yes.
- [laughs]
- I knew I looked fierce,
I knew that my outfit could not
be touched.
I felt like all the attention
was on me.
I was just ready to serve it to
all the judges.
- I think that's a honey badger
on her shoulders.
- Maybe we do need another hero.
- We might just need another
hero, Santino.
- Lashauwn Beyond.
- Oh!
- Fabulous.
- Lashauwn be hot.
- Yes, ma'am.
She's got the whole world on
her...head?
- I thought a giant chicken laid
an egg up there.
- I live for what I put down the
runway.
I had the world on my head, and
my "post-apoc-oloptic" couture
costume.
It was sickening.
- Now, I wonder if she can get
cable TV with that on her head.
- [laughs]
- Chad Michaels.
- Okay.
- Oh.
- Ooh, how chic.
She could walk a mile for
a camel toe.
- Real fish caught in the net.
- I'm a perfectionist.
It's something I pride
myself on.
I'm feeling very confident.
I love what I'm wearing, very
post-apocalyptic diva, and I'm
feeling really, really good.
- Very "Lawrence of my labia."
[laughter]
- Up next, The Princess.
- [gasps]
- Wow.
- Wow, clown slippers.
Looks like a life jacket.
- Yes, queen overboard.
- I'm giving the judges
Waterworld couture.
I feel like I'm really living
for what I'm serving.
I love it.
- In case of emergency, your
scarf can be used as a flotation
device.
[laughter]
Kenya Michaels.
- Ooh.
- Oh.
- She's a phoenix rising from
the ashes.
- That's right.
- That's it.
- Firebird.
- Walk that walk!
- [squawks]
- I feel amazing.
I'm feeling fire, I'm fuego!
That moment I remember for all
my life.
- Cock-a-doodle-doo.
Lil' Kim in the house.
- Something's sprouting back
there.
- Her garden is in full bloom.
- Latrice Royale.
- Yes, she is.
- Whoo!
- Ooh, it's Latrice
from Whoville.
- Yes, mama.
- I'm Latrice, so of course I
stomped it on out, and I'm
givin' big girl sexy, showin'
all my curves and swerves, and
givin' a little face, givin' a
little attitude,
and a lot of ass.
- Yes, beyond thunder thighs.
[laughter]
Serve, honey.
- Mm-hmm.
- A queen for all seasons,
Alisa summers.
She's got goggles up there.
- Apparently,
she's going skiing.
- Ooh, I hate when drag queens
have bigger boobs than me.
- I'll say.
The hills are alive.
- I'm givin' them sexy, I'm
givin' them dominatrix, and I'm
on top of the world.
There's no feeling like that,
ever.
- And she's an all-terrain
vehicle.
- Yes.
- She a ATV summers, all-terrain
vajay-jay.
- That's right.
- Oh!
[laughter]
- Paris, London, Tokyo, Milan.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh.
- Wow.
- This is an infected Betsey
Johnson, right?
- Yes, it is.
- Love is a Battlefield.
- I'm serving the judges
savage beauty.
I'm feeling ferocious.
- I'm ready to attack.
- Milan is burning.
Now, let this be a lesson to all
of us--don't smoke in bed.
[laughter]
- Next up, Jiggly Caliente.
- Oh.
- Look, she's got a leg up on
the other girls.
- Yes, she does.
Apparently, hoarding is the new
black.
[laughter]
- I'm here on the runway, and
my adrenaline is on fire.
Everything is pulsating through
me, and I'm like, "Oh, here we
"go, bitch, I'm gonna show you
plus-size supermodel."
- She's one hot potato.
- And she seals in her natural
juices.
[laughter]
- Dida Ritz.
- Work.
- Come on, girl.
- Yes.
- Ooh.
- Chocolate Barbie doll.
- Legs for days.
- I'm doin' my runway,
it's sickening.
I am definitely channeling
Naomi, I am channeling Giselle.
I'm feeling it.
- You know, everything tastes
better when it sits on
a Dida Ritz.
- With thighs like that--
- You better ass somebody.
- Crack is whack.
- Oh, Madame LaQueer.
- Looks like my leftovers
last night.
- Give her an inch, she'll take
a foot.
- Take that, Betty Rubble.
- I'm serving attitude and I
feel so great, like I have never
felt before in my life.
- The entree of the evening,
filet of sole.
- Mmm, goes great
with some toe jam.
- Mmm.
- Ew!
- All right for Sharon Needles.
- Ooh, look at those eyes.
- Nosferatutu.
- Oh, she's bleeding.
- A dead woman walking.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Zombies.
- Somebody call a dentist.
- I hope she's wearing
a dental dam.
[laughter]
- Coming down the runway, the
best part was slowly letting out
a giant mouthful of fake blood
all over my body, and that's
when I really saw Ru's
eyebrow raise.
It's a disco bloodbath.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
- It is.
- Anyone told her
about fluoride toothpaste?
- Gingivitis never looked
so good.
Welcome, ladies.
Judgment day has arrived.
Now, based on your totally toxic
photo shoot and your
post-apocalyptic presentation,
I've made some decisions.
Will the following queens please
step forward.
Willam.
Milan.
Dida Ritz.
Latrice Royale.
Madame LaQueer.
Phi Phi O'Hara.
Chad Michaels.
Seven of you look like you've
been to hell and back.
Con-drag-ulations, you're safe.
- [exhales]
- Just safe?
My outfit was amazing, and not
"just safe."
- You may leave the stage.
Oh, ladies?
While you're back there, you may
want to think of ways to make a
more memorable impression
next week.
- Yes, ma'am.
- That's all.
Ladies, you six represent the
best and the worst of the week.
It is time for the judges'
critiques.
First up, Lashauwn Beyond.
In the workroom you seemed
kind of nervous.
Do you feel
more comfortable now?
- No.
It's a competition.
I'm always worried, I'm worried
now, I'm nervous.
- America's next drag superstar
needs nerve.
She doesn't need to be nervous.
- I am impressed that she can
carry that giant thing
on her head.
I mean, I have this giant thing
on my head, and it's bad enough.
- [laughs]
- As a symbol I think it's
really great, of, like, a
strong, black woman with the
world on her head.
I love all the disparate parts
that you put together to create
this overall silhouette.
- Is there anything you'd like
to say to the judges, Lashauwn?
- I'm just in disbelief.
- What can't you believe?
- That I'm here.
- Bitch, you're here.
- Yeah, honey, you better snap
out of it, you're here.
Play to win.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Up next we've got
Sharon Needles.
- Hello, RuPaul.
- How'd it feel up there
on the runway?
- Oh, I felt drop-dead gorgeous.
[laughter]
- This is my kind of ghoul.
I mean, I love the blood,
and this is a whole different
kind of take on drag queens.
- You know, everyone sort of
like survived the apocalypse,
and made do with what was left.
You took it one step further,
and you didn't survive
the apocalypse.
And then you came back to life
to terrorize these bitches.
[laughter]
- Thank you, Sharon Needles.
Next up, Jiggly Caliente.
- Hey, mama.
- Okay, no one's gonna
accuse you
of not havin' a great pair
of legs.
- [laughs]
- First of all.
But there's a little too much,
it's sort of like,
"Oh, my god, ah."
I'm getting my eyeballs
assaulted.
Just a little bit less could
have been more.
- Jiggly is a ball of energy,
and funny, and I love that.
- Thank you.
- But, girl, right now
you're a mess.
Things are fallin' off.
Fix your tutu.
I be seein' your privates
and stuff.
- No, girl, that privates
are put away.
- Jiggly, is there anything
you'd like to say to the judges?
- There's more, so much more.
- More than what you've got on?
- Well, but I'm talkin' about
all my clothes, all my drag,
when I wear it out here--
- We've heard that story before.
You have got to bring your
A game every single time.
There's $100,000 at stake.
- The time to bring it is every
single time you come out
to this runway.
Every single time.
- I will, mama.
- Next up, Kenya Michaels.
- Hola.
- So why a firebird?
- I really--she's a firebird
because if you're thinkin', uh,
end of the world, you're think
on fire, and I love that.
- You pounded this runway.
You came out, you were on fire.
I wish you had your wings with
you right now, because I'd like
to see the work you put
into them.
- You know that old phrase,
"Don't get your panties
in a bunch"?
- Yes.
- Your panties look a little bit
like they're in a bunch,
like a little diaper.
- My problem is, it doesn't
look really post-apocalyptic,
but I still think you're
beautiful, and you kill
a runway.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Kenya.
Next up, Alisa Summers.
Tell me about your outfit.
- I wanted to give kind of
a post-apocalyptic S&amp;M goddess.
- And tell me the significance
of the tool jutting out
of the areola.
- I like to shoot fire
out of my titties.
- Oh, okay.
- The boobices, where'd those
come from?
- What it is, it's like--it's
built like a swimsuit, and it's
just got the titties built right
onto it.
- I was getting scared.
I thought you were gonna say you
pulled everything up
from down there.
- From down here, all the way
up, yes.
- You've got some big ones,
girl.
And I'm feeling right now like
my makeup is looking natural.
- When you came out, I didn't
really see anything
post-apocalyptic
about your wardrobe.
It's not couture, either.
Even had you come out looking
like a big garbage heap, or
something, then there would have
still been more effort made,
to me, than what you have on.
- Who the frig says what
couture is, anyway?
I don't get it.
For him to say that's not
couture.
Well, it's couture to me, girl.
- [laughs]
- And I love how much makeup you
have on.
- Thank you.
- We kind of match.
- All right.
Next up, the princess.
- Nice outfit.
Who shot the lifeboat?
- It feels like it has a
nautical theme, a little bit,
to me.
- I'm kind of like Dennis Hopper
in Waterworld.
- I love that you approached it
from a nautical standpoint, the
world being consumed by water,
as opposed to fire and
brimstone,
which is what everyone else did.
- Thank you.
- You put together
a well-constructed look,
but there's no dirt, and you're
going through an apocalypse.
Like, it's completely--like,
your whites are whiter
than I've ever...
[laughter]
Done my laundry in my life.
- All right.
Well, girls, I think
we've heard enough.
- While you enjoy an Absolut
cocktail in the interior
illusions lounge, the judges
and I will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
All right, just between us
girls, let's start with
Lashauwn Beyond.
- I thought the outfit
was fierce.
I love the headdress, but she's
kind of uncomfortable,
she kind of
looks like she's at her first
prom, and--
- Yeah, what was that about?
- Eh, maybe she needs a couple
more years to cook, you know?
- I thought Lashauwn, more than
any of the other queens, really
met this challenge head on.
- There's definitely some skills
that are worth exploring,
but she definitely needs to
overcome her shyness.
- Yeah, it's cute for a taste,
but not for a swallow.
- Sharon Needles.
Now, I really dug her outfit.
It really told the story.
- It's obvious she's polished,
and she knows what she's doing,
but I want to see her in girl
drag, too.
- I love Sharon Needles.
It's hard for me to find
something bad about that.
- Jiggly Caliente.
Really funny, funny kid, but
that costume, I don't even know
where to start.
- She looked like she threw
everything but the kitchen sink
in there, but I think I saw
the kitchen sink in there.
- [laughs]
- It was the complete opposite
of the apocalypse.
- Right.
- But I'm so in love with her
as a person.
- Me, too.
- Kenya Michaels.
Cute kid.
When she walked down the runway,
she dazzled us with
those wings, but then she just
lost them.
- Yeah.
- She lost the most exciting
part of her outfit.
- I did have an issue with
the bedazzled diaper.
Not apocalyptic at all.
- No.
- But that bitch
is fierce.
- Alisa Summers.
- She's so stunningly
beautiful, I think she's used to
kind of resting on those
laurels, do you know
what I mean?
I think it threw her
a little bit.
You know, you need more
than beauty.
- I got to say, Alisa 's outfit
was very tacky.
- She built her whole costume
around that breastplate, instead
of using it as a detail within
some, like, grander, couture
sort of concept.
- Right.
- Her outfit reminded me
of the worst movie in the world.
- What?
- Showgirls.
- Stop it right now!
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Mistress of the dark.
- I mean, my favorite movie.
- All right. The Princess.
- I loved the blue and
the orange together.
That was my high school colors.
- Go bears!
- I liked and appreciated her
overall look, but it wasn't
really post-apocalyptic.
I wasn't picking up
her references.
- You know, I immediately got
that Waterworld reference.
I love the Pete Burns,
androgynous sort of vibe.
I think she's great.
- All right.
Silence!
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Now, which one of you bitches
will inherit the earth?
Lashauwn Beyond.
Your post-apocalyptic outfit
towered above the other queens,
but your personality fell flat.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- You may join the other girls.
Jiggly Caliente.
Your totally toxic photo shoot
was winning, but your
post-apocalyptic couture was
an unnatural disaster.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- When Ru tells me I'm in the
bottom two, I want to die.
I know the outfit looks jank,
but damn.
- Sharon Needles.
You killed this bloody
challenge, and you really stuck
it to the other girls.
Con-drag-ulations, you are
the winner of this challenge.
[applause]
You'll receive immunity from
elimination next week.
- Thank you.
- Plus, a custom gown from
sequinqueen.com.
That's sequinqueen.com.
- I won the challenge today,
and I'm feeling ecstatic.
- [squeals]
I'll have my dress made
in black.
- Thank you.
- With a plunging neckline.
- Hey, wait a minute.
- All right, Sharon, you may
join the other girls.
The Princess.
Your Waterworld inspired
couture got a little lost at
sea...but I'm throwing you
a lifeline.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Kenya Michaels.
You pummeled the runway, but
your firebird didn't fly with
the judges.
Alisa Summers, your
post-apocalyptic showgirl left
little to the imagination, but
you were not "breast in show."
Kenya...
you are safe.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Alisa, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- Ru says I'm in the bottom two.
It was just like, "really?"
I--I can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you to
lip sync for your life.
- I am not givin' up my spot in
this competition, no way,
no how.
They have to pry this out of
my cold, dead hands.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Baby, can't you see ♪
♪ I'm callin' ♪
♪ A guy like you ♪
♪ Should wear a warnin' ♪
♪ It's dangerous ♪
♪ I'm fallin' ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Too high, can't come down ♪
♪ Losin' my head ♪
♪ Spinning 'round and 'round ♪
♪ Do you feel me now ♪
- I'm giving them face, I'm
giving them movements.
I'm feeling very confident.
- ♪ With the taste of your ♪
♪ Lips, I'm on a ride ♪
♪ Your toxic ♪
- All I could think about is
"Kill it, kill it, kill it, hit
every move, hit every beat."
I have to pull out every trick.
If I have to shoot ping pongs
out of my ass, I will do it.
- ♪ It's getting late ♪
♪ To give you up ♪
- Alisa is not turning it as
much as Jiggly is.
She's kicking, she's doing
choreography,
she's really turning the party.
She had marked her territory.
She shit On the stage.
- ♪ With the taste of your ♪
♪ Lips, I'm on a ride ♪
- Jiggly started sheddin'
feathers and ornaments like a
Christmas tree that was gettin'
thrown out the window.
I was entertained.
I would-a given it some money.
- ♪ Toxic ♪
- The whole number that Alisa
was doin' was slo-mo, girl.
This is called Drag Race, not
Drag Walk.
- ♪ Intoxicate me now ♪
♪ With your lovin' now ♪
♪ I think I'm ready now ♪
♪ ♪
[applause]
- Ladies, I've made my decision.
Alisa Summers.
You are beautiful, talented, and
a queen for all seasons.
Just not this one.
Now sashay away.
- [whispering indistinctly]
- I definitely didn't think I'd
be the first person to go.
I definitely thought there were
other people more eligible to go
home before me, but I'm not
disappointed in myself.
I'm disappointed in what could
have been.
- Jiggly Caliente.
May I call you Jiggly?
- Yes, mama.
- Shante, you stay.
- Thank you.
- You may join the other girls.
The toxic 12, con-drag-ulations.
You live to die another day.
Now, remember, if you can't love
yourself, how in the hell you
gonna love somebody else?
Can I get a "amen" in here?
all: Amen.
- [laughs]
Now let the music play.