- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
Ladies, the password is...
Snatch Game.
[cheers and applause]
I might not be the biggest
star here,
but I got the biggest
knockers, okay?
[guffaws]
- I just want to say to
Lady Gaga that I am the only
boss here.
- This was a real heavy
Diana Ross.
- [imitates fart]
- Oh, my goodness.
- I don't know why they book me
on these chickenshit gigs.
- Condragulations.
You are the winner of this
challenge.
[applause]
It's very important for you to
understand we're looking for
the top.
Bring your "A" game.
- I will.
- Milan, shante, you stay.
Kenya Michaels, sashay away.
[cheers and applause]
And tonight...
oh, oh, oh, oh.
The dolls get wet.
And wild.
Ohhh!
With extra-special guest judges
NCIS star Pauley Perrette and
Kelly Osbourne.
The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX Cosmetics,
a one-of-a-kind trip courtesy of
alandchuck.travel, headline
logo's Drag Race tour featuring
Absolut Vodka, cocktails
perfected, and a cash prize of
$100,000.
And may the best woman win.
- I'm getting the hangers.
- Oh.
- We're back in the workroom
this morning, and Kenya's not
here anymore, and it's sad,
'cause my best friend's gone.
- "Phi phi, I love you.
Sisters forever."
all: Aww.
- You sent both of
the Puerto Rican girls home.
- I know.
- You ain't never gonna be
in West Side Story again.
[laughter]
Not even a touring production,
bitch.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Uh-uh.
- Bye, Kenya. I love you.
Uh! This hurts.
- Things got emotional
on the runway last week.
Today we've had a little time,
you know, to heal up, refocus.
I'm so, so happy that I won
the Snatch Game.
It was almost overshadowed by
how sad we were,
and it was hard
for me to celebrate, but I did
celebrate yesterday.
[laughter]
- I'll be honest.
I felt like my drag was
misunderstood.
Like, I'm so across the board.
I like to teeter-totter in the
boy world.
- I think teeter-tottering in
the boy world works when you're
super feminine.
It's hard for a drag queen to
teeter-totter in the boy world
while still being that drag.
- I have always had to deal
with people's perception of what
drag is, but I have to remain
true to myself.
I'm not gonna compromise.
- We know that you are
an accomplished actor.
Now, were those tears real,
Willam?
- Those were real, yeah.
I can cry on cue, but I wouldn't
have cried ugly like that.
- She was acting.
That was not real.
This bitch is faking it.
- My lashes were falling off.
- I didn't know Satan could
cry.
[alarm wails]
all: Ooh.
Here we go.
- Ooh, girl, you got shemail.
Greetings.
My name's RuPaul, and I'll be
your cruise director.
Come aboard.
We're expecting you...
to make waves.
Okay?
Big waves.
Holla!
'Cause sometimes to avoid being
stonewalled, a girl's got to
rock the boat.
all: What?
- I don't get it.
- Hello, hello, hello.
[together]
Good morning, Ru.
Hello, Ru.
- Now, you all have been working
so hard that I've decided to
give you a break.
A spring break.
[cheers and applause]
- Tramp stamps.
- Today's mini challenge is
your chance to soak in the sun
and let it all hang out
in an all-American wet T-shirt
contest.
- [howls]
[applause]
- Now, just outside is a thirsty
crowd of spring breakers.
Each of you needs to "wet" their
appetite, wearing a Glamazon
T-shirt and a pair of your new
bosom buddies...silicone
breastplates courtesy of
boobsforqueens.com.
And the queen that gets the
biggest reaction from the crowd
will win.
[cheers and applause]
Jelly.
- This is money in the bank.
I got this.
- You have 30 minutes to style
and stuff your T-shirts.
I'll see you outside.
Let's go.
- Boobs!
- Holy moly.
- Show me your tits.
- Playing girlyish and bouncy
and sexy is something really
foreign to me.
- What and what and where is
the body, baby?
- My look is, "God, I want to
"go to Miami, but I can only
afford Fort Lauderdale."
- Mama Chad looks like a MILF.
Chad, damn.
It's called Forever 21,
not Forever 41.
- Let's go to the beach.
[cheers and applause]
[whistle blows]
- Welcome to spring break at
Dragtona Beach.
[cheers and applause]
Are you ready to get wet
and wild?
First up, from The Big Apple,
London, Paris...Milan.
She's got two big apples.
Oh.
She not shy.
She is mopping the floor.
Chad Michaels.
Oh, oh, drop it like it's hot.
- My tits are big, my hair is
big, and my ass looks good.
I'm just feeling like
a drag cougar.
- It's Jiggly Caliente.
Her milkshake brings all the
boys to the yard.
Touch all of this, Jiggly.
Sharon Needles.
[laughs]
- I'm not one of those
fishy queens.
I never want to create a
character that someone would
want to fuck.
I like to mock sexiness.
[exclamations]
- She's a regular Danny Thomas
with that spit take.
Phi Phi O'Hara!
Uh-oh.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, ouch, ouch, ouch.
- I was shaking my boobs, and
all of a sudden my boobs
came off.
- She's coming undone.
- And then they poured
the water,
and then all of a sudden,
my wig fell off,
and it was a mess.
- Phi Phi, do you have all your
body parts?
[laughter]
Willam, Hollywood honey.
Oh, squirt. Squirt it.
I hope that lotion's
waterproof.
- I feel amazing,
because I know I look great.
And I was serving 'em sex,
and I just soaked it up.
- Oh, my God, she's driving
the crowd crazy.
She's a dirty, dirty girl,
that Willam.
Everything tastes good on
a Dida Ritz.
She's soaking wet.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Chocolate milk.
Put your hands together for
Latrice Royale.
You need some cooling down,
girl.
Oh!
- You know my alter ego is
a stripper.
I'm loving every bit of it.
- Give it up for
Latrice Royale.
Thank you, Latrice.
You were all wet and wild.
Damn!
One of y'all really worked
the crowd into a lather.
Can I get a drumroll?
[drumroll]
The titular winner of today's
mini challenge is...
Willam.
- Yeah!
- Yes.
- I won; you know, it's kind of
a hobby of mine.
Thank you, God,
for all this bod.
- Condragulations, Willam.
Spring break 2012!
Now that spring break is over,
it's time for a little
herstory lesson.
Back in 1969, at the Stonewall
riots, it was a drag queen who
had the charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent to dig her
heels in and start a revolution.
And every year since, drag
queens have been the shining
stars of pride celebrations
around the world.
For this week's main challenge,
you'll be styling
a fashion-forward look for our
very own pride parade.
Now, the theme for this year's
pride is hope floats.
In addition to your outfits,
you'll need to design parade
floats using these colorful
accessories.
[laughter]
Ships ahoy.
Each of you will be assigned
a different boat based on the
eight colors of the original
rainbow flag.
Willam, you won the mini
challenge, so you get to assign
the color themes,
using these hankies.
- I want blue.
Indigo blue.
I think this is the fairest way
to do it.
- Jiggly gets orange.
Phi Phi gets violet.
Dida gets red.
Turquoise for Latrice.
Pink for Chad Michaels.
Yellow for Milan.
And green for Sharon needles.
Now, ladies, you can use your
own drag, plus materials
provided by Michael Levine
fabrics.
Your ensemble needs to be super
chic and take pride over the
rainbow and on to the runway.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- Yay.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, look, shamrocks.
- This might buckle
my runway game.
- Your walk is your everything.
I don't know about that.
- Give it to me.
Give me Gautier
in a boat stripe.
- This is the ugliest color
ever.
- I love orange.
- It doesn't look good on me.
I went from baked potato to
sweet potato.
- Jiggly, what are you doing?
What is the concept of your
costume?
- As of right now,
I have no clue.
I'm not good at the creative
stuff.
This is the challenge where I
could sink to hell.
I want to incorporate this
somehow.
But then I just don't want it to
look like a Thanksgiving float.
And it's gonna look like
a turkey.
- Yeah, you don't want to look
like a turkey.
You don't want that to happen.
- Fuck, I'm screwed.
- Today our main challenge is,
we have to create
a Pride Parade float
with a matching outfit
in one of the colors
from the Pride flag.
- Originally, for the old
gay rainbow flag,
green stood for nature.
There's nothing natural
about me.
- You made a snake.
Are you doing a Garden of Eden
theme boat?
- Um, more like a Medusa.
Like, "Look at me, and I'll turn
you into Stonewall."
- Oh, yeah.
- So who here knows what
Stonewall is?
- Stonewall was in June of '69,
and the cops decided to go in
and cause some trouble.
- They were just, you know,
giving this one particular bar
all kinds of hell.
They just put their foot down.
They weren't gonna take it
anymore.
- I heard if you wore women's
clothing or makeup, they would
douse your head in the mop
buckets of nightclubs.
- Wow.
- You had to wear at least
three articles
of clothing that
were assigned to your genders
at all time,
or you could be arrested.
- I grew up in a religious
household, and that being gay
was just not something that
was accepted.
But this challenge does help me
rethink my perspective, because
it makes me very proud to know
that other queens have paved
the way.
- Chad, what was it like
to be there?
You were, what, 29 at the time?
[laughter]
- Okay.
I think for everybody to know
where we came from.
A legacy of drag deserves
to be carried on.
Me and Bob used to just
sit around for hours
and just glue sequins
onto dresses.
Bob's no stranger to a glue gun
in a pinch.
- That whole impersonating thing
you have to really do
your homework
to get every nuance,
ever characteristic.
- You do.
Celebrity impersonation
is my passion.
And it has been
from the beginning,
because when I started
in my show, the Dreamgirls,
it was all look-alikes
and all comedy,
and if you wanted to be
in the show,
you had to do
celebrity impersonations.
- Wow.
- I'm absolutely here
to be a role model.
This art doesn't have to die,
because it is dying.
There aren't very many people
like me anymore who do,
like, actual
"celebrity impersonation."
That's what I've done
for most of my career
is be a celebrity impersonator,
and I've loved it.
rock it out.
I've been, you know,
in the business a while.
I want to inspire the younger
generation of drag queens
to step up and do it right.
- [blowing]
[spits]
Fucking swallowed glitter.
- You've swallowed worse.
We're gonna have dinner soon.
Stop eating the glitter.
- Stupid-ass bitch.
- Goddamn it, Jiggly.
- Fuck you.
- Oh, my God.
I love my boat already.
I want to go on my boat so bad.
- You fucking cunt.
- [laughs]
I decide to do all-over pattern
of stars, or stickers, that have
my face on them.
The theme is hope floats, and
I've always hoped to be a star.
- That's you?
- Yes, it's me.
- You dirty bitch.
- Narcissistic much?
- Willam's boat was covered
in stickers of himself
and to me did not represent
Pride at all.
- How are you feeling
about this challenge?
- This is not something
that I normally do,
and I'm really--I'm trying
to focus on the boat first
and make sure I get
something down for that.
Trying to do what I can.
Sink or swim.
The most difficult thing
about the challenge for me is,
my brain goes in 20 million
different directions.
Sometimes being an artist
can be difficult.
- Here's your micro-dot, babe.
- Oh, shit.
I didn't realize that.
The clock was ticking,
and all I could think about was,
"Try to convey some type
of message on this float."
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi, Ru.
- It looks like
a Kylie Minogue concert
exploded in here.
- [chuckles]
- Jiggly Caliente.
- Hello.
- May I call you Jiggly?
- Yes, you may.
- Oh, good.
What we're looking for is
fashion-forward.
You know,
the theme is hope floats.
What statement are you going
to make?
- I--the statement I want to
make is that, um...
dreams are possible.
- Huh.
Now, what are your plans to
decorate your boat?
- Um, I plan on adding the
trimmings, the fabrics, and then
I'm gonna add the flowers and
other knickknacks.
- Yeah.
- Ru is not buying my bullshit
at this.
I know it.
I can see it in her eyes.
- I don't want to worry you,
but you do seem a little bit
behind.
We're looking for an expression
of Jiggly.
- Definitely.
- All right.
Get back to work.
- Thank you.
- How am I gonna do this?
- Dida Ritz.
- Hi, Ru.
- So what are you gonna do?
- I'm going for a '70s
really hippie vibe.
Very love, peace, and harmony.
And my whole concept
is a jumpsuit.
- With a blouse.
- Maybe with a blouse,
maybe not.
I don't know yet.
- We're looking to see the best
Dida that there is.
We want fashion-forward,
you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'll see you out
on the parade route.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Good luck.
Hi, Chad.
- It's time for another edition
of Ru's Clues.
- [laughs]
What are you gonna do
to make sure that your boat
and your costume and everything
represents hope
and the future of gay pride?
- I really want it to be,
you know, cyber showgirl,
fashion-forward.
- Now, you're boat.
- My boat.
- You've got a lot
going on there.
You have netting around there.
- I have netting.
I'm capturing hearts and minds
with my net.
- Are you planning to edit
the boat at all?
- I feel like it's got
a really futuristic feel to it
with, you know--
- The metallic.
- The metallic and the square,
like,
faux sequin and all that.
- I can't wait to see it
on the runway.
- I'll be there.
- All right, Chad.
You get back to work,
Lady Chad-erly.
- All right, bye.
- Bye.
- Well, well, well, Willam.
- It's starship Willam.
- Wow.
- In your book you had a quote
that said,
"Even when I was down,
"I treated myself as
a star.
And eventually, the rest of
the world would catch up."
And I wrote that on my little
binder in eighth grade.
I've adopted that theory too.
I've always treated myself like
a star and just knew it was
gonna happen.
- We got on your case last week
about being more vulnerable, and
that story's very vulnerable.
And what do you plan on wearing
if anything?
- Do you remember that episode
of Sex and the City
where Carrie
fell down on the runway?
- Yes.
- Dolce &amp; Gabbana coat.
Oh, well, look who's got it.
- Is that the exact one?
- It's not the one she wore.
- I see.
- Because, you know, she's so
much bigger than me.
- [laughs]
I'm gonna let you get back
to work here.
Bye.
London, Paris, Milan.
- Hi, Ru.
- So tell me about this boat.
- My inspiration for this,
honestly, I mean, we're doing a
future thing, but I wanted to
try to do a flashback
to the future.
- A flashback to the future.
- Yes.
- But we're asking you to be
fashion-forward.
Now, you live in New York city,
the most fashionable city...
- I do.
- In the U.S.
Where do your costumes
come from?
- Um, usually I have people
make them for me.
- I see.
- 'Cause a lot of my costumes
are characters,
like the housewife or that looks
like the lady next-door.
- You don't want the audience
to know who you are.
You want them to see
a character.
But we want to know who you are.
- No, I definitely want them to
know who I am.
- Because you have lip-synched
twice.
- I have.
- Make that Milan come out.
- Okay.
- Get back to work.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Hi, Ru.
- How are ya?
- I'm good. How are you?
- Good.
So what are you working on?
- I have a one-armed catsuit
right now.
- Is that Uranus on...
- It is my-ranus.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- The theme is hope floats.
I want to know about your
darkest hour and how you were
able to get over that.
- Well, as a kid, I had--I grew
up in a really abusive, like,
household.
And it wasn't a very good
childhood.
And it took 16 years for us to
figure it out, but we did.
It feels good to leave all that
stuff back there.
Chicago's a fresh start for me.
I get to live the life that
I want to live.
- So you've come a long way,
baby.
You've pulled yourself up out
of some really dark places.
This is your chance to shine.
I'm counting on you to pull
through.
- Okay.
- Okay, you've done it before.
You can do it again.
- I will.
- All right. Get to work.
- Yes.
- All right.
At ease.
- All right, ladies,
gather round.
Tomorrow on the main stage,
we'll be celebrating Pride with
our extra-special guest judges,
fashionista and TV star, my good
pal Kelly Osbourne will be here.
- Oh, my God.
Yay.
[cheers and applause]
- I love Kelly Osbourne.
Even to even get read by her,
I don't care.
It's an honor.
She's sickening.
- And a woman who's no stranger
to the navy.
From NCIS, Pauley Perrette
will be here.
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
[applause]
- Wow.
- How many times did you work
with her, Willam?
- Just once, so fuck off.
[laughter]
- Now, ladies, remember...it
ain't the size of your boat but
the motion in your ocean, okay?
- Okay.
- Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay. All right.
- See you later.
- Thanks, Ru.
- Bye.
- Arts and crafts day.
- Our challenge today is to make
fabulous fashion-forward
outfits and gay pride floats.
So with challenge,
you have to have a crafty eye,
and you have to be creative with
your float and your costume.
This competition
is really gonna show
who can keep up
with the big girls.
Fucking shit.
Fuck.
- I did it all wrong.
- Oh, my God.
Now I just fucked it up.
- But that's pretty.
Girl, you're gonna win.
- You can kiss my ass.
- [laughs]
- Ugh.
It is very hard to create an
outfit from scratch in a day and
decorate a boat.
It's damn near impossible.
My God, this making a boat crap
is just--is not the type of
dress...
all righty.
- You okay?
- No.
- She doesn't know her idea
for her boat.
- You have a bunch of stuff over
there,
and you have a lot
of good stuff too.
Open stuff up.
Look at the textures.
Look at all that stuff
and just play with it.
Jiggly's just out of her element
being on this competition.
She is so far behind, and it's
just like, "Girl, just get your
crap done."
- The hardest part about this
challenge is not telling
everybody else that I'm gonna
win.
- Wow, that is really cool.
- Yeah, I mean, it looks
egotistical,
but it's got a message,
like, "I'm gonna handle myself
like I'm gonna be
somebody someday."
- You're sickening, bitch.
You're sickening.
- Sickening?
More like absolutely disgusting.
- Really?
- Yeah, bitch.
- Thank you.
- So has anybody ever done,
like, pride performances or
pride shows?
- Bitch, I put my gay pride
time in, honey.
In my years.
- In Pittsburgh, they don't
ask me ever to do Pride.
I mean, maybe they just think
my act is reserved
for nighttime only.
- Maybe it's because she's
a spooky bitch.
- I like spotlights,
not sunlight.
- What was it like for you guys
in your hometowns
growing up being gay?
- I'm from Texas, so Texas is
not about the whole
being gay thing.
I remember, when I first went
out to the gay clubs, there was
a lot of, like, gay bashing,
and, like, guys would come by
with, like, baseball bats.
Like, moving to Chicago, I can
hold someone's hand walking down
the street or I can be
affectionate.
And In Texas, you can't do that.
- Damn.
- It's kind of hard
for me to talk about it.
I don't really like
where I come from.
I don't--it is not
a lot of good memories.
I was teased a lot
when I was young.
I hate talking about it,
'cause it makes me just pissed.
Like, the people that called me
a fat girl,
some of them still work--
no shade--
but still work at McDonald's,
still work at Burger King,
still living at home
with their parents,
ain't got a life.
Home is not a good memory
for me.
- Theresa,
I knew you grew up in Compton.
- Ugh.
- What was that like?
- You don't even think about
saying the world "gay"
or that you're gay.
It's straight-up hood there.
You know what I mean?
So I was threatened
and beat up and told
if I was ever--turned out gay,
I would get killed,
and it was rough.
So I just kept all that
to myself
until I was big enough
and bold enough
and grown enough to move.
And so I did, you know,
and...
- Is the New York drag
community all in Manhattan?
- The New York drag community
is sort of everywhere.
Definitely certain areas where
there's certain drags
you can see.
There's the singing girls,
there's the campy girls, there's
the grunge girls...
- So what are you?
Like, what's your...
- I'm a floater.
My style kind of bounces around.
I don't want to be pigeonholed
as just a drag "queen."
I think it's important for
people to see that there is
an artist on stage.
- I have dignity looks and
paycheck looks.
Dignity is when I will not bend
for anyone, and I don't care if
I make a dollar.
I'm doing what I'm doing.
- Right.
- And there's times the
electric's about to shut off,
so I dress up like Lady Gaga.
- Right.
[laughter]
- Jiggly, is that a men's shirt
or a women's shirt?
Your hanger strap is showing,
and I already know the answer.
- No, it's not.
- You cross-dresser!
We're supposed to be boys today,
and you're cross-dressing.
- Really, girl? Really?
Her slick-ass comments are gonna
drive me crazy.
- ♪ Watching my boat ♪
- Shut up.
- You shut up.
- Ugly bitch.
- You shut your ugly boat
mouth.
- Oh, you have something to
say, bitch?
- Yeah, your boat's ugly.
- You narcissistic whore.
- Your boat's ugly.
- I don't care.
My boat could be ugly, bitch.
- But your face is ugly.
- Your boat don't float.
Your boat don't float.
- Come here and say that,
bitch, 'cause I will inject this
shit right in your cheeks,
ho.
- Ohh, don't talk to me like
Chad Michaels.
You know how passionate he is
about silicone work.
- [as Cher]
Shut up, stupid.
Willam runs his mouth a lot.
It's kind of like a spigot you
can't turn off.
And it started to get on my
nerves.
I'm Cher, bitch.
- You guys, you know what my
boat reminds me of?
- What?
- A winner.
[laughter]
♪ My boat is the best ♪
♪ My boat is pretty ♪
- Selfish bitch,
learn your words.
You will be in the bottom two.
- ♪ I want some breasts ♪
- Bitch.
[alarm goes off]
- Anchors aweigh, bitches.
- Cluck-cluck, ladies.
- So much to do.
- Let's get to work.
- I was having panic attacks
about this damn snake.
- The mood in the workroom
right now is intense.
Queens are hustling,
people gluing, going crazy.
It's insane right now
in the workroom.
- Does this look like a fucking
anchor yet?
I ended up with the final
concept for my boat last minute.
Now I just got to finish it.
Sharon?
- Yeah?
- Does this look like an anchor?
- It kind of looks like
a dick.
- It does look like a penis.
- What's the theme of your
boat?
- The whole, "It gets better,
love you for you,"
very Saint-Tropez.
Bright colors.
Very Saint-Tropez.
So I'm just, like,
scrambling for time.
- Jiggly's is still a mess.
She kept adding crap upon crap
on top of more crap, so it just
looked like a big pile of crap.
- I'm just gonna try to go for
obvious things--sunlight,
yellow, you know, happiness.
- Right.
- I'm gonna get a little grade
school at moments.
- There ain't gonna be nothing
about grade school on my boat.
My boat's gonna be an all-adult
function.
- If I would have made Milan's
boat, I wouldn't have put
The Milan Invasion on it.
I would have blamed it on
someone else.
Like, "I didn't do this boat.
No, this is her boat.
That girl's boat, not my boat."
- I'm looking around the room,
and I'm in drag, everybody else
is practically done and in drag,
and Jiggly's still stapling and
gluing stuff to her float, and
I'm like, "Hello, you only have,
"like, minutes left until you've
got to be in drag and on that
runway."
- It's sink or swim.
You better be ready,
and you better care.
- Jiggly is a hot mess.
Good luck, girl.
- Oh, shit.
Where the fuck are my tits?
- Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Hey, guys.
- Hey, gorgeous.
- Hi.
- Michelle Visage, are you
proud of our girls?
- I am proud to be an American,
and I am proud of our girls.
- [laughs]
Billy B., are you ready to see
our girls?
- I am so ready.
- Kelly Osbourne.
- Hi, Ru.
- You've been grand marshal
of Gay Pride here in
Los Angeles.
- Yes, with my mama.
- Well, you'll feel right at
home here.
- I already do.
- Pauley Perrette,
welcome aboard.
- Thank you.
Happy to be here.
- I love a parade.
Don't you?
- Yes.
- This week our queens were
challenged to design Pride
floats.
Now they're ready to parade
them down the runway.
Are you ready to see their true
colors?
- Hell, yeah.
- Gentlemen, start your
engines,
and may the best woman win.
- ♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ ♪
- Chad Michaels. Ahoy.
- Glamorous.
- She's showboating.
- My outfit is fashion-forward
showgirl--always beautiful,
always painted, nearly naked.
- Starbooty!
- She's serving the deadliest
catch...
- Snapper.
- Dida Ritz in red.
Oh, I love a harem pant.
- I'm serving float
coutureness.
I'm not letting this boat get
in my way.
I always leave my mark.
Honey, I pee on the runway.
Trust.
- Red sky at night,
sailors' delight.
Nice aft.
Up next, Jiggly Caliente in my
favorite color, orange.
- Tangerine dream.
- Yes.
- I look good.
My wrap is flowing.
My hair's flowing.
My makeup is right.
My lips look right.
I look sickening, bitch.
- Mm, it reminds me of
Orange Julius.
Or is it Lrange Jiggly-us.
Milan.
- Hello, sunshine.
- I'm feeling proud of what
I created.
My float is The Milan Invasion.
It's inspired by Fire Island.
- Boatload of wigs.
- It's nice to have extra wigs,
though.
- It is, 'cause, if you end up
on Gilligan's Island and you
want to do shows, well...
- Hello.
- Yeah.
- Ooh, Sharon Needles.
- She is from the
Garden of Eden.
- Does her snake have one eye
or two?
- I was really serving them
some snake realness.
I can strike at any time.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I love!
- Latrice Royale in turquoise.
- The goddess of the sea.
- Wow.
Look at all that water.
- I just want it all to hang
out today.
I have this hair that I baked
and sculpted and hand-painted.
- Love those lips.
- She fell face-first at
Claire's.
- [laughs]
- Now that is a Poseidon
adventure.
- Willam.
Oh, dear.
She's a low rider.
- Check that out.
- Dropping anchor.
Land ho.
- Oh, my God.
Permission to come aboard.
- Ooh, girl, I'm dusted.
- My costume's right,
my body's right.
This challenge is right up my
lagoon.
- She's showing us her
starboard side.
Stick it in the porthole,
Willam.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Like a float warrior.
- Ooh, love is a battleship.
- My look I'm channeling is
fashion-forward sci-fi.
I'm trying to give them
a bad-ass bitch.
- It's the Phi-Phi-tanic.
- She's going down with
the ship.
- Love it.
- Purple for passion.
My colorful queens,
I love a parade.
But now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Chad Michaels.
And what does your float say
about you?
- Obviously, with the stripes
on my costume
and the stripes on my boat,
I'm a drag cougar.
- [laughs]
- Rrargh.
I basically wanted to go with
classic showgirl,
but fashion-forward.
- Can you turn around so I can
see your butt, please?
That's my favorite part of your
whole costume.
I love it.
- Thank you.
- To me, it is traditionally
showgirl.
There's not something so fresh
and modern about it.
- Next up, Dida Ritz.
Wow, and your hair is all big
and everything.
- Take a little bit of advice
and put it to use.
- You have the cutest face.
So adorable.
- You do have a pretty face.
Sometimes I think that you might
rely on it too much.
What you have on,
it's not particularly an event.
You always seem sort of
pedestrian.
- Your boat, it looks a little
bit piñata-like.
You know, you want more.
It is a parade.
- Jiggly Caliente.
Tell us about your float.
- Right now, there's a lot of
gay youth being bulled.
I decided to use "Love you for
you."
I wanted to class it up a bit,
make it very Saint-Tropez.
'cause my outfit is really
a swimsuit.
- Oh, wow.
- Oh, yeah.
- Very Saint-Tropez.
- I'm really happy you took
your cape off.
I was dying to see what was
underneath there,
and it's adorable.
- It's the big reveal.
- You should have walked
the runway without the cape.
The boat, you said you wanted to
give it some class.
It's, like, sixth-grade class.
- Ugh.
- Next up, London, Paris,
Milan.
- Basically I wanted to
represent the history
of the
drag performance invasion on
Fire Island with the girls who
have long passed who have paved
the way for me to go forward in
the future.
And I named it
The Milan Invasion,
because it's me,
and I'm invading the world.
- I know all about Fire Island.
The thing is, the boat didn't
really read that.
It was hard to understand.
- You know, everyone else sort
of had a real message about
pride, and the biggest thing
about your boat is that you made
it about you.
It sort of offended me.
- Sharon Needles.
You've got a little snake story
line going on there, don't you?
- The original green color in
the rainbow flag stood for
nature.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause all gays were hippies
in the '70s.
[laughter]
I used the snake because they're
feared for the wrong reasons.
And I've always been feared for
the wrong reasons.
- I'm so into your hand snake.
- My hand works great on
a snake.
- I think you look beautiful.
Your boat on the other hand
looks like it sank a few years
ago and it's covered in moss.
It sort of lost boat to me.
It just became this big green
thing.
- All right, next up,
Latrice Royale.
Lady turqu-ahh.
- I love anything that
sparkles, and you sparkle from
head to toe, and I love it.
- My lips are gonna crack.
- Tonight you're giving us
Nefertiti meets Ursula
the sea witch.
- Yes!
- I'm gonna challenge you on
one thing, Latrice.
- Tell me.
- The boots.
- [sighs]
- Girl, we seen 'em quite a bit
now.
- Are you saying those boots
weren't made for boating?
[laughter]
- You really are an event.
It's a beautiful, simple boat,
and it has a chicness that you
always seem to have.
It's a good job.
- Thank you.
- Next up, Willam.
- I'm giving you maritime
realness with the starship
Willam.
[laughter]
Amenities include Wi-Fi.
There's a party deck and
a business center.
[laughter]
- Why is Pride important?
- I got married in California
when it was legal, and then now,
all of a sudden, it's not.
Prop 8 got my ass down hard.
So I love that I got to do
a Pride challenge, and this is
Dolce &amp; Gabbana, so I love it.
- So the coat is Dolce, and
the swimsuit is Gaultier.
It's chic, it's fashionable,
it's modern.
The boat looks like it was
professionally done even.
You give very good mast-head.
[laughter]
- And P.S.,
fuck you for
having the most amazing body
ever.
[laughter]
- Thank you, house of Willam.
All right, up next,
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- I just thought purple warrior
princess when you came out.
- I love your boat a lot.
I love the way you coordinated
the outfit with the boat.
And your makeup--you're on
the right track.
- I think you're like a
long-lost Kardashian sister.
You're so beautiful.
- Thank you.
- My one critique is just watch
out for your body shape still.
Right, if you're gonna be wide
there, then you got to give us
more hips, so just pay attention
to it, but you look stunning
tonight, baby.
Keep this up.
- Okay. I will.
- All right, ladies, I think
we've heard enough.
Now, while you untuck in
the interior illusions lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
Now, just between us girls,
what do you think?
Latrice Royale.
- Latrice, I think,
is the real deal.
The boat was very chic...
- The makeup was truly artwork.
Those friggin' boots.
- Oh, my God, they're like
Goth lesbian hiking boots.
I will burn them.
- All right, let's move on.
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Before, I had a problem with
the makeup every single time.
Today was the best that it's
been.
- She is listening, and I think
the more we critique her,
the more she'll get it.
- On down the line we go to
Jiggly.
- I would have loved all of it
had she taken her cape off.
It looked like a tent.
- It almost looked like she was
walking in a straitjacket.
- It's because she could barely
fit in the boat.
- How very dare you?
- What?
- Big is beautiful.
- Love Jiggly.
Tonight it was an epic fail.
- Chad Michaels,
the pink cougar.
- Chad can do no wrong, but,
see, now I'm starting to have
a problem with that.
I want to see Chad be human
and not robotic.
- I have to agree with you.
I would like to see her a little
bit more messy.
- Sharon Needles.
- My mother's maiden name.
- Your mother's maiden name is
Needles?
- Sharon Needles.
- [laughs]
- I loved her whole snake
thing.
- She's very H.R. Pufnstuf.
[laughter]
- I love the fact that she,
like,
she didn't have perfect hair.
It was a bit messy.
All the stuff that we don't like
about Sharon Needles we love
about Chad, and all the stuff we
don't like about Chad we love
about Sharon Needles, so they
need to kind of, like, take tips
from each other.
- All right, Milan.
- I think she thinks she's
more real than she really is.
- Like, she don't need padding.
- Exactly.
- And her body language is
totally "dude in a dress."
- If she lip-synchs tonight and
that wig comes off,
stop it already.
- Right.
- All right, all right, Willam.
- Does anyone really look like
that?
My God.
- How dare they have better
legs than me!
How very dare they!
- Now, Billy, you really liked
the design of the float.
- It was so well done.
It wasn't as vulgar as Milan 's
was.
- The fact that she got out of
it and then made a performance
out of it was also very
entertaining as well.
- Dida Ritz.
- The outfit was very
pedestrian, very mall-like.
- If Dida didn't wear a T-shirt,
I would be saying something
completely different.
- Right.
- Does she deserve to be in the
bottom two
because of the T-shirt?
- Yeah!
- A T-shirt is half your outfit.
- She was the only one up there
with a camel toe.
- Hello!
- Very hot.
- I didn't go there.
[laughter]
- You always have to go there,
darling.
Especially when they're tucking.
[laughter]
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back...
my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
It was the late, great drag
queen and civil rights pioneer
Marsha P. Johnson who fought
back when the police raided
Stonewall.
To honor her legacy, it's up to
you to keep on breaking through.
Based on your pride-filled
presentations, I've made some
decisions.
Chad Michaels, you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Latrice Royale...
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Sharon Needles...
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Willam, you navigated this
challenge beautifully, and we
were swept away.
Condragulations, you are
the winner of this challenge.
[applause]
You will receive a cruise,
courtesy of alandchuck.travel.
- I'm okay with that.
- [laughs]
- It feels correct to win.
When it's right, it's right.
Yes, girl!
- Phi Phi O'Hara...
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Jiggly Caliente...
your message was uplifting,
but your float left us with
a sinking feeling.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- Fuck.
I cannot go this far and get
sent home.
Are you fucking kidding me?
- Dida Ritz, you're just
finding your sea legs, but has
the ship already sailed?
Milan, you set a course for
fabulous, but your message got
lost at sea.
Dida Ritz...
I'm throwing you a lifeline.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Milan, my dear, I'm sorry,
but you are up for elimination.
- Ugh, I'm in the bottom again.
But when it's time for me to
bring it, I want to bring it.
Because it's a competition and
I'm here to win.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you to
lip-synch for your life.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- It doesn't matter if you
love him or capital H-I-M.
♪ ♪
♪ My mama told me ♪
♪ When I was young ♪
♪ We are all born superstars ♪
♪ So hold your head up, girl ♪
♪ And you'll go far ♪
♪ Listen to me when I say ♪
♪ I'm beautiful in my way ♪
♪ 'Cause God makes
no mistakes ♪
♪ I'm on the right track,
baby ♪
♪ I was born this way ♪
- I'm feeling ferocious.
I'm ready to attack.
I'm giving them 110%.
- ♪ I was born this way ♪
♪ Born this way ♪
♪ Ooh, there ain't ♪
no other way ♪
- Jiggly is working it.
She is feeling herself down.
She's trying to save her ass
right now.
- ♪ Don't be a drag ♪
♪ Just be a queen ♪
[judges cheer]
♪ Left you outcast, bullied,
or teased ♪
♪ Rejoice and love yourself
today ♪
♪ 'Cause baby
you were born this way ♪
♪ No matter gay, straight,
or bi ♪
♪ Lesbian,
transgendered life ♪
- Milan, girl.
That's clearly a dude.
- ♪ I'm beautiful in my way ♪
♪ 'cause God makes no mistakes
♪
♪ I'm on the right track, baby
♪ I was born this way ♪
- Baby, you were born this way.
- ♪ I'm on the right track,
baby ♪
- You were born--you were born
this way.
- ♪ I was born this wa-ay ♪
♪ I was born this wa-ay ♪
♪ I'm on the right track,
baby ♪
♪ I was born this wa-ay ♪
- Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies...
I've made my decision.
Jiggly Caliente...
Shante, you stay.
Jiggly, you may join the other
girls.
- Thank you.
- London, Paris, Milan,
the world is calling.
Now, sashay away.
- Thank you.
It was my moment to stop, and so
now I take on the next journey.
Have fun.
Realize that your purpose here
is to be an ambassador, to teach
a message of hope and love,
and every now and then, be the
bitch out of the competition.
- My lucky seven.
Don't be a drag.
Just be a queen.
And, remember, if you can't love
yourself, how in the hell you
gonna love somebody else?
Can I get a amen up in here?
all: Amen.
- All right, now let the music
play.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪