- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
you'll need to survive
the biggest drag disaster
of all time.
The Rupocalypse.
- [screams]
- Ooh, shit,
it's falling apart.
- Jiggly's costume
is a hot mess.
- Jiggly Caliente...
Lashauwn Beyond...
The Princess, Sharon Needles.
- This is my kind of ghoul.
- Con-drag-ulations.
You are the winner
of this challenge.
- Thank you.
- I'm just in disbelief
that I'm here.
- Bitch, you're here.
- Yeah, honey, you better snap
out of it.
Play to win.
Jiggly Caliente,
shantay, you stay.
- Thank you.
- Alisa Summers, sashay away.
And tonight...
you'll be transforming
yourselves into wrestling's
trashiest fighters.
The dolls throw down...
- Get out.
- You're fake-ass hoes.
Get out of here.
[audience oohing]
- And take flight.
- Chicago, bitch.
[screaming]
- With extra-special
guest judges
NBA stars Rick Fox
and John Salley.
[cheers]
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics, a
one-of-a-kind trip courtesy of
ALandCHUCK.travel, headline
Logo's Drag Race tour, featuring
Absolut vodka:
cocktails perfected,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And may the best woman win.
- A gorgeous day.
- Good morning, cluckers.
- We walk in the work room this
morning, and we see Alisa's
message, and it's kind of sad.
I mean, it was official.
Week by week, we're all going to
be going home.
- "Keep it cute, ladies!
"Shady sisters 4-ever!
Love, Alisa."
- Look what you've done.
- That's what you've done, baby.
- It was either her or me,
and I was not going home.
- Let's take a vote.
Can we switch Jiggly for Alisa?
- Yeah, I agree.
- Whoo!
[laughter]
- Being in the bottom two
shook me.
I feel like there's a target
on the back of my head.
And all these bitches are trying
to assassinate me.
So nervous now.
'Cause now I have to really
prove myself.
- Well, can I give you
a piece of advice?
Just really try to stay
more focused
on the competition.
Like, don't--
- I know.
- It was, like--I thought
that I was focused.
I feel like I have to claw
and dig my way
back to the top.
- So you're feeling good
about your win?
- Oh, I'm feeling fantastic
about my win.
- You fucking rocked it.
It was kind of made for you.
- I know.
I'm such a natural loser
that it was very odd for me
to win a challenge.
I'm the freak queen,
and back home,
I'm kind of like
the laughingstock
of the drag community.
And I'm not
used to winning anything.
So it's exciting,
but at the same time,
it's really humbling.
- They're calling you the silent
killer, bitch, because
everybody thought you were gonna
win the challenge.
- I mean, I did think I was
gonna win,
but I understand
why I didn't win.
- Well, after she had said--
- I'm too quiet.
- Yeah, you're too quiet, bitch.
- I was quiet because I was
trying to focus.
My strategy isn't gonna change,
because I know that I prepared
a package to beat these girls.
So, I mean, I'm fine.
- Speak up, Lashauwn.
- Can everybody hear me?
- Fly away.
[siren wails]
[all oohing]
- Girl, you got she-mail.
[cheers]
Hello, dolls.
all: Hi.
- I've come to pump you up.
And I don't mean your lips.
So get ready to beat your mug,
pummel the runway, and fight for
the spotlight.
It's time for some necessary
roughness.
But, remember, just anything
but the face.
I'll get the money, mister.
Just don't hurt my face, please.
[applause]
Hello, hello, hello.
- RuPaul!
- Hi.
[cheers and applause]
Now, ladies, as you know,
padding is the foundation
of drag.
A queen's girlish figure
depends on it.
For today's mini challenge, I
want you to make an ass
of yourself.
Literally. Oh, pit crew.
- Whoo!
- You have 30 minutes to put
all this junk in your trunk.
I'm dividing you
into three groups.
And the one queen from each
group with the juiciest ass
will win.
Ready, set, style.
[exclamations and shouting]
- Don't kick over my packing
peanuts.
- I make fierce pads, but this
ain't how I usually make my
pads, y'all.
- 30 minutes is not enough.
You need at least a good hour
to even start making pads.
- When making your ass, always
draw the shape of Africa.
- That's it.
- Or, as Latrice would say,
the homeland.
- [giggles]
I'm Polynesian, bitch.
Get it straight, honey.
- I thought we were doing an
athletic challenge,
so I'm in a jock.
Sorry about it.
- Okay, lady-kins, time's up.
All right.
Apple bottoms.
Now Jiggly is serving cellulite
realness.
[laughter]
- Yeah, that's how realness is.
- Now walk that ass.
Bottoms up.
Shake it, don't break it.
Phi Phi O'Hara, now that's what
I call a power bottom.
Seems like your pants are coming
down, Madame.
- [screams]
[laughter]
- Madame.
- Next up, the ghetto booties.
Make it pop. Now walk.
- Hips don't lie.
But that ass do.
Girl, can I get some fries
with that shake?
[laughter]
Damn.
- I had a proper ghetto booty,
and I was the only one wearing
lipstick.
- Next up, the badonkadonks.
- A badonkadonk booty, it's
like a whole bunch of
donkadonkadonkadonkadadadada...
- Now walk.
Ass everywhere, ass everywhere.
Ass everywhere.
Ooh, two scoops.
Ladies, all y'all
is sassy assassins.
But three of you really
killed it.
The winners of this mini
challenge are...
Miss Phi Phi O'Hara...
[cheers]
Miss Willam...
[applause]
Miss Chad Michaels.
- Hey.
- Con-drag-ulations.
If I were you, I'd hold on tight
to my padded ass, because, for
this week's main challenge,
you'll be transforming
yourselves into wrestling's
trashiest fighters--the luscious
ladies of the WTF.
- Yes!
- Whoo-hoo.
- I am a big bitch.
Who is gonna outwrestle me?
Nobody.
- Oh, my god.
I am not athletic at all.
- This week, you'll need to
flex your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent to become
over-the-top wrestling
characters.
You will compete in teams.
Phi Phi O'Hara, Willam,
Chad Michaels, since you won the
mini challenge,
you are team captains.
You get to pick your queens,
starting with Phi Phi.
- I'd have to go with Latrice.
- Yes.
- Dida.
- I will take Milan.
- Yeah.
- Come on down, baby.
- Kenya.
- [growls]
- Princess.
- Miss Needles.
- I am a knockout.
[laughter]
Uh, ow.
- I didn't want Jiggly or
Madame LaQueer because they're
always complaining that their
feet hurt or they don't want to
do active stuff.
Lashauwn.
- [growls]
- There we go.
- All right, Willam, it's
between Jiggly and
Madame LaQueer.
- I'm just praying, "Please pick
me, pick me, pick me,
pick me, pick me."
- Jiggly.
- [grunts]
- Yes!
- Wah!
[laughter and applause]
- All right, so that means
that Chad gets Madame LaQueer.
- It feels kind of weird
being, like, the last picked.
You know, the weird boy, but
I'm used to it, though.
- Each team needs to decide
which two will play the
heroines, or the faces, and
villains, or the heels.
In a moment, you'll meet three
pros who will coach you in the
art of wrestling.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
- Let's do a script.
- Mama, you got a dream team
here.
- I know.
That's why I picked it.
- There's something very
important.
I had a previous injury
in my right ankle.
I hurt my right ankle
doing a show.
I didn't saw the step, and my
ankle goes click, and suddenly
I couldn't walk.
- Are you gonna be okay, I
mean, like, with your ankle?
- Don't worry about my ankle.
- I am gonna worry about it,
because it's important.
If your ankle's hurting and you
can't do something, you need to
let me know, because I can't
read your mind.
- I'm so happy with this team.
- I know. I'm excited.
- This challenge includes a lot
of steps.
We have to come up with a back
story, looks, costumes,
moves, everything.
I'm really good with falls and
being, like, stunted.
I do stairs. I can do anything.
I'm really excited because I
usually play people who get beat
up, and I got my ass kicked on
every major network.
- And we just make sure that
we--attitude, attitude,
attitude.
- Wrestling isn't my thing.
I'm not a violent person.
So I'm a little concerned.
- We are gonna ace this,
you guys.
We gon' kick their ass.
- So our challenge is to become
wrestlers.
We're the first team to go up
and practice.
I see three humungous dudes just
going at each other.
Oh, my god. This is real.
- [whimpers]
- I'm "Hollywood's Own"
Joey Ryan.
- Yo soy Hector "El Chido"
Canales.
- I'm Mr. K.O.S.
"King of Submission"
Ryan Taylor.
- Let's now get into a little
bit of the choreography.
Go ahead and throw her
onto Ryan.
- Oh.
- You're gonna catch her and
fall.
- This bitch heavy.
- And then you fall
on your back.
- Oh, my god.
- Fall, bitch.
- As safely as possible.
- Oh, my god.
- I'm worried Lashauwn's not
gonna actually get the concept
of what she has to do here.
Come on, girl. Come on.
- [speaks indistinctly]
- [whimpers]
- [growls]
- Everyone in my group's
personality is so loud...
[yells]
And I'm not really like that.
I'm really quiet and soft.
Oh.
[laughter]
- My god, Latrice.
- We're gonna show you
some strikes to the gut.
- [grunts]
- The big reaction is his sell.
And your sell will be here
and to the camera.
- All right.
I'm an actor.
I've been on TV a lot.
I'm cool. I can do it.
[grunting]
- Pop off, bitch!
- And I did.
I sold it.
I get a People's Choice.
- So the bad guys make their
entrance, they cannot care less
about the audience, right?
Make us hate you.
- Be yourself.
- I got this.
This is cake. Fuck y'all.
I don't give a shit.
New York, motherfuckers.
Brooklyn!
- Jiggly was very aggressive.
- Fuck y'all.
I've got this shit.
- And I was like, girl, take it
down a notch.
- New York, baby.
- I'm not from New York.
- Oh...
- And you were good too.
Princess is giving
closed-captioning,
while she's in stereo.
- Okay, you guys.
Exaggerate, okay?
Like, "Aah!"
Loud. Noise.
- Ahh!
- Larger than that.
- What the hell was that?
- I'm worried about Princess
because she's quiet.
I'm going "Rah! NY, baby!
This is--"
And she's like...
[mumbling indistinctly ]
And I'm like, "Huh?"
- We're gonna demonstrate some
holds for you.
Some wrestling moves for you.
We were thinking of a body slam.
- [laughs]
- Do any of you guys
have a problem with that?
- I'm a little worried
about the physical
extremities of this challenge.
- Let's have you try that
to her.
- Okay. All right.
Come on, Mrs. Ed,
with that horse face of yours.
- Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop a second. Stop.
Stop a second. Stop a second.
You don't want to pick--
- Like a baby.
- Yeah.
- Oh, come on, Grandma.
Oh, my God!
Let me go.
[both grunting]
RuPaul once famously said
that drag
is not a contact sport.
Apparently, she's gone back
on her word.
[coughing]
- From there, we're gonna have
you give her
the airplane spin,
which they're gonna demonstrate
right now.
- It's a very fun--
- Okay.
- I'm concerned that something
could happen with my ankle and
making our team lose.
I have a lot
to be nervous about.
- All right, come on, Madame.
My damn face is sick
of looking at you.
- [grunting]
- Oh. Oh!
- Get her up.
- Put me down.
- Take your time. Slow.
- Jeez Louise.
- Ugh.
- Sorry.
- Ouch.
- You okay?
- I'm nervous about Madame
LaQueer.
She's not as physical as the
rest of us.
She really has to push, push,
and push through it.
- Ouch.
- Y'all got enough sewing
machines over there?
Y'all look like a sweat shop.
- I'm sorry, but did you see
Willam's outfit?
- Yeah.
- Phi Phi's gonna like me
eventually.
I know it.
I think her and I should just
unite with mutual enemies.
- [scoffs]
- I mean, it's just easier
to go after ugly people,
but, I mean, the ugly people
are gonna be gone
soon enough anyway.
- Okay, well, then who's
the ugly people?
- Well, not me.
- Hello.
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi.
- Well, team Phi Phi O'Hara...
- Yes.
- Which team is the faces?
- It would be me and Lashauwn.
- So, of course, these two
are the heels.
What is your story?
- They gave us the wrong
treatment, and we grew beards
instead, and we're a little
bitter about that.
- Are you actually gonna
be wearing beards?
- Yes.
- You know, that concerns me a
little bit, because the luscious
ladies of the WTF need to be
beautiful.
- I think our story will get
across, and it's not that they--
- But you're not the one who's
gonna be looking hideous,
are you, darling?
People watch wrestling because
they want to be excited, they
want to be turned on.
They want beauty.
Now, Lashauwn, can you give me
a little taste of what your good
guy says?
- "Oh, I'm gonna kick your ass."
- In wrestling, the good guys
are just as loud and obnoxious
as the bad guys.
Is it fair to say that you're
still working on it,
you haven't...
- Yeah, we are
still working on it.
I mean, yeah, we are.
- I'm gonna let you
get back to it.
All right.
- Bye, Ru.
- Team Willam, what's going on?
Who on your team are the faces?
[laughs]
Now what are your costumes
gonna be like?
Was that something that you made
or you already had?
- We just embellished
on top of it.
- Oh, I see.
- And I'm embellishing on top
of mine as well.
- Jiggly, you took some heat
last week for your costume.
- Yeah.
- You know, we are looking for
the luscious ladies of the WTF.
- Oh, I'll be luscious.
I'm not trying to be in that
bottom two again.
- Gather around, dolls.
Now, tomorrow at the WTF
main event,
we'll be joined by our
extra-special guest judges...
NBA champions Rick Fox
and John Salley.
[cheers and applause]
- I think I'll tuck extra-tight
for Rick Fox and John Salley.
- Now, remember, safety first.
But, whatever you do,
don't fuck it up.
all: Bye, Ru.
- Whoo.
[cheers]
- Ladies and gentlemen, are you
ready to experience a female
phenomenon?
[cheers]
Bring on the glamazons!
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my god, can you believe
those Bitter Betties
came in here to ask us for help?
And I even let them use, like,
my really good hair products.
- That product?
- Yeah.
- That's the hair-growing tonic.
- [speaks native language]
- You--look what you did
to her hair.
- Are you upset because you
can't handle all this fishiness?
- Your plastic hair and your
plastic tits
and your plastic ass.
We'll handle you.
We'll get in the ring.
- Bring it. Bring it on.
- Come on, girls. Come on.
[cheers]
[rock music]
- Mess with these nasty girls
and you'll end up with a bad
taste in your mouth.
Give it up for Latrice
"The Beast"
and "Killer" Kenya,
the Bitter Betties.
- Ooh.
[booing]
Go.
- Give it up for L.A.'s finest,
Lashauwn "The Blonde"
and Phi Phi "Fierce."
- The crowd was chanting and
all the signs had our names
everywhere.
It felt so good.
I was ready to beat those
bitches down.
[bell clinks]
- You're so pretty.
[exclamations]
- Ooh.
- Whoa!
[booing]
[cheers and applause]
- Get up!
- [speaks Spanish]
- Um, honey, I don't speak
Spanish.
[booing]
- I want to teach you Spanish
right now.
Puta!
[exclamations]
[screaming]
- Oh, hell, no.
- [shouts]
- Now I'm gonna show you how
to really beat a mug, bitch.
[screaming]
[booing]
Let me go! Let me go!
[screams]
[overlapping statements]
[screaming]
[exclamations]
[shrieking]
[bell rings]
[booing]
- Bitter, bitter pill
to swallow.
The Bitter Betties win.
[booing]
- Those other teams
better watch out
because, me and my girls,
we kicked ass.
[booing]
- Touch this skin, honey.
They can't take it.
- Mm-mm. They're overgrown...
both: Orangutans.
- Speaking of orangutans.
- What are you doing in our
dressing room?
- We know it's your dressing
room, as tacky as it is,
like y'all two bitches.
both: Tacky?
- Oh, no, honey, we don't want
to go there.
We saw you two
in Coach Carter's office.
- Oh, so that's how we got
kicked out of school?
'Cause of y'all bitches?
- Get out.
- You're fake-ass hoes.
Get out of here.
[cheers and applause]
- Tuck and cover...
- Shut up!
- Get the fuck out of here.
- For "Pucker Up" Princess
and "J-Train" Jiggly,
the Thunder Booties.
Get on the wrong side of these
sexy scissor sisters, and
they'll cut you--
Willamina "Hater"
and Dida "Diddles".
They're DWF.
- Come on, bitch.
[booing]
[bell clinks]
- Get 'em, girl.
- You plus-sized jujube.
- Oh, please.
[exclamations]
- Come on, bitch.
- I'm giving it all, balls to
the wall, badass, crazy,
wrestler bitch.
- Whoop her ass.
[cheers]
- Get her!
- [yells]
- The Princess, she's not going
as crazy as I am.
So if I get in the bottom two
because of this bitch, it ain't
gonna be cute.
[shouting]
What?
- It's not fair.
[indistinct shouting]
That's not fair!
- Sumo smash!
[exclamations]
- And thank you.
[bell rings]
- The winner is Thunder Booties.
- Team Willam
put on a goddamn show.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, Milan "LaModel", I have
to be honest with you.
I woke up with an itch down
there,
an itch in my pubic hair.
- I've got snatch-scratch
fever too.
- But forget about
this bitch of an itch.
Look who it is.
It's the Bitch Kickers.
- What's up there, Knockouts?
How's it hanging,
scratch 'n' sniff?
- [speaks nonsense]
- They must have gotten our
special delivery we sent in
when we banged their boyfriends.
- [chatters nonsense]
Boink, boink.
- Oh, my god.
- That's right, LaQueer.
- Those Bitch Kickers.
Oh, those cheap, terrible girls.
[cheers and applause]
- Serving face with a side of
whoop-ass.
Give it up for Sharon "Shocker"
and Milan "LaModel"--
the Knockouts.
Don't hate these girls because
they're beautiful.
[booing]
- Shut your pie hole, you slut.
- Hate them because
they're bitches.
- You want some of this?
We got plenty for you too.
- Chadarella "Chainsaw" Michaels
and Madame "LaCrush"--
the Bitch Kickers.
[bell clinks]
- You skinny little
blonde bimbo.
You can run, but you can't hide.
- All right, well, I'm fast
as a butterfly--
[exclamations]
No!
[booing]
[coughs]
- I am a little bit worried
about Madame LaQueer 's ankle.
I mean, you're the captain
of the ship,
you're going down
with the ship.
- All right, Kirstie Alley
before Dancing with the Stars.
[exclamations]
[shouts indistinctly]
This is not in my contract!
- If my ankle hurted, I forgot
about everything.
I was Madame "LaCrush"
in that moment.
[cheers and applause]
- Joan Jett called.
She wants her wig back.
[exclamations]
[shouting]
[crowd chanting indistinctly]
- You're mine now, baby!
I'm gonna hit you
in your visage.
[crowd chanting "USA"]
- No one hits my sister!
Why?
Because I'm sickening, bitch!
[cheers]
- Chicago, bitch!
[shouting]
[cheers and applause]
[bell rings]
- Okay.
- The Knockouts have won!
[cheers and applause]
- We might have been slightly
sloppy,
but I think our team created
the best characters.
[cheers and applause]
- Yay.
- Miss Cheesecake.
It's elimination day, and
everyone's really anxious right
now to find out how they did in
the wrestling challenge.
I think we have a really good
shot at winning.
- I hope.
- I'm just worried.
- What are you worried about?
You did great.
You were so funny.
Were you unpleased with anything
when you left the ring
yesterday?
- With me, no.
I am kind of iffy
about Princess.
It is a competition, and, they
don't like one thing, the whole
team goes on--
it's a team challenge.
- That energy you're giving off
is bringing everybody else down.
Girl, I cannot be bothered
right now.
- Are you nervous today?
- You know what, I am a little
bit nervous.
You might feel some sort of kind
of way, and you could be dead
wrong.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thinking you sickening bitch
and talented bitch,
and they be like, "wah-wah-wah."
- I'm a little nervous to see
what the judges think about me
in the ring.
I did my best, but you never
know what they're gonna say.
- You sew for all the girls
back at home?
Like, the girls.
The girls the girls.
- Just girls like you.
By me sewing so much, I don't
really get a chance
to even be in drag myself.
- Uh-huh.
- So it's like I missed
my drag childhood.
- Ha ha.
- So that's why the competition
is perfect for me, 'cause I'm
just filling in for what I
missed out on.
- That's sickening, 'cause you
definitely
about to make up
for some lost time.
- Ooh.
- Hey-hey, that's what you get.
The ultimate drag boot camp
of life.
- Madame, what does your family
think about you doing drag?
- I'm not close to my family
at all.
My family, for me, are my
friends.
They're the best friends
in the whole world.
Baby, don't. It's okay, mami.
- We're selfish and vain
creatures of beauty, and isn't
it bizarre how we make the best
friends in the world?
- [laughs maniacally]
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, baby.
- Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, my tag team
sister.
- I got a full nelson for you
right here, mama.
- [chuckles]
Billy B, welcome home.
- Thanks, Ru.
- Are you wrestling
with something?
- Not since I was trying to get
my wallet back
from Michelle in the back.
- [chuckles]
Hey, Rick Fox, what did you
think of my girls?
- I was impressed.
Think there was a lot of fight.
- Good. And John Salley.
- Hello, Ru.
- BK in the house.
[laughter]
I'm so glad you're here.
This week, our queens were
challenged to hit the mats as
the luscious ladies of the WTF.
Tonight, I've asked them all
to come decked out in their best
girly-girl attire.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
First up, Kenya Michaels.
Gorgeous.
You know, lil' Kim only wishes.
- It's a pink Monday.
- I love the runway.
I feel amazing
because I love to walk.
- Now that is a living doll.
- Mary-Kate Minaj.
Lashauwn Beyond.
She melts in your mouth,
not in your hand.
- Got a penny? She's got a ball.
- [laughs]
- I'm serving bubble gum
yum-yum,
just having fun being
flirty, pretty, going girly
beyond.
- I'd like to stick a quarter
in her slot.
- Where is her slot anyway?
- Sharon Needles.
- Ooh.
The lost Arquette sister.
- Oh, wow, she's doing femme.
She got an injection of beauty.
- Playing girly-ish, bouncy,
and sexy is just something
really foreign to me.
Just want to show the judges
that I could bring beauty
to the stage
in this competition.
- Mwah.
For your consideration,
Jiggly Caliente.
- Kimora lee Simmons
has put on some weight.
- You're jiggling, girl.
- I'm serving banjee girl
meets sweet 16, very new York.
- It's Jiggly 's quinceanara.
London, Paris, Milan.
I see London, I see France, I
see Milan 's underpants.
- I am feeling like black Barbie
meets a valley girl.
But, because John Salley is
there, I'd rather
be the Salley girl.
- Once she gets pumping,
it's hard to make the body stop.
- Madame LaQueer.
Representing Puerto Rico.
- [speaks Spanish]
She's working the asymmetrical
hairdo.
- Or a hair show in Mississippi.
- I feel great.
I feel like I'm floating.
I think is the most beautiful
I've looked
throughout all the competitions.
- Where there's smoke,
there's a pussy on fire.
[laughter]
- This is why I love this show.
- Dida Ritz.
- I thought
it was P. Diddy's mom.
- [laughs]
- Janice Combs.
- I'm giving fish, I'm giving
face, I'm giving you vogue.
I know my runway is fierce.
- Look at those legs.
My good--and they go
all the way up.
- They do? Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- They're not wooden?
- Chad Michaels.
Lady "chadderley".
Oh, my goodness, the world
according to Paris.
- Paris Hilton,
where are they now?
- I'm serving up girly-girl
realness fish on a stick.
I kind of look just like
a yummy little cupcake.
- Heidi Montag called.
She wants her old body back.
The Princess.
She had a little time
for a quick blowout
before she came out.
- It's a windstorm backstage,
I'm thinking.
- Yes, yes.
- The look I'm going for is
very rock star
meets little girl.
I am so pumped
for my look today.
- Rock on.
- It's like there's something
about The Princess.
- [laughs]
- Up next, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Telemundo.
- Telenovela realness.
- I was showing
a little bit of skin
and giving them dragged-out
Miami housewife.
- Ooh, her legs are like peanut
butter--easy to spread.
Latrice Royale.
Ooh, crown Royale.
I'll have one on the rocks.
- I am feeling good and
looking gorgeous, darling.
Pretty in pink.
I was very pleased.
- Star Jones called.
She wants her old body back.
- She can't have it.
It's otherwise preoccupied.
- Allegedly.
[laughter]
Next up, Willam.
- Hey.
- Wow.
Look at those shoes.
- My look for today
is rich bitch mistress.
I'm serving girly-girl on a
platter to go,
sauce on the side.
- Look how her outfit
accentuates her sugar walk.
- Toddlers and Tiaras,
where are they now?
- I think she's Tanya Tucker.
My girls.
You look smashing.
Yesterday, you changed the face
of professional wrestling
forever.
I smell a spin-off.
But one group in particular
really smacked down
the competition.
The winning WTF team is...
Team Chad Michaels.
- Whoo!
- Jesus.
[laughter]
- Thank you, Ru.
- Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
But two divas stole the show.
Madame LaQueer, Chad Michaels.
- The Bitch Kickers.
- Good job, ladies.
- You are both the winners of
this week's challenge.
You'll receive a selection of
wigs from Risque Wigs.
- Oh, my god, I feel so great.
I certainly actually proved them
wrong about having
picking me last.
- However, neither of you will
receive immunity next week.
Team Chad Michaels, you may
leave the stage.
Ladies, it's time for the
judges' critiques.
First up, Willam.
Hey, mama.
- Hi.
- Did everything turn out
the way you had planned?
- I think our moves kicked ass.
- Oh, I thought the competition
was weak in the ring.
The faces she was giving us
just didn't seem believable.
It was fake.
- Wait a minute.
Wrestling is not fake.
- No, that wrestling was fake.
- Thank you, Willam.
Next up, Dida Ritz.
Now why'd you choose this
as your girly look?
- I'm really channeling
Carrie Bradshaw,
so I thought downtown
New York, very chic.
- In the ring, you had,
you know,
the girl that sort of walked
around the ring thing perfect,
better than you had
the wrestling down.
- Thank you, Dida.
The Princess.
- I'm a fan from the hair
to the dress.
I think I bought that dress
for my daughter.
- I disagree. I hate your hair.
I think it looks
like a bad hair show.
- As far as the performance
goes, we didn't see any of the
rebel that I know you are.
- I'm a very Zen person.
Just know that
that was me really trying.
- Try harder.
- All right,
let's go to Jiggly Caliente.
May I call you Jiggly?
- Of course you can, Ru.
- How'd you feel on the runway?
- I felt so cute.
The lollipop in my mouth,
door knockers in my ears.
- The lollipop was more
interesting for me
than what you're doing
style-wise.
- And tell me about in the ring.
- It was very energetic
and over the top.
- Jiggly, what was the hardest
part of this challenge?
- The thing is, Princess is very
Zen, she's very quiet.
We needed to be, like, crazy,
badass bitches.
- It's hard,
when you're in a team,
and you're trying to make up
for both of you.
- Thank you, Jiggly.
Next up, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Hi.
- You were reading older
than you have to.
You could be younger
and more modern.
- I'm watching you, Phi Phi.
I love you.
I think you're gorgeous,
and in the ring,
you were freakin' hi-lar-i-ous.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Phi Phi.
Lashauwn Beyond.
- Hi, Ru.
- How are your balls?
- My balls are great.
- On the runway,
the gumball machine
told me exactly what
those balls were doing
on your chest.
- Better than on her chin.
- Ha!
- I couldn't disagree more.
Your hair and your makeup,
you look like
a backup singer for
Luther Vandross in 1988.
- Rick Fox, what'd you think?
The ring?
- It's not memorable enough
for me.
I would have liked
a little more story
and color to the character.
- Next up, Kenya Michaels.
- Hola.
- I thought it was Nicki Minaj.
I'm not joking you.
Except she doesn't have the ass
of Nicki or the money.
- What about as a wrestler?
As "Killer" Kenya?
- It was like it was
Biggie Smalls and lil' Kim
all over again.
Baby, baby.
- [laughs]
- You look like a star, you
look modern, you look
fashionable, and I think you're
the one to beat.
- Thank you.
- Latrice Royale.
- Hello, Ru.
- Shag-quille O'Neal Latrice.
- [laughs]
- You set the tone for the
whole afternoon.
- Oh!
- You had me at splat.
- [laughs]
Thank you, Latrice.
Well, ladies, I think we've
heard enough.
While you girls untuck in the
Interior Illusions Lounge, the
judges and I will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
All right, just between us
brothers and brother-lovers...
- Thank you.
- Let's start with Willam.
- I think Willam is extremely
fierce and extremely talented
and very freakin' funny.
But I also think there's
a borderline of smarminess.
I think there might
be an attitude in there
that can get in the way.
- She seemed like a team captain
that didn't lead.
- I think she did a good job
of leading.
I don't feel that The Princess
did a good job of following.
- All right, let's talk
about The Princess.
- Her performance
was really flat.
- I kind of thought
there was a rock star in there.
- She's not charismatic enough
to be a rock star.
- Dida Ritz.
- She's pretty.
It's just the wigs are not
styled, they're not done.
- You know, she was going
for Sex and the City,
and it was more like
Sex in the Alley.
- Oh, okay.
Well, I'm not gonna turn
that down either.
- [laughs]
- Jiggly Caliente.
- In the ring, she uses
everything she has.
I thought that was an outfit
until I realized that was really
her belly.
- [laughs]
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- I don't know what's under
all that makeup,
but she doesn't
paint herself pretty.
- I know she's heavy-handed
on the makeup, but hey...
who isn't?
- [laughs]
Lashauwn Beyond.
Now, it was remarked that
Lashauwn's personality
was kind of shy.
- She'll get out of that shyness
when she realizes it doesn't get
her anywhere.
- She's a mess.
And her personality is like a...
Like a brick.
- All right, Kenya Michaels.
Little Puerto Rican sweetheart.
- She's half the size
of any of them
with double or triple
everything else.
There was nothing wrong.
- Her performance was flawless
as well.
I thought she did a great job
as "Killer" Kenya.
- Latrice Royale.
- She owned that role
in the ring.
It was hard for anyone else
to do better than that.
- I was very happy with her,
and I do really like her
and her personality.
So she's gonna be fun to watch.
- All right, silence.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your presentation
in the main ring
and on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Latrice Royale, Kenya Michaels,
Phi Phi O'Hara,
you ladies jumped
on this wrestling challenge
and came out on top.
You are all safe.
- Thank you.
- You may leave the stage.
Jiggly Caliente,
we want to know,
is there more to you than just
a queen from the 'hood?
You are safe.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- You may join the other girls.
The Princess.
You were channeling pink,
but your performance was beige.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- I'm shocked.
My outfit was on it today,
whether Billy B
liked my hair or not.
And I worked my ass off
yesterday in the ring.
There's no reason why I should
have been in the bottom two.
- Willam...
you're safe.
- Bye.
- Lashauwn Beyond,
as a wrestler, you were more
mumble than rumble.
Dida Ritz, your Sex and the City
couture
does not deserve a sequel.
Dida Ritz...
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Lashauwn Beyond, I'm sorry,
my dear, but you are up
for elimination.
- My whole body started pumping.
I'm nervous because I want
to stay in the competition
and I know this dictates
if I will or not.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me and save
yourself from elimination.
The time has come to lip-sync
for your life.
- I'm pretty amazing,
and I'm ready to show it.
Bring it on.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
-  Hey, beep beep
Bad girls
Talking about the sad girls
Sad girls
Talking 'bout bad girls
Yeah
- I want to show Ru that I can
give more personality.
It's not over yet.
I'm not ready to go.
-  Now you and me
We're both the same
-  Both the same
-  But you call yourself
By a different names
-  Different name
-  Now your mama
won't like it
When she finds out
-  Finds out
- I'm telling myself, soak up
this moment right now.
Live in it.
Balls to the wall do it.
-  Toot-toot
Hey,
beep-beep
- To do the whole song with
no shoes in closed-toed
pantyhose like a web-footed
duck, Lashauwn 's drag mother's
gonna read him for not even
starting the song in shoes.
-  So you want
to spend some time
Yeah
Beep beep
Talkin' 'bout bad girls
Toot toot
Haa
Beep beep
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies...
I've made my decision.
The Princess...
Shantay, you stay.
You may join the other girls.
Lashauwn...
you are a young queen.
May this experience lift you
to new heights above and beyond.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you.
It's bittersweet, but...
I'm happy for me to be so young
and I've only been doing it for
such a short amount of time.
Some of these girls
being 40 and 50
and so...it was sickening.
- Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get amen up in here?
all: Amen!
- All right, let the music play!