- It's Michelle Visage,
reporting live
from the red carpet
at RuPaul's Drag Race
Reunited.
- It's like the Oscars
with better acting.
- Listen, honey, those hoes
got knives
in their breastplates.
They're not coming after me,
no, ma'am.
- Are you jealous?
- Roxxxy encompasses everything
that a drag superstar
should be.
- I love Jinkx.
- I think I want Alaska to win.
- It's anyone's game
at this point.
- All will be revealed tonight
on RuPaul's Drag Race
Reunited.
- Mwah.
- I think it's gonna be
an amazing night.
[cheers and applause]
- Give it up for the queens
of season five!
♪ ♪
The Cincinnati sensation,
Miss Penny Tration!
[cheers and applause]
Now, we gotcha!
Serena ChaCha!
[cheers and applause]
WeHo adjacent,
Monica Beverly Hillz!
[cheers and applause]
Sweeter than maple syrup,
Honey Mahogany!
[cheers and applause]
Catch of the day,
Vivienne Pinay!
[cheers and applause]
Light it up for Lineysha Sparx!
Taste this crazy rainbow,
Jade Jolie.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
Ivy Winters!
[cheers and applause]
She don't get cute,
she gets drop-dead gorgeous.
Alyssa Edwards!
[cheers and applause]
Everybody's cuckoo
for Coco Montrese.
[cheers and applause]
The totally addictive Detox.
And our final three.
The 49th state, Alaska!
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
The sleeper from Seattle,
Jinkx Monsoon!
[cheers and applause]
And the queen on everybody's
lips, Roxxxy Andrews!
[cheers and applause]
[soft music playing]
♪ ♪
- Ladies and gentlemen,
RuPaul!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ All the dreams you had ♪
♪ All the things you wanted ♪
♪ Don't turn your back ♪
♪ It's not too late ♪
♪ You better love yourself ♪
♪ Before you love somebody ♪
♪ Love somebody,
love somebody ♪
♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
- ♪ Amen ♪
- ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
- ♪ If you can't
love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell you gonna ♪
♪ Love somebody else? ♪
♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
- ♪ Amen ♪
- ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
- ♪ If you can't love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell you gonna ♪
♪ Love somebody else? ♪
- ♪ Amen ♪
- ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
- ♪ If you can't love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell you gonna ♪
♪ Love somebody else? ♪
♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
- ♪ Amen ♪
- ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
- ♪ If you can't love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell you gonna ♪
♪ Love somebody else? ♪
♪ A-amen ♪
Hoo!
[cheers and applause]
[clears throat]
Thank you, thank you.
Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race
Reunited.
- I love you, Ru!
- I love you.
I'll meet you after the show.
Let's get some money, though.
[cheers and applause]
Now, I am beyond excited
that all my girls are back
to help me crown
America's next drag superstar.
[cheers and applause]
[giggling]
But the thing that makes
tonight
and every night
so extra special
is you,
the Drag Race fans.
[cheers and applause]
Honey, you have turned
Monday night into par-tay night!
That's right.
It's true.
I know that you all get
together, get your drink on,
scream shit at the TV screen.
I know what you do.
So whether you're watching
in a bar or at a house party
or kiki-ing with
#friendsonline...
[audience laughs]
I want everyone
within the sound of my voice
to scream,
"I'm sick and twisted,
and I'm not gonna take it
anymore!"
Come on, say it with me.
all: I'm sick and twisted,
and I'm not gonna take it
anymore!
- Again.
all: I'm sick and twisted,
and I'm not gonna take it
anymore!
- All right!
[cheers and applause]
So keep your freak flag
flying high.
And from the bottom
of my heart,
thank you for making this season
the biggest
in Drag Race herstory.
It's true.
You know...
RuPaul's Drag Race
isn't about who gets eliminated,
it's about who keeps
coming back.
And tonight, so many
of our queens have returned.
Give it up for
the Drag Race royal box.
[cheers and applause]
Hey, pork chop!
[laughing]
Now, are you ready for some
reunion realness?
[cheers and applause]
'Cause I have one thing to say.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman...win!
[cheers and applause]
These first three queens
were only here
a few short weeks,
but they made a big splash.
Take a look.
- Hello, boys.
My name is Penny Tration.
I was chosen
in the online voting contest.
- Deeper, Penny Tration.
Girl, you're gonna put
Shelley Winters out of work.
- [laughing]
- My name is Serena ChaCha,
and I'm interested in
fine art drag.
There is, um, a new art movement
called soft sculpture.
It's more about creating
a sculpture
rather than just tailoring.
- Hello, girls.
I'm Monica Beverly Hillz.
I have been called
ghetto,
banjee, trashy.
I was raised in the ghetto.
You know, I'm street smart,
and there's nothing wrong
with that.
- That is a nice ass.
- And it's not padded.
- Monica is slaying the hell
out of Serena,
and I'm very happy.
- We all love you.
- We love you.
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome, ladies.
Welcome.
First up, Penny Tration.
Now, Penny, was it hard to, uh,
go home first?
- It was great.
I got to get away
from these bitches.
- Oh, okay. All right.
So now, which of the challenges
would you have rocked?
- Oh, I think
the reading challenge
was pretty much my forte.
- Oh, well, today's
your lucky day, darling,
because the library is open!
- Let's start with
a hometown favorite,
the lovely Detox.
Detox, when you walk down
the runway,
I do expect for the credits
to start running
for Gorillas in the Mist.
[laughter]
And to my dear, dear Serena,
I would read you,
but it does appear
life already has.
[audience "ohs"]
- All right.
Okay, well, now, the library
is closed...officially.
Next up, Serena ChaCha.
Now, your art school background
seemed to rub people
the wrong way.
So what would you have done
differently?
- I would've shut my ass up
and worn a sequin dress
and asked to borrow
one of Coco's pair of earrings
and walked down that runway
full of glam.
- Okay, well, which challenge
would you have rocked?
- As a fan of telenovelas,
Luis Fernando Sylvester
Montalban...
[speaking Spanish]
[cheers and applause]
- Escandalo!
Ugh!
Now, a lot of big revelations
happened
on the main stage,
but one of the most moving
came from Monica Beverly Hillz.
It raised a lot of questions
about what is drag
and what is trans.
When we come back,
I'm gonna ask Monica
for some answers.
Don't go away.
- Coming up,
the queens answer
viewer questions.
So let's get this mother
trending.
Are you team Alaska?
Team Jinkx?
Or team Roxxxy?
Let your voice be heard
as we prepare to crown
America's next drag superstar.
- [laughs]
Welcome back
to RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited.
We are just moments away
from finding out which queen
will be crowned America's
next drag superstar,
but first, let's talk
to another fierce queen,
Monica Beverly Hillz.
- Hi, mama.
- Now, Monica, you came
on to the show with passion,
poise, and a secret.
Let's take a look.
Monica, tell me
what's on your mind.
- It's true what you're saying.
There is a lot going
through my head.
I feel I'm not here.
I've just
been holding a secret in,
and I've been trying so hard,
and--
- What secret?
- I'm not just a drag queen.
I'm a transgendered woman.
[cheers and applause]
- Monica...
You know, there's a lot of
confusion out there,
so help everybody out.
Okay, now, can a girl
be a drag queen
and a trans woman
at the same time?
- Yes.
Drag is what I do.
Trans is who I am.
- All right. All right.
Yeah.
And you know, for the record,
everybody out there,
the only requirement
for being here is the desire
to be America's
next drag superstar,
and the only thing we screen for
is charisma, uniqueness,
nerve,
and talent.
[cheers and applause]
Now, uh, how have things been
since the show?
- It's been really great.
I actually got approached
by a cosmetic line.
I'm a face model now, so--
- What?
- I'm good at giving face, baby.
It's my moneymaker.
- Next up, a sexy Puerto Rican
and a bicoastal twosome
that made me do something
I thought I'd never do:
a double elimination.
Oh, shoot!
[laughs]
Take a look.
Honey Mahogany,
Vivienne Pinay,
neither one of you showed me
the fire it takes to stay.
I'm sending you both home.
Ladies, welcome.
Now, Vivienne, you've been
called
the fishiest queen ever.
Now, do you think
being fishy is enough?
- Well, for me it is.
[laughter]
Now, was it enough
for this season?
Obviously not.
If it were America's
next drag supermodel,
I would definitely be
in the top three.
- All right, all right.
Now...
Girl, I heard a rumor
that you work
for Alyssa Edwards now.
Is that true?
- [laughs]
Well, she likes to think so.
But I haven't received
my first paycheck, so...
- Oh, bitch.
- I don't know.
[audience "ohs"]
[laughing]
But what I have been doing,
I've been doing
makeup tutorials online.
- Oh, okay.
Do you think
I'd look good in makeup?
[audience laughing]
No, I'm serious.
I mean, I wanna try it.
- Well, girl...
[cheers and applause]
Girl, I like you
how you are right now
in your natural state.
- Uh-huh.
- But if you do wanna try it,
I would start off
with a tinted moisturizer.
- Okay, okay.
That's good advice.
Up next, Honey Mahogany.
Yes, mama.
Now, Honey, your style
was criticized
for being a little too
Bed, Bath, and Beyonce,
you know?
Now, what do you have to say
for yourself?
- Well, I found myself
a fab new style team
in San Francisco, where the look
does matter.
[audience cheers, laughs]
And, um, I have a little
something I'd like to show you.
- Oh.
Ooh, ooh.
Ooh!
[cheers and applause]
- All right.
- [mouthing words]
- Wow.
- Do you want me
to turn around?
Should I turn around?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- All right.
TrimSpa, baby.
[laughter]
Now, Honey, as our first
San Francisco queen,
can you describe
the San Francisco style?
- You know, it's hard to
describe the San Francisco style
because there are so many
different types of drag
in San Francisco.
We have fairies,
we have bearded ladies,
we have glamour queens,
pageant girls,
the Ducal Court--
we've got it all.
- Oh, all right.
I love it!
Now, Honey, San Francisco
is so proud of you
and so am I.
Keep representing, girl.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Up next, Lineysha Sparx.
Now--
[cheers and applause]
So, now, Lineysha,
Charo couldn't make it tonight
to translate, so why don't you
address the audience
in Spanish?
It might be easier
in your native tongue.
- Of course.
[speaking Spanish]
[cheers and applause]
- I couldn't have
said it better myself.
Really, I couldn't have.
Lineysha, you know I love you,
but this season,
you committed a sin
that is unforgivable.
- Yeah?
- Take a look.
Who is playing Diana Ross?
- That would be
Miss Lineysha here.
- Are you familiar with
Diana Ross and the Supremes?
- Um, not really, no.
[glass shattering]
- Okay.
- [laughing]
Lineysha, do you know
who Diana Ross is now?
- Well, right now, yes.
I love--she's banana dance.
That is not--
- That's Josephine Baker, baby.
- Ah, sorry.
Um, no, but it's just kidding.
It's just kidding.
- Okay, so name
a Diana Ross song.
- Diana Ross song?
I know that she move like this.
And she's--
That was--I was practicing.
- Um, immigration?
- Ru! How rude!
[laughter and applause]
- Immigration?
- [giggling]
- Well, you're not alone,
because I know there are
a lot of young'uns out there
that could use a course
in gay miracles.
Pay attention, because there
will be a pop quiz.
Time for your Drag Race
herstory minute.
The reading rainbow
begins with
the one and only Judy Garland.
You know, she played that girl
in the stoner film
about the ruby-red pumps.
The glamorous '40s gave us
broads like Bette Davis,
Joan Crawford,
and Lena Horne.
The '50s dropped
atomic blonde bombshells--
Marilyn Monroe, Doris Day,
and Etta James.
That's right, a sister can have
blonde hair too.
The swinging '60s gave us
the super-duper Supremes,
"Tinta" Turner,
and Barbra Streisand.
Well, hello, gorgeous!
The "me" decade of the 1970s
saw Diana go solo,
Dolly split with Porter,
and Farrah told
Charlie's Angels
to kiss her T&amp;A good-bye.
The '80s were a holiday,
as the rhythm nation showed
its true colors with Madonna,
Janet, and Cyndi.
Oh, and Faye Dunaway
stole my heart
with just three little words:
"No wire hangers!"
The '90s were dominated
by Mimi,
Whitney, Britney, and X-Tina
and a little girl group
goin' by the name
of Destiny's Child.
Which brings us to today's
reigning divas:
Gaga, Beyonce, Katy, and Nicki.
And if you didn't learn
anything else,
just remember one thing:
Cher, Cher, Cher, Cher, stupid.
And that's today's
drag herstory minute.
[laughs]
And, honey, that's just the tip
of the iceberg.
So please tweet me
your favorite divas @RuPaul.
It takes a village, people!
- Coming up...
The final face-off between
fierce rivals
Coco Montrese
and Alyssa Edwards.
Who will be crowned America's
next drag superstar?
Find out when RuPaul's
Drag Race Reunited continues.
- [laughs]
Welcome back
to RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited.
Now, these next two queens
represented
the ultimate contrast
in styles.
One was quiet, ladylike,
and demure,
and the other was, well,
Jade Jolie.
Take a look.
- I'm the sweetest bitch
you'll meet,
but if you come for me,
then you'll see
a whole new side.
Girl, you ain't that pretty.
- Oh.
- Cover girl,
don't cover boy, baby.
You're a dirty bitch.
- I don't understand
why you're trying
to like come for me.
- You had rolls
all over the place in the back.
It was disgusting.
- Back rolls?
- My name is Ivy Winters.
- Are those your pictures
on there?
- They're all my face.
I will figure out a way
to turn it into a costume.
- You make everything
that you wear?
- I do.
- You're mind-blowingly
talented.
- This week's winner is...
Ivy! Ivy!
[echoing]
Ivy Winters!
- Hi, mama.
- [laughs]
Miss Jolie.
You know,
when you first arrived,
everybody thought you were
gonna be the sweet one.
But you turned into
a Sour Patch Kid.
What was going on?
- Me too.
I swear I was America's
sweetheart until I watched it.
I was like,
that's a cunt, honey.
[laughter]
But it was rainbowy
and gorgeous, so it was okay.
- Now, I wanna ask you,
do you regret accusing
Alyssa Edwards of having...
back rolls?
- Oh, my gosh.
- Back rolls?
- [laughs]
I consider Alyssa
one of my very good friends,
and I think she's fabulous
and fierce.
- All right.
Up next, Ivyyyyy Winters!
Now, Ivy, you showcased
one breathtaking outfit
after another.
Now, do you think
the other queens were jealous?
- No, I sew
for a lot of drag queens,
so if you're jealous, you can
always call me.
- Oh, okay. All right.
Well, it pays to advertise.
[laughter]
Do you have any regrets?
- Yes, I would have to say
my Marilyn.
- Oh, is that who you were
playing?
- That's what I was--
[laughs]
- What was it like
to see yourself
as Norma Jean, Miss Thang?
- That was, like, the first time
I've ever tried
impersonating someone.
- Yeah.
- I wish I would've went
with my second choice.
- So what would you have done
if you hadn't done Marilyn?
- I would've done Julia Child.
- Really?
- [as Julia Child]
Bonjour!
Welcome to my kitchen.
My name is Marilyn Monroe.
[cheers and applause]
- Keep that sewing machine
humming away, girl.
Now, Ivy, I've gotta confess.
I wanna tell you why I say,
"Ivyyyyy Winters!"
- Thank God.
- Yes.
Now, to help me with this
explanation,
please welcome the star
of Life With La Toya,
La Toya Jackson.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Hi!
- Thank you very much.
- Now, La Toya, you have been
a guest judge
on RuPaul's Drag Race
more than any other person.
- [giggles]
- Why do you keep coming back?
- Because I love the show, Ru,
and I love you.
- Aw, thank you.
Thank you.
- I do.
- That's very sweet.
Now, La Toya, in 1989,
you did a pay-per-view concert
called A Sizzling Spectacular.
Do you remember that?
- Sort of, yeah.
- Well, I gotta tell ya.
I became so obsessed
with the way
you introduced
musician Edgar Winters.
Would you introduce him
for me now?
- Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Edgar Winters!
- Yeah, okay.
Well, but I gotta tell ya,
it was more like,
"Ivyyyyy Winterrrrs!"
- Edgarrrrrr Winters!
- I want everybody
in the audience to say it.
all: Ivyyyyy Winters.
- Okay, now, La Toya,
you say Edgar Winters.
- Okay.
Edgarrrr Winters!
[laughter]
- Ivyyyyy Winters!
- No! Edgarrrrr Winters,
you guys!
- [cackling]
- It is.
I don't know.
Now you know.
- La Toya, thank you so much
for clearing that up.
And I know you gotta go,
but would you like to hear
a little bit of our new duet
as you leave?
- Ooh, of course I would.
Are you kidding?
- It's called Feel Like Dancin'.
Hit it!
- ♪ I feel like dancin' ♪
- Let the music play.
See you later, Toy-Toy.
- ♪ Keep on dancin' ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
- ♪ Till then I say ♪
♪ Live for today ♪
Oh, wow!
Now, all drag queens
throw shade,
but this season,
Coco Montrese
and Alyssa Edwards
were heavyweight champions.
Let's take a look.
- Oh, boys!
- And then walks in
Coco Montrese.
- Oh, my God!
Alyssa Edwards.
- We haven't spoke
in two years.
- It was pure hell!
- And the Academy Award
goes to--
- Fuck you, Alyssa.
- And look how orange
you fucking look, girl.
- Now, Miss Alyssa...
- Whoo-whoo!
- Now, you pushed it.
- I'm joking with you.
- I'm not joking, bitch!
- Ladyboys and gentlemen,
it's the rematch of the century!
The Rumble
in the Lipstick Jungle!
Welcome to the center ring
Coco Montrese
and Alyssa Edwards!
[cheers and applause]
- Oh!
both: Mwah. Mwah.
- Ladies, welcome.
- Hello, hello.
- Now, I think I speak
on behalf
of all the Drag Race fans
everywhere when I say,
"Girl, your feud was endless,
honey."
And confusing!
It was so confusing,
am I right?
But I think I finally
figured it out.
So I'm gonna try
and explain it to everyone
just like my play cousin
Cornisha would, okay?
All right.
Alyssa was crowned
Miss Thing USA,
but after she came up,
she wasn't holding it down
no mo'.
- [scoffs]
- So and since Coco
was still thirsty,
she damn well
cold-snatched the crown.
So Alyssa thought Coco
was frontin',
just 'cause she was grinding up
as first runner-up,
you know what I'm saying?
So basically, y'all mad
'cause y'all friends.
Am I right, ladies?
- [laughs]
- Yeah!
- That's what I thought.
- That's it.
- I will say that coming
into it and seeing Coco,
I really wasn't bothered so much
about the pageant drama...
More or less how we were going
to be interacting
with each other.
- Yes. Okay.
So, Coco, what was it like
hearing the other queens say
that your makeup was busted?
- I mean, watching myself
back on TV,
I was like, "Ooh!
You do look like a Dorito."
[laughter]
But I think I got it now,
I think.
[cheers and applause]
- It looks good.
Well, Coco and Alyssa,
your lip-sync battle
was epic,
and I'm not the only one
who thinks so.
Watch this.
- Hi, Alyssa. Hi, Coco.
It was so exciting for me
to see you two ladies
lip-sync to my song
Cold Hearted Snake
during this year's
Drag Race.
If it were up to me,
neither of you'd go home.
You were fantastic.
Just remember this, ladies.
America loves you,
and so do I.
And so does Thumbelina.
[cheers and applause]
- Coco and Alyssa,
stay right where you are.
I'm not through with you yet.
- ♪ I feel like dancing ♪
- Coming up, Detox comes clean,
the queens answer
your questions,
and we get the T
from the final three
before we crown America's
next drag superstar,
when RuPaul's Drag Race
Reunited continues.
- [laughs]
Welcome back
to RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited.
I'm here
with best frenemies
Coco Montrese
and Alyssa Edwards.
Now, Alyssa, your father
sent a message
and it really did bring
everyone to tears, you know?
Let's take a look at that.
- Oh, gosh.
- Somebody's dad
is on the phone.
- I know it's not mine.
My dad wouldn't even know
how to use the Skype.
[chuckles]
- Hey, Alyssa, this is Dad.
- Alyssa...
- [gasps]
- I just wanted you to know...
[voice breaks]
That I'm proud of you.
And now I'm not ashamed
to tell people
that my son's gay.
- Oh, oh, my God.
[crying]
- Wow, wow.
- Ooh.
[applause]
- So, Alyssa...
what's happened with your dad
since the show aired?
- For the very first time
in my life,
I'm starting to feel
forgiveness.
It's the most powerful feeling
one could ever feel,
and we are working on developing
a relationship.
My father is a grandfather,
and everything
that he couldn't do
for me or my siblings,
he's making up for with my niece
and nephews.
- I love it. I love it.
[cheers and applause]
That's right.
You know, RuPaul's Drag Race--
still bringing families
together.
[laughter]
It's true.
Now, Alyssa,
Santino accused you
of wearing the worst dress
in five seasons.
But sometimes, the memory can
play tricks on us.
Take a look.
There's corn hanging
from her hand!
[laughter]
- It's not just an outfit,
it's a lifestyle.
[all screaming]
[laughter]
[buzzer]
- She's a little frosty.
- I see a lot of armpit.
Like, armpit!
- But it's fresh.
[laughter]
- ChaCha.
- She has to start thinking
about the way she's gonna
execute her fashions.
- Well, she executed this
fashion.
[laughter]
- Yes, honey,
this is a two-page spread.
- Ugh, it looks like a couch
from Rent-a-Center.
- Oh, Lord.
- Well, right now,
you're a mess.
Things are falling off.
No one can accuse you
of not having
a great pair of legs.
- [laughs]
- First of all.
[laughter and applause]
- No T, no shade, ladies.
Now, Santino.
- Yes?
- Do you still think Alyssa's
dress is the worst
in five seasons?
- I do.
[laughter]
And this is why, okay?
- Can we take a vote?
Can we take a vote?
- This is why.
Every season, Ru asks the queens
to make a dress
and do it
in four to six hours.
Alyssa, you brought that dress
with you.
[laughter]
You brought that dress
with you.
That dress, it doesn't look
as bad on TV
as it did in person, but--
[audience "ohs"]
But I tweeted to you,
I said,
"You know, the thing I hope
for Alyssa
"is that she can tour the world
"so that everyone can see
the worst dress
in Drag Race history."
[laughter and applause]
- You know, I'm sensing
a lot of sexual tension
between you two.
I mean, you guys,
I think y'all need to hook up,
and make this shit happen.
Y'all need to go and fuck,
you know what I'm saying?
[laughter and applause]
You two. You two.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
- That's--that's what needs
to happen.
- Yeah.
- That's exactly
what needs to happen.
- Now, our next queen
was one of the best ever
in the history of Drag Race.
Don't believe me?
Just ask her.
Take a look.
- Wow.
[cheers and applause]
My name is Detox,
and I am 27 years old.
- How many black cocks
had to die for that outfit?
- [laughs]
- My tits are bouncing
everywhere.
I have a great body,
so why not show it off?
The only thing
I haven't had done
is my knees and my nose
and my big toe.
And I'm the queen bee,
so eat it up
and crown it.
[cheers and applause]
- Detox, welcome!
Welcome, Detox.
All right, first question.
Why it gotta be gray?
- [laughs]
Um, well, it was a gray day
in Los Angeles
when I got kicked off, so--
- Oh, okay.
- Was it not?
- Yeah.
Now, Detox, coming into
this competition,
you were one fierce
and funny queen.
- I was?
- Yes, and now that
the competition's over,
girl, you still are.
How you feelin'?
- I'm feeling amazing.
It's been, like, the most
magical experience
I've ever had.
It's been a complete blast,
and the fact that I'm able
to tour the world
with some of my best girlfriends
and do something
that I love and art of drag
that I love so much
is just beyond amazing to me,
and I'm so happy and thrilled.
- I love your collaborations
with Willam and Vicky Vox.
Now, I heard that you were all
recently performing in Dubai.
- Yeah.
Li-li-li-li-li-li-li!
- Did you have to wear a burka?
- No, we wanted to wear burkas,
but then we just said
fuck it,
and we're sluts.
I mean, hello, look at Willam.
That's his aesthetic.
- Now, you were also outspoken
in your criticism
of some of the younger queens.
Do you still feel that they
treated the show as...
[old woman voice]
Rupaul's School for Girls?
- There were certain girls--
like, some of the larger names
and the people that have been
in the industry
for a long time
that would be torn apart
for doing
what they do the best,
whereas some of the judges
were treating them
as, you know, students.
Yes, you.
- Are you talking to Santino?
- I'm talking to both of 'em,
Santino and Michelle.
- Oh.
[laughs]
- I don't give--y'all know
I don't give two shits.
[laughter and cheering]
- Now, just between us girls...
- Mm-hmm.
- As a member of Rolaskatox...
- Who should be crowned
America's next drag superstar?
- Detox.
- [laughs]
[cheers and applause]
But--yeah, you're not eligible.
Oh, whatever.
- [laughs]
- Thanks for sharing, Detox.
Now, before I go any further,
I'd like to take this moment
to say something
I've actually never said
on national television before.
Can you bring the camera closer?
[laughter]
Closer.
Now, back the fuck up.
Not that close.
[sighs]
Okay, this is hard for me.
Due to the fact that her thighs
spread just like...
♪ Peanut, peanut, peanut... ♪
♪ P-p-peanut, peanut,
peanut... ♪
♪ Peanut butter... ♪
♪ P-p-p-peanut butter... ♪
♪ Peanut butter,
peanut butter ♪
♪ Gonna walk right through
that door ♪
♪ Like before
high, high heels ♪
♪ On a hardwood floor ♪
♪ They all comin' back
for more ♪
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
♪ Back, back for more ♪
♪ Hit it up and do it right
this time ♪
Whoo-hoo!
♪ Ass so fine ♪
♪ Never gonna stop
till he is mine ♪
♪ Come round,
if you're so inclined ♪
Whoo!
- ♪ RuPaul, RuPaul, RuPaul ♪
- ♪ Must be jelly ♪
♪ 'Cause jam don't shake ♪
♪ Must be jelly ♪
Don't go anywhere.
We'll be right back
with the final three, hunty.
- Coming up, we'll announce
the viewer's choice
for Miss Congeniality.
Who should be America's
next drag superstar?
Are you team Alaska,
team Jinkx, or team Roxxxy?
Let's keep things trending
as RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited
keeps on keepin' on.
- [laughs]
Welcome back
to RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited.
And now, the reason
we're all here tonight.
Please welcome back
to the stages the final three.
Alaska.
Jinkx Monsoon.
Roxxxy Andrews.
Welcome, ladies.
You look sickening.
Now, I have so much
I have to ask you,
but first, we're gonna
take some questions
from the fans.
Inquiring minds want to know.
This first one here
is for Jinkx.
The Duchess of Dork
wants to know
about your crush on Ivyyyy.
"Did you guys ever hook up
after the show?"
- Well, when you're held
in captivity
in a little pink hamster cage,
eventually, you just look
for the cutest person
in the room,
and I chose Ivy Winters.
[laughter]
- You know, Ivy,
was there a love connection?
- I was actually shocked
when I was watching
the episode with my boyfriend...
- Me too.
- And he was like, "Oh."
- I didn't know
they were gonna air that.
[laughter]
But nothing ever came of it,
and we're actually
just very good friends,
you know,
and I've met her boyfriend,
he's very charming.
- I mean, honestly, wha--
I mean, really,
what's the problem?
I mean, triads
are really in right now.
- [laughs]
- And honestly,
I could see a spin-off show
like, you know,
Drag Sister Wives
or something like that.
All right, this next question
is for Alaska.
Oscar asks, "Do you think
being part of Rolaskatox
helped or hurt you?"
- I knew Detox
from a long time ago,
and she knew Roxxxy
so we were just, like,
friends,
and we needed a prescription
drug for gagging,
so we called it Rolaskatox.
- [laughs]
- I don't think it really
hurt me,
but Michelle hated it.
And she called us "Rolodex."
I don't even know
what a Rolodex is!
[laughter and applause]
- Now, Roxxxy, what about you?
Do you think it helped
or hurt you?
- To me, it was never,
you know,
"Well, I'm gonna be
on Survivor right now,"
and be like,
"This is my alliance,
"and we're gonna stick together
and get everybody out of here."
It was never that,
so when she said
she wanted to go off
on her own,
we were like, "Girl,
we love you no matter what."
Like, "Go on and do your thing
if that's what you feel
you need to do."
- Jinkx, you were not
in Rolaskatox.
What are your thoughts?
Did you feel alienated by it?
- Well, you know, cliques
can either help or hinder you.
They can be a big distraction,
but even though they had
a clique, I had a mantra.
[laughter]
- Which was?
- Let's say it together,
ladies and gentlemen.
all: Water off a duck's back.
[laughter]
- Now, this next question
is for Roxxxy.
Gwen asks,
"Do you honestly feel
"that comedy drag
is insulting,
or was that you just playing
mind games?"
- You know, I take drag very,
very seriously,
and sometimes--
I noticed on the show--
too seriously.
And no, it's not insulting
at all whatsoever,
and you know,
they're my complete opposites,
and that's what
makes them magic,
and I can learn a lot
from them.
- All right.
Now, this next question
is from Johnny B.
This is for Alyssa.
"Have you figured out
what Alyssa's secret is yet?"
[laughter and cheers]
- Well, Johnny, if I told you,
it wouldn't be a secret.
- So is--that's a "No,
you don't know what it is"?
[laughter]
- It's 9 inches
and fully functional.
- Oh, my God!
[laughs]
[cheers and applause]
Not so secret anymore,
is it?
Now, this next question
is to all the queens.
Ian asks, "What motivated you
to do the show,
the title or the $100,000?"
Let's start here with Alaska.
- Um, what motivated me
was the fact
that I auditioned
for every single season
and never made it,
so it eventually became
a personal vendetta
to get on the program.
[laughter and cheers]
- And what about you?
- Honestly, since I was
five years old,
this is what I wanted to do.
You know--
- This show was on
when you were five years old?
- No, I used to say--
I used to watch
Death Becomes Her,
and I knew I wanted to grow up
to be Meryl Streep.
[cheers and applause]
- All right, Roxxxy,
title or moola?
- Definitely the title
and the competition.
I'm a pageant girl.
I like to compete,
and that was the platform
to show the world
that I could be
America's next drag superstar
and compete with
the best of the best,
which,
I think this season is the best
of the best.
Nothing against the other ones.
[laughter and jeering]
- Now, you know, every year,
we ask our fans to vote
for Miss Congeniality,
and this year,
the choice was tougher
than ever.
Now, to help me bestow
this honor, please welcome
last year's Miss Congeniality,
Latrice Royale.
[cheers and applause]
Hey, mommy.
- Hey!
- Looking good.
- And feeling gorgeous, baby.
- Hey.
Now, Latrice, would you please
do us the honors?
- This year's Miss Congeniality
is...
[suspenseful music]
Ivyyyyy Winters!
- Condragulations, Ivy.
You have won a six-night stay
plus airfare
for you and a guest
from Hilton Hotels and Resorts.
Now, you can stay Hilton.
Go out at one of their
550 locations in 80 countries.
- Oh, my gosh.
Oh, thank you guys so much.
Thank you so much.
I feel like I just won!
Thank you, mwah.
- All right, Ivy.
Now, sissy that walk.
Sissy that walk.
[cheers and applause]
- I love you.
- Who will be crowned
America's next drag superstar?
Are you team Alaska,
team Jinkx,
or team Roxxxy?
Keep tweeting,
and find out when
RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited
continues.
- [laughs]
Welcome back
to RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited.
Now, I'm here with
our final three: Alaska...
[cheers and applause]
Jinkx Monsoon...
And Roxxxy Andrews!
[cheers and applause]
Now, in less time
than it takes
to microwave
a chicken pot pie,
one of them will be crowned
America's next drag superstar.
Not only did these three queens
snatch our hearts, but they
tickled our funny bones.
Take a look.
Direct from Grey Gardens,
it's little Edie Beale.
- Oh, hi, RuPaul.
- How is big Edie doing?
- She's always begging
for the pate,
but the label is faded.
I can never tell if it's pate
or if it's giblets for the cats.
[laughter]
- My old, old friend,
Lady Bunny.
- You know, the last time
I had a battle of the browns
was about ten minutes ago
in my dressing room.
[laughter]
- Tamar Braxton!
- Get your life.
- Paula Deen is out of control.
This morning, she put a stick
of butter--
- On her--boom!
Louboutins,
'cause her fat-ass feet
don't fit in 'em.
[laughter]
Boom, boom, baby.
Rock, rock.
- [laughs]
Now, Alaska, were you nervous
to play a character like
Lady Bunny, who's you know,
already very funny?
- I was really nervous,
'cause she's so old.
[laughter]
- [gasping laugh]
- And I was gonna do
Michelle Obama,
but that was already taken,
so...
[laughter]
- Oh!
- Now, when Coco
and some of the other queens
hadn't heard
of Grey Gardens,
it caused quite the controversy
online.
- Quite the scandal, really.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- Now, Jinkx, were you surprised
by that?
- Uh--I was surprised by
America's reaction.
I didn't know that many people
knew about her,
but I was thrilled to see it,
you know?
- All right.
Roxxxy, now, you say you're not
a comedy queen,
but your Tamar Braxton
slayed the children
dot com, girl.
- Dot com.
- Yes.
- I wanted to do somebody
that I knew
could be funny off the bat.
Her personality
is so off-the-wall
that if you didn't know her,
you wanted to laugh at her,
so that's why
I went with Tamar.
I love you, Tamar.
- Well, they say imitation
is the sincerest form
of flattery,
but sometimes, it could really
piss people off.
Let's take a look.
The final three are so bitchy,
they don't just throw shade,
they "blank" it.
- Well, I don't know them
personally,
so I said they airmail it,
though that's frightfully
expensive.
Hi, Jinkx, it's me, Bebe Wood
from The New Normal.
You do the second-best
impression of little Edie.
- [laughs]
- I just know Ru's
going to make
the staunch decision.
- [squeals]
- Good luck,
and don't funk it up.
- [screaming laugh]
- Lady Bunny, same question.
- They throw it so hard
that it casts
more of a shadow than
Alyssa Edwards' overbite
on her nonexistent chin.
[laughter]
Alaska, I wanted to tell you
that your impersonation of me
was spot on.
And I'm gonna get you for that.
[laughter]
- All right, Tamar Braxton!
- They do that on over-the-top
shade dot com, okay?
Boom!
Get your life.
[laughter]
Where my Roxxxy at?
She is my queen dot com,
and I know she fixin' to do me
proud, okay?
Boom! Yes!
- Boom!
[laughter]
- I love it!
I love it.
Condragulations, ladies,
you're a hit.
Now, ladies, it's time to get
serious.
Assume the position, because I'm
about to do one final
examination of your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent.
I hope you showered.
First up, Alaska.
Hi-ee.
- Hi-ee.
- Hi-ee!
[laughter]
- Now, your wicked wit
and junkyard couture
have served you well
in your journey from tragic
to magic.
Let's take a look.
- Hi-ee.
Hi-ee. Hi-ee!
My name is Alaska.
- You're finally here.
- I know, yay.
- A tired, second-rate version
of your husband.
- Ohh!
[both grunt]
- Isn't Sharon the superstar
of the relationship?
- I had to choose,
am I gonna
be bitter
or become her biggest fan?
♪ Can I get a... ♪
[singing over each other]
- Whoa, stop there.
- Don't worry about your group,
whoever you're with.
Worry about you.
Something's missing, Alaska.
Bring it.
- Dangerous.
Flawless.
Overpriced.
- You're the winner
of this challenge.
- Ah!
- You are the winner
of this week's challenge.
- Ah!
I am the queen
who takes the tragic
and turns it into magic.
I take trash and turn it into
treasure,
and having never fallen
into the bottom two,
I am Alaska,
and I am America's next
drag superstar!
[echoing]
Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
- I love it.
Now, Alaska,
what has Drag Race meant to you?
- It's just, like--like, I
can't even believe
I'm sitting
in this spot right now,
and all these
fucking people are here.
Hi-ee!
all: Hi-ee!
- Now, Alaska, you're part
of a drag super couple.
Now, is that a blessing
or a curse?
- I think it's an awesome
blessing,
because I couldn't choose
a better person who is--
who could be so supportive
and who's always there for me
and always believes in me,
even when I don't believe
in myself.
And I get to wear
all of her designer clothes.
[laughter]
- So, Sharon, what's it like
watching Alaska up here?
- It's--it's embarrassing.
Um, no, I'm--I'm--it--
[laughter]
I'm--I'm kidding.
When you look
at Alaska Thunderfuck--
when I look at you right now,
you have the tangible,
marketable beauty
of Roxxxy Andrews
and the campy theatrics
of Jinkx Monsoon,
and in my heart,
you are America's
next drag superstar,
and you and me
will be the most famous people
in reality television
from Pittsburgh, next to
Abby Lee Miller, of course.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- Pam, did you know that Alaska
would grow up to be
a world-famous drag queen?
- Never in a million years
would I have ever dreamt
that he would've grown up
to be a famous drag queen.
I-I have four children,
I'm proud of all of them,
and I wanted them all
to be happy.
I have an Air Force man,
an Army man,
a medical daughter,
and now--
- And this.
- I'm well--no!
I'm so--I'm so well-rounded
with you.
I love you.
I'm so, so proud.
- Now, Alaska, what would it
mean to you
to be America's
next drag superstar?
- [stammering]
[laughter]
I mean, it would change my life.
And just being here and doing
this experience has already
changed my life, and that would
just be so amazing.
And with the money, I would buy
100,000 slices of pizza
and share it with all of you.
- Oh, yummy.
- Aww.
- I love pizza.
- Me too.
- Alaska, it's been a real joy
to watch you blossom,
and you walk
in no one's shadow.
You are a force to be reckoned
with, because Alaska
is a thunder-fucking star,
y'all!
[cheers and applause]
- Coming up, Jinkx and Roxxxy
spill the T when
RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited
continues.
- [laughs]
Welcome back
to RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited.
In a moment,
we'll be crowning
America's next drag superstar,
but first,
I've drilled Alaska.
Now, it's time for me to probe
Jinkx Monsoon.
Take a look.
- My name is Jinkx Monsoon.
I am Seattle's premier Jewish
narcoleptic drag queen.
- What's on your head?
- Just a little headpiece.
- It's rather pedestrian.
Jinkx, oh, Jinkx.
[sighs]
I love it!
- [laughs]
I left my youngest brother
with a woman
who wasn't ready to be a mom.
To say that
"You're just a comedy queen"
is belittling something
I have made my whole career on.
- Jinkx, I have--
- I am talking.
- Oh.
- I am in it to win it.
To dismiss me
would be a bad move.
You should be taking me
as a threat.
[snores]
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- Wow.
[laughs]
So, Jinkxy, how are you feeling
at this very moment?
You're not sleepy at all,
are ya?
- I-I-I could use a nap, but--
[laughter]
I feel like a more fully
realized drag queen.
realized human being.
I remember hearing you say
you've been through many phases
in your drag,
and I think I've entered
Jinkx 2.0,
the butterfly phase.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- So tell me, what has been
your proudest moment
on the show?
- Honestly, working with Dave,
my veteran.
[cheers and applause]
Right there.
- You've been very open about
some childhood issues
you had with your mother
and your brother.
How are things now?
- You know, things are
wonderful.
Drag Race kind of brought
our family back together again,
and it caused us to have
some really
adult conversations.
- Are they here?
Are they here tonight?
- He's right over there.
- Oh.
- They're both there.
- So, Deanne, what was it like
having your Jinkxy discuss
family issues on television?
- Well, it hurt, mainly because
I saw how much
I hurt my child,
but at the same time,
it was good,
because it--it made--
it helped us to become
even closer.
- All right, yeah,
let the healing begin.
[applause]
Jacob, what's it like having
a drag queen for a brother?
- [chuckles]
Well, I never
really thought of him
as a drag queen.
I've just always thought of him
as my big brother,
and I know he's worked
so hard,
and I'm so proud of him
for being here.
And don't forget,
it's Monsoon season.
- [laughs]
[cheers and applause]
So, Jinkx, what would it mean
to you
to become America's next
drag superstar?
- I would love to be given
the chance
to use this as a platform
to be an advocate
for social change.
I'm lucky enough to live in
Washington
where gay marriage
is legal, and...
[cheers and applause]
I don't want to rest until
that's the truth
for all of America.
[laughs]
- Well, Jinkx, you have
continued to surprise
and delight your fans.
Best of all, I think you've even
surprised yourself.
I'm so proud to have you
sitting here tonight.
Now, our next queen is a blast
from drag's proud pageant
past
and an important part
of its future.
Roxxxy Andrews.
Let's take a look.
- My name is Roxxxy Andrews.
- Condragulations.
- Oh!
- You are the winner
of this challenge.
- ♪ Put on
a shiny sequence gown ♪
[record scratch]
- Are you saying "sequin" or--
- Sequence dress.
- "Sequin dress" I think
is what you mean.
- Sequence.
- What do you call it
when you flat-line?
- You're dead.
- I come off as a strong
character,
but I'm so weak
at the same time!
[sobs]
- Bam!
- Oh.
- Condragulations,
you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
- You look stunning.
- Thank you so much.
I think it's time to crown
a thick and juicy kind of girl.
- You're an amazing queen.
[laughs]
[cheers and applause]
Roxxxy, Roxxxy, Roxxxy,
how are you feeling
at this very moment?
- Oh, my God,
words cannot express
how happy I am to be here
and to experience this,
and y'all showing me
so much love.
I love it.
- Well, I know that getting
ready for the finale, you were
very emotional.
Tell me about that.
- Um, some of the things
on the show that--
how I was acting,
and I was acting that way,
it got the best of me at points,
and, you know,
I said a lot of hurtful things
to Jinkx,
and the most important thing
to me is our relationship,
and she is an amazing person
and she's extremely talented
and just as good as a competitor
as I am, if not better.
[applause]
- More than ever before,
a lot of people
have attacked you online about
how you were on the show.
How has that affected you?
- It's affected me a lot.
You know, you want to say
you don't listen to it
and you don't pay attention
to it, but when you're, like,
going on social media networks,
you do run into those things,
and it hurts my feelings,
and you know, I just
have to pick myself back up.
Like--you know what I'm saying?
Like, you can't let it
get you down, just, you know,
that there's people out there
who do love you
and do understand where
you are coming from
and have been
in that same place.
We're all human.
We all make mistakes.
That was completely messy,
and I can't believe
I went there,
but I shouldn't have done that.
- Is there anything you'd like
to say to Jinkx right now?
- I love you to death,
and regardless of the things--
I wrote her, and I've written
you and I've told you that,
you know, I love you.
- And called me personally.
- And regardless if I win, lose,
or draw this contest,
she's somebody that I want
in my life
for the rest of my life,
and I have learned so much
from her and Alaska.
- Now, Jinkx, is there anything
you'd like to say to Roxxxy?
- I think people forget
sometimes that even though
sisters love each other,
sisters can also get
into some pretty bad fights,
you know?
But through all of it,
we're sisters.
- I think you two hookers
should hug it out.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- [laughs]
- Okay.
[laughs]
- And if I may, I think
you're both awful.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- Sadly, your legendary
drag mother Erica Andrews
recently passed away.
Did she get to see the show?
- She was at the hospital,
and she was texting me,
and she was telling me,
um, how proud she was of me
and, you know, she got to see
at least two episodes,
and then she ended up passing.
She was a wonderful person,
and if you ever got to meet her,
you knew exactly...
How beautiful she was, and...
[sniffs]
The hardest thing was during
rehearsal yesterday.
I had a little breakdown.
Those were the times
I would call her
and she would know exactly
what to tell me,
and I didn't have her to call
yesterday,
but my heart always tells me
what she would say,
and I knew inside,
she was just,
"Pick yourself up,
show them how beautiful
"you can be inside and out,
and...
walk with your head
held high."
- That's right. I love it.
I got to tell you,
you are my child now.
We, as gay people,
like I said before,
we get to choose the families.
We create families on our own
on this journey,
and all of my girls--you--
all of the girls
on this stage and the girls
in the audience,
we are one big, happy family,
and we will all be
there for one another.
Promises? Okay.
[cheers and applause]
- We are seconds away
from finding out
which one of these
fabulous queens
will be crowned
America's next drag superstar.
- Can't get enough of my girls?
Then have I got
a mobile game for you:
Rupaul's Drag Race Dragopolis.
Oh, my goodness!
Work it out, boss lady.
Work it.
Serving glamour!
Available now on iTunes.
[laughs]
[cheers and applause]
Welcome back to RuPaul's
Drag Race Reunited.
Alaska, Jinkx, Roxxxy,
one of you
is just moments away
from being crowned
America's next drag superstar.
Now, if, for any reason,
our queen is unable
to perform her duties,
Coco Montrese
has graciously volunteered
to finish out your reign.
[cheers and applause]
Too much?
Is it--was it too soon
for that joke?
- No!
- Now, I want to give
a shout-out
to my two best squirrel friends,
Santino Rice
and Michelle Visage.
[cheers and applause]
Can you smell me?
- Yes.
- Any last words?
- Your sequence brocog gown
is real "eloguent."
- [laughs]
- Yes.
- Are you ready?
both: Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- [laughing]
Thank you, thank you.
Now, ladies, whoever snatches
the crown tonight
will be standing
on the shoulders
of five legendary champions.
Please welcome the Drag Race
royal family:
previous winners
Bebe Zahara Benet...
[cheers and applause]
Tyra Sanchez...
Raja...
[cheers and applause]
Chad Michaels...
And Sharon Needles.
[cheers and applause]
In addition to the title
of America's next drag
superstar,
tonight's winner will walk away
with a sickening supply
of Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip, courtesy of
ALandCHUCK.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring Absolut vodka--
cocktails perfected--
and a cash prize of $100,000.
[cheers and applause]
The time has come
to crown our queen.
[dramatic music]
As always, I have consulted
with the judges and the fans,
but the final decision
is mine to make.
Alaska.
Jinkx Monsoon.
Roxxxy Andrews.
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race,
America's next drag superstar
is...
Jinkx Monsoon.
[cheers and applause]
Condragulations.
Now prance, my queen.
Do you have anything
you'd like to say?
- Get ready, bitches,
'cause it's Monsoon season.
- [laughs]
[cheers and applause]
I love it.
Great, everybody.
Thank you so much.
If you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" in here?
all: Amen!
- All right.