- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
you get to enlist these men
into your drag house.
- Oh, shit.
I've never done anyone else's
makeup.
- You are going to be with
Roxxxy Andrews.
- I think it was sabotage.
It pissed me off.
[drum line playing]
♪ ♪
- You made a gown for yourself,
and you gave your sister
the scraps that were kind of
left over.
- It seems like every week
I'm letting you down,
letting you down,
letting you down.
- Roxxxy Andrews, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
[cheers and applause]
Detox, shantay, you stay.
- [crying] Thank you.
- Coco Montrese, sashay away.
- Thank you.
- Top four, bitches!
- Final four!
[all cheering]
- We're back in the werk room.
And after four lip syncs,
Coco is finally gone.
all: "I love you all.
Give them hell, girls."
- I plan on it.
- We love you, coquito.
- I think that her purpose here
was to get that whole Alyssa
and her thing accomplished and,
like, out of the way.
And I think that after she got
that, she was kind of just like,
"That's what I needed."
Coco Montrese was here because
she needed closure with Alyssa.
And you know what?
I'm here to be America's next
drag superstar.
- How about you, Miss Winner?
- Congratulations.
- I won a challenge, yay!
Day one, we walked in here as
Rolaskatox.
And, girl, here we stand with
little Jinkx.
No offense, Jinkx.
- Jinkx--it's like "Rolaskatox!
And Jinkx."
- Rolaskatox and Jinkx.
This is my worst nightmare
come true.
If one of them is given
the opportunity
to sell someone down the river,
they're gonna choose me.
- I have to go plot against
you guys.
- I need to go burn
Jinkx's costumes
from the '40s and
the '50s and the '30s.
- If we're doing a sewing
challenge, Jinkx is gonna be
left out with the tumbleweeds,
bitch.
She needs to go home.
[engine starts]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race receives
a sickening supply of
Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip courtesy of
ALandCHUCK.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And tonight extra special
guest judges
Bob Mackie
and Marg Helgenberger.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win,
best woman win ♪
[tires squeal]
[upbeat music]
- Whoo-hoo!
- Oh!
- It's so empty.
- It's the top four.
We're a millimeter away from
being the top three.
And if I have to inch my way to
the top three, I'll do that.
And I deserve it.
It's so crazy
that it's almost over.
- It's just us.
- It's just getting down
to the nitty-gritty, honey.
- You two are gonna have
a lip sync this week.
I've had it with you guys
not lip-syncing at all.
- How are you supposed to be
America's next drag superstar
if they've never even seen you
perform?
- I would prefer to go to
the top without ever doing it,
like, Tyra Sanchez style.
[alarm blares]
- Ooh, girl!
- Saved by the bell.
- You've got shemail.
Hey, kit kats.
Don't snicker.
Sometimes you feel like a nut.
And sometimes you feel like
a $100,000 bar-none.
Use your whatchamacallit.
Kisses.
[giggles]
Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi.
- You know, every now and then,
a drag queen needs to get things
off her chesticles.
So for today's mini challenge,
we're gonna have a good
old-fashioned bitch-fest.
And we're gonna do it with
puppets.
- Oh!
- [laughs]
- Why?
all: Everybody loves puppets!
- First, pick a puppet
that represents one of your
competitors.
Second, drag it up.
Third, you and the puppet have
a bitch-fest.
- [giggles]
- Detox, you're up first.
I want you to reach deep inside,
and I don't mean the pit crew's
Andrew Christian underwear.
- Oh, man.
Ooh, it's so squishy.
Alaska!
- Next up, Alaska.
- Isn't this a little high?
- Oh, my goodness.
It's like A Fist called Wanda.
- [laughs]
- [gasps]
Roxxxy!
- Jinkx Monsoon.
- Feed that hole, girl.
Who'd you get?
- Aw, DD.
- Next up, Roxxxy.
The suspense is killing me.
- I got Chucky.
[laughter]
It'll be so easy.
- All right, ladies.
On your mark, get set, go!
[dubstep music]
- I find the rattiest, dirtiest
blonde wig I can find,
then spray-adhesiving it
and rubbing it together,
making it matty and gross.
- I hate you, Detox.
- [chuckles]
- This is my opportunity to
make fun of Jinkx Monsoon.
I am painting the Nike check
cheek in black,
'cause that's
how she likes to contour.
♪ ♪
- All right, ladies.
Time's up.
Let the bitch-fest begin.
- Detox, it's time to come out.
[as Detox] I've had it.
[normal voice] Detox, come out.
[as Detox] Fuck.
[laughter]
[as Detox] You ever been blown
by a girl with silicon lips?
I call it a slip 'n slide.
I mean, I just want to put my
mouth on it and go like this:
[babbling]
Meh!
[laughter]
- I don't know where she picked
up that slip 'n slide joke.
I've never said that.
I always call my mouth "my Black
&amp; Decker pecker wreckers."
- [as Detox] I've had it.
I've had it. I've had it.
- [laughs]
- [as Alaska]
Detox, I'm so upset.
[normal voice] Why, Alaska?
You look so gorgeous.
[as Alaska] But I don't have
any nice shoes!
Sharon got all the money, and I
can't get anything for myself.
Aah!
[normal voice] My whole idea was
to make her really whiny,
'cause Alaska has this kind of
whiny voice.
[as Alaska] Wah!
[normal voice] Okay, you need to
pull it together,
you bowlegged
fucking son of a bitch.
I've had it with you.
[laughter]
- Jinkx, girl, it's time for
the runway.
[as Jinkx] [snoring]
Jinkx?
Jinkx.
[as Jinkx] [snoring]
Huh? Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
Do I look okay?
Can you guys help me with
my makeup?
Michelle told me that my cheeks
were too much.
Is this too much?
Is the blend okay?
[regular voice] So, Jinkx,
you think you're America's next
drag superstar.
[as Jinkx] You know, I try to
seem so innocent all the time,
but I'm really a bitch.
And I'm here to win,
and you guys have no idea.
[normal voice] Okay, Jinkx,
I've had enough.
You can go home.
[as Jinkx] Anyone know which way
Seattle is?
This way.
- That was rude.
- That wasn't rude.
- The shade of it all.
- Roxxxy, you look amazing.
Where'd you get your outfit?
[as Roxxxy] Same place I always
get my outfit, girl.
I made it ten minutes before I
got on the runway.
Hey!
Where my people at?
[normal voice] Oh, my god--
Roxxxy, I don't think that wig
is really working with this
outfit.
[as Roxxxy] That's okay, y'all.
I got another wig underneath!
[laughter]
[normal voice] I'm clocking
that tear-away.
[as Roxxxy]
Girl, I got a tear-away
underneath my tear-away!
- [laughs]
- A swimsuit!
Hey!
Where my people at?
- Yeah, bitch, you better keep
repeating that,
'cause America's gonna know.
When they buy that song
on itunes, Can I Get a Amen?,
they're gonna say,
"Where my people at?"
- Wow, you girls didn't pull
any punches.
But one of you really made your
fellow queen eat it.
The winner is...
Alaska.
- [as Roxxxy] Hey!
Hey!
Where my people at?
- Ladies, I hope you left room
for dessert,
because for this week's
main challenge,
we're throwing the first ever...
[echoes] Sugar Ball.
You'll each need to whip up
three luscious looks.
First category is...
Super Duper Sweet 16,
teenage party girl.
Second category is Sugar Mama,
executive realness.
Third category is the tastiest
of them all,
Candy Couture.
- Ooh!
- Edible eleganza.
You'll be making high-calorie
fashion
using these sticky and
sweet confections
provided by Candy Warehouse.
Alaska, you won
the mini challenge,
so you get
a 15-second head start.
Go.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- Ooh!
- This challenge is about
sewing and creating.
Aah, my balls!
These bitches don't know how
to sew.
This is my element of drag.
- Does everyone know
what kind of direction
they're gonna go in?
- I know exactly the direction
I'm going in.
- Do you?
- Yes.
I'm going Alexander McQueen
does Christmas.
[chuckles]
- Girl, she's going for
a winter wonderland look, bitch.
- It looks crazy.
Just 'cause you throw some
antlers on your goddamn head
and you call it
an Alexander McQueen look?
Good luck, Jinkx.
- Coming up...
- I've fucking had it.
- Girl, could you please stop
banging?
- Are you passionate about
becoming America's next drag
superstar?
- [laughing]
[techno music]
- This week's main challenge
is the first ever Sugar Ball,
where we have to create three
different looks--
a Sweet 16 party girl look,
a Sugar Mama executive realness
look,
and a Candy Couture
fashion look.
- I'm gonna eat
my entire costume.
- Alaska, do I remind you
of someone?
- Detox!
- They're not that big of
a stretch, really.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hi.
all: Hello.
- How are things going here
on the good ship Lollipop?
- Delish.
- Alaska.
- Hi.
- I came over to borrow a pair
of edible panties.
May I eat this pair?
- You can eat those shorts
all day.
- Oh, wait.
These aren't edible.
[sniffs]
Ew!
- Ew!
- [laughs]
Now I want to hear all about
your Candy Couture look.
- I like, like,
fluffy cotton candy.
- How are you putting the candy
on there?
It's just glued, right?
- Yeah, it's hot glue.
- Huh, interesting.
But you've been criticized
for being a little rough
around the edges.
You know, the stakes
are very high.
And you've really got to wow us
to get into that top three.
All right.
Can't wait to see it.
Hi, Jinkx.
You're not known for being
a seamstress.
- No.
- What are you doing?
- Well, I want to do, like,
Christmas in July candy cane
reindeer monster kind of thing.
- Wait now.
Say that again slower for me,
because I'm trying to get that
all up in there.
- Christmas in July candy cane
reindeer monster.
- Do you think it's too much,
though?
This your Candy Couture look.
- Yes.
- But where's the candy?
- Well, I'm going to look like
a candy cane overall.
- It's a candy challenge.
Where the candy at?
- And I'm very excited to give
the Sweet 16 a shot.
- Now, you know we're not
talking 1916, right?
- [laughs] Yeah.
Is it okay if I'm sweet 16
but in the '70s?
- Well, the judges have
challenged you
to be a little more, you know,
modern, contemporary.
Good luck.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Hey, Detox.
- Hi, Ru.
- So how are you gonna bring it
for your Candy Couture?
What do you have planned?
- I'm so in love
with acid green,
and I really want to do some
reptilian-looking...
- Uh-huh.
- Funk.
I don't know what I'm thinking
of yet, but I see it in my head.
- Detox's concept right now
is more based on a color.
I'm not seeing the candy
inspiration in it.
- I'm just trying to play it
all by ear.
- Well, now, looking
around the room,
it looks like you're
a little bit behind.
Now, last week, you were
in the bottom two.
- I know.
- There's a certain expectation
that, um, really just hasn't
been met.
I don't know what to say
about that.
- Right. I don't--
I don't either, honestly.
- Are you passionate about
becoming America's next drag
superstar?
- It's kind of like a slap
in the face.
Of course I want to be America's
next drag superstar.
That's what I want.
It's something
that I've always wanted.
- All right, get to work.
See you in a minute.
Roxxxy Andrews.
- Hey, Ru.
- Now, top four,
every moment counts.
- It's $100,000 at stake here.
- $100,000 at stake.
- And that's no game.
It's gonna be a fight
till the end, baby.
- So tell me about your
Candy Couture outfit.
- My Candy Couture,
I'm going very extravagant,
very extravaganza.
- Now, how's your body-ody-ody
gonna play into this outfit?
- Well, it's a corset,
so I kind of brought it up
over here
so that you could still get
a shape on that side,
a good silhouette.
- Uh-huh.
Well, just, you know, make sure
it flatters your figure
and that, you know, you can
serve true Roxxxy Andrews.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know?
- Yeah.
Ru's looking at me funny,
and I'm not sure that he likes
what I'm doing.
- Yeah, yeah. Wow.
- Now what am I gonna do?
- You better bring some hard
Roxxxy candy on the runway.
Get back to work.
- Thank you, Ru.
- All right.
All right, gather around,
my little gumdrops.
Now, tomorrow at the Sugar Ball,
we'll be joined my our
extra special guest judges,
CSI star Marg Helgenberger...
- I love her!
- Whoo!
- And fashion's most delicious
designer.
Bob Mackie will be here.
[all gasp]
- What?
- Shut up!
- Ahh!
- Bob Mackie has done
Diana Ross, Liza Minnelli, Cher,
everybody.
He's a master at what he does.
- No pressure.
- Right.
- And there's just one more
thing.
In addition to creating your
three sickeningly sweet looks,
you need perform a Sugar Babies
opening number.
Now, Alaska, as the winner
of the mini challenge,
you're in charge
of the choreography.
- Oh!
[laughs]
- Oh, god.
- Get your bowleg on.
all: Get your bowleg on.
Get your bowleg on.
- Alaska's got
about this much rhythm.
So this is gonna be
a hot fucking shitty mess.
- I expect to see sugar and
spice and everything nice,
so don't fuck it up.
See you later.
[indistinct chatter]
- After Ru's walk-through,
I look over, and Roxxxy's look
is completely gone.
- Ru said something
about my silhouette, so--
at this point in the game,
if she's saying something,
it's for a reason.
- Right.
- I'm starting
back at square one.
I'm going with this licorice.
It looks like spaghetti.
This licorice is so thin.
But I'm putting on there
one at a time.
It's so tedious.
So this much time,
this much work.
- [whistling]
[pounding]
- Jinkx, really?
I'm stressed right now.
I have a lot to get done.
Like, girl, could you please
stop banging?
- Jinkx and the hammer is
driving me berserk.
And I've fucking had it.
[pounding]
- Huh!
- Merry Christmas.
- Coming up...
- ♪ Our lips are glazed ♪
♪ Our eyes are candy-crazed ♪
- You're wrong, Jinkx.
Girl, it's left to right.
- 'Cause I don't want
to hit you
when you walk past me.
- If you hit me, I'm gonna
hit you right in the face.
- Aw, fuck.
It isn't going on.
What the fuck was that?
Aah!
I broke my entire outfit.
- [laughing]
[techno music]
- Today we have to come up with
a lip-sync performance
to a song called Sugar Babies.
All right.
- This musical number
is right up my alley.
This is me in my element.
- I'm no Alyssa Edwards when
it comes to choreography.
- You're not a choreographer
to the stars?
- I'm not.
We'll enter in that order--
you, her, her, me.
- You want us to enter and
go where?
And how do you want us to enter?
We all know Alaska is not
the best dancer,
so we don't know
what's gonna happen.
- ♪ We are, we are ♪
♪ That's right ♪
♪ The sugar babies ♪
- We gotta do something else
here.
- [coughs]
- 'Cause this is totally cute
for the first part.
- Yeah.
- But then what are we gonna do?
Should we do, like, a little
up, down thing too?
Like, Alaska and I--
[laughs] yeah.
- It's confusing to me, though.
- ♪ We are, we are ♪
♪ So simple ♪
Alaska's lucky, 'cause if it was
some kind of pop, pop, booty,
kind of pop, pop, pop, pop, pop,
it'd be a hot mess.
- That's too complicated.
[laughs]
- It would be funny
if we did something
where we're licking the suckers
and then we're having, like,
a sugar high.
- Why don't we do
the circle thing?
They always do a circle thing.
- Jinkx is acting
a little too wild,
and I know Roxxxy and I are
getting annoyed.
We don't have time for any
of that bullshit.
Which way are you gonna start,
Rox?
- I'll start right to left.
- Okay.
- Left, right.
- Should we all be going
the same way?
- No, opposites.
- I can't see anybody,
so follow me.
- Well, you would have to--
yeah, we'll all follow you.
- ♪ Sugarcoated cones ♪
♪ Our lips are glazed ♪
♪ Our eyes are candy-crazed ♪
- Whoa.
- You're wrong Jinkx,
on the lollipop.
Girl, it's left to right.
It's not science.
- ♪ Our lips are glazed ♪
- We're so off.
- We're all relying
on each other
to figure out where we're
moving our candy canes.
And Jinkx is going super fast.
It seems like she's trying to be
a scene stealer,
and that's throwing the rest
of the group off.
- The reason I keep
getting off, Roxxxy--
you pass by me so close
that I don't want to hit you
when I'm doing this.
- 'cause it seems like
you switch.
- Oh, I thought she was fine.
- But you were still off.
- 'Cause I don't want
to hit you
when you walk past me.
- If you hit me, I'm gonna
hit you right in the face.
Just sayin'.
- Roxxxy's grasping at straws
to try to shake me.
I think it's because I've never
had to lip-sync for my life.
And so any chance she gets,
she's coming for me.
- ♪ We're sweet as pie ♪
♪ The kind you wanna try ♪
♪ With jelly-friendly
sugarcoated cones ♪
- So, um, are you not
lip-syncing on purpose?
- I don't know it yet.
I don't even know
what I'm saying.
- I'm just checking.
We're all sort of at least
faking our way through
the lip sync, but, like,
Roxxxy's just, like, not moving
her mouth at all.
It's like, "Oh, okay."
- Do you want me and Detox
to end
with both of our hands up?
Or the right on the right hand,
left on the left hand,
and you in the middle?
- Yeah, that.
- Am I in the middle or
the side?
Where do you want me?
If it totally tanks,
I don't think
that it's anybody else's
responsibility
except for Alaska's.
- Whew!
- We're back in from rehearsal.
We all have a lot to do.
We have three looks to plan
for tomorrow.
And the tensions are high,
so let's get to fucking work.
- So, girls,
it's awfully quiet.
- Yeah, girl, we got work
to do.
- [yawns]
[snores lightly]
There is still so much to do.
And the narcolepsy kicks in,
and it's a struggle just to keep
my eyelids open.
I can't even see what I'm
looking at anymore.
[can rattling]
Oh, fuck.
I'm starting to get so tired.
Like, I'm half asleep,
trying to make a dress.
When I shake myself out of it,
I look at my dress,
and I'm like,
"What the fuck happened?"
This isn't what I wanted it
to look like.
I'm panicking, yeah.
- I've never seen Jinkx
so freaked out,
on the verge of tears.
A little part of me is so happy,
because the judges are finally
gonna see
that she's a whole hot
shitty trailer Christmas mess.
About time.
- Ugh!
- [fake crying]
- It's elimination day,
and we have a lot of work to do
for this Sugar Ball.
At the end of today, there will
only be three of us.
It's scary.
- Is it hideous,
or is it not hideous?
- I mean, it's a lot of stuff
going on.
- I mean, a big part of me
just wants to ditch
the big hoop skirt thing,
but then I only have candy
on my corset.
- Right.
- I'm going back and forth.
It's like cut this and lose
most of the candy
and most of the work I did
or keep this
and risking looking like
a complete joke on the runway.
I feel like an idiot.
- How much work does everyone
have left to do?
- I still have to, like, finish
this jewelry up
and then put a strap
on this dress.
And then I'm gonna start working
on hair.
Did you change anything?
- I just added some more candy,
And I need to finish adding
candy.
I'm liking it a lot much better
now I added these little
carnation things to it.
I'm gonna do a couple more.
- I love it.
- Detox's Candy Couture outfit
doesn't look candy-inspired
in the slightest.
Herein lies the problem
of having a best friend
in this competition.
Roxxxy's so close to Detox,
she can't bring herself to say,
"Detox, that dress doesn't read
as candy."
- Aw, fuck. Goddamn.
What is wrong with this?
I don't know why
it isn't going on.
It's fucking pissing me off.
We're completely running out
of time.
This was supposed to just go on
and look good,
and that's not happening.
[object clatters]
What the fuck was that?
Aah!
- What just happened?
- The candy is falling off.
Chunks of the cotton candy
clouds are just shattering.
- Fuck cok-sucking hell shit.
I broke my entire outfit, so--
- What?
- I don't know how this thing's
going to get down the runway.
I'm completely panicking
right now.
Ow.
- Alaska and Jinkx,
they're both the weakest
in the competition.
- Jesus Christ.
- It's time for them to
lip-sync for their life.
- Coming up...
- It makes me question
your taste level.
- She was a really
promiscuous-looking 16-year-old.
- You know, they want to look
like a whore.
- [laughing]
[laughing]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl ]
♪ ♪
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, hey, sugar.
- You are giving me Jersey
couture tonight, honey.
- [laughs]
- Santino Rice, you want
some candy, little boy?
- Oh, yes, please.
- Marg Helgenberger,
you look scrumptious.
- Thank you, Ru.
You look fabulous
in that animal print.
- So happy to have you here.
And he's back!
The very first judge of
the very first episode
of Drag Race,
my idol, Bob Mackie.
- You're looking gorgeous.
- You know what I always say:
Cher was born naked,
and the rest was Bob Mackie.
[laughter]
This week, our queens were like
kids in a candy store,
creating three different
sartorial confections.
Are you ready to get
this Sugar Ball rolling?
- Hell yes!
- Yes, ma'am.
- Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
[whimsical music]
- ♪ We're sweet as pie ♪
♪ The kind you wanna try ♪
♪ With jelly-friendly
sugarcoated cones ♪
♪ Our lips are glazed ♪
♪ Our eyes are candy-crazed ♪
♪ And chocolate powder's best
for undertones ♪
♪ Although we aim
to please ♪
♪ Confection's such a tease ♪
♪ Diabetes sure
can kill the mood ♪
♪ We're just here
to celebrate ♪
♪ So have your cake
and eat it too, dude ♪
- ♪ We are, we are ♪
- ♪ That's right ♪
- ♪ The sugar babies ♪
♪ We are, we are ♪
- ♪ Uh-huh ♪
- ♪ The sugar, sugar,
sugar babies ♪
♪ We are, we are ♪
- ♪ Amen ♪
- ♪ The sugar babies ♪
♪ We are, we are ♪
- ♪ The sugar, sugar, sugar,
sugar, sugar, sugar, sugar ♪
♪ Sugar, sugar, sugar, sugar,
sugar, sugar ♪
♪ Babies ♪
♪ Sugar! ♪
Yeah!
[laughter, applause]
- Let the Sugar Ball begin.
Category is Super Super
Sweet 16.
Oh, my god.
First up, Alaska.
Hi!
- Dad got me this nose for
my birthday.
- Yes.
[laughter]
- It's her 16th birthday, and
her dad paid for everything,
but her stupid friends
won't text her back.
- Young lady, you better not be
sexting.
- Mom, you've ruined
everything!
- Next up, Jinkx Monsoon.
Oh, hippy girl.
Almost Famous.
- This is Pacific Northwest
stoner chick extravaganza look.
- Jinkx, I read your diary,
and we need to have a talk.
- My name's not Jinkx anymore.
It's Dreamcatcher.
[laughter]
- Up next, Roxxxy Andrews.
- Usher is performing
at my sweet 16.
- Oh!
- She got a marshmallow ring?
- Yeah!
- Where my peeps at?
- I'm loving every minute.
The judges are smiling.
I'm giving them 16-year-old
realness.
- She's 16 going on sickening.
[laughter]
Up next, Detox.
- She's a Pink Lady.
- Pink Ladies rule the school.
- Yeah.
- My sweet 16 look is
'80s-inspired.
I'm working this lollipop,
sexy sweet 16.
- Rizzo's P.G.
- Pass it on.
- [laughs]
- Category is Sugar Mama,
executive realness.
Alaska.
- Cougar lady.
- Yes.
She's serving Barbara Corcoran.
[laughter]
- This woman takes her job
very seriously.
She's coming to visit
the construction site,
and, by god, there better not be
any bullshit.
- Tear down that bitch of
a bearing wall.
[laughter]
Jinkx Monsoon.
Darling, it's Lacroix, darling.
It's Lacroix.
[laughter]
- I am just camping it
down the runway
with every utensil I could find
stuck in my little French twist.
- She does give good
headmistress.
Roxxxy Andrews.
- Pork bellies?
Sell! Buy! No!
- Tina Knowles, I'm not buying
your line.
- Yes.
[laughter]
- I'm in my little short velvet
dress with my gummy bears,
and I am feeling sickening.
C-E-oh-no-she-didn't.
- Up next, Detox.
Serving Mugler.
- Oh, yeah.
- No lady is ever sure
at night.
- That's right.
- I've Angel perfume and
my Thierry Mugler bag.
Take that and suck on it.
- Love that blazer.
It's a real power top.
- [cackles]
Kind of like me!
- [laughs]
Category is Candy Couture,
edible eleganza.
First up, Alaska.
I think the material is
a cotton candy blend.
- I was having
some serious issues
with this cotton candy
fantasy.
So I'm feeling beautiful and
right,
but please, candy couture,
don't fall apart.
- Fluff the magic drag queen.
- Mmm.
- Jinkx Monsoon.
It's a hard candy Christmas.
- And her breath
is minty fresh.
I decided not to wear
that damn hoop skirt,
and I couldn't be more pleased
with the way it turned out.
I am the Abominable Snow Jinkx.
- Peppermint patty realness.
- This is a stag party.
[laughter]
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Ooh.
- Wow, taste the rainbow.
- Bitches.
- Those judges cannot take this
coutureness.
Miss Thing, I know
my body looks right.
This licorice is exactly where
I need to be laying.
- Melts in your mouth.
- I wonder if her panties are
edible too.
- They are.
- Detox.
Very Splenda in the grass.
- My candy couture look,
it's Detox.
It's electric.
It still has a little touch
of the '80s.
- Lollipopulence.
- Yes.
- Is that some black licorice
I see?
- Uh-huh.
Licorice and lace.
Coming up...
Which one of you sweethearts
does not deserve to be
in the top three?
[dramatic music]
- [laughing]
Welcome, ladies.
Thanks to your candy couture,
I've got a cavity.
And it's throbbing.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Alaska.
- Hi.
- Alaska, so Sugar Babies was
really cute.
I thought that it was
a little simple.
But your sweet 16, perfection.
- I see these girls all over
my part of Los Angeles. [laughs]
And I love how you committed
to the character.
- The cougar lady,
perfect in every way.
And the cotton candy is, to me,
the best representation of
candy.
I knew exactly what you were
when you walked out.
That's important.
- All right, next up
Jinkx Monsoon.
- The Sugar Babies number,
you really stood out,
'cause I did like your
googly-eye bit.
- Your sweet 16 party girl,
16 going on 47.
Like, she didn't feel young
at all.
- When I walked
into the werk room,
you had a big hoop skirt
that you had doctored and--
- Oh, yes.
I think it was a good choice
not to try to do too much
in one look.
- Jinkx, you break my heart.
I really want to see candy
glued to every piece of fabric
that you have on.
A hoop skirt
would have allowed you
to glue more candy onto
your outfit.
- Up next, Roxxxy Andrews.
- Your sweet 16 party girl,
I love that you did the edible
marshmallow jewelry,
although she was a really
promiscuous-looking 16-year-old.
- The executive look, I love.
You just looked like a bitch
on wheels.
I loved it.
- You reminded me of
The Devil Wears Prada.
And I love the candy couture
outfit.
You should make it for yourself
out of real fabric,
because you look great in it.
It's so flattering.
- Up next, Detox.
- I liked your sweet 16
'80s look--
your attitude, the jacket.
And the sugar mama executive
reminded me of, like,
Glenn Close in Fatal Attraction.
- Your candy couture, though...
girl, it's a stretch.
- It's unfortunate that there's
a disconnect
between buying something
off the rack
versus designing something for
yourself.
And it makes me question
your taste level.
- All right.
Thank you, Detox.
Ladies, I hate to end
on a sour patch,
but I have one
final question.
Which one of you sweethearts
does not deserve to be
in the top three and why?
Starting with Jinkx.
- The one who has fallen short
most often up here is Detox.
- Alaska, same question.
- I would say Jinkx Monsoon.
I absolutely love her, but
I feel like there's maturing
that I would like to see.
- Roxxxy Andrews?
- Jinkx Monsoon.
The challenges that she needed
to step outside of her box
and design and be creative,
she didn't do well.
I had to be funny where I had
to be funny.
And it when it landed me
in the bottom,
it landed me in the bottom.
- Detox?
- I do agree
with the other girls.
It's not really a school
for girls.
It's a competition for the best
of the best.
- All right.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Now, while you untuck in the
Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
[engine starts]
All right.
Just between us "goils,"
what do you think?
Let's start with Alaska.
- Alaska really brought three
fully realized looks.
I liked her sweet 16 number.
- The only thing is, I would've
maybe have liked to have seen,
like, a light color dress.
Like, why black?
- It's the days of wearing
a lot of fluffy pink
doesn't exist anymore.
You know, they want to look like
a whore.
[laughter]
- What's wrong with that, Bob?
- The executive sugar mama,
she committed to who she was
bossing around.
I loved it.
- It could go really bad
for a man in drag
wearing a blazer
and a pair of slacks.
But the way she cut it in
at the waist,
the way she padded herself,
I bought it.
- I thought the candy costume
was the only one that really
said candy when she walked out.
And I think she knows how to use
those legs.
- She's bowlegged.
[laughter]
- Yeah, she is,
but, boy, from the crotch down,
she's a star.
[laughter]
- Detox.
- Her sweet 16 just left me,
like, "Ugh. Really?
I feel like you can do better
than that."
I'm not getting what I want
from her.
- The executive look,
what I liked most
about it was the crazy-ass hair
juxtaposed with that, like,
very sleek suit.
- She was very prepared with
the fashion that she brought.
But then when she is asked to do
something from scratch, like,
the taste level, like,
disappears.
- If they're gonna design
their own dress,
they have to know
how to work that dress.
She didn't work it at all.
She never did anything
except just stumble over it
and trip all over it.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Roxxxy was the only one
who brought candy
to each and every one
of her looks.
- The sugar mama executive,
I loved her attitude.
There was something--I kind of
liked that it was a short dress,
and she's kind of got, you know,
muscular thighs.
- Her candy couture was my
favorite of the night.
- But we didn't know
that was candy.
- But she worked it.
- When I was backstage
with her,
she had something completely
different,
something that looked like
a candy-coated Dorito.
- [laughs]
That sounds good.
- Yeah, it sounds delicious.
But I questioned it, and she
changed it, you know?
And that's the sign of someone
who is paying attention.
All right,
moving on to Jinkx Monsoon.
- I think she's a terrific
performer.
But as far as the candy couture
outfit goes,
it just didn't really work.
- If you can't tell that your
'70s-inspired look
isn't really doing
the sweet 16 thing,
I don't know when you're gonna
know that.
- She looked like Bette Davis
in Hush...Hush, Sweet Charlotte.
- [laughs]
- I mean, truly.
That long wig
and that weird lacy, ugly dress.
- Jinkx kind of failed
at every single one
of the things tonight,
although I did feel, really,
that she was getting thrown
under the bus by Rolodex here.
- Rolaskatox.
- Yeah. They're Rolodex.
I think they were like, "Oh,
let's get to the top three
together."
It was like season one
of Survivor.
- [laughs]
- Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
[laughing]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Alaska, your candy couture gave
the judges a real sugar rush.
You are the winner
of this week's challenge.
- Ahh!
[applause]
- You've won a private portrait
session
with celebrity photographer
Austin Young.
- I'm in the top three.
I am so happy.
- Roxxxy Andrews, I'm gonna
keep this short...
and sweet.
You're safe.
Condragulations.
You've made it
to the final three.
You may step to the back of
the stage.
Detox, Jinkx Monsoon,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you are up for elimination.
- It's more than I can even
process right now.
My body, it's all numb.
- I'm pissed off that I'm here.
It's devastating.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you to
lip-sync for your life.
- The lights go down, and
the last things I say to myself
are "I love you, Nana" and
"water off a duck's back."
- Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- [singing in Spanish]
- This is a perfect song for me
to play up a schtick.
Thank god I'm not wearing
that hoop skirt.
♪ ♪
- I'm throwing in, like,
a little salsa twist here.
I'm being very sexy.
Gonna send that bitch packin'.
♪ ♪
- I look over at Detox, and
she's doing her thing.
She's playing the opera singer.
She's doing her quirky little
lip-moving thing.
If I was Jinkx, I'd be worried.
♪ ♪
- Jinkx is kicking and dancing,
and she's bumping her hips.
I hate to say it, but Detox
might be getting out-danced
by Jinkx.
- [singing in Spanish]
♪ ♪
[laughter, applause]
- Ladies, I've made
my decision.
- Water off a duck's back.
Water off a duck's back.
Jinkx Monsoon,
shantay, you stay.
Detox, you had me hooked
from day one,
and I can't get you
out of my system.
And now
neither can anyone else.
Now sashay away.
- It's been so magical and
so humbling.
Thank you so much, from
the bottom of my heart.
- Thank you, Detox.
- I'm gonna miss
all of you guys.
I love you.
I love you so much.
- [yells]
It really fucking sucks
that I didn't all the way
to the top three,
like I had intended to.
A better fit
would've definitely been
to have me in the top three.
But I just can't thank Ru
enough.
The only thing I have left to
say is...I've had it.
Bye.
- The top three.
One final challenge stands
between you and $100,000.
Now remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen!
- [laughs] All right.
Now let the music play.
[RuPaul's The Beginning]
♪ ♪