- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
- Coco Montrese.
- Alyssa Edwards.
- The pageant
tore our friendship apart.
- Alyssa and I will have
our moment later.
- Jinkx, on the runway,
I think you should have prepared
more than one look.
- Every week I've done
a different look.
- Bullshit.
Jinkx, she's all comedy
and no glamour.
- You will be creating
your own signature fragrance.
- My fragrance is called
Alyssa's Secret.
- What is Alyssa's secret?
- Son of a bitch.
- Can we see your background?
- New York City.
- Uh, that's Tokyo.
- Oh, is it?
- I have a crush
on Ivy Winters.
- [gasps]
- Red, for filth.
Are you red-y for me?
- Alaska, you're the winner
of this challenge.
- Ha-ha!
- Alyssa Edwards,
shantay, you stay.
Ivy, sashay away.
- Aw, Ivy Winters.
- "I love you girls so much.
You always have a friend in me."
- Girl, she is
an amazing person.
- Yeah.
- Amazing, amazing.
Ivy and I were really connecting
and really feeling very close.
And the person who's been
such a good friend to me
is now gone.
- Coco, now I know
what it feels like
to be in the bottom,
twice.
- Was it horrifying
being up there again?
- No, I'm a performer, baby.
This is what I do.
So if I have to
lip sync for my life
all the way to the final,
I'll do what I got to do.
- So what you're saying
to me is,
"Well, it doesn't matter
about the challenges.
If I fall short every time,
I'll just lip sync my way back."
- I'm confident about
performance.
I'm not confident in my acting.
That horrible cologne commercial
and that Katy Perry and that--
- But those are our challenges.
- Listen, let me explain
something to you.
- No, you're not my mama,
don't explain nothing to me,
sweetie.
- Some people should just
call a spade a spade
and say,
"Hey, I like competition.
I just don't like the work
that comes along with it."
- Coco, you and I need to talk
about something too.
Something that keeps getting
said to me and to Alaska.
I feel like I've been labeled
as a comedy queen
in a belittling way, and--
- Oh, my God.
- There's a double standard
going on right now.
When I do well
in the challenges,
they just kind of
roll their eyes
because I don't have
their respect.
I am working just as hard as
anyone else here at everything.
- Jinkx--
- And to say that you're just
a comedy queen is belittling...
- Jinkx--
- Something I have made my whole
career on--I am talking.
It is something
I work very hard at.
- How many times have y'all
called us pageant queens?
- Jinkx, I told you the same
thing when you brung this up.
That you said "pageant queen."
- That's all I had to say.
- Oh.
- These pageant girls
keep telling me,
"I don't want to be a pageant
girl for the rest of my life."
Well, then, fucking stop
calling me the comedy queen.
I'm sick of that.
- Of course, the pageant girls
are going to discount
the comedy freaks.
The best revenge
is just to do better.
- ♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a sickening supply
of Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip courtesy of
alandchuck.travel,
headline Logos Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut vodka--
cocktails perfected--
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And tonight,
extra special guest judges,
Maria Conchita Alonso
and Jamie-Lynn Sigler.
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
- Yay.
[overlapping chatter]
- Good "mornting."
- This morning, I'm kind of
on pins and needles.
Everyone else is just out
for themselves.
I hope we get to do a challenge
and not be in a group.
[siren blares]
- Ooh, girl!
You've got shemail.
Like sands
through the hourglass,
so are your days
at RuPaul's Drag Race.
Escandalo!
To become America's next
drag superstar,
you need to deliver the drama,
mama.
Adios, muchachas.
- All: Ooh.
- Hello, hello, hello.
[overlapping greetings]
For today's mini-challenge,
we're going to play
the crying game...
- Oh, no.
- Where you need to cry on cue.
Tears.
So put on some mascara
and meet me
in the sharing circle.
Alaska,
cry me a river.
- Sebastian and I were wed,
but suddenly, last summer,
everything changed.
- It was my first dance recital
ever.
I waved bye to Grandma.
Bye.
- I knew that one day
I wanted to become a woman.
[sobs]
- I know this will be
hard to believe,
seeing as I'm the most polished,
prettiest drag queen here.
- Being an Orange County
housewife...
is not as glamorous
as it seems.
My husband,
he was addicted to sex.
- It gets so hard
being called the bearded lady.
[sobs]
- Separate rooms
on our second honeymoon.
[sobbing]
Oh, God.
- There's nothing more sad
than the tears of a drag queen.
- Maybe it's just time for me
to go home
to Seattle.
- Jinkx was supposed to be
making me cry,
but she was making me laugh.
[laughs]
- [sobs]
- I gave that man everything
I had.
- Detox.
- Um, I'm not gonna lie.
I'm having a hard time
with this challenge.
It's hard for me to even try to
be in character right now.
I really want to be
just completely honest
and just say how difficult
this is.
[sniffles]
I lost my boyfriend
two years ago...
and looking around the room
and seeing
mournful-looking characters,
and I feel like I felt
the day that I saw him dead.
And it's really hard for me
to try to stay out of that
right now.
[sniffles]
[sobs]
I'm not used to being
so vulnerable
and looking so vulnerable,
and I feel very uncomfortable.
- Thank you for sharing
your story.
- I'm so glad that she is
sharing her story.
And it's never something
that's gonna get easy.
But something that every time
you talk about,
will make it easier.
- Okay, girls,
no more tears.
Ladies, thanks again
for sharing.
The two winners of today's
mini-challenge are...
Detox and Alyssa.
Condragulations.
[applause]
For this week's main challenge,
you'll be starring
in two primetime soaps.
And you'll be doing it...
telenovela style.
- Son of a bitch.
And it's another
acting challenge.
- One script is Casa de Locas.
House of the Crazies.
The other, Ella No es Dama.
She's No Lady.
Detox and Alyssa.
First, you need to pick
your cast.
Detox.
- Roxxxy.
- Como?
[laughter]
- Alyssa.
- Jinkx.
- All right, Detox.
- You know I love you, Coco,
but I have to reform Rolaskatox.
- Por que?
Ay, dios mio.
[laughter]
- Uh-oh, I don't want the judges
to see me relying
on the crutch of a clique.
- So that means, Coco,
you're with Alyssa.
- After all that drama with
Coco, Jinkx, and me,
we're all on the same team.
Go team Alyssa.
- Caballeros,
start your engines.
And may the best mujer win.
[all shouting el grito]
- This is the first time that
members of Rolaskatox are
working together
since I sort of decided that
we should all be free agents.
- [Italian accent]
We are now r-r-r-rich!
- You're so Italian.
- Muy r-r-r-rico.
[both laughing]
- That was perfect.
- It's terrible.
- Sometimes Detox's
sense of humor
gets in the way of
taking the things
that need to be taken seriously
serious.
- Michelle already warned you.
Cliques can be dangerous.
That reunion of Rolaskatox might
be broken up real fast.
- Coming up...
You cast Coco as the ugly,
stupid maid?
- Yes.
- You look beautiful, Detox.
- Ah!
- [laughing]
- Oh, my God, that's sickening,
miss thing!
You have to use it.
- Today's main challenge is
serving up telenovela realness.
Oh, my God, I love it.
[trills]
- All: Vaya con dios.
- Telenovela is very loud
and in your face and dramatic.
- Muerte.
- And I am carrying his baby.
- [whispering indistinctly]
- Alyssa's not an actress,
but I guess like she said,
"I'll be bad in every challenge
and just get by
on the lip sync."
- I have the same disease!
I'm gonna be real drama there.
- You got to really, like,
bring it in,
'cause you rushing it like,
"I have the same disease!"
- I think Coco is definitely
trying to throw me off my game,
and I have to zone her out.
- Hola, hola, hola.
[overlapping greetings]
Donde esta el drama?
- All: Aqui, aqui, aqui, aqui.
- Hello, team Alyssa.
- La casa de locas.
- Yeah.
So what role are you playing,
Alyssa?
- I am playing a glamorous
woman of the house.
The ruler.
- Uh-huh.
- And Jinkx is my 18-year-old
virginal daughter.
So you cast Coco as the ugly,
stupid maid?
- Yes.
- Coco, in the past,
you and Alyssa
have had your differences.
Have you guys worked through
that?
- No.
- Well, I'm just trying to gauge
how close you guys were
and how big this rift was.
- We were close.
- I'm thinking The Turning Point
with Anne Bancroft
and Shirley MacLaine.
- Let's do Tyra Banks
and Naomi Campbell.
- Oh, okay.
- Oh, I'm Tyra Banks.
- Can I hear a little bit of it?
- Mamacita, mamacita,
Pablo asked me
to mar-r-r-ry him.
- Wait a minute,
is she Italian or is she--
- Oh, is it coming off Italian?
- Yeah, a little bit.
- Have I been Italian
this whole time?
[laughter]
- If you hear the names of food,
you will violently orgasm.
Read my lines.
[laughs]
- You got a lot of lines
to memorize.
You know, we're down
to six girls now,
and the stakes are very high,
all right?
- Thank you.
- I'm gonna let you
get back to it.
Adios.
- Thanks, Ru.
- Adios.
- Team Detox.
Oh, my goodness.
- Hi, Ru.
- So you're playing
the young ingenue.
- Yes, I am the virginal
18-year-old.
I think we know
why I'm a virgin.
[laughter]
- Now, Detox, you reunited
Rolaskatox.
- Uh-huh.
- Is that a good idea?
Could it be a little bit of
a easy crutch?
- We just are so full
of personality,
and we have a lot of fun
working together.
- Well, you know,
it's great to have fun,
but you also need to take
this challenge seriously.
Now, Alaska, what are you
worried about in this challenge?
- If every line is over the top,
then it's like, the really,
like, zinger lines lose their--
- I have to take this off.
[laughter]
- Now, Detox,
on the main stage,
the criticism you get is that
we're getting "B" plus.
We want "A" plus from you.
And I'm just interested that
you're going to take it to that
place wearing a mask.
- Whatchu talkin' 'bout,
Willis?
- This is getting down
to the wire.
Somebody's gonna go home.
And you got to make sure
it's not you.
- Right.
- You got a lot of work to do.
Get at it.
- All right, ladies,
gather around.
In a moment, you'll head
to the telenovela set,
and tomorrow on the main stage,
the category is...
Latina lamorosa extravaganza.
- Ooh.
- Señoritas.
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
Bye, eses.
- Her critique was about
this mask.
I don't feel it anymore.
- Girl, I've been read too many
times for wearing masks.
- Yeah.
- I've been working with
this mask the whole day.
- I always listen to critiques,
and she told us that
for a reason.
- I think that people are taking
this whole mask thing
a little bit too seriously.
- So we're good on costumes?
- Uh, pretty much.
- Do you think I should wear
this dress, Jinkx?
The gold one.
- Now she's just going through
my wardrobe.
- I don't know what's going on
with Alyssa.
She's over in Jinkx's wardrobe,
trying to find something to wear
for the challenge?
Good luck with that.
- Ow, fuck!
- What are you doing?
- I just stabbed myself.
Girl, all tea, all shade,
the dress doesn't fit.
- [sighs]
- You've got a ton of--
- Bull fantasy fat.
- Alyssa, for a pageant girl,
she sure didn't bring
no clothes.
I think it's time for her to go.
And I don't think I'm the only
one that feels that way.
- Coming up...
Meet your handsome leading man.
- What?
- [screams]
- [moans]
- That's your orgasm, Alyssa?
- Have you ever had one?
- [laughing]
- Team Detox.
Hola, como esta?
- Oh!
- My group is just about to
start shooting our telenovela,
and we're ready to blow it out
of the fucking park.
- Welcome to this lavish set,
furnished by Form Decor.
And say hello
to Maria Conchita Alonso.
- Que bonitas.
[overlapping greetings]
- And, ladies, meet your
handsome leading man...
Wilmer Valderrama.
- What?
[screaming]
Shut up!
- He is so gorgeous.
I want to have his babies.
- All right.
Accion.
- Diego.
Que paso?
- He is dead.
And now we must determine which
one of us killed him.
- I couldn't kill him.
Diego loved me.
And...
I gave him my virginity.
[all gasping]
And--
- Cut.
Try to keep the pace up.
Accion.
- Bring us the poison.
[glass clinking]
Our poison bit is going on
a long time.
Roxxxy and I are sort of
standing there like--
- Cut.
When you're serving it,
you don't really
have to be serving three
because we can't see that
you're going one, two, three.
- Okay.
- So to make it faster, just--
you know?
- Oh, okay, so--okay.
- Ladies, let's get into
your positions.
Now, Roxxxy, are you inching
over to Wilmer's crotch?
- Only my hand,
but you can't see it, right?
[laughter]
- Horn dog.
- Action.
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
- Agh!
- Cut.
Could we tighten up
the slapping?
It looked a little,
you know--
- Both: [grunt]
- Agh!
- Cut.
Okay.
Ladies, you're fine.
- What?
- Thank you very much.
- Bye, Wilmer.
- Team Alyssa.
Como esta?
- Muy bien.
- Si.
- We're prepared,
and we are prepared
to take this set by storm
and really deliver the drama.
- Accion.
- [gasps]
- It is I who cast the spell.
- You are muy estupida
if you think you are going to
take over our familia.
I am serving up
some Sofia "Vergar-r-a-rasa"
realness.
When I'm not talking,
I want to be reacting to what
other people are saying.
- Maria, I have some bad news.
If you hear the names of food,
you will orgasm so violently.
- Chimichanga.
- Ah, oh!
Ay, ay, si, si!
Si, si!
- Nacho grande!
- Ah!
- Ay, ay!
- Oh, oh!
[gasping]
- Cut.
When Jinkxy is doing the orgasm,
Alyssa, you need to at least
match
what Jinkx is doing.
- Okay.
- Ah, come on, Alyssa,
I really, really want you
to pull this off.
We are a team.
- And it's supposed to be
an orgasm, so, you know--
- Yeah.
I was trying to be like
a 48-year-old having it.
- Yeah, but you also want to
steal the scene, you know.
- Yeah, okay.
- Chimichanga.
- [moaning exaggeratedly]
- [whimpering]
- Whoever Alyssa is sleeping
with
is apparently
not doing their job.
- [sobbing]
No!
- And cut.
That's your orgasm, Alyssa?
- Have you ever had one?
- Yeah.
I'm feeling so insecure,
and it's frustrating
because I want to be so fierce
and so sickening,
and I'm not.
- Action.
- Have you seen Maria
or her mother?
- No esta aqui.
- Cut.
- No estan.
- Aqui.
- Yes.
- No estan aqui.
They are--
Oh, my God.
Wilmer.
Ooh.
- Cut.
- I looked at him,
and I forgot my line.
- Would you like to have dinner
with me?
- [purrs]
I forgot my line, Ru.
- That's not gonna do anything
for us as a group.
I'm nervous because
I don't want my very best
to be overshadowed
by someone else's very worst.
- That's a wrap.
[energetic salsa music]
- Ooh.
- Get ready for the kraken.
- Get ready for the kraken,
darling.
- Coming into tonight's
elimination,
we're all on pins and needles,
because we do not know
what the edited,
finished product
is gonna look like.
Look, someone's gonna go home,
so I need to get my wigs ready.
- Alyssa, if you wear
one more do, bitch,
where you whip it off
to one side--
- Girl, if you wear one more
stretch costume, girl--
- [gasps]
- Go work on your outfits,
'cause I think
you're running out.
- Ooh!
- It's done.
- Wait, wait, wait, Alyssa,
do you have enough stuff
to get through
the rest of the competition?
- Girl, yes, ma'am.
And I can sew if I have to sew.
- Alyssa, you ain't gonna
have to sew
'cause you'll be goin' in
everybody else's wardrobe.
- Oh!
- Ah!
- Hold on now,
let's get something clear.
That was for the challenge.
Baby, I ain't never wore none
of y'all's stuff on the runway.
I ain't never had to,
and I never will.
- Girl, if you had as much
energy in your orgasm yesterday
as you got right now,
we would have been fine.
- Ooh!
- Coco thinks she's smart.
I think it's a part of Coco's
character to take low blows.
When all the pageant stuff
went down,
she did the same thing.
- Are you scared going into
this runway?
- I feel confident
with my look today
because it's a clear concept
from head to toe.
I'm gonna do Dia de los Muertos.
I'm gonna do skeleton makeup.
- Jinkx Monsoon,
the buffoon.
What are you thinking, girl?
You're going out there
as Skeletor?
One judge did say,
I think it was Michelle,
that you're kind of costume-y.
- I really want to wear
this costume.
- But it's a risk.
- If it doesn't land,
it's like me telling jokes.
Then it was,
it was a complete miss.
- Are you single right now?
- I started trying to, like,
kind of date a little bit.
- Yeah.
- Afterwards, um--
Opening up about my ex-boyfriend
is still really difficult.
Our relationship
was so tumultuous,
especially towards the end.
When I ended up trying
to break up with him,
he got really crazy
and started stalking me,
and was, like,
threatening my life
and, like, telling me...
- What?
- He was gonna find me.
Then, two weeks later,
he was dead, so--
You know, I saw the body.
I got to the house,
and there he was.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
there's not a day that goes by
that I don't think about him.
♪ ♪
But it was tough, girl.
It was so hard.
- I just want you to know
that I always will love you,
okay?
- Letting Roxxxy know a little
bit more about it was nice,
because I've never gone
to a therapist.
I've never really talked
to anybody about
the way that I feel.
And I think this experience
is just bringing Roxxxy
and I closer together.
- Coming up...
- I have no freakin' clue
what you said in that novela.
- I don't get it.
I don't get
what it's supposed to be.
- [laughing]
[dramatic music]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl]
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
Hola, mama.
- Hola, mi corazon.
- Shake the dice
and steal the rice and beans.
Santino.
- Ya tu sabes.
- Ay caramba,
it's Maria Conchita Alonso.
You look gorgeous.
- Gracias.
- And a sexy señorita
who's no stranger
to primetime drama.
From Guys with Kids,
Jamie-Lynn Sigler.
You look so pretty tonight.
- Not as pretty as you.
- This week,
our queens were challenged
to deliver the drama
in two telenovelas.
And tonight,
they're ready to make us gag
on their Latina glamorosa
eleganza.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[RuPaul's I Bring the Beat]
- ♪ Commence shake down ♪
- Up first, Detox.
I'm bullish on that look.
- I'm serving up
mariachi realness.
Oh, ay, dios mios.
[shouts el grito]
- [laughing]
I bet she's got
some cock-and-bull story.
Roxxxy Andrews.
Check out those chichis.
- Hey, I'm the only Latina left.
I have to represent.
- I can see
her coochie-coochie.
- Okay.
- The 49th state, Alaska.
- Ay, caramba.
- I'm shaking my maracas.
I bought cha-cha heels for
Christmas.
- I got to teach you
how to play the maracas.
- [laughs]
- Mucho muchacha.
Alyssa Edwards.
- Very dramatic, huh?
- She's a Spanish fly girl.
- Um, tonight,
I'm serving Latin fish drama.
- Look at that legwork.
- Yes.
- Hyperextension.
- Serving Tex-Mex.
Coco Montrese.
- Ooh.
- Loco for Coco.
- I'm giving the judges Dorothy
Dandridge Latina glamour, baby.
- Her name was Lola Falana.
- Lola, do you wanna?
- Jinkx Monsoon.
[gasps]
- Drag of the dead.
- I feel fan-fucking-tastic.
Looking spooky and sexy
all at the same time.
- You know, Jinkx is like
all the other supermodels,
just skin and bones.
- [laughs] Yes.
- Buenas noches, ladies.
Let's take a look
at your telenovelas.
First up, Ella No Es Dama.
[melodramatic music]
♪ ♪
- We must determine
which one of us killed him.
- [gasps]
[gasps]
[all gasping]
- I couldn't kill him.
I gave him my virginity!
- [gasps]
- And...
I'm carrying his baby.
- Ah!
Agh!
Diego loved me.
- [gasps]
- He didn't mind
that I was old.
And I am carrying his baby.
Agh!
- How could Diego love you,
when he loved me?
And I am carrying his baby dos.
- [gasps]
- There is only one thing left
for us to do.
Bring us the poison.
- [gasps]
- All: Vaya con dios.
- [sobbing]
- All: [choking]
[gasp]
[choking]
[exhale]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- So stupid.
- You're telling me.
- Oh, my brother.
The beautiful drag queen.
- [grunting]
- No eres una dama.
- I've been working here
five years.
You'd think they'd notice this
Adam's apple from now, huh?
We will now be very rich.
Muy rico!
- Both: [laugh evilly]
[laughter and applause]
- Next up, Casa de Locas.
[peaceful guitar music]
♪ ♪
- I have bad news.
Hilda...
get out, you ugly, stupid maid.
Maria, you have a rare,
fatal condition.
- Oh!
- If you hear the names of food,
you will orgasm so violently
that you will...
die.
I have the same disease.
- [gasps]
[screaming]
Nooo!
[normal voice]
Now that you mention it,
we never talk about food.
- [laughing]
[ominous music]
It is I who put the curse on
la casa de locas.
- [gasps]
- [hisses]
Hilda!
You are muy estupida
if you think you are going to
take over our familia!
- Chimichanga!
[Alyssa and Jinkx moaning]
Si, si!
Y... fish taco!
[Alyssa and Jinkx moaning]
- No!
- Yes!
[chokes]
- [gasping]
- Is Maria or su madre here?
- No estan aqui.
Maybe I can help you
with something?
- Would you like to have dinner
with me?
- I thought you'd never ask.
- [laughs awkwardly]
[scattered applause]
- Now, this week you've worked
in groups.
But tonight, you'll be judged
as individuals.
It's time for
the judges' critiques.
Coming up...
- I think you were intimidated.
- That dress is probably
one of the worst I've ever seen
in five seasons.
- [laughing]
All right, it's time
for the judges' critiques.
Starting with...Detox.
- I'm not sure about
the sombrero.
It's so campy,
and the outfit is so not.
- On to the telenovela.
I think the villain has to have
the biggest presence,
so I wanted you to just have
something a little bit greater.
- Next up, Roxxxy Andrews.
- Tonight on the runway,
your makeup looks amazing.
More so than ever before.
- This is the least amount
of makeup I've worn ever.
- [laughs]
- You look stunning.
- Thank you so much.
- And the telenovela,
from the way you moved your body
to your high-pitched voice,
the way you moved your head
when you got slapped.
You took that role, and you did
great things with it,
and I was really impressed.
- Up next, Alaska.
- Hi.
- Tonight on the runway,
you gave us another upbeat walk,
and it works for you.
- Cruella de Vil.
That's what I saw
when you were acting,
which you did a very good job.
- I think you're really,
really gifted.
I could take notes from you,
for sure.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Alyssa Edwards.
- Alyssa,
I have no freakin' clue
what you said in that novela.
- [gasps]
- You turned into Dracula
a few times.
I was like, what?
- Tonight, that dress
is probably one of the worst
dresses I've ever seen
on this runway in five seasons.
It is such a mess.
I don't get it.
I don't get what
it's supposed to be.
- Okay, when you go
to the clubs,
every single,
each and every night,
you don't ask the girls,
"Did you sew that?
"Did you make that?
Were you funny the other night
to get here?"
But if you say tonight,
lip sync for your life,
I'm gonna lip sync for my life,
and if I'm able to stay,
I'll do it every damn week
because I am an entertainer.
- Alyssa, every last one of
these girls
are amazing performers.
- I didn't discredit nobody.
- It comes across as if,
"I'm the best entertainer
up here,
"and if I have to lip sync
for my life every night,
I'll lip sync my way
all the way to the crown."
That's not what this is about.
- Alyssa,
we know you got it.
Your characteristics are funny,
you're beautiful,
you have the total package.
I'm just not sure if you know
how to connect the pieces.
You know?
- Thank you.
- All right.
Thanks, Alyssa.
Next up, Jinkx Monsoon.
- Um...
you confuse me sometimes.
And that's a good thing.
- [laughs]
- Keep me on my damn toes.
- I was really shocked
by your outfit tonight,
but I love it.
I think it's really fun.
- In the telenovela,
you were perfection.
Your change of emotion
on a dime
to you humping the couch
when you were having
your orgasm.
- [moaning]
[gasping]
[squeals]
You did the best orgasm!
- [laughing]
- Next up, Coco Montrese.
- Hi, Ru.
- Your look tonight
on the runway, I love it.
It's a beautiful mango color.
You worked that jumpsuit.
Great choice.
In the telenovela,
I was left wanting more.
- I think you were
a little bit intimidated
when you got next to Wilmer.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
All right,
just between us chicas,
what do you think?
Let's start with Detox.
- Tonight on the runway,
this really wasn't Detox's
best effort.
And I expect more from her.
- Well, she slapped very good.
[laughs]
- Which is very important
in a telenovela.
- Yes.
- She was funny-ish
with baby dos
but could have been
so much bigger.
Like, that was
a wasted opportunity.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- She looked so pretty
with that black hair,
and her makeup looked gorgeous.
And her body shape
with the cinch waist.
She just melted my loins.
- Well, I loved seeing her
cinched in like that.
And the hair, and she drew on
the Latin curls.
- Oh, on the face.
That's so cute.
Yeah.
And in the telenovela.
- She was strong.
Everything she did,
the physicality,
her voice, the pitch.
She stood out.
- Roxxxy redeemed herself
this week
from the past two weeks
of kind of letting us down.
- Alaska.
- Ella No Es Dama really was
the better of the two
telenovelas because of Alaska.
- It was a very layered
performance.
She's a gifted comedian.
- Tonight on the runway,
the dress looked really cheap.
But she gave us
a little more ass.
- Yes.
- And you like that.
- Hell, yeah, I like more ass.
[laughter]
- Alyssa Edwards.
What did you think of her outfit
on the runway?
- Whoever made that for her
is fired.
- Thanks a lot, Grandma.
- [laughing]
- And what'd you think of her
in the telenovela?
- That role could have been
so, so big and funny,
because she's so intriguing
to me.
- How is it that
she doesn't know
how to ham it up
in front of a camera?
- She doesn't know
what she's got.
- She was already talking about,
like,
having to lip sync for her life
tonight.
- If that inner dialogue
is saying,
you know,
"I'm gonna fail at this
or I'm not any good at this,"
well, hello,
that's what you get, you know.
- Yes.
- Jinkxy Monsoon.
- She is a very good actress.
She's beautiful.
She's funny.
- She took that script,
and she made it her own.
- That takes a really talented
person to be able to do that.
- She looked flawless
in that telenovela.
- Yeah.
- The Dia de los Muertos.
It was shocking.
I think she looked fierce
the way she did it.
- I loved the cojones
it took to do that,
and it really did
catch me by surprise.
Coco Montrese.
- I thought she looked gorgeous.
I mean, this is her color,
the shape,
even the cheapish flowers.
In the novela, there were a lot
of weird choices
and missed opportunities.
A lot of literal acting out,
which is, like, cardinal sin
number one.
- I wanted her to stand out
so much more.
It felt as if her role
was insignificant
until the end
when you realized what it was,
and then you just wished
that it was more than that.
- Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
- [laughing]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Roxxxy Andrews,
as Teresa the virgin,
you really gave it up.
You're safe.
- Alaska...
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Jinkx Monsoon,
this week, you came,
you saw...
and you came again.
You're the winner
of this week's challenge.
[applause]
- Thank you.
- You've won a pair
of faux fur coats
from Fabulous-Furs.
- It's muy magnifico.
I am the first one
to win two challenges
in this competition.
- Alyssa Edwards,
your performance
in the telenovela
did not have us screaming
in ecstasy.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- [sighs]
- Coco Montrese,
as Hilda the maid,
you were a little...
dusty.
Detox, as Consuela the maid,
you...
didn't clean up.
Coco Montrese...
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- Ooh.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Detox, you may join
the other girls.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you
to lip sync for your life.
- From the first day
I walked into the workroom
and I saw her face,
I wanted to step on that stage
across from her
and get vindication.
- After all the drama with
our last pageant experience,
we both want this crown.
This will be the tiebreaker.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ He's a cold-hearted snake ♪
- ♪ Girl ♪
- ♪ Look into his eyes ♪
♪ Uh-oh ♪
♪ He's been telling lies ♪
♪ He's a lover boy at play ♪
- ♪ Girl ♪
- ♪ He don't play by rules ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Girl,
don't play the fool now ♪
♪ How come, how come he can
he can tell-a tell-a ♪
♪ You're-a you're-a always
always number number one ♪
♪ Without a doubt
when-a when-a he is he is-- ♪
- I'm making sure the judges
see every word
that's coming out of my mouth,
as if I was Paula Abdul herself.
- ♪ You could find somebody
better, girl ♪
♪ Let me tell ya
he's c-cold as ice ♪
- That spinning jump
into the split?
I mean, come on.
- Coco's spinning
very beautiful.
Her outfit works perfectly
for the dance moves.
Miss thing, she is everything.
- ♪ C-c-c-cold-hearted ♪
♪ S-s-s-snake ♪
- [laughing]
- ♪ Cold-hearted
s-s-s-s-nake ♪
♪ He's a cold-hearted snake ♪
- The lip sync is jaw-dropping.
It's gonna be neck and neck.
- ♪ Girl, don't play the fool ♪
[cheers and applause]
- [howls]
- Wow.
Ladies...
I've made my decision.
Coco Montrese...
shantay, you stay.
- [exhales heavily]
Coco, you may join
the other girls.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- [inaudible]
- [sighs]
- Alyssa Edwards,
the next time you look
in the mirror,
I hope you see what I see--
a triple threat.
A dancer,
a beauty queen,
and one fierce-ass
"entertainter".
Now, sashay away.
- Thank you.
[applause]
Deuces.
I cannot say
that I'm heartbroken,
because I gave it my all.
And to say that
I am in the top six
of America's finest
in this art form
is a privilege,
and it's an honor.
Always and forever...
[echoing]
Alyssa Edwards!
- Condragulations,
my ferocious five.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- All: Amen.
- Let the music play.
[RuPaul's The Beginning]
- ♪ Right, right ♪
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ G-g-get it, get it right ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪