- Tonight on RuPaul's Drag Race:
Countdown to the Crown ...
We're just one week away from
crowning America's
Next Drag Superstar.
Are you team Alaska, team Jinkx,
or team Roxxxy?
To help you decide, we have a
play-by-play analysis
of a season full of shock...
and shade.
- Look how orange you fucking
look, girl.
[alarm blaring]
- Orange alert!
Fashion dos...
- Whoo!
- And "Oh, no,
she better don'ts."
- I will not wear
another caftan.
- In never-before-seen moments,
celebrity guest stars exposed.
[all imitating monkeys]
Queens bare all.
- Whoa!
- These girls are cock-hungry
dick pigs.
- And later, find out what
stars are saying
about your drag idols.
And then, for the first time
anywhere,
we reveal Untucked:
The Lost Episode.
- What I have,
you guys don't have.
- To help break this shit down,
we'll be joined
by countdown correspondents,
Latrice Royale, Willam,
Sharon Needles,
and a world exclusive Ru-on-Ru
interview.
Just how damn old are you?
Oh, it's gonna be like that,
huh?
Are those your real teeth?
All this, plus the music video
world premiere of The Beginning.
From the thrill of victory...
- Yes.
- To the agony of defeat...
- Oh!
- Let the Countdown to the Crown
begin!
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a sickening supply of
Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip courtesy
of ALandCHUCK.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race Tour
featuring Absolut Vodka--
cocktails perfected--
and a cash prize of $100,000.
[tires screeching]
- Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race:
Countdown to the Crown.
Alaska, Jinkx Monsoon,
Roxxxy Andrews.
With one week remaining, this
season
is the closest contest
in Drag Race history.
Even I can't quite put my finger
on the charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
it will take to win the title
of America's
Next Drag Superstar.
That's why I want to hear
from you.
Which queen deserves to win,
and why?
Tweet your pic to
@RuPaulsDragRace;
#TeamAlaska, #TeamJinkx,
or #TeamRoxxxy.
And sound off via Facebook,
Instagram, Tumblr,
and Pinterest.
To win the crown,
your favorite queen
needs all the help you can give,
tonight and all week long.
Now speaking of favorites,
I want to check in with
my countdown correspondents,
Latrice Royale, Willam,
and Sharon Needles.
Welcome, ladies.
- Hi-yee!
- Hey, Ru.
- Can you help me make sense
of this crazy season?
- Ru, the suspense is killing
me, and not in a good way.
My marriage is at stake.
- Boo-hoo. I'm mad.
Season five was all about
performing,
and I could have tore it up,
like an episiotomy.
- Ooh, Ru, I'm living
for these season five girls.
Honey, you've got some funny
characters on this season.
Bitch, I live!
- Well, thank you, ladies.
I'll be checking back with you
in just a minute.
Now, to truly understand
how Alaska, Jinkx, and Roxxxy
ascended to the top three,
we need to do an instant RuPlay
of the bad-ass bitches they beat
down in their battle to become
America's Next Drag Superstar.
Game on.
- Hello, boys.
- Week one, Cincinnati cougar
Penny Tration hit the field
with a seasoned swagger.
Thousands of fans voted to get
her here,
but it took just one devastating
block by rookie
Serena Chacha to send
her packing.
all: Hi!
- College draft pick Serena
Chacha arrived a young pup,
eager to run with the big dogs.
- I have a feeling you just
like to be the only pretty one.
- I just think you're annoying.
- But on her second outing,
a flag on the play...
- Doo-de-doo-de-doo.
- Signaled that Serena was a
little out of her league,
and she cha-cha'd her way out
of the game.
- To the other queens,
pick up a book and go read.
- Hello, girls.
- Big-hearted Banji girl
Monica Beverly Hillz...
- With a "Z."
- Was a prospect with promise.
- Monica Beverly Hillz
is very good at giving face.
- While she didn't always bring
her "A" game...
- Can't you see I'm trying to
get some sunlight--
[stammers]
- Cut!
She bravely shared her "T"
with the rest of the world.
And when she lip-synched
for her life against Coco,
Monica Beverly Hillz
was sent back to
the 9-0-2-1-oh, no,
she better don't.
- Hey, sisters.
- San Francisco treat
Honey Mahogany
brought her own mystique
to the challenges.
- Bitch, I am from Chicago!
- But in her dance debut,
her kicks were incomplete.
- You know, I've never done
Diana before.
- Clearly.
- Hey, y'all.
- Week after week, catch
of the day Vivienne Pinay
felt stiff-armed
by the competition.
- Great.
A bunch of loudmouths.
- But her dance in the end zone
failed to put her
on the scoreboard.
A lackluster lip sync came down
to a coin toss,
and both Honey and Vivienne
hit the showers
in Drag Race's first
double elimination.
- Oh!
- Oh, word!
- Now, if pretty scored you
extra points,
Lineysha Sparx would have been
an all-star.
Her Tyra-nese performance got
her named MVP.
But sadly, Lineysha's snatch
game was over before it began...
- French fries.
- Leaving Detox to bench
this beauty for good.
- Hey, girls, hey!
- Jade Jolie arrived all
sparkles, rainbows,
and sunshine.
Her laugh was her best defense.
- [laughing]
- But still this queen could
dominate the offense whenever
shade was in play.
- Some people shouldn't come
down and wear a two-piece
because the view
that I had was not too cute.
- But instead of finding
her voice...
- ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
- She found herself lip-synching
against Coco,
and in the end, sashayed away.
- Uh-oh.
- Hey, ladies! Aah!
- Oh!
- Ivy Winters turned out to be
a triple threat.
She could sew, she could sing,
and she gave great face.
Although sometimes it seemed her
presentation
was a little stilted.
Wah!
Sadly, a fumble in the fragrance
challenge...
- New York City.
- Uh, that's Tokyo.
- Kept this queen from making
the final playoffs.
Texas Tornado Alyssa Edwards
hit the field,
ready to play hard
and settle old scores.
- Game on, bitch.
The sequel.
- She gave game face
for the ages.
- [smacks lips]
- And her countless
Alyssa-isms...
- I don't get cute.
I get drop-dead gorgeous.
- Gave inspiration...
- Back rolls!
- To the nation.
- Why you being cute?
- On the main stage,
this dancing diva
had all the right moves.
But by the telenovella...
- I have the same disease!
- Her pageant prance
was played out.
- What?
- And she was sent home
by her archrival...
Coco Montrese.
- The diva has arrived!
- A Vegas veteran who was
always ready to rumble...
- Don't try it, little boy.
- Or lip-synch the house down.
Ever the underdog, Coco scored
a big win at the roast...
- Pants so high, he look like
he in New Orleans at
Hurricane Katrina, girl.
[laughter]
- But dropped the ball
in the army-navy makeover,
forcing this beauty queen
to take her final bow.
Feeling overwhelmed?
You need to Detox.
This silicone cyclone put in
major work before suiting up
for Drag Race.
- I've had my hips
and my ass done.
I've had my pecs done.
Underneath my eyes done.
My six-pack done.
- And once here,
she had a few surprises
to pull out of her b-b-b-box!
- [clucking] Hi, kids!
- A runway rock star, Detox
never let us see her sweat...
all: Oh!
- Prompting some to accuse her
of coasting toward the end zone.
Ultimately this final four
standout
hit a sugar wall
in the sugar ball.
And after losing her lip sync
to Jinkx,
parting was bittersweet.
- I've had it. Bye.
- Well, there you have it,
skorts fans.
This season's rocky road
to the top three.
Damn!
I need a protein shake.
Coming up...
- The shade of it all.
- With Latrice, Willam,
and Sharon Needles.
Plus never-before-seen
too-hot-for-Drag-Race outtakes.
- Come here and sit on my face,
bitch.
- And for the first time
anywhere,
we reveal Untucked:
The Lost Episode.
- No one's hiding any knives or
shivs on their dresses,
are they?
- Keep tweeting who you want to
be crowned America's Next
Drag Superstar,
as RuPaul's Drag Race: Countdown
to the Crown continues.
[laughing]
Welcome back to RuPaul's Drag
Race: Countdown to the Crown.
This has been the stormiest
season on record.
- I could give a fuck.
- One thing's for sure,
the forecast always included
a 100% chance of...
- Shade.
- Early in the season,
super storm Coco collided
with hurricane Alyssa
and let us have it.
- I don't think she wants
to talk about it.
But we're gonna talk about it...
if she doesn't go home first.
- Shade.
- Just pearls hanging off
her boobs, baby.
- Very you.
- Shade.
She's won several pageants,
and unlike Savannah, she's
completed all of her reigns.
- Shade.
And then the tears come out.
And the Academy Award goes to...
- Shade.
You need to be worried about
what's going over there with
that same makeup
every single time.
- Look how orange you
fucking look, girl!
- Girls, you're both pretty.
both: Shade.
- Now is it just me, or are you
over this pageant feud mess?
Officially.
Ain't nobody got time for that.
Now I got some extra yummy,
never-before-seen leftovers
from the RuPaul roast.
- Michelle, your nails are
so long,
how the fuck do you wipe
your ass?
- Oh-ho!
- But better yet, how do you
wipe Ru's before you kiss it?
[laughter]
- Let me tell y'all about
Santino.
All the hems on his clothes
be crooked.
You know why?
'Cause he's always looking
at you like this.
[laughter]
- Knock, knock.
all: Who's there?
- Ivy Winters.
all: Ivy Winters who?
- Exactly.
[laughter]
- RuPaul, you don't need
a roast, mama.
By the looks of your face,
it's been roasting
for quite some time.
[laughter]
- Ru, you're always saying,
"You're born naked,
and the rest is drag."
but in your case,
you were born naked,
and the rest was just fucking
terrible.
[laughter]
- Now, joining us live from
the Drag Race Weather Center,
mother meteorologist
Latrice Royale.
Hi.
- Hi. I got news for you.
- Ooh, child.
Now what do you think of all the
romper room fuckery this season?
- Ru, I have one thing to say.
The shade.
The shade of it all.
- [laughs]
Now, Latrice, does the
competition bring out the worst
in some queens?
Or are they just shady ladies?
- RuPaul, in my experience,
the camera don't lie,
and neither do I.
Oh, and, girls, stop blaming
the editing, okay?
- Bible.
Bible, girl, uh-huh.
Tell it. Tell it!
- But you know what I love
about Drag Race?
Just when you think everything
has gone dark,
out comes a rainbow
of truth and light!
Hallelujah.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Let's take a look at some of
the most heartwarming moments
this season.
- Hey, Alyssa, this is Dad.
- Oh!
- I just want you to know...
- [cries]
- [cries] I'm proud of you.
And now I'm not ashamed
to tell people my son's gay.
- Oh! Oh, my God.
[crying]
- Forgiveness is free, baby.
Give all you can.
- I've just been holding
a secret in,
and I've been trying so hard
and--
- What secret?
- I'm not just a drag queen.
I'm a transgendered woman.
Every day is hard.
- I invited you here
because you were fierce.
The only person
who does not believe is you.
Stay strong,
Monica Beverly Hillz.
- I will.
- God makes no mistakes.
You be you, child.
- I continually regret and,
like, second-guess the fact that
I left my youngest brother
with a woman who wasn't ready
to be a mom.
When I'm, like, doing shit like
this, I feel so selfish...
- Don't, Jinkx, don't.
- [cries] To have left
my youngest brother.
- Don't.
Not at all.
- It feels like--right now,
like I've abandoned him.
- You haven't.
- Patience and love, honey.
Patience and love.
- My mother left my sister
and myself
at a bus stop
when I was three.
[cries] I try to stay so strong,
but I'm so weak
at the same time.
[crying]
It just hurts that I was left.
Nobody cared.
- You know, we as gay people,
we get to choose our family,
you know?
We get to choose the people
that we're around.
I am your family.
We are a family here.
- Bless us all.
Bless us all.
This is large and in charge,
chunky, yet funky,
Latrice Royale.
Back to you, Ru.
- Thank you, my queen.
- Aah!
[beep]
- Tonight, we're getting up
close and personal
with each
of our top three queens,
starting in alphabetical order
with the 49th state, Alaska.
Wiggling in from Pittsburgh,
Alaska arrived as a dark horse.
She auditioned for every season,
only to watch her girlfriend
snatch the crown last year.
But when this bowlegged beauty
arrived, she had me at "Hi-yee!"
- Hi-yee!
Hi-yee.
- Hi-yee.
- She tanked her first challenge
and quickly joined forces
with Rolaskatox.
But after some tough love...
- No!
- Alaska declared a state
of independence.
- Alaska.
- Until last week, she was the
only queen never to lip-synch
for her life.
And, girl, when it comes
to making us laugh,
Alaska has always been
right on the money.
- [whispering]
Your makeup is terrible.
- From the fragrance challenge
to the sugar ball,
she delivered one
of the strongest finishes
in Drag Race history.
And her triumphant testimony
on the main stage last week
showed us why Alaska could be
America's Next Drag Superstar.
So if you believe in Alaska,
let me feel it.
Tweet us at @RuPaulsDragRace
#TeamAlaska,
sound off at the RuPaul's
Drag Race Facebook page,
or show some love via the
RuPaul's Drag Race Instagram.
Coming up,
find out what Nicki Minaj,
Adam Lambert, and Sally Jessy
Raphael say about our queens.
Plus, Drag Race Deep Dish with
Willam and Sharon Needles.
- And I'm currently sitting on
my balls, like Mother Goose.
Honk!
- And a Ru-on-Ru
exclusive interview.
And later, we reveal
for the first time anywhere,
Untucked: The Lost Episode...
- You can be glamorous without,
like, 1,000 million stones
on your dress.
- Oh, Miss Thing.
- As RuPaul's Drag Race:
Countdown to the Crown
keeps on keeping on.
[laughing]
Welcome back to RuPaul's Drag
Race: Countdown to the Crown.
Drag Race fans are the best
fans in the whole wide world.
And because of you, our show
is trending on Twitter,
taking over Tumblr,
and winning America's
favorite reality show
on RyanSeacrest.com.
That's RyanSeacrest.com.
Hi-yee!
When it comes to Drag Race,
celebrities are just like us.
When they see something they
love, they tweet all about it.
Rolaskatox had Adam Lambert
gagging.
The legendary Sally Jessy
Raphael lives for Jinkx Monsoon.
- Jinkx Monsoon, you're special.
Shout-out to you.
- And Nicki Minaj is in love
with my girls.
Her favorite new expression...
- All "T," all shade.
- And, Mariah,
what you got, girl?
Now this next queen is so viral,
she's sickening.
Hi, Willam.
- Thanks, Ru.
Hey, superfans, you tweeted us
questions, and I got answers.
[beeping]
@johnbrunskill--
that's a lot of name.
"If you had to pick,
which season five gal
would you kai kai with?"
Coco, she's black.
@mcbrewster,
"You're a friend of Detox."
@fozziebare, "Don't you agree
that we need #LessFishMoreFun?"
No.
If you want ugly,
turn on Discovery Network.
Good-bye.
@bck2mono--
Oh, I've had that too.
[chuckles]
"What was more shocking,
the Honey and Vivienne Pinay
double elimination or yours?"
Mine.
They didn't even throw up.
Fucking amateurs.
@RuPaul, "Love you baby,
but your time is up.
Thanks, gi--"
Oh, I gotta go.
- Thanks, Willam.
And for the record, opinions
expressed by Willam
do not reflect that
of RuPaul Inc.,
Logo TV, President Obama,
or Tuckahoe State Prison
for ladies.
- [hums]
- Now, our superfans don't just
watch the show,
they do recaps and become stars
in their own right.
I love them all.
But these are some
of my favorites.
Can I get a RuCap up in here?
- Hi-yee.
- That was best episode ever!
- Whoever is making up these
mini-challenges, bitch,
they need an Emmy.
Did you see--whew!
- My favorite walk
of this runway was Alyssa.
- [laughs]
both: Alyssa Edwards.
- She ain't gonna win.
- With that fucking
faux dog-rat thing.
- [laughs]
- That is if she don't go home
first.
- Like, I wanted, like,
5, 6, 7, 24, 52.
- Jade is a string of pearls
away from becoming a showgirl!
- I am serving you fish, honey.
Fish on a platter.
[laughs]
- It was the best mini-challenge
of any reality TV show,
past, present, and motherfucking
future, bitches.
- Some of the biggest
Drag Race fans
are our extra special
guest judges.
Hold onto your wigs for
celebrity guest stars exposed.
- Do you tuck the balls, too,
or just--
- You gotta tuck them balls,
girl?
- Yes.
- How do you tuck the balls?
- Well--
- Actually, I give a detailed
description in my book,
Workin' It!,
which is available on Amazon.
- You can definitely tell
Alaska has two feet,
but we embrace the two feet,
and we're trying to help her--
- The left--
Everyone has two feet.
Two left feet.
- Sorry, two left feet.
- This one.
Sharp as a knife.
- Anita, I think Coco's
in trouble.
- I think so too.
[laughs] If she had done what
Santiago had suggested--
- Or Santino.
- Oh, Santino, I'm sorry!
- Or Santino!
- And from the Fashion Police,
George Kotsiopoulos.
What are you gonna do,
arrest me for smoking?
'Cause my pussy's on fire.
[both laugh]
- It's "bro-cod," black
and with this gold,
horrible "bro-cod,"
but it's, like--
- Are you trying to say brocade?
- No, I say "bro-cod."
- It's brocade.
- Uh, in France, it's "bro-cod."
- It's fucking brocade.
- I don't care where the fuck
you went to school--
- It's brocade.
- Swear to God.
- They so crazy!
But nobody get it twisted
like my girls.
I try to raise them right,
but what you gonna do?
- Whoa!
- [laughs]
- I won the challenge!
- Oh, my God.
Not by my bag!
Not by my bag, not by my bag!
- Aah!
- Some of these girls
are cock-hungry dick pigs.
- I want to see Lineysha naked.
- Trade! Trade!
Come here and sit on my face,
bitch!
- They said, "What do you like
the best about the werk room?"
I said, "There's a lot
of naked men."
- Trade!
- Would they have to blur this?
- I made this for you.
- [laughs] That's wonderful!
- Do you see
what's happening there?
- Gay sex in the service!
- It's time to play America's
new favorite game,
"Cut or Uncut."
[laughter]
Blue! Not a match.
- I sucked.
- Oh, not a match.
- Well, I didn't suck.
I wanted to, but--
Sorry, Mr. Cameraman.
- She bring it
to you every ball.
Why y'all gagging so?
Did you understand that?
If not, you could use
a refresher course
in drag linguistics.
#ShitMyGirlsSay.
- Can you say "not on tonight,"
Miss Roxxxy?
- Not tonight.
- No.
"Not on tonight."
- That makes no sense, girl.
- "Mama, they ain't gonna be
able to read me.
Not on tonight."
Not on tonight.
Not on
tonight.
Not on tonight.
- I've had it.
I have had it.
I've had it, officially!
- Detox, I'ma need you to stop
playing with my outfit.
- Well, I'm gonna need you
to stop relying on your body.
[laughter]
- Whoo!
- Stop relying on that body.
- Stop relying
on that body.
- Stop relying on that body.
- Stop relying
on that body.
on Sharon Needles.
- The time has come for our
next up close
and personal profile.
Top three queen, the sleeper
from Seattle--Jinkx Monsoon.
- Ow!
[laughter]
- At 14, Jinkx's drag career
started with a wig
her grandmother gave her.
- And I've had it ever since.
- She brought her show biz
skills to RuPaulywood.
- ♪ Can I get an amen ♪
- From the very start, Jinkx
kept getting the same criticism.
- It's rather pedestrian.
- But before you could say...
- Water off a duck's back.
Water off
a duck's back.
- Jinkx became a real contender.
[gasps]
- I love it!
- Ah!
- And her breakout performance
as Little Edie got everybody
talking.
- This is the revolutionary
costume for the day.
- From Snatch Game on,
Jinkx gained momentum.
- Si, si, si!
- But she nearly crashed
at the sugar ball.
At last week's courtroom,
she brought the drama, mama.
- You can't handle the "T"!
- And as one of the most
talented comedy queens ever,
Jinkx has stolen our hearts.
But can she mop the title
of America's Next Drag
Superstar?
What do you think?
Is it monsoon season?
Let us know.
Tweet us @RuPaulsDragRace,
#TeamJinkx.
Sound off at the RuPaul's Drag
Race Facebook page
or Instagram.
Coming up, drop-dead gorgeous
Sharon Needles.
- Boo.
- This season's fashion dos...
[cheers and applause]
And "no, she better don'ts."
plus, an exclusive Ru-on-Ru
interview.
And later, we reveal Untucked:
The Lost Episode,
as RuPaul's Drag Race:
Countdown to the Crown
continues.
[laughing]
America's Next Drag Superstar
has to do it all...
lip-synching...
dancing...
acting...
crunking.
Still, looking good never hurts.
- The look is not
that important.
- Ah!
- Ripped from the pages
of this season's look book,
our fashion dos and "oh, no,
she better don'ts."
Read it and weep, Anna Wintour.
Category is "crafty queens."
style to D.I.Y. for.
[buzzer]
- Shakira meets--
- Pinocchio.
- Category is
"executive realness."
Oh, is that an Adderall?
- Elementary school teacher?
[buzzer]
- Eleganza extravaganza!
Straight up glamour, no chaser.
[buzzer]
- This is very Singapore
Airlines.
- Come fly with me.
- Sashay, shantay.
[buzzer]
Duvet, duvet, duvet.
- Very Bed, Bath, &amp; Beyonce.
- [chuckling]
- We call this one
"Ru wore it best?"
What becomes a legend most?
Living on the fringe!
Orange you glad
I wore this dress?
Shine bright like a diamond!
Gag on this, Michelle Visage.
This season's fashion dos and
"oh, no, she better don'ts" was
brought to you by peanut butter.
Peanut butter by RuPaul.
Must be jelly,
'cause jam don't shake.
Now, to find out what it means
to be the champion,
I've invited back our reigning
queen Sharon Needles.
- [laughing] Hi, Ru.
How are you?
- Now, everyone wants to know.
Who do you want to win?
- That's an obvious answer.
Lil' Pound Cake.
[both laughing]
- So if Alaska wins, can two
queens live happily ever after?
- Yeah, she spent a year
blowing my prize money.
So I would love to just get
a little bit of that back.
- Now, I wanna ask you
about winning,
and how has it changed
your life?
- This year has been
a nightmare, um, come true.
I've gotten to travel the world,
I've been the face of PETA,
I played Frank Furter in the
Rocky Horror Picture Show,
I came out with a whole album.
Um, what the crown can do
for you
is make all your dreams come
true if you let it.
- Yeah, wow.
- And it's been great to see
kids all over the world identify
with this, you know, kooky,
spooky, bat-shit crazy
drag queen
that I really thought would
just, uh, be making people
laugh in small bars
in Pittsburgh.
- Sharon, any words of wisdom
for America's Next
Drag Superstar?
- What other people think of you
ain't none
of your damn business.
- That's right.
- My advice, when in doubt,
freak 'em out.
And of course, what Lady Bunny
always says, "Retire!"
[both laughing]
- Oh, I almost forgot.
Do you have anything
to shamelessly plug?
- You can buy my album PG-13
now available on iTunes.
Oh, and make sure to check out
all the fabulous music
that the RuPaul Drag Race girls
have been making.
- Like what?
- Like these...
Tammie Brown's Love Pinata.
Rock the Beat by Nina Flowers.
Bebe Zahara Benet, Dirty Drums.
Raja, Sublime.
You Like It Wild
by Jessica Wild.
Shangela's Werqin' Girl.
I Wanna Have Some Fun
by Pandora Boxx.
Tatianna's Losing Control.
Look At Me, Tyra Sanchez.
Manila Luzon and Latrice
Royale's The Chop.
Major by Milan.
It's Honey by Honey Mahogany.
Honey Mahogany has a song?
- [laughs]
- Detox's Boy Is a Bottom.
Mimi Imfurst, Xelle, Party Girl.
Venus D-Lite's I'm Not Madonna
and many, many more.
- Wow.
That's the best mothertuckin'
playlist ever.
But on a serious note...
today you can vote
with your pocketbook.
So get off your ass,
go to a club,
and support
your local drag queens.
- Ru.
- [gasps]
- That was beautiful.
- Oh, Sharon.
I didn't know you were there.
You really are spooky.
I thought you had left.
- Boo.
- It's time to get up close
and personal
with top three queen
Roxxxy Andrews.
Hey.
Where my people at?
A cute kid from Orlando,
Roxxxy Andrews got her start
as a pageant queen.
She dropped 70 pounds...
70 pounds?
Before dropping
into the competition.
But she never lost her thick
and juicy personality.
She won the first main
challenge,
then formed the super group
Rolaskatox.
A true knockout, Roxxxy always
came out swinging,
on the runway
or in the werk room.
- This isn't a joke to me.
- I don't think--
- This competition
is extremely serious.
- Roxxxy proved she could make
us laugh...
- [with lisp] I am ready
to toss your salad, Anita.
Get your life.
- Make us cry...
- [crying]
- And she could even make over
a soldier.
And in the music video,
Roxxxy's
hairography blew the other
girls away.
She could also be the first big
girl
to snatch the title of America's
Next Drag Superstar.
If you want Roxxxy,
let the world know.
Tweet us @RuPaulsDragRace
#TeamRoxxxy,
or show her some love
at RuPaul's Drag Race
Facebook page or Instagram.
Coming up...
Untucked: The Lost Episode.
Plus, a Ruvealing interview.
Don't mess with me, little boy.
And later, the music video world
premiere of The Beginning.
Don't move a love muscle because
RuPaul's Drag Race:
Countdown to the Crown
is about to pop off.
[laughing]
Now, sometimes when you tuck
things away, they get lost,
especially if you've been
sitting all day.
But lucky for you,
the long-lost episode
of Untucked
has not only been found,
it's been restored,
filled with extra
dramatic sound effects,
and brought to us by its host:
the one and only RuPaul.
Hello, hello, hello.
My dear, you look gorgeous.
Oh, you.
So what do you got for us?
Girl, it's a doozy.
I can't wait.
Rupaul, is it true that you
never get to see Untucked
until the show airs?
Yes, I see it
when America sees it.
They shoot Untucked when the
judges and I are deliberating.
So it's not like I can be
in two places at once.
Duh.
Duh!
Now, Ru, while I have you here,
fans are dying to know what was
up with your lighting, girl,
in season one?
We couldn't even see you, child.
"Exsqueeze" me?
And just how damn old are you?
Oh, it's gonna be like that,
huh?
Are those your real teeth?
Well, I bought 'em.
Hey, Urkel, uh, you trying to go
Untucked on me right now?
Don't mess with me, little boy.
Oh, no "T," no shade,
Miss Thing.
Let's keep it cute.
Yeah, uh-huh.
That's what I thought.
Now, without further ado,
for the first time anywhere,
Untucked: The Lost Episode.
Welcome to Untucked.
This week, our top three queens
took it to court,
stating their cases for becoming
America's Next Drag Superstar.
- What they don't have,
I do have.
I have grace.
I have beauty.
I have professionalism.
- I was able to adapt and grow
while still being true
to who I am as a performer.
- Roxxxy was faced with
a challenge of presenting
a 16-year-old girl.
What did she present?
A tawdry, 27-year-old tramp.
And Jinkx Monsoon, she failed
three different looks.
- Afterwards, Roxxxy, Alaska,
and Jinkx
headed to
the Interior Illusions Lounge
to have an Absolut cocktail
and let off some steam.
- So how do y'all feel?
- Well, I wrote out the things
that I was gonna say
specifically about you two.
Then all of it seemed forced.
I was ready to tear down Roxxxy
and compare myself to Alaska.
But on the stage,
none of that seemed to matter.
- I knew exactly where I wanted
to go with it and made,
like, an outline.
But when I went to on the stage,
I was just coming
from the heart.
I made a choice not to call
everybody out on this runway
because doing that is not me.
- I just did the assignment.
I mean, we were supposed to,
like, cite exact things.
- Oh, Miss Thing.
Like, I could've sat there and
critiqued Jinkx and, you know,
critiqued Alaska
and these things--
I didn't wanna go there.
I just wanted to say--
- But I think that's
what they wanted us to do.
The assignment was specifically
not to give pageant answers.
Sorry, it's hard,
but it's our last challenge.
- I don't know.
I-I--all I could say was
that what I have,
you guys don't have, so--
- Like beauty and grace?
You said that onstage.
- No, I know.
- I may not have grace...
- [slurping]
- But I can possess beauty.
You can take a garbage bag
and be a fucking beauty queen.
You can be glamorous without,
like, 1,000 million stones
on your dress.
- It's just how I know
how to do drag.
Right now in the gold bar,
there's a lot of tension.
It was, once again,
my defense going up.
And I realized
that I owed them an apology.
This has been such
a learning experience.
In the pageant world, I feel
like I'm on top of my game.
And coming into this,
it's a whole nother story,
where you're up against
all these girls
that can beat you
at other things.
You're competing to be
the Next Drag Superstar.
And a superstar is not just
someone who can walk a runway
in a gown and be--
you know,
anybody can kinda do that.
- Except us.
- [laughs] Exc--
- Except you two 'cause you--
you can't possess it.
But, you know,
and anybody can do that.
And it's so much more than that.
- You know what's so funny,
is it has really been a similar
experience for me,
but in such a different way.
It got to a point where I felt
so attacked by other drag queens
because I have my own way
of doing things.
And then I come here,
and then all of a sudden
I'm not a pretty girl,
I'm the comedy girl.
Where back home, I'm, like, one
of the prettiest drag queens
there are.
- And I didn't have to bring it
up on the runway,
but I really
wanted to apologize for what
I said to you in the werk room.
It was being mean and--
and I didn't mean it.
- It meant something to me that
you apologized,
just so that our last
interaction together
didn't have to be a fight.
- Wow. Bam, bam.
Oops.
Bam, bam.
Oh!
On fire.
You caught me playing
with myself.
I mean, playing my fabulous new
game,
the RuPaul's Drag Race edition
of Dragopolis,
available May 6th for iPhone
and iPad on the App Store.
Fierce!
Now, which one
of my top three girls
is your Next Drag Superstar?
Are you Team Alaska, Team Jinkx,
or Team Roxxxy?
Don't go away.
Because we've got
the world premiere
of the music video
The Beginning,
as RuPaul's Drag Race: Countdown
to the Crown continues.
[whirring]
[laughing]
One week from tonight, herstory
will be made as we crown
America's Next Drag Superstar
at RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited.
Who do you think deserves
to win...
the witty and wild Alaska...
- Hi-yee!
- This year's consummate
chameleon,
evolving at every turn?
Or the sleeper queen,
Jinkx Monsoon,
who brought Broadway brass
and vintage va-va-voom?
Or bronze bombshell
Roxxxy Andrews,
the queen of wham, bam,
thank you, glam?
I wanna hear from you.
Tweet us @RuPaulsDragRace.
Comment on Facebook and make
your voices heard everywhere.
Thanks to my countdown
correspondents,
Latrice, Willam,
and Sharon Needles.
And most of all,
I wanna thank you,
all my squirrel friends
out there watching at home.
We couldn't do it without you.
The world premiere of my new
music video The Beginning
is dedicated to you.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen.
- That's right, baby.
Now let the music video play.
- These are serious allegations.
- We have one thing to say.
all: No comment.
[laughter]
- I plead innocent.
- I'm guilty of being fierce.
- You can't handle the "T."
- You're out of order.
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ G-get it, get it ♪
♪ Breaking up ♪
♪ Fading out ♪
♪ Holding on until tomorrow ♪
♪ Shake it off ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ It won't be long ♪
♪ Till it's a brand-new day ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
- We want the "T."
- You can't handle the "T"!
- Sickening!
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
♪ You better get it, get it ♪
♪ G-get it, get it ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ G-get it, get it ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
- The accuser
is one cold-blooded biatch.
- Objection!
Reading the witness.
- This had better be good.
♪ That was then ♪
♪ This is now ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
- The murder weapon--
a size three stiletto.
- I wear a size 14.
- ♪ Miracles happen every day ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
- I can't face it.
I can't face it!
- What is it you can't face?
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
- [spits]
- ♪ You better get it, get it ♪
♪ G-get it, get it ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ G-get it, get it ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ G-get it, get it ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ G-get it, get it ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
♪ Change the world ♪
♪ Change your mind ♪
♪ We defy space and time ♪
You're out of order!
You're out
of order!
Why, I ought to throw the book
at all of you.
- Jesus!
What the--
- [grunts]
You, over here!
- Aah!
- ♪ We defy space and time ♪
♪ Change the world ♪
♪ Change your mind ♪
♪ Get it, get it ♪
♪ We defy space and time ♪
♪ Right, right ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
Court dismissed.
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪