- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
To make it in RuPaulywood,
you've gotta dive in
the deep end.
- Agh!
I can't do it.
I fail.
- Welcome to the slums of
Beverly Hills.
- Aah! Mommy!
- Ow! That's my leg.
You know, I have a feeling
you just like to be
the only pretty one.
- You're just--
like, so immature.
It's just really aggravating.
- Little bitty Serena,
she's fucking irritating
the shit out of me.
- ♪ Serena Chacha ♪
Penny Tration.
Alaska.
Roxxxy Andrews.
You made rubbish look ravishing.
Condragulations.
- Oh!
- You're the winner
of this challenge.
Serena Chacha,
Shantay, you stay.
Penny Tration,
sashay away.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, look what Penny wrote.
- Aww.
- We love you, Penny Tration.
We're back in the workroom
after Penny was just eliminated,
and it's really hard 'cause
I'm really gonna miss her.
- All right, Penny,
here we go.
Bye-bye.
- All: Bye, Penny.
- I happen to have stumbled.
And that's okay.
I know that destiny
wanted the queens to see
how good of a performer I am.
Maybe that's what I needed for
the queens to really respect me.
- Well, I already thought
I was gonna be on the bottom.
It scared the shit out of me,
and I realized looking
at you guys competing,
I was like, "You know what?
That could've been me."
I just feel like
I'm different
from the rest of these girls,
you know.
My head, mentally, it's, like,
somewhere else.
- There was something
about Monica
at Penny's elimination.
She just wasn't happy
that we were safe.
- I thought Penny was revving up
for it at the beginning.
I was like, "Watch out, girl."
- Aw, does that mean you guys
were rooting for me?
Were any of you guys
wishing I went home?
- I love Penny.
And Penny and I have gotten c--
you know what I'm saying?
And I'm not trying to be a bitch
or anything,
but you've kind of gotten on
my nerves a little bit so far.
I'm upset because I really would
rather see Serena go home.
- Serena has annoyed me
to the point where
I can't say anything nice
about her.
I'm just gonna try my best
to avoid Serena,
and if she's gonna
get in my way,
I'm just gonna smack her
like a fly over a cow patty.
Just go home, bitch.
[dramatic music]
- ♪ RuPaul Drag ♪
- ♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a sickening supply
of Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip courtesy of
alandchuck.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut vodka--
cocktails perfected--
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
And tonight,
extra special guest judges
Kristen Johnston
and Juliette Lewis.
- ♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
[tires squeal]
- Rolaskatox...
- Is in the room!
- In the house.
- Ooh.
- Rolaskatox is Roxxxy,
Alaska, and Detox.
Rolaskatox.
It's the new prescription drug
for people who are gagging.
Sorry about it.
- It sounds like
a venereal disease.
[shouts and laughter]
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl!
You got shemail.
My queens,
for the first time
in Drag Race history,
I am not going to say,
"For the first time
in Drag Race history ."
[laughter]
Now, the queen that doesn't know
her herstory
is destined to repeat it.
[contestants ohh]
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and applause]
- Hi!
- Condragulations,
Serena Chacha.
You survived the first
lip-synch for your life.
- Yes!
- Let that be a lesson
to all of you.
To win $100,000,
you're going to need to put your
money where your mouth is.
Oh, pit crew!
[big band music]
- Ooh!
[laughter]
- What?
- Now, for today's
mini-challenge,
you need to pucker up
and impress me with the power
of your pie hole.
- Whoa.
- Using just your mouths,
I want to see winning
lip-synch performances
of my songs Tranny Chaser,
Ladyboy,
and Peanut Butter,
all available on iTunes.
[laughter]
You'll be competing
in three groups,
and the best lip sync
from each round will win.
So put on some lipstick,
and then go for the glory.
[laughter and cheers]
[energetic techno music]
- There are some crazy lips
in this room.
Detox looks like the Joker.
Lineysha looks like
a painted peacock fantasy.
And Coco's looking like she just
fell into a vat of glitter.
- Ladies, assume the position.
[dramatic drum roll]
You do that all so well.
[laughter]
[RuPaul's Tranny Chasers]
♪ Is some tranny chasers
up in here? ♪
♪ Welcome to my stratosphere ♪
♪ Fierce, fierce ♪
♪ Make a move ♪
♪ What you wanna do? ♪
♪ I ain't got no time
for no looky-loo, boo ♪
♪ Is some tranny chasers
up in here? ♪
♪ Let me make one thing clear ♪
♪ Fierce, fierce ♪
♪ Make a move ♪
♪ What you wanna do? ♪
♪ I ain't got no time
for no looky-loo, boo ♪
[laughter and applause]
That was awesome.
But one of you...
really, really...
popped.
[laughter and applause]
Serena Chacha.
- I won a mini-challenge.
Boom.
Take that, bitches.
[gong crashes]
[RuPaul's Ladyboy]
- ♪ This groove
is for my girls ♪
♪ Little lady boys and girls ♪
[musical interlude]
[laughs]
♪ You got me
oh, oh, oh oh oh ♪
♪ You got me going ♪
♪ Oh, oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ This groove is for my girls ♪
♪ Little lady boys and girls ♪
[laughter]
- Wow.
- Whoo!
- The winner is this kisser
right...
here.
[cheers and applause]
Detox.
[laughs]
- My jaw hurts a little bit.
- Yeah, I bet.
[RuPaul's Peanut Butter]
- ♪ Peanut, peanut, peanut ♪
♪ Peanut, peanut, peanut
p-p-p-p peanut butter ♪
♪ Peanut butter,
peanut butter ♪
♪ Gonna walk right through
that door ♪
♪ Like before ♪
♪ High, high heels
on a hardwood floor ♪
♪ They all coming back
for more ♪
♪ Back, back for more ♪
♪ Get it up and do it right
this time ♪
♪ Act so fine ♪
♪ Spread that jelly ♪
♪ Spread it good ♪
♪ Peanut, peanut,
peanut, peanut ♪
♪ Peanut, peanut p-p-p-p ♪
♪ Peanut, peanut, peanut,
peanut, peanut,
♪ Peanut, peanut butter
work ♪
♪ Peanut butter,
peanut butter ♪
♪ Let me get another ♪
[laughter and applause]
Hungry, hungry holes.
Ooh.
Ivy Winters.
[cheers and applause]
Nice lip jobs, ladies.
But consider that
just a warm-up.
For this week's main challenge,
it's gonna be a lip-synch
extravaganza.
[queens cheer]
You'll be taking classic moments
from the herstory of Drag Race
and recreating them
in your own scene-stealing
viral videos.
You'll be lip-synching
to the spoken word, darling.
I'm Laura Linney, and this is
Masterpiece Theatre.
[laughter]
Serena Chacha, Detox,
and Ivy Winters,
you're team captains.
Serena, you choose first.
- Ms. Roxxxy Andrews.
- I want my Lasky.
- [laughs]
- Toxy!
- Lasky!
- Ms. Lineysha.
[laughter]
- Ms. Alyssa, come here, baby.
- Give me Monica.
- Ms. Vivienne.
- Ms. Jinkx,
come here, baby.
- Coco Montrese,
get your ass over here,
bitch.
- Ivy Winters,
take your pick.
I'm sorry, Jade, but I'm gonna
have to go with Honey.
- That's okay, girl.
- And that means Jade Jolie
goes with Serena Chacha.
- I'm not exactly, like,
the person
that would normally
be picked last.
That kind of pissed me off.
- Yay!
Welcome to our... team...
- Ladies, I need your lip syncs
to be as tight
and unforgettable
as your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve,
and talent.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- Our team gets an envelope,
and we are gonna be lip-synching
to a video of past seasons
of Untucked.
And we are doing season three's
Raja and Delta
and then the scene with
Shangela, Mimi, and Mariah.
Shangela.
- Shangela.
- Mariah.
Somebody has to be Mimi.
- I think you should be Mimi.
- I think I should be Raja.
- I think you're Raja,
hands down.
- Yeah, I'll do Mimi.
- Okay, guys, so let's just
finalize this.
We have Raja, we have Delta,
we have Shangela--
- I'm Delta?
I was pretty much ignored.
I kind of got dealt with
what was left.
If our team is in the bottom,
I am gonna throw Serena right
into the freaking pit.
- Coming up...
Jade, did you choose
to be Delta?
- Do it again.
- Can I have a second?
- Oh, but you want to
really fight.
- [screams]
- [laughs]
- So Ru tells us that
we will be reenacting scenes
from Untucked from seasons
two, three, and four.
- Aah!
- Season four.
- So we have
Ms. Lashauwn Beyond,
Jiggly Caliente,
Phi Phi O'Hara,
and my boyfriend,
Sharon Needles.
- We're Sharon and Phi Phi!
I call Phi Phi.
- No!
- I call Phi Phi.
- Okay, I'll be Sharon.
- I'll be the--Jiggly.
- You wanna do Jiggly?
And you'll be Lashauwn?
- Here we go.
- Phi Phi, I was not trying
to throw you under the bus.
- Girl, what you do best
is you act.
- Can you please
put a wonky eyelash on?
That's all I ask.
- Yes.
- This is gonna be sick, girl.
Anybody have any orange paint?
I know Phi Phi personally,
and I think she's
a lovely person,
but I'm taking this exaggeration
to the nth degree.
- [laughing]
Whoo!
- My foundation
is sickeningly dark,
and one of my lashes is gluing
one of my eyes shut.
That might be a little too dark.
- Um, Lineysha,
why don't you play Tyra?
- Tyra Sanchez.
I am doing season two.
We've got Morgan McMichaels,
Mystique, Tyra,
and Tatianna.
- There isn't anything else
to say.
- But why are you talking?
- Why are you talking?
- Because if I have a problem
with someone
or I have something to say to
someone, I say it to them.
If I don't like you,
I don't like you.
- Quite honestly,
I think Lineysha
is going to struggle
the most because of
the language barrier.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hello, Ru.
- Hi.
- Team Serena Chacha.
- Hola, hola, hola.
- Serena, you're playing...
- Raja.
- Yes.
- Did you assign the roles
for each person?
- We did it evenly.
- Jade, who are you playing?
- I'm Delta.
- Did you choose to be Delta?
- No, I was kind of, um,
a team player and just
gonna work it out.
- Okay.
So Jinkx is Mimi Imfurst.
What about you, Roxxxy?
Who are you playing?
- I'm doing Mariah.
- Mariah, of course.
- Mm-hmm.
- And you're playing?
- Shangela Halleloo.
I put her in drag
for her very first time.
- You did?
- Yes.
- A family that drags
together...
- All: Stays together.
- As you well know,
one of the best queens who's
ever used spoken word
in lip sync is Lypsinka.
- Yep.
- She is famous
for using dialogue
from Joan Crawford
and Bette Davis films.
Absolutely the best.
So now, are you kids gonna
give me just a taste?
- Are you, like,
curious at all
as to why Stacy didn't, like,
immediately pick you?
- I smell fear in her,
and I tend to kind of--
not pick on her, but I'm just
very, like, hard on her.
- So you're reading
off the thing.
You haven't memorized it yet.
And you haven't done any
characterization yet of Raja.
[dramatic music]
- Um, well, she doesn't really
move very much.
- She would still
have character.
Bring it up.
- Bring it up. I can do it.
I can do it. I can do it.
- Y'all make it work, okay?
See you later. All right.
- Thank you.
- Just make up a character,
honey.
Make up a something.
- Team Detox.
- Hi, Ru.
- Now, I know you're doing
season four.
Who's playing Sharon?
Who's playing Phi Phi?
- Phi phi.
- Duh.
- You're Phi Phi?
[laughs]
And you're Sharon?
- Yeah.
- It's interesting.
You live with Sharon.
Why didn't you play Sharon?
- I do Sharon all the time.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
Now, who are you two?
- Ms. Jiggly Caliente.
- Jiggly Caliente.
- I'm Lashauwn Beyond.
- Lashauwn Beyond.
- Yes.
- What is the key to doing this?
Have you ever done spoken word?
- Not that much.
- What's the biggest challenge
with this scene?
- Honest, just listening to
Phi Phi's voice over and over.
- Yeah.
- Well, I'm gonna let you kids
get back to it.
- All right, Ru.
- And make it special.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Ivy Winters.
- Hi, Ru.
- So you're doing season two.
- Yes.
- And who are you playing?
- I'm playing Morgan.
- Tatianna.
- Tatianna, of course.
- Yes.
- And you are?
- Mystique Summers.
- Mystique Summers Madison.
I wanted to call her
Mystique Summers eve.
But she wasn't having it.
Okay, who are you?
- Tyra Sanchez.
- You're the other, other Tyra.
Can we hear a little bit
of Tyra and Tatianna?
- Sure.
- Tapped me on the shoulder.
- I tapped you on the elbow
first.
- If it bothered anyone,
if they would have just said,
"Could you keep it down?
It's bothering me,"
that had would've been fine.
- And I did that.
- If someone comes to you...
- [laughs]
- And saying you're obnoxious--
- I'm watching you lip-synch.
- Ah, okay.
- That's not how I started it,
though.
I tapped you on the shoulder.
First I-I said your name
across the room.
- Okay, well, you got a lot
of work to do.
Get at it.
- Thank you, Ru.
- All right, see ya.
- Mwah.
- All right, dolls.
Now, I warned you this is gonna
be a lip-synch extravaganza.
Read my lips.
[silent]
[laughter and applause]
- Queens: Bye.
- Bye, Ru.
[hip-hop music]
- Oh.
My train, girl, my train.
Our challenge this week
is to lip-synch
to a past scene from Untucked.
Where do you want me to be?
- Mimi over here, then.
- My team had to do scenes from
season three.
It's Shangela, Mimi Imfurst,
and Mariah.
- Boo, just 'cause you got
a sugar daddy
who pays for everything
for you--
- Bitch!
- Oh!
- Hey, hey.
- No, no, no, no.
- Okay, ready?
[beep]
- Boo, just 'cause you got
a sugar daddy
who pays for everything
for you--
- Bitch!
- Oh!
- Hey, hey!
- No, no, no, no. No.
- Oh, my gosh. Watch out.
Watch out, watch out, watch out,
watch out, watch out, watch out.
Anybody get hurt?
- Graceful.
Do it again. Come on.
Push play.
- Bitch!
- Oh!
- Hey, hey!
- No, no, no, no. No, no.
- [laughing]
- Do it again.
Do it again.
- Can I have just one second
to get this back on?
- Here.
- Just get it for her fast.
Ready?
Five, four--
- Oh, shit!
- Do it again.
Just roll it up.
- I will never look like that.
- True.
[dramatic music]
- Do it again.
- It is easier for you to say,
"Do it again," okay?
- Hold on.
- Can I have a second?
- Oh, but you want to
really fight.
- It got to the point where
I had to yell and scream
and snap at people
just to be heard in that group.
[choked up]
And this is too important to me
to let them get to me like this.
- Coming up...
- Sweetie, if I hit you...
- You already lost.
- That would take the lose away.
- Honey, you are already out.
- I'm really starting
to get annoyed.
- [laughs]
- Our challenge today is
we have to lip-synch
from a past season.
The second scene is with myself
and Serena.
We're playing Delta and Raja.
- Like,
it's like a soccer player
from, like, Paraguay
or something,
mixed with, like, Afghanistan
and Charro.
- I wonder if people
talk about us this way.
- At the end,
when you hear,
"I wonder if they talk about us
this way,"
you turn to us like you just
heard the entire conversation
or whatever.
- Okay.
- Then I'll just pass out.
I come from
an arts school environment,
and I believe that drag
is performing gender
through various skills, like
makeup as a form of painting,
fashion as a form
of self-sculpture,
and showmanship
through performance.
- I wonder if people talk
about us this way.
[coughs]
- Serena playing Raja...
that was really bizarre.
- All right.
How'd you guys feel about that?
I feel good.
[clapping]
How did you guys feel?
- Oh, my God.
We're so gonna be on the bottom
because of you.
- All right, ladies.
- All right.
The first scene that
my team is performing
is a catfight between
Morgan McMichaels
and Mystique Summers
from season two.
- Go fix your hair.
- I don't need some--
- Fix your mug.
- I don't need to fix my mug,
bitch.
- Honey, you do need to fix
your mug.
- Sweetie. Sweetie.
- You do need to--
- I don't gotta hit your ass
to probably get voted off,
bitch.
- Hit me. Do it.
- Walk off. Step off, bitch.
- Do it.
- Lineysha's acting crazy.
- Okay, let's do it again.
- We should be working
as a team,
and she's goofing off
and playing around.
- Don't be, like, banging
'cause the argument's
mainly about
what Morgan and Mystique
are saying.
- Hit me.
- Sweetie, if I hit you...
- You already lost.
- That will take the lose away.
- Honey, you are out. Lost.
- You already lost.
- I think Lineysha wants
all the eyes on her,
and I'm really starting
to get annoyed.
- Ooh.
- I'm playing Tatianna
in a scene where
Tatianna and Tyra are bickering
back and forth.
- If I don't like you,
I don't like you.
- And I don't like you.
Are you happy?
I don't like you.
- I was not talking to you.
- I'm saying it to your face.
Then why are you looking
in my direction?
- Ugh.
- I don't like you.
- I was not talking to you.
- I'm saying it to your face.
Then why are you looking
in my direction?
- [laughs]
Lineysha was the worst person
to work with,
but her performance as Tyra
was awesome.
She was so on point.
Um, she's one
to be reckoned with.
- Okay.
My team has two scenes
to reenact from season four,
one of which is between Phi Phi
O'Hara and Sharon Needles.
- Do you really think I'm upset
that I didn't get a cruise?
- The only thing
you keep saying is,
"I promised Alaska one thing,
"and that was to bring her back
a trip.
[whiny voice]
Why didn't I get a cruise?"
- I will say that
I really wanted a cruise,
but I wanted the $100,000 more.
And look. Guess what.
We got both.
[laughs]
- Do you really think I'm upset
that I didn't get a cruise?
- The only thing
you keep saying is,
"I promised Alaska one thing,
and that was to bring her back
a trip."
- I'm doing an okay job,
but luckily,
Phi Phi does this a lot,
so I can do that
to cover the fact
that I don't know what
she's saying.
- It's bullshit.
- No, you're bullshit.
- [laughs]
- That was a lot better.
- Hell, yeah. That was fun.
- Our second scene is between
Jiggly and Lashauwn.
- I'm not here to make
best buddies, bitch.
This is not RuPaul's
Best Friend Race.
- No shit, Sherlock.
- Of course, I get to be
Lashauwn Beyond,
who has a little bit of problem
with her makeup.
I'm not saying that I do,
'cause I think I'm beautiful.
And then Monica
got to be Jiggly--
after the weight loss.
- If you lacking one thing
somebody else ain't lacking,
then shut the fuck up.
- I didn't say anything about
you going on the runway,
looking like that.
I said nothing about your look.
- Okay, really quick,
Monica,
you're fumbling a little bit
on the lines,
so when you're doing that,
just act up.
Just get nasty with it.
- Okay.
- If you lacking one thing...
- [muttering lines]
- Somebody else ain't lacking,
then shut the fuck up.
- Monica started
to talk her lines,
when we're supposed to be
lip-synching.
It kind of threw me off
a little bit.
I felt like I was just
letting you have it
'cause you didn't throw it back
at me.
Throw it back at me.
- This is not RuPaul's
Best Friend Race.
- No shit, Sherlock.
- Ew.
- I'm like, "Ugh,
I'm fucking it up."
I'm not focused, and I don't
have my 100% in this competition
because I have so much going on
in my head.
- I feel like Monica
gets a little bit nervous,
so I'm hoping that
she shakes out of that.
[dramatic music]
- Rolaskatox is in the building.
- Ding-dong!
- It's always a little tense
on elimination day.
- I do not want to be in
the fucking bottom.
- We won't be in the bottom.
I promise.
- We're sort of looking
around the room
to see who's gonna be on
the chopping block.
- Something's a little different
with Monica.
I'm not sure exactly what it is,
but there's something
on her mind.
You all right?
[sad music]
- I have so much on my mind,
and I don't want to be here.
I'm petrified to tell these
girls my huge secret.
I don't know how they're gonna
take it.
[crying]
It is hard being here.
- Listen, you're here
for a reason.
You could tell inside
she's just breaking down.
I don't think she's all here
at the competition.
[dramatic music]
- [laughing]
[music crescendos]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl]
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
[applause]
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
- Darling, this is the best set
of queens yet.
- From your lips to God's ears,
darling.
- Mwah.
- Well, shut my mouth.
It's Santino Rice.
- Oof, my fair lady.
- Kristen Johnston,
how are you doing tonight?
- I can't believe it,
but I'm actually very attracted
to you right now.
- [laughs]
Juliette Lewis,
you look g-g-g-gorgeous.
- Thank you.
I'm happy to be here.
- This week,
our queens paid lip service
to Drag Race herstory.
And tonight, they've come
dressed to impress.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Coming up...
- The lip-synching was
completely off.
- What the "F"?
- I don't want to see boobs
when I'm at Drag Race.
- [laughing]
[laughing]
[electronic music]
- Commence shakedown.
- First up, Lineysha Sparx.
Gorgeous. Look at those legs.
- I'm looking Latina.
I feel caribena.
Totally flawless.
- I wore that at the beach
last week.
- [laughs]
I'll meet you at the cabana.
Oh, yeah.
Honey Mahogany.
Caftan realness.
- I'm feeling pretty fierce.
This look is gonna slay
the judges.
- Juliette, is she wearing
a Cape Fear?
- [laughs]
- Hello!
- Ivy Winters.
Wow.
- Oh.
- Now, that's what I call
stiletto.
- Being a circus queen,
I decided to pull out my stilts,
and I did a butterfly goddess
look.
- Does anybody have a really big
butterfly net?
- [laughs]
- Mwah.
- Vivienne Pinay.
- She's got her own stilts.
Check 'em out.
- Yes.
Sissy that walk, honey.
- I'm wearing a sick gold dress,
low cut, very short,
looks fucking fierce.
- Little Grecian goddess.
- Oh, mighty Isis-is-is-is.
- [laughs]
- Alyssa Edwards.
- [barking]
- I think she's choking her dog.
- I have my clutch
in my left hand
and my baby chinchilla
in my right,
and I'm serving Rodeo Drive
fishness.
- She walks like
a dressage horse.
[laughter]
- Serena Chacha,
representing Panama.
- That's it.
- You can't even fit that
through the Panama Canal.
- Walking around
in this carnival costume
from the Republic of Panama
is a dream come true.
- Pants-off dance-off.
- [laughing]
Yeah.
- Jade Jolie.
It's the missing Ringling
sister.
- Screw the rainbows.
Give me leather.
- I'm serving up real
lion tamin' realness.
Bitch, send in the clowns.
- [laughs]
- Our little Jade
is all grown up.
Roxxxy Andrews.
If Cher had breastfed,
this is what she'd look like.
- I like to have the fringe
going down my boobicles
and on my booty and want to try
and win two times in a row.
- Tita Turtur.
- Turtur.
- Tina titties.
- [laughs]
- Jinkx Monsoon.
Hollywood glamour.
- Meets space.
- I am serving up
Hollywood 3012,
space-agey and beautiful.
- Very 3rd Rock From the Sun.
- Yes!
- Monica Beverly Hillz.
- Oh, yeah.
- Can you pay
my telephone bills?
- [laughs]
- My moneymaker is my face.
I know for a fact
that I'm beautiful.
- That is a nice ass.
- And it's not padded.
Natural-born thriller.
Alaska.
The 49th state.
- I'm trying to give sass
and flirt
and be cute
and sell this garment, sweetie.
- Party girl on her way home.
- Oops, I left my phone inside.
- Coco Montrese.
- This is Patti Labelle
meets Ziggy Stardust.
- Yes.
- I love fetish,
so I thought I'd give Santino
a little bit of something to
dream about tonight
while he's at home.
- You better "ass" somebody.
- Damn, girl.
Detox.
- Ohh.
- Snow White and the hunty man.
- Tonight I am wearing
an over-the-top gown
and feeling really sickening.
- How many black cocks
had to die for that outfit?
- [guffaws]
[laughing]
- Welcome, ladies.
Let's take a look
at your viral videos.
First up,
team Serena Chacha.
In the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
Shangela and Mariah
confronted Mimi Imfurst.
- You told them
you could do glamour
and you were high-fashion.
Do you feel that you delivered
that today?
That's the question.
- No, but I don't think
that was the challenge.
- Don't tiptoe
around the answer.
The thing is,
you just told us
that what you do is camp.
- You'll never be glamour.
- Boo, just 'cause
you got a sugar daddy
who pays for everything
for you--
- Ooh!
- I've never had a sugar daddy.
If I wanted a sugar daddy,
yes, I probably could go out
and get one,
because I am what?
Sickening, bitch!
- Hey, hey!
- No, no, no, no.
[laughter]
- Meanwhile, in the bar,
Delta gossiped with Raja.
- Manila was just that,
like, amalgamation
of every Asian stereotype.
- She was, like, Chinese,
Japanese,
dirty knees,
look at these.
Remember that?
- Right, like,
she's like a place in France
where the naked ladies dance.
- She was Cambodi-China-no.
- She was, like,
middle-America's interpretation
of Asian people, but when they
call them Oriental.
- [laughs]
I wonder if people talk about us
this way.
[coughs]
- All right.
[applause]
- Watching Serena was like
watching an old Chinese movie.
[silent]
- Next up, team Ivy Winters.
In the gold bar,
Tyra defended her singing,
which infuriated Tatianna.
- I'm not gonna replay it
because I already know
what happened,
and you already know
what happened.
- Okay, well, then--then
there's nothing else to say.
- I'm not replaying it with you
over and over again.
There isn't anything else
to say.
- But why are you talking?
- Why are you talking?
- Anyway, if you have a problem
with someone, address it.
And that's probably why
I seem like a bitch.
If I don't like you,
I don't like you.
- And I don't like you.
Are you happy?
I don't like you.
- I was not talking to you.
- I'm saying it to your face.
Then why are you looking
in my direction?
[laughter]
- Back in the lounge,
things were getting heated
between Morgan and Mystique.
- Go fix your hair.
- I don't need to.
- Fix your mug.
- I don't need to fix my mug,
bitch!
- Honey, you do need to fix
your mug.
- Sweetie.
- You have no manners.
- How do I have no--no manners?
- No class and no manners.
- No class, no manners?
You piss me off some more,
I will whoop your fucking ass.
Bitch, I am from Chicago.
[laughter and applause]
- I'm actually super confident
that I'm gonna be the winner
of the challenge
because I feel like
I turned it out.
- Next up, team Detox.
In the gold bar,
Jiggly was mad at Lashauwn.
- I'm not here to make
best buddies, bitch!
- Neither am I.
- I'm not here
to be your friend.
Then shut the fuck up!
You been everybody's B.F.F.
and ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki.
No.
- Clearly, I don't get along
with you.
- That's fine.
I don't have to be your friend.
This is not RuPaul's
Best Friend Race.
- No shit, Sherlock.
- Back in the lounge,
Sharon defended herself
for calling Phi Phi O'Hara
cutthroat.
- I wasn't tarnishing your--
- Bullshit.
- I said you were cutthroat
and you hogged that
choreography, which is true.
- Because I'm fucking fierce,
and I'm good at what I do?
- No, you're the one
that fucking lied,
saying I'm just here for a trip.
We all know that's a joke.
- Bullshit.
Every fucking time.
It's bullshit.
- No, you're bullshit.
[laughter and applause]
- Oh, my lord.
- Ladies, you all did
an amazing job.
But one group was more
in synch than the others.
The winner of this week's
main challenge is...
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Coming up...
- Is that a prosthetic nose?
- You were like Chewbacca
in drag.
- Is this really your best drag?
- [sobbing]
- [laughing]
[laughing]
Ladies, one group was more
in synch than the others.
The winner is...
team Ivy Winters.
- Yay!
[laughs]
Yay.
- But one of you really
lip-smacked the competition...
Lineysha Sparx.
- [laughs]
- Oh.
[applause]
- You've won a couture latex
outfit from Siren Latex,
plus immunity from elimination
next week.
- [laughing]
- You may leave the stage.
- Yes.
- Ladies, it's time for
the judges' critiques.
Alyssa Edwards.
- Your Shangela lip-synching
was--
- Was better than Shangela.
[laughter]
- I do a bit of acting myself
on the side.
But I love
when people transform,
and I didn't recognize you.
- That's a good thing.
- Yeah.
- Serena Chacha.
- What the "F" was with that
little teeny flag?
You come out with this ginormous
thing and, like,
♪ Do do-do do-do do-do ♪
- The panties are almost abuela,
grandma panties.
And the lip-synching
was completely off.
- It was just kind of
uncomfortable to watch too.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Mariah--it was a
great lip-synch,
and you gave it
over-the-top Mariah-isms.
- With all the fringe
hanging down and the color,
I thought that you were like
Chewbacca in drag.
- [gasps]
- Shut up, Santino,
because that's perfection.
- [laughs]
- Come on.
- All right, Jinkx Monsoon.
- The hair was a little thirsty.
- I tried to tease it,
but I just pissed it off,
I know.
- [guffaws]
- Yeah, it's that--
- Your Mimi--I couldn't
take my eyes off you.
You're bananas,
and I love it.
- Jade Jolie.
- Your Delta--work!--
was hilar.
- Thank you.
- You should've practiced
with that whip, though,
a little bit more.
If you're gonna walk
with a whip,
you better crack that shit.
Am I allowed to say whip?
- [laughs]
- Just kidding.
- Monica Beverly Hillz.
- Jiggly's probably
one of the biggest characters,
and you let that
completely go away.
- Also, on your runway as well,
I don't know, maybe you're sad
today or it's a hard day.
You're kind of disconnected.
- Monica, tell me.
What's on your mind?
- It's true,
what you're saying.
There is a lot
going through my head.
I feel I'm not here.
[crying]
I've just been
holding a secret in
and trying so hard, and--
- What secret?
[sad music]
- I'm not just a drag queen.
I'm a transgendered woman.
♪ ♪
Ever since I got here,
I've been lying to myself
and to other people.
[sobbing]
I'm a transgender woman.
The only way I'm gonna be able
to give 100%, if I come clean.
I feel like I'm not
being myself.
Every day is hard.
- I invited you here
because you are fierce.
You deserve to be here,
and that's why you're here.
You have to believe in yourself,
and the only person
who does not believe is you.
Stay strong,
Monica Beverly Hillz.
- I will.
- I think she's here now.
- I think you're here too.
- It felt good to say that.
- Monica has been through
everything.
Right now, she's my hero.
She's the strongest girl
in this competition.
- All right.
Alaska, the 49th state.
- Hi.
- The Phi Phi--
♪ Genius ♪
- Is this really your best drag?
- This is actually Detox's
best drag.
- [guffaws]
[laughter and applause]
Coco Montrese.
- I think everything
is flawless.
You're yummy.
- If it ever comes down
to lip-synching against Coco,
I fear for each and every
one of you
because she is no joke.
- Thank you so much.
- ♪ Detox ♪
- Your Sharon Needles scared me.
- [laughing]
- And that's hard.
- You've been around
a little bit,
I can tell, right?
- Oh, what are you
trying to say?
- Been there, done that.
Just a little vibe of that
coming from you.
Just loosen up a little bit
on everything.
- It's a shock to hear
that I'm overconfident.
This is something that I've been
wanting to do for years,
and to finally be here,
I'm humbled.
- Well, my queens,
I think we've heard enough.
While you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
[engine revs]
All right, now,
just between us "goyls"...
Alyssa Edwards.
- She revealed
this whole other talent
with the lip-synching.
- I love her mouth so much.
It's very hard for me
to take everything else in.
I get hypnotized.
- All right, Serena Chacha.
- I have a special place
in my heart for Raja,
and she got nothing right.
Don't swim in the big pond
until you got your little
floaties on, girlfriend.
- I see improvement.
Is it enough improvement?
I'm not sure.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Her performance as Mariah,
it was spot-on.
- Yeah.
- But I don't want to see boobs.
I mean--
- Why are you sitting
next to Michelle, then?
- I don't want to see boobs
when I'm at Drag Race.
- Jinkx Monsoon.
- This is not meant
to be offensive,
but is that a prosthetic nose
tonight?
- No, that is her real nose.
- Oh, my God.
- So do you think that,
the way she shaded it,
it looked almost
Alice the Goon-ish?
- Yeah.
- That said,
she's certainly the best actress
up there.
I mean, she's phenomenal.
- Jade Jolie.
- Had it not been for
her portrayal of Delta,
that whole thing would've been
unwatchable.
- I'm a little bored.
You know, come on.
Fat suit, funny.
- Monica Beverly Hillz,
who confessed to us
that she actually is
in the middle of transitioning.
- Good for her.
I think she looks great.
She's gonna have a great life.
- But she didn't embody
any Jiggly.
She could've gone all the way
and blacked out some teeth.
- Yes!
You could've even done
her expression,
you know, that, like--
- [guffaws]
- I don't see the performer.
- Alaska.
- Her Phi Phi was fantastic.
- I actually think her
performance really failed.
I thought it was over the top
in not a funny way.
- Coco Montrese.
- She is such a badass.
The lip-synching she had down
to a tee.
- Her Lashauwn was beyond
Lashauwn.
- Detox.
- Flawless and beautiful.
- It just didn't do it for me.
She didn't do it for me.
She kind of feels like
she's figured it all out.
You love her.
We get it.
- No, I love all of them.
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
- Thank God.
- [mumbles incoherently]
- [laughs]
- [laughing]
[laughing]
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your performances
in this week's challenge
and on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
[suspenseful music]
Monica Beverly Hillz,
please step forward.
Serena Chacha.
Monica,
your performance this week
was a little too Jiggly
and not enough caliente.
And, Serena,
as team leader,
you forgot to cover
your own ass.
I'm sorry, my dears, but you are
both up for elimination.
The rest of you...
may join the other girls.
- It was no surprise to me
that I was gonna be
on the bottom two.
[sighs] I should've said
something earlier.
- Bottom two again.
Fuck my life.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me,
to save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
to lip-synch...
for your life.
- Sorry, Serena.
I'm gonna lip-synch
for my motherfucking life.
- Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
- ♪ La-la la la ♪
♪ I want you to love me ♪
♪ Like I'm a hot ride ♪
♪ Uh, yeah ♪
♪ I wanna make you beg for it ♪
♪ Then I'ma make you ♪
♪ Swallow your pride ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Want you to make me feel ♪
♪ Like I'm the only girl ♪
♪ In the world ♪
♪ Like I'm the only one ♪
♪ That you'll ever love,
like I'm the only one ♪
- I think I'm the bigger
contender, honestly.
I think I have a lot more
than she has.
- ♪ Only one ♪
♪ Take me for a ride ♪
- Oh, my God.
Serena did a split.
Oh, wait, she did that
last time.
- ♪ High, high ♪
♪ Let me make you
first, first ♪
♪ Make it last all night ♪
♪ Want you to make me feel ♪
♪ Like I'm the only girl ♪
♪ In the world ♪
- Monica is slaying the hell
out of Serena,
and I'm very happy.
Serena can get the hell out of
here.
- ♪ In the world ♪
♪ Girl in the world ♪
- [laughing]
Whoa!
[laughter and applause]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Monica Beverly Hillz,
shantay, you stay.
- [exhales]
- You may join the other girls.
- Thank you.
- Serena Chacha,
you are a young
and talented queen
with so much more
to show the world.
Keep on keeping on, Pana-mama.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you.
It sucks.
I feel like there was a lot more
to offer.
But there's nothing
I would change,
except for not being
team captain.
To the other queens,
pick up a book and go read.
- One dozen queens,
one step closer
to becoming America's
next drag superstar.
Now remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- All: Amen!
- Now let the music play.
[RuPaul's The Beginning]
♪ ♪
♪ Get, get, get, get ♪
♪ Get it right ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪