- Previously,
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
you'll be starring in two soaps.
Telenovela style.
- Son of a bitch.
It's another acting challenge.
- I have to reform Relaskatox.
- I don't want the judges to
see me relying on a clique.
- Chimichanga!
- [gasps] Oh!
Ay! Ay! Si! Si! Si!
Oy! Oy!
- Alyssa, you need to at least
match what Jinkx is doing.
- That dress is the worst dress
I've ever seen in five seasons.
- When you go to the clubs,
you don't ask the girls,
"Did you sew that,
did you make that?"
I am an entertainer.
- Alyssa,
that's not what this is about.
- Jinkx Monsoon, you're the
winner of this week's challenge.
[applause]
Coco Montrese,
shante, you stay.
Alyssa Edwards, sashay away.
- Girl...
- Agh!
Going into the workroom,
it really was a sweet moment
to see Alyssa leave the stage.
- "The sky is the limit
when your heart's in it."
- How do you feel?
- I feel free.
I feel a weight
lifted off of me.
- Are you making another
fat joke about her?
- Oh! Miss Jinkx!
- I'm happy that this book
is closed.
- Coco believes
that this has closed
a big chapter in her life.
So the hope now
is that she doesn't take
all of that Alyssa aggression
and put it on one of us.
- Now it's time to be
America's next drag superstar.
Thank you, girls.
all: Ooh...
- Jinkx, you bitch.
You're the first one
to win two challenges.
- It was such a toss-up
between you and 'Laska.
- Jinkx is my biggest
competition.
She's really funny,
and so am I, so...
[clicks tongue]
- And Roxxxy was in the top
three too.
- We're trying to get Jinkx
out of here.
She's a big threat, and I don't
know where I got to get you,
but I got to find
somewhere that you lack.
- RuPaul, can we please sew
something for next week?
- No sewing, Ru!
- So I can win a damn challenge!
- Let's just hope
I have enough fabric
to braid myself another dress.
[laughs]
- I'm sorry, my dear.
Your sewing looks like shit.
- I just feel like
there are people
who are just waiting for me
to screw up big-time.
- Your sewing looks like
Coco's performance.
Shit.
- It's turned quickly from
Sisterhood
of the Traveling Pants
to "Sisterhood of I'm going
to kill you so I can win."
- The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a sickening supply
of Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip,
courtesy of alandchuck.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring Absolut vodka,
cocktails perfected,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And tonight,
extra-special guest judges
Clinton Kelly
and George Kotsiopoulos.
- ♪ The top five ♪
♪ The top five ♪
- ♪ Top five, top five ♪
- Cinco, cinco, cinco.
We're back in the workroom,
it's a new week,
and I am terrified
of messing up now.
[siren blares]
- Ooh, girl!
You've got shemail!
Sometimes a drag queen's gotta
do what a drag queen's gotta do,
whether it's laying a foundation
or painting the house down.
You've got to spackle,
Neely, spackle!
- [laughs]
- Remember the golden shower
rule:
Do unto others
as you would have them
do unto Ru.
- Oh...
- What?
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi, Ru.
- Now, to keep you
in fighting shape,
for today's mini challenge,
you're going to go to...
drag booty camp.
- Oh...
- [chuckles]
- So put on your workout gear,
including heels by Le Dame
and boobs from
The Breast Form Store.
Go!
- Ooh.
- Le Dame.
- This must be
what my mom feels like.
Yeah, yeah.
- Ladies, meet your
personal trainer.
From Barry's Bootcamp, Storm.
- Mash.
- Now, the one queen
that outlasts the others...
wins.
- Ooh.
- Let's get it up, come on.
I don't know,
but I've been told.
all: I don't know,
- Drag queen shade
is mighty cold.
all: Drag queen shade
- Pump it, girls.
Pump it, ladies.
Keep that energy up.
Jinkx, you took off your heels.
- They fell off!
- Come on, you call yourself
a drag queen?
- Here we go, ladies.
- Pull up.
Come on, count it off.
- I don't like working out
around other people.
I get ugly when I work out.
- Get up, get up, get up!
- [grunting]
- Detox, you're out.
Keep crunching, come on.
Coco, you're out.
Keep it going.
Roxxxy, you're out.
Up!
It's just between
Jinkx and Alaska.
Come on, now.
- Finally, my opportunity
to push Jinkx
down the proverbial stairs.
- Who's gonna be the last queen
crunching?
- Oh, Jinkx is out.
Alaska wins.
[clapping]
- Whoo-hoo!
Let's do some more!
- Alaska, condragulations.
- Thank you.
- Bye, ladies.
I'll see you at the gym.
- See ya there.
Not really.
- Now, you ladies have bravely
soldiered
through challenge
after challenge.
Now it's time to give back
to those who have
sacrificed so much
to serve this great nation.
Oh, boys!
- [gasps]
- God bless America.
- These gentlemen,
who also happen to be gay,
served our country
before the repeal
of "Don't ask, don't tell."
Thanks to these men,
we have the freedom
to be fierce.
And now, you get to exercise
that freedom
by enlisting these men
into your drag house.
- Oh, shit.
I'm nervous, 'cause I've never
done anyone else's makeup.
- Now, Alaska,
you won the mini challenge,
so you get to pair
the queens with their vets.
- Well, everything happens
for a reason...
- Uh-huh.
- And these men came in
in this order for a reason.
So I want to go straight down
the line, so--Izzy, is it?
- Yes.
- You are going to be
with Roxxxy Andrews.
- Alaska tells RuPaul,
"Everything happens
for a reason."
I think it was sabotage.
I thought we were closer
than this.
It pissed me off.
- Dave, you're going
to be with Jinkx Monsoon.
- Hi, Dave.
- You'll have so much fun
with Jinkx.
Jinkx is my biggest
competition right now,
so maybe it would be an
impediment having an older man.
Steve, you're going
to be with Coco.
- So big and strong.
- Aaron, you're going
to be with lady Detox.
- You're beautiful.
- Thank you.
- And, Alaska,
that means you have Mack.
- I think pairing myself
with the tall, pretty one
is probably
a really good strategy.
- Now, ladies,
we're gonna be looking
for a strong family resemblance.
A true expression of your drag.
Attention!
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman...
win!
- So you've never,
ever been in drag before?
- No, I have not.
- Okay.
[laughs]
Who are some of your
diva inspirations?
- Uh...
Judy Garland.
- I can see us doing a Judy/Liza
kind of thing together.
- I knew Judy, by the way.
- You did?
- Yes.
- You knew Judy Garland?
What was she like?
- She was actually really nice.
- That's amazing.
I feel like the luckiest drag
queen in this room right now,
'cause I know these young guys
don't have stories like that.
And look, Detox
is more concerned
about sleeping with her, um...
- I can tell.
- Ha!
- Even though I got paired up
with the oldest vet,
I get to work
with one of the sweetest,
coolest people in the room.
- We have to give you body.
- Okay.
- Stand up for me.
- You can't tell in these pants,
but I have a big butt.
- Do you have a big butt?
That's perfect,
'cause I have a huge ass.
Oh, it is a nice butt.
We're still gonna
make it bigger.
- I got a really hot guy.
Like, ah, Jesus.
He's really sweet, and a total
sissy, and I really like that.
I just want all you bitches
to pay attention really quick.
And let Aaron show you
how it's fucking done.
- Oh, my God,
she's done this before.
- I love it!
- I'm not happy at all.
Izzy is shorter
and he's hairy.
I'm pissed.
- Coming up...
Can we see a little bit
of her walk?
- Yeah.
- Ooh--whoa, whoa.
- I got--I got it.
- Really?
- I think I might have killed
Judy Garland.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
- Today, we have to make over
our gay vet.
Have you ever worn Leg Avenue?
- [laughs]
No.
- And we have to do a complete
family resemblance runway look.
Is that the Michael Levine
fabric?
Oh, my God,
we're gonna be gorgeous.
[chuckles]
- Give me a little runway.
Oh, fuck.
- Oh, my God, hold on.
I got to see this.
You look like Jennifer Lopez
as Jesus.
[laughs]
- I got another thing comin'
for y'all.
I have a fuel under my ass.
He's going to be
drop-dead gorgeous.
- Get naked.
Let's try this on you.
I'm having a difficult time
working with my partner
because he's fucking beautiful.
[whistles]
So do you have a boyfriend
or anything?
- No.
- Thank you, gay God.
I just got lady wood
for you walking.
- If Detox doesn't
win this challenge,
she'll have no one
to blame but herself.
Here, put on these.
- Okay.
You got to understand
that bending over
can be a trip sometimes.
I have a medical condition.
In fact, I fell down
the other day.
- Dave's kind of top-heavy,
and it makes it very hard
for him to walk around.
Hold my hand.
Focus on walking on your toes
a little bit more.
It's a distinct possibility
I'm going to be
in the bottom two tomorrow.
Okay.
- Ooh--whoa, whoa.
- I got--I got it.
- You okay?
This big, buff man
in camouflage pants
and a pair of heels...
I never thought I'd be putting
a man's breasts on.
- [laughs]
- Oh, God, Steve,
we've got to pull this off.
'cause if I'm in the bottom two,
this may be my last supper.
- You haven't?
- Uh-uh.
- Well, how'd you
get yours, then?
- My friend made them for me.
- Oh.
- I've seen
a YouTube video of it.
All I have is a pair of scissors
and this really hard foam,
and so I'm just hoping
they'll look passable.
What inspired you to, like,
get into the military?
- I grew up in foster care,
and my 18th birthday,
my foster mom was like,
"You have to find a place
to live.
I'll give you a week."
and so I joined the military,
and I got out of it structure,
discipline...
- Wow.
- And now I'm ready
to be out on my own.
- It shows a great
amount of wisdom.
He said, "My life needs order
that I never got."
It's very admirable.
All right, now remember,
you're a woman, not a man.
Walk softly.
Mack is walking
like a Mack truck driver.
Ladies take soft steps.
Any advantage I thought I had
because of Mack's appearance
completely vanishes
because of the way
that he is holding himself.
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi, Ru.
- Oh, dear, I see
lots of titties up in here.
Hello, Jinkx and Dave.
- Hello.
- Hi, Ru.
- How's it going over here?
- He and I decided we're going
to do a Judy and Liza tribute.
- Oh, my goodness.
- And I've got the backstory.
- Tell me about that.
- I think I might have killed
Judy Garland.
[record needle scratch effect]
We were talking
one night at dinner,
and she asked me
about the new sleeping pills
that were out.
I told her about a new one,
and she died of an overdose.
- Dave has got Ru speechless.
How do you respond to, "I think
I killed Judy Garland"?
He's a monsoon, all right.
- Well, you know, Dave, she
worked real hard to get there.
All right, listen,
you kids get back to work,
and I can't wait to see ya.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- All right.
House of Alaska.
Mack has big, old titties,
no makeup,
and your skin is perfect.
- Oh, you haven't seen
my walk yet.
- Well, right, uh...
- Can we see a little bit of it?
- It's a work in progress.
It's hard breaking
the man out of Mack.
- Really?
The Armed Services
pushed it inside of you.
I--that came out wrong.
- [laughs]
- You have a lot of work to do.
You better sissy
that walk, Mack.
- You got it, Ru.
- I'll see you guys later.
Detox and Aaron.
Oh, my goodness,
you are working on it already.
- Hi, Ru.
She's my little baby doll.
The first thing
out of her mouth was,
"I need to put shoes on now,"
and she's been sissying
that walk up and down
this entire workroom.
- Good, good.
- [laughs]
- So, Aaron,
Don't Ask Don't Tell--
how has that
affected your life?
- I've served before and after.
And serving before,
it was tough, because I was,
you know, 22 and living
in the Castro,
and, like, gay, gay, gay.
- Yeah.
- And it was such culture shock
coming back in the closet.
- What's it like now?
- It takes
a little weight off you.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it's nice to be able to,
without fear of repercussion,
just really be that person.
- I'm so happy that
you are here with us,
and that you are out and proud,
and I cannot wait to see you.
- Me too.
- Thank you, Ru.
- See ya.
- Bye.
- The house of Montrese.
- Hi, Ru.
- Now, you've got some
wide hips, there.
Have you done drag before?
- No, never, Ru.
- Never.
- I feel, like,
how do they do that?
I mean, you guys got balls,
seriously.
- Oh, yeah, we do have balls.
- [laughs]
- Steve, now what made you
join the military?
- I always had an issue with
my--with being homosexual.
It was a way for me
to become straight.
I thought I would go in there,
they'll buff you up,
and yell at you.
- When you hear that,
you think about the other guys
that did it too.
Why can't people just let people
be who they are?
- I was young, I was stupid...
- Yeah.
- The Marines did teach me,
you know, how to be a man,
and how to not take things
so seriously.
- A lot like drag.
- Yeah.
- Now, let me tell ya,
Coco needs your help.
She was in the bottom two
last week.
- Ya gotta bring that up, Ru?
Really?
- She's counting on you
to be a fierce queen.
- [laughs]
- All right, kids,
get back to it.
I will see you
on the main stage.
- Bye, Ru.
- Roxxxy and Izzy--now, Izzy,
have you ever done drag before?
- Never.
- Have you ever worn heels
before?
- Never.
- So are you gonna show a little
of the--[clicks tongue]
You know, 'cause that's what
the Andrews are famous for.
Do you have any peanut butter?
- No.
- [sighs]
- What's the biggest challenge,
in this challenge, for you?
- I want to make sure that
whatever I'm making her,
that she is gonna feel
comfortable 100%.
- Well, I'll let you
get back to it, okay?
- Okay.
By no way, shape, or form do I
think I'm done and feeling good.
- All right,
gather round, everybody!
Now, tomorrow on the main stage,
we'll be joined by our
extra-special guest judges,
two men who know
a lot about makeovers.
From What Not To Wear,
Clinton Kelly will be here.
[cheers and applause]
And from The Fashion Police,
George Kotsiopoulos.
[cheers and applause]
Oh, and one more little thing.
In addition to
walking the runway,
each team needs to come up with
a patriotic
color guard presentation.
So raise your flag high
and don't fuck it up.
Coming up...
- Mack is extremely manly.
- Oh!
We don't know what the fuck
we're doing.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
- How do you feel at it?
- I feel alive.
- Our main challenge today
is to make gay veterans
into part of our drag family,
and to come up with a color
guard routine
to present on the runway.
Hmm, hmm, three...
- Oh, fuck.
- We don't know
what the fuck we're doing.
We haven't really
planned anything,
we're kind of making it up
as we go.
Oh!
[laughs]
Closer.
[sighs]
Do you have any ideas?
- Turn, turn, turn.
And turn around.
- Turn around.
- Don't fall, don't fall.
- I won't fall, I'm good.
- Those shoes
are killing you, huh?
Steve is determined to do
his rehearsal in these heels,
but the aches and pains
are all over his face.
Ah!
- Shut up.
- I think as much as Steve
wants to be prepared
for what it takes
to be in these heels...
Take 'em off.
Yeah, just take 'em off.
I don't think
he was ready for this.
- Oh, uh-uh.
- No?
- Oh, no, baby.
I'm gonna fall off of these.
- Are they too high?
- Yeah.
- I don't want you
to hurt yourself.
- I mean, I do have
a medical condition, you know?
- What's that?
- I will be honest with you.
And, uh, I took a medicine, and
it caused me to look like this.
It also wasted the muscles
in my legs.
I just can't hold myself up.
- Okay. We're gonna
find a way to work with it.
- Okay.
- I mean, there's a million
and one things
we can do to overcome this.
And we're a team.
You're not in this alone.
- I'll be right back.
- [whimpers]
Dave is surviving with HIV,
and his body went through
a massive transformation,
and it makes it very hard
for him to walk around,
let alone walk in heels,
but Dave's heart is so in it
that he wants
to give it his all.
We're gonna work with it,
not against you.
- Pop that foam, girl.
Pop that foam.
Hey, how you doin'?
[laughter]
I love it.
And...
Can we do that together, though?
- I'm just scared.
I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared.
- All right.
I don't know what color guard
or flag twirling is.
So let's start
from sword fighting.
- And then like that,
and then what if I took
this one away
and then touched yours?
And then, you pull it back.
You're, like... [groans]
[laughs]
Like you just touched my dick,
or my sword fantasy,
whatever you call it.
- Well.
We're figuring it out
a lot on the fly.
[mimics marching music]
Um...
and then what?
- Dave is using the flag
as a cane,
both for comedic
and practical reasons,
but I choreographed our piece
to be well within
his capability.
Come on, Mama!
Come on!
And give the Judy Garland
a little swagger.
I have been trying to pull away
from camp and schtick
in this competition,
but I would rather him be safe
than try to lay all this
complicated choreography on him.
It's me and my mama!
- [laughs]
- Do one around.
- Uhh!
- Mama,
your skirt's falling down!
- I know.
- Oh, Mama!
Tomorrow, I wanna win
for Dave's sake.
- It is time to become women.
- Let's do this.
- Ready or not, here comes Mama!
- Today's elimination day.
I have a bunch of things
to do with Izzy.
We have to get him shaven.
It's time to get some clippers
and get this hair off of him.
[razor vibrates]
Blah! Uhh!
I hate body hair.
- [laughs]
- Fish, dude.
Let's get this chest.
Izzy turned out to be an angel.
He knows that whatever
he has to do to help us win,
he's gonna do it.
He's definitely being a trooper,
no pun intended.
[laughter]
[spits]
You're the only hairy one here?
That's okay 'cause guess what?
We can get rid of hair.
They can't get rid
of those faces.
- Exactly.
- All makeup, no talent.
- "All makeup, no talent"?
Is that what you're saying,
Coco?
Coco and Steve are throwing
a lot of shade,
but let's see when
the faces come out,
'Cause Coco don't know
how to paint faces.
- She's making you a black girl.
- I am not!
- You are, girl!
- All that makeup on his face!
- [laughs]
- Get the fuck away from me,
Detox.
Shit.
I don't paint
other people's face.
That's not something
you can learn overnight,
and I got a few hours.
- Horchata looks like a cross
between one of the Jackson 5s
and a member from Cats.
- Oh, shit.
I look scary.
- Am I doing this right?
You know I don't know
how to glue down brows.
Sweetie, we're in a competition.
I can't help you
or your manly man.
- But look how pretty he is.
- Tell me what happened
when you were discovered
to be a homosexual
in the service.
- The house that I had
in Washington, D.C.,
we had four of us,
two Marines and two sailors.
We decided we wanted to go
to our favorite gay bar
in full uniform, what we called
"high drag" in those days.
There was a spy.
It got back to the base,
and all four of us
were put on notice that
we were going to be discharged
for being gay.
- He's been through everything
that you could guess
a 67-year-old gay veteran
could have possibly
been through.
- One of the boys ended up
being court-martialed
because, in those days,
it was illegal to be gay,
and he ended up in Leavenworth
ward for a year.
- It's so important
to learn about the struggles
that people like Dave have been
through to get us the rights
that we take for granted.
- So that car accident
that you were in--
- Mm-hmm.
- What happened there?
- I was leaving a gig,
and apparently,
there was this guy who got
kicked out of the bar.
He left his car parked
in the middle of the freeway
with no lights on
and was sleeping in his car.
We just ran into him
going 80 or 90 miles an hour.
My face kind of ricocheted
off the windshield,
and I lost, like,
this part of my forehead.
I severed the main artery
in my head, and...
- Oh, my God.
- Like, almost bled out
in a matter of minutes.
- Jesus Christ.
Did that change anything
about you?
- I didn't leave the house
for, like, two months
because I just felt like
such a Frankenstein.
After the accident,
it was pretty traumatizing
because I was in the hospital
for so long,
and I was really weak.
I was so depressed.
I would go visit drag shows,
and they really kinda
pulled me out of that,
and, were, like,
"Just get back into it, girl.
You look fine, you'll be good."
Getting back into doing drag and
throwing myself into my work
really helped me,
but I still can't
grow eyebrows on this side.
Luckily, I can paint them on.
[snickers]
I just pull it down
and then take the rest
of your weed whacker
and pull it all the way back.
- That's not gonna hurt?
- No, just try it.
- [laughs]
- Now, what do you tape it to?
- You pull the tape
up to your butt.
[tape ripping]
It's time for Steve to tuck,
and this is a process.
A very long process.
How the fuck do you do this?
The bucket's slipping out.
- Do I have to come back there
and put it up for you?
'Cause I will.
- Oh, looks like camel toe.
- Camel toe is in this season.
[chuckling]
- [whistles]
Can't walk in it.
- Coming up...
- You were making
major missteps.
- And that was not glamorous.
It was not elegant.
It was not chic.
- Just show us a smile
from time to time.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
all: ♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
- Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
for those about
to frock, we salute you.
- Ahoy!
- The great Santino.
- You look gorgeous, Ru.
- Thank you.
From What Not To Wear,
Clinton Kelly!
Guess what I'm not wearing.
[laughter]
Makeup.
It's true.
- Au naturel, I love it.
- And, from The Fashion Police,
George Katsiopoulos.
Now, are you excited to be here?
- This is more exciting
than the Academy Awards.
Are you kidding me?
- [laughs]
- I love this show!
- So happy to have you here.
This week, we challenged our
queens to earn their stripes
by transforming gay veterans
into members
of their drag family.
Gentlemen, start your engines
and may the best woman win.
- Immediately, I drop a flag.
Bam!
Fuck.
- Our flag routine is fun,
goofy, and weird, just like me.
- Horchata is turning it out.
She's smiling.
She's buckin'.
She's doing her thing.
- Every time I looked over
at Isabella,
she was doing exactly
what she needed to do.
Could not have gone any better.
I think we might
pull through tonight.
- Commence shakedown.
- Ladies, forward march.
From the house of Monsoon,
Jinkx and Fortuna.
- Judy looks more like Liza
these days.
- Yes!
- We are serving mama
and gypsy realness.
I think we really hit the nail
on the head with this one.
Meet me in the middle
and give 'em a little hip!
Here we go, and, oh!
You got it!
[laughter]
Now, that's enter-taint-ment.
The house of Andrews,
Roxxxy and Isabella.
- That's the Andrews sisters.
- Uh-huh.
- Bam!
- The look on Izzy's face--
she is feeling it.
She is loving it.
Yeah, bitches, get into it.
- The missing Kardashian
sisters.
- Big booties
must run in the family.
- Yeah.
- The house of Alaska
featuring
Alaska and Nebraska,
cat burglars.
- Okay, that's more
like Miss Nebraska
'cause she is a beauty queen.
- Yes.
- We're feeling good.
We're skipping down the runway.
I'm very proud
of little Nebraska.
- I didn't know Patty Hearst
had daughters.
- Uh-huh.
[laughter]
- The house of Detox:
Detox and Bethadone,
hunting for red October.
- Bethadone and I are stomping
it out and being playful,
and you can just tell that
he's living for himself,
which is the purpose
of this whole challenge.
- America the booty-ful.
Lucky for these girls,
it's fleet week.
The house of Montrese!
Coco and Horchata Montrese.
Mm, I'm thirsty.
- Horchata's giving you nothing
but pure showgirl,
and I'm giving you
nothing but red carpet,
Montrese-style.
- Red sky at night,
sailor's delight.
- Is that your boa, or are you
just ready to flock me?
- [laughs]
Coming up...
- The boots are just
unforgivable.
I hate them.
- Those pads, it looks like
there's hams in there.
- You seem very upset.
- It was a shit show.
- [laughs]
Welcome, ladies!
First up, the house of Monsoon,
Jinkx and Fortuna.
Dave, let's take a look
at your before.
And look at you now.
- As complicated
as your choreography was,
you were both in sync
with one another,
and it wasn't overly complicated
where you were dropping things
or making major missteps.
- You did have
a very difficult task
dressing someone in their 60s,
and I actually wouldn't change
anything about the styling.
I think you guys look
incredible.
- Well, Dave, I'm honored
to have you here,
especially since you're one of
the queens from back in the day.
- I thought you were gonna say
"The oldest."
- [laughs]
- That would be Michelle.
[laughter]
- Up next:
The house of Andrews,
Roxxxy and Isabella.
Now, this is Izzy before,
and this is Isabella.
So how do you feel, Izzy?
- I feel like I could give
Santino a mustache ride.
- [shouts]
- Come on with it!
- One thing about
the house of Andrews:
We're hos, miss thang, and this
one came right into it.
- You are absolutely gorgeous.
I love that you did
the traditional Andrews ass,
and you really look like
family members.
- Wow.
- You were in perfect unison
for most of the routine,
which was really fun,
and, Isabella,
that booty shake was seriously
grade A.
I mean,
I could not get over that.
- Next up,
from the house of Alaska,
Alaska, the 49th state,
and Nebraska, the 37th state.
- Ohh.
- Mack, let's take a look
at your before picture,
and let's take
a look at you now.
Ooh, ooh!
Nebraska, tell me about
the challenge.
What was the hardest part?
- I was a little bit
uncomfortable at the beginning,
and as soon as she
brought out the weapons
and I was in the gear,
I was ready for battle.
- Stop using sex
as a weapon, Nebraska.
- [laughs]
- Well, didn't you get
the pretty pearl?
I mean, Nebraska came out,
and I was, like, "Whoa!"
The flag routine
didn't really come off
the way you wanted it to.
I think there were things
out of sync
and falling apart
here and there.
- Those hip pads, I mean,
it looks like there's
hams in there.
- You had, like,
the perfect model to work with,
and it just makes me sad
to see lumpy padding,
and the boots
are just unforgivable.
I just hate--I hate them.
- All right.
Next up: The house of Detox,
Detox and Bethadone.
- Hello.
- This is Aaron before,
and look at you now.
So, Bethadone, what was tougher:
Basic training
or getting up into drag?
- I'm definitely gonna
have to say basic training...
[laughter]
But this definitely wasn't easy.
- I'm interested in why Detox
put that bow in the front
after we read Roxxxy
down for that.
- Oh, 'cause I don't
pay attention to Roxy.
[laughter]
- But you should
pay attention to critiques.
- That performance,
you dropped the flag.
They got twisted up.
God, it was just--
- It was a shit show.
- Bethadone looked like
she was having a lot of fun.
She was really smiling,
and you didn't seem to be
having as much fun.
Just show us a smile
from time to time.
- All right, next up:
The house of Montrese,
Coco and Horchata.
Now, this is Steve before,
and look at you now.
Steve, what was the hardest part
of it for you?
- The heels and the makeup.
- Good, then, it's working.
- [chuckles]
- You guys really went
for, like, the Olympics here
with your flag routines.
It's not necessary.
- I can tell
that you've never done
someone else's hair and makeup.
There's subtle blending
and highlighting
that you didn't do.
- And the irregular hem makes
it seem like you made a gown
for yourself and you gave
your sister the scraps
that were kind of left over.
- You seem very upset.
- It seems like every week,
I'm letting you down,
letting you down,
letting you down.
- Listen, it's part of the game
of being criticized by judges.
I've been in front of any kind
of critic you can imagine.
Have fun with it.
As an entertainer, you know
that if you're not having fun,
the audience doesn't have fun.
You just gotta remember that.
I'm so proud that we got
to share this with these fellas
from the military
and showing them
what they were fighting for.
They don't tell them that
when they enroll,
that you're fighting for our
freedom to dress up in drags.
This is a fabulous country!
And I'm so proud, right now,
to be an American citizen.
All right, a little ki-ki
on the stage.
- Ohh!
- Thank you, ladies,
and thank you, veterans.
Now, while you untuck in
the Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now, just between us
civilians, what do you think?
Jinkx Monsoon and Fortuna.
- When she and Fortuna came out
with their flag routine,
I thought, "Jinkx is going
to be in the bottom,"
but I have to tell you,
she made up for it and then some
with her mother-daughter Gypsy
Rose Lee and Mama routine.
- My only criticism would be
that Dave is 67,
but Fortuna looks
a little bit older than that.
- The house of Andrews,
Roxxxy and Isabella.
- It wasn't too complicated,
but what they did do,
it was well practiced,
well rehearsed.
Roxy did a bang-up job.
- Well, I love the Mini-Me vibe
that they were giving out,
and oh, my God,
they should just win
on that padding alone
because I didn't even know
it was padding.
It was amazing.
- What did you think of house
of Alaska and Nebraska?
- I think Alaska
needs to work on her craft.
That transformation
was really weak
compared to
what she had to work with.
- I was not as compelled
by Alaska
as I was by Nebraska,
and I think that's a problem.
- Moving on to the house
of Detox and Bethadone.
- The complicated flag twirling
was a mess, seriously.
- They look like deranged
Raggedy Ann dolls,
and I'm just questioning
whether or not
there's a taste level there.
- Coco and Horchata Montrese.
- Poor Horchata.
I mean, poor, poor Horchata.
- That was not glamorous.
It was not elegant.
It was not chic.
You know, I'm thinking Coco
might need to go
back to beauty school.
- The flag show was a disaster,
and she would never
let herself go out
with a busted-up face like that.
- Never, ever.
- No?
- Please.
- It was like Frida Kahlo.
It was a giant eyebrow
walking down the stage.
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back the girls.
[laughs]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Jinkx Monsoon, your Liza
and Judy-inspired drag
took us over the rainbow.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- I'm safe.
- Roxxxy Andrews, you set out
to turn a salty seaman
into your sexy sister.
Mission accomplished.
Condragulations, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
[applause]
- Girl, you won!
- You and your drag sister have
each won a shopping spree
at American Apparel.
Izzy can decide
if he wants to shop
in the men's
or the women's department.
- Female.
- Gah!
This is my second win.
Finally.
- Coco Montrese.
Tonight, you didn't give us
what we were thirsty for.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- Oy.
- [speaks Spanish]
- For the fourth time,
doesn't look too good.
- Alaska, your cross-country
crime spree
didn't steal the show.
Detox, your Marine makeover
hit a snafu.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Alaska, you may join
the other girls.
- Thank you.
- Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip-synch performance
of (it takes) Two
by Seduction featuring
Michelle Visage.
Ladies, this is your
last chance to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lip-synch
for your life.
- On a scale of one to ten,
my lip-synching
is probably a 25.
- Ready, set, go.
Let's do this.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, ♪
♪ It takes two to make ♪
♪ A thing go right ♪
♪ It takes two ♪
♪ To make it out of sight ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ From the start ♪
♪ It's plain to see ♪
- I'm giving it my all.
This is Michelle Visage's song,
and I'm gon' wear it out
just for her.
- ♪ You know that ♪
♪ It's a shame ♪
♪ But I am here ♪
♪ To ease your pain ♪
♪ Because I know, together ♪
♪ We can really turn ♪
♪ This mother out ♪
♪ Whoo-hoo ♪
♪ Don't you know that ♪
♪ It takes two ♪
♪ To make a thing go right ♪
♪ To make it out of sight ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
- I pull out all these
old-school dance moves,
and I'm just sitting there
whopping it out
and doing the cabbage patch
and having a good time.
- ♪ It takes two to make ♪
♪ A thing go right ♪
♪ It takes two ♪
♪ Ah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It takes two, it takes two ♪
♪ Whoa oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ It takes two ♪
♪ Me and you ♪
♪ It takes two to make it ♪
♪ Out of sight ♪
♪ My baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ My baby, baby ♪
- Yes!
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies, I've made my decision.
Detox, shante, you stay.
You may join the other girls.
- I'm sorry.
- Coco Montrese,
I want you to hear this.
You never let me down,
and I am cuckoo for Coco.
Now sashay away.
- [crying]
Thank you.
[whispers]
- Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
- This is one of the most
amazing experiences of my life.
I did my best.
I think Alyssa and I can put
the past behind us.
I gained a lot of closure, which
I probably would have never got
if it wasn't for RuPaul,
so I'm very happy.
- My fab four.
Condragulations.
Victory is yours!
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen.
- All right,
now let the music play.