- Previously on
Rupaul's Drag Race...
- Coco Montrese.
- Alyssa Edwards.
- We haven't spoken
in two years.
The pageant
tore our friendship apart.
- Alyssa and I will have
our moment later together,
'cause we need a moment.
- You'll be lip-synching
to the spoken word, darling.
- I think Lineysha
is going to struggle the most
because of the language barrier.
- This is not
Rupaul's Best Friend Race.
- No [bleep], Sherlock.
I'm not focused, because I have
so much going on in my head.
[choked up]
I'm not just a drag queen.
I'm a transgendered woman.
- One of you really
lip-smacked the competition.
Lineysha Sparx.
- [laughs]
- Monica Beverly Hillz...
Shante, you stay.
Serena Chacha...
sashay away.
[footsteps approach]
- [sighs]
- Chacha, adios, darling.
- We're back in the workroom,
and Serena went home.
Came a mess.
Left a mess.
- Ooh!
[laughter]
- As you can tell,
I am just very upset.
[laughs]
- "Keep hearing light."
What does that mean?
- "Bearing light."
- Oh.
- Oh, okay.
'Cause the only thing I was
hearing was "Sashay away."
[laughter]
- Well, on that note.
[sighs]
I'm happy I survived
the lip-synch.
And I let out a huge secret.
It really took a toll today,
and I just felt like,
you know what?
I can't hold
that secret no more.
- Yeah, seriously.
- Be proud.
- We all love you.
- We love you.
- So, speaking of secrets,
what the hell is going on
with you and Coco?
- Look, at the end of the day,
this, right here, I won.
- Mm.
- But who's in the picture?
- Miss Coco.
- I think you should ask Coco.
- I want to know the T
on what happened
between you and Alyssa...
- Oh, God.
- Because this has been
going on for so long.
- They crowned her
that night, you know?
And things happen, and...
obligations weren't fulfilled.
And it put us in a situation
where our friendship
was on the line.
- 'Cause you took her spot.
- Legally, I had to do that.
- Every story has two sides.
- With all the controversy
at Miss Gay America,
this is a personal vendetta
for myself.
I think it's time for me
to get this off my chest.
- The winner of
Rupaul's Drag Race
receives a sickening supply
of Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip
courtesy of alandchuck.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And tonight,
extra special guest judges
Paulina Porizkova and Coco.
- Whoo!
- Whoo.
- Yay!
- [together]
Rolaskatox.
- It's a new day.
I'm walking into the workroom,
wondering what the hell
is about to happen.
No more groups.
- No.
- No more groups.
[siren blares]
- Ooh, girl!
You've got shemail.
Hey, my little ladyboys.
all: Hey.
- Growing up is so overrated,
and America's next
drag superstar
needs to really embrace
her inner child
if she's gonna become one fierce
mother-tucker.
This message was brought to you
by the letter T.
- Oh, my God.
- Yes.
- Oh.
- Hello, hello, hello.
[overlapping greetings]
Do you know what time it is?
all: No.
- It's time for the junior
drag superstar pageant!
- Oh!
[all exclaiming]
- Instantly, I'm thinking,
"A pageant?"
This is my gig, and I've been
quite successful at it.
- But, ladies, you won't be
the contestants.
You need to turn these boy toys
into cutie patooties.
[giggles]
[laughter]
Pick a partner.
- I looked to the left and said,
"Oh, hell no.
I'm not working with Alyssa."
- You've got 15 minutes.
The team with the most sickening
painted baby will win.
Ready, set, drag the children.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- You know, we're all
considered kai kai now.
We have daughters
with another queen.
- Our girl's gonna win
grand supreme.
You just watch.
- Little flippers.
- [laughs]
- Don't mess it up,
or you won't get no go-go juice.
I immediately
turn into pageant mom.
Now, I never could make it
in the pageant scene
when I was a girl, so you're
so lucky you get to do this.
- Time's up.
Now, may I present the drag
superstars of tomorrow.
First up,
Roxxxy Andrews and Detox.
- Hi, I'm Rachel Zoe,
and this is our daughter,
Vaxeline Androxxx Zoe.
She just wants to go to Paris
every weekend and see the shows,
dressed in
all the finest couture.
And because I'm Rachel Zoe,
we allow that.
- [laughs]
- She's kind of a big deal.
[camera shutter snaps]
- I'd like to present
little Tina Lou Devereaux.
She wants to make makeup
and fashionable accessories
more accessible to young girls,
because it is never too young
to start upholding
the "Amurrican" ideal
of "femininitity".
[laughter]
- I couldn't have
said it better myself.
- Watermelon is decked out
in glitz,
glamour, and a flipper
she's able to grow into
for the years to come.
She's a world champion
watermelon seed spitter.
- [laughs]
- I present to you
our very own Savannah Lee.
She is a former Miss Mesquite,
Little Miss America.
Her platform in life
is world peace for all.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
[applause]
- Now that's a modern family.
- I'd like everyone to meet
Lil' Pound Cake.
Her catchphrase is,
"You're not my real dad,
and you never will be."
- [laughing]
- Lil' Pound Cake
enjoys riding dirty
and being a straight-up
mother [bleep] [bleep] pig.
[laughter]
- [cackling]
- Monica and I have our
daughter, Patty Park Place.
She's won several pageants,
and unlike Savannah, she's
completed all of her reigns.
- Oh!
- Coco Montrese decides
to throw a little bit of shade
to be real cute.
I don't get cute.
I get drop-dead gorgeous.
[whispers] Shade.
- So, the miss junior
drag superstar is...
Lil' Pound Cake.
- Oh!
- All hail Lil' Pound Cake.
[camera shutter snaps]
Now, for this week's
main challenge,
you'll be creating lovable,
eccentric characters
for your own
kidster television shows.
[all exclaiming]
- Children's TV?
I'm like, "What the
mother [bleep] hell?"
- Your target audience
is the young
and the young at heart,
so your program
should be both entertaining
and "edumacational."
You'll be working in two groups.
Lineysha and Alaska, since
you won the mini-challenge,
you'll be team captains.
Lineysha, you pick first.
- Honey.
- Toxie.
- Coco Montrese.
- Hey, girl.
- Roxxx-an.
- Rolaskatox!
both: Rolaskatox!
[laughter]
- Jinkx.
- Vivienne.
- [nasal voice]
Ivy Winterrr.
[laughs]
[nasal voice]
Winterrrs.
- "Montica".
- Yay.
- All right, Lineysha.
Who do you choose next?
- [whispers indistinctly]
We were all in Lineysha's ear
saying, "Don't pick Alyssa."
- Jade.
- [whispers] Thank God.
- So Alyssa will go
to Alaska's team.
- Darling.
- I might have been picked last,
but honestly,
I ended up on the team
that I wanted to be on.
The queens of the competition.
- Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
- I have a idea.
Why you can't make,
like, a muppet,
and take talking like,
"la la la la," and--
- Ohh.
- Ventriloquist?
- Ventriloquist, so--
- Yes, you,
and she's the little girl.
- Oh,
like a ventriloquist dummy.
- Girl, they 'bout to try
to send me home.
In the show in Vegas,
I'm the star.
So when you give me a role
like a ventriloquist doll...
- So what are some things
that we can talk about?
Um...
- Um...
- Now is the hard part.
We have to actually
come up with the material.
I'm trying to find out--figure
out how to make it funny.
- This is really, really hard.
- At some point,
I think Coco got frustrated
and kind of walked off.
- I want to wear my hair up.
I'll be glad when
the group challenges are over.
- I'm kind of panicking.
How are we gonna pull this off?
- Coming up...
It never occurred to me that
you'd actually be out of drag.
- I'm in drag, Ru.
- But you're in a male drag.
- I heard that you went around
everywhere and badmouthed me.
- [bleep] you, Alyssa.
- [laughing]
- So our challenge
is to put together
a children's television show
which is full of sneaky little
dirty double-entendres.
Our word of the day is "box."
This is the challenge
that I've been waiting for.
Finally we get to act
and we get to write
and we get to create.
I'm gonna be a farmer.
And we can each be,
like, a barnyard animal.
- I'll be the chicken lady.
- And you should be, like,
Venus Xtravaganza.
You should be her.
"Oh, you wanna talk about..."
both: "Reading, dahling."
- You can just be Uncle Dick
the cross-dresser.
- Be, like,
real butch about it.
[rough voice]
Look at how pretty I am.
And not fishy.
- Really?
The cross-dressing uncle?
Girl, they're pulling the patch.
Can't be bothered.
Do you think
it would be more funny,
'cause she's fishier than me,
if she was the Uncle Dick?
- I like you
as a cross-dresser.
I'm a little worried about
Alyssa because she's very much
into, "Oh,
Alyssa has to look this way,
and Alyssa
has to look that way."
And I hope that doesn't
hold us back.
- Hello, hello, hello.
[all shouting greetings]
Did I catch you boys
playing dress-up?
- Uh-huh.
- Well, hello, team Alaska.
all: Hi, Ru.
- How's it going over here?
- It's going.
- Who's gonna be your host?
- Hi.
- Now, what character
are you doing?
- Buffalo Bill.
- Oh, okay.
- And, um, it's a barnyard,
and our show is called something
like Barnyard Boogers.
- [laughs]
So who's doing
the word of the day?
- That's me.
- What is the word of the day?
- Box.
- Box?
- B-o-x.
- Of course.
And it's just now coming to me
how you can make--
- A lot of things
come in my box.
- [laughs] Yes, a lot of things
could come in your box, exactly.
[laughter]
Now, what are you kids doing?
- She's teaching the social
lesson of the day.
- Don't be throwing no shade.
- And how do you get kids
to not throw shade?
Well, you know,
the thing about these shows,
especially, like,
Pee-wee's Playhouse,
is that a lot
of what you're doing here
has a subversive twist to it.
Do you have a message
that you're trying to convey
to the children?
- Down with communism.
[laughter]
- Okay.
You guys have
a lot of work to do,
and I'm gonna let you
get back to it, okay?
- Thank you, Ru.
- All right, I'll see you later.
- Hey, team Lineysha.
all: Hi.
- So tell me about your
kidster show.
Who's gonna do your "how to"
segment?
- Lineysha and myself.
- Oh, really?
- We are making banana splits.
- In two languages.
- What are you gonna do to
really send it over the top?
- It's gonna be funny.
[laughs]
- All right.
Are you the host?
- Yes, Lineysha asked me
to be the host.
- And which--
what part of the challenge
have you been assigned?
- Actually, Coco and I
are both doing
the social lesson
for the day.
- Which is what?
- It's "Always tell the T."
- Of course.
- T.T. and Tiny.
T.T.'s always teaching Tiny
to tell the T.
- Right.
Are you gonna be able
to bring the funny, though?
- I think we're gonna
focus more on quality
and not quantity.
- All right.
Well, you kids have a lot
to work with.
You've got a lot to do.
So I'm gonna let you
get back to it, okay?
- All right. Thanks, Ru.
- All right, turn it out.
- Thank you, Ru.
- We'll just have to show Ru
that we all can be funny.
- Look, do you like that look?
- You look like Willam.
- [laughs]
- Hello, ladies.
- Hi, Rupaul.
We're right about to shoot
our TV show for kids,
and I'm feeling very excited,
because I really feel like
we're gonna nail it.
- It's funny, 'cause when
we talked in the workroom,
and you said Buffalo Bill,
it never occurred to me
that you'd actually
be out of drag.
- I'm in drag, Ru.
- But you're in a male drag.
That's an interesting choice.
- Here we go.
We're going to get read
before we even start?
Two thumbs down.
- All right, Michelle and I
are here to direct you.
So show us what you got.
Action.
- Look, everybody.
It's clucky the cock!
- [clucking]
It's our secret word of the day.
You want to hear what it is?
It's "box"!
- Whoa!
- [laughs]
- Cut.
Clucky, you're delivering
your lines to Buffalo Bill.
You've got to play
more to the camera.
Action.
- So many things
fit inside my box.
- [laughing]
- This is a petite box.
I don't think it's Michelle's.
- [guffaws]
- [squawking]
Boxes!
- [lisping]
I am so excited to be here!
I'm ready to toss
your salad, Anita.
First thing you want to do
is clean your lettuce.
- I like a cheesy salad.
- Cut. Vivienne...
- Yeah?
- If you can bring your energy
up to meet Roxxxy's--
- Okay.
- It feels like you're in
two different sketches.
- You get lost.
- [flat] Say, let's go get our
other friends to toss our salad.
- Moving on.
- It's real sunny up here,
but I do like
a little bit of shade.
- Can't you see
I'm trying to get some sun?
Sunlight on the skin...
Boom. I blank.
- Cut.
- Can't you see I'm trying
to get some sun on this skin?
Sunlight is, uh--
- Cut.
- Can't you see I'm trying
to get some sun?
Sunlight on the skin--
[bleep].
I'm, like, totally [bleep]
my [bleep] bathing suit.
And that's not cute.
- Monica, do you want to look
at the lines again?
- Yeah, they're right here.
- Oh, they are.
- And you're not reading it?
- All right, ladies.
Fantastic.
- When you're team captain,
if the whole thing
goes like a train wreck,
then it's you
who has to pay for it.
Ugh.
- Coming up...
- A nice, plump banana.
- En Espanol, guineo.
- Lineysha just literally
translated it.
- And this is my little friend.
Coco doesn't know
what her lines are.
- Is that it?
[laughing]
- We're walking on set to shoot
our children's television show.
- And they are all in drag.
- Funny how that works
on Rupaul's Drag Race.
- Uh-huh.
- Comedy's kind of my thing,
so I'm really excited
to really shine.
- All right,
let's see your big opening.
- Are you guys excited
for today's episode?
The word of the day is...
"blow."
- Jinkx revealed my word, blow.
It kind of threw me off.
I had a speech ready,
and everything rhymed,
so I just had to scramble
and just kind of
come up with something quick.
If you think of blow,
I think of bubbles.
- Oh, look at all those bubbles
you're blowing!
- Blow.
[giggles]
- Cut.
Jade, it took you a little bit
longer to land the lines.
Get to the point
a little faster.
- Little aggravated.
- Action.
- Now, my favorite treat
is the banana split.
And the ingredients are a nice,
plump banana.
- En Espanol, guineo.
- Lineysha is not really
bringing the Latin flavor
that I thought
she was going to bring.
- Go ahead and cut that in half.
- En Espanol,
cortalo por la mitad.
- She just literally
translated it.
- Cherries.
- All right, moving on.
- Hello, everyone.
I'm T.T., and this
is my little friend...
we haven't even practiced.
Coco doesn't know
what her lines are.
- Jessica.
- All right, cut.
- Your timing is too slow.
You need to pick it up.
Coco, you need to be on it.
- Ready, and action.
- What's the T?
Why do they really
call you Tiny?
- 'Cause I'm small.
Yeah.
I'm a ventriloquist doll.
I don't know if I'm supposed
to look at the camera,
look away from the camera.
- Coco, think more Pinocchio
and less the puppet from Saw.
- Do you have something
that you'd like to say?
- Is that it?
- That's it.
- All right.
Do you have any notes?
- Nope.
- Okay, that's a wrap.
all: Rolaskatox.
- It's elimination day, and
today's theme for the runway
is "think pink".
Jinkx.
- Mm-hmm?
- Are you gonna
add that hair into that hair?
- Yeah.
My grandma got me this wig
when I was, like, 17.
- So your grandma
was buying you wigs, girl?
- My mom wasn't really into it.
- Uh-huh.
- But my grandma and I
would be getting me in drag,
and then I'd go out to the club.
She'd let me be
who I wanted to be, you know?
My grandma made it possible
for me to do drag
at a very early age.
And that's when I really started
coming alive.
She helped set up my life
to put me where I am today.
So it has a lot of sentimental
value to me.
- I feel so mentally drained
right now.
I'm trying to finish my costume,
and this whole Alyssa thing,
it's still bothering me.
We competed at Miss Gay America
together.
- Huh?
- They crowned her.
I ended up having
to take over the title.
We haven't talked in two years.
- Coco, if you want to come talk
to me, you can talk to me,
but you don't have to read me
over there, though.
- I'm not reading you.
I'm not saying
anything about you.
I've got to get this
off my back.
This needs to be done.
Can I talk to you, like,
five minutes, just me and you?
- Oh, [bleep], this is gonna get
[bleep] interesting.
Let me get some popcorn.
- It was pure hell.
- Okay.
- How would you feel
if you're standing onstage
with a crown on your head,
singing your song,
and someone yells out,
"You ain't the real
Miss America anyway!"
I just smile and wave.
In the inside, I am torn.
I almost lost my relationship
because of that whole thing.
That whole thing
turned my world upside-down.
- Well, I lost
my whole reputation
I'd worked ten years for.
[chuckles]
He didn't win Miss Gay America.
I did.
So he wasn't the one embarrassed
in front of the whole community.
I was. I'm the very first
to get dethroned.
Nobody gets dethroned.
I'm not a drug addict.
I'm not an alcoholic.
I'm a teacher.
I'm a mentor. I'm a leader.
But, Coco, I heard
that you went around everywhere
and badmouthed me, saying
I couldn't fulfill my reign.
You got on your face--hold on.
Let me finish.
But, see, you're doing all that,
and you're not even
being fair to me.
- I am being fair to you.
I'm listening to you.
- Girl, you are saying, "I'm on
the beach drinking a margarita.
I'm the one with the crown.
I'm the one."
- I don't--I--
- Why did you write
on your Facebook,
"Alyssa shouldn't have won
in the first place"?
Do you feel like
that was a hit below the belt?
- [crying] I laid in bed next
to my husband, and, like, God--
he's like,
"What is wrong with you?"
And I can't--I couldn't take it.
And--
- And then the tears come out.
Coco is doing what he does best.
He's making it seem like
he's the victim.
He's always the victim.
And the Academy Award goes to...
- [bleep] you, Alyssa.
- I gave him the benefit of
the doubt and got nothing back.
- This whole thing
was not resolved.
I'm done with that situation.
I got to get ready
for the runway.
- [laughing]
Welcome to the main stage of
Rupaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
won't you be my neighbor?
- Always, my little lemon drop.
- [laughs]
Santino Rice.
- I am ready to school
these children.
- I look at her here,
and I see seductive.
I look at her hair,
and I see wicked beauty.
Paulina Porizkova.
- I am so glad to be here.
I've been trying to get on your
damn show for five years now.
[laughter]
- Mrs. T's in the house.
Coco.
Rupaul loves Coco too.
- I love Rupaul.
- [laughs]
This week,
our queens were challenged
to create breakout characters
in their own
kidster television shows.
And tonight, they're dressed
to tickle you pink.
- Whoo.
- Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Coming up...
- You committed the number one
crime in showbiz--
you bored me.
- [laughing]
First up, the 49th state,
Alaska.
So pink mafia.
- I look like a ghost
from the Civil War.
A McQueen fashion show.
- She bleeds pink.
- She's a sex pistol.
- Monica Beverly Hillz.
Someone caught the bouquet.
- I'm feeling extra fishy.
My nails are right.
My hair's tight.
I'm just giving it.
- This is very
Singapore Airlines.
- Come fly with me.
- Alyssa Edwards.
- I want that outfit.
- I am channeling
my Little Miss Perfect gig.
It's the deal. It's the ish.
- Madonna reborn again.
- Yes.
- Vivienne Pinay.
- Hold me closer, tiny dancer.
[laughter]
- I'm feeling cute,
prissy, and girly.
And the judges
are really eating it up.
- Ooh.
- I think I just saw
her pink slip.
[laughter]
Next up, Detox.
- This is
Playboy: The Victorian Years.
- My tits are bouncing
everywhere.
I mean, I have a great body,
so why not show it off?
- Okay, no kidding,
I have this outfit.
- [laughs]
- She is a hot mesh.
Roxxxy Andrews.
- Bam.
- Pink Panther on the runway.
- The dress is flowing.
I look drop-dead gorgeous.
- It's a mullet dress!
- [laughs]
- Uh-huh.
- Business in the front,
party in the back.
- Lineysha Sparx.
Sell the garment, honey.
- I feel so fierce, flawless,
like a top model.
- Looks like Cinderella's
got a hot date.
Jinkx Monsoon.
- Ooh, la, la.
- Oh, Dangerous Liaisons.
- I am flouncing
down the runway
with my snuff box,
let them eat all this cake,
bitches.
- Marie Aqua Net.
[laughter]
- Coco Montrese.
- Shirley Temple Black?
- Why it got to be black?
- I am giving you
your baby doll fish.
I look so cute.
- I didn't know
she was into bears.
[laughter]
[nasal voice]
Ivy Winterrrs.
- Where is Crystal Conner
when you need her?
- Yes.
- I'm strutting
like a Vegas showgirl.
I feel like
a beautiful flamingo.
- You can just stick her
in somebody's front lawn.
[laughter]
- Honey Mahogany.
- She just jumped out of bed
and grabbed the duvet cover.
- Very Bed Bath and Beyonce.
- [laughs]
- I am feeling really strong,
pummeling the runway.
- That face is Iman...
- Yes.
- But that walk
is pure pissed off.
[laughter]
- Jade Jolie.
- Work it.
- Very Girls Next Door
Holly Madison.
- I'm feeling so pretty in pink.
I'm serving the judges
pure fish, hunty.
- [laughs]
- Barbie girl in a Barbie world.
- Life in plastic,
it's fantastic.
- Welcome, ladies.
Let's take a look
at your kidster TV shows.
First up, Barnyard Buddies.
[cow moos, cow bell clanks]
- Hi, everybody!
I'm Buffalo Bill.
Let's meet
some of my amazing friends.
- [clucks]
- Look, everybody!
It's clucky the cock!
- [clucking]
Hi, kids!
- Now, I heard
you're sitting on a secret.
- It's our
secret word of the day.
Shh.
It's "box"!
- Whoa!
[laughter]
- Can I borrow your horse?
- Yeah, sure, clucky.
- Let's try to cram it
in the box!
- Cram it in! Yeah!
- Your horse won't fit
in the box!
[kids giggling]
Your horse is just too big
for my pink box!
[kids laughing]
- Look, everybody.
It's Anita Bum!
- Today we're gonna learn
how to toss salad
with my good friend,
Tasha Salad.
- [lisping] I'm so excited
to be here today.
Well, let's get started.
First thing you want to do
is clean your lettuce.
- Now, is it harmful
to toss a dirty salad?
- Some people are into that.
- Instead of using
the uncut carrots,
can we use the cut carrots?
- Yes. What you want to do is
peel the skin back.
Cut carrots always seem
to be cleaner. Okay?
We're tossing salads one person
at a time across America.
[kids cheer]
- What's up, Fanny?
- Today I'm going to be...
teaching a social lesson.
Don't be throwing no shade.
- Look, it's everyone's
favorite cross-dresser,
Uncle Dick!
- It's real sunny up here.
But I do like
a little bit of shade.
- Don't be throwing
no shade, sir.
Can't you see
I'm trying to get some sun?
Sunlight on your skin
creates vitamin D
and elevates the mood, so...
all: Don't be shady.
Be a lady.
- Bye-bye, everybody!
- [clucks]
- Bye!
[laughter and applause]
- Next up, The Magic Bush.
- My name is Princess Pinklips.
Are you guys excited
for today's episode?
Then let's all bounce.
And now shake your hands
like this.
Ooh, isn't this fun?
Oh!
Today we have a special word of
the day.
The word of the day is...
"blow."
- I always think of bubbles.
Now with bubbles,
you really work it.
Just give it your all.
Kind of like an explosion
of bubbles.
- You're so good at blowing,
Jolly Jade.
- Well, I don't have blue lips
for no reason.
[laughter]
- Next we're going to welcome
Cherry Chocolatina
and Lola the Exploda.
- Now, my favorite treat
is the banana split.
Now, go ahead
and peel the banana.
- Suavemente, vas a pelar
para atras el guineo.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
- Ooh, Miss Lola's
favorite part is the cream.
- [panting]
Help me, girl.
[both panting and murmuring]
- Ooh! Oh!
- Oh!
- Wow.
- It exploded!
- Hello, everyone.
I'm T.T.,
and this is my little friend.
- Tiny.
- That reminds me.
It's time for
our social lesson of the day.
Always tell the T.
- Is my T my truth?
- Yes, your T is your truth.
Do you have something
that you'd like to say?
- Uh-uh.
[awkward silence]
[solo clapping]
- All right.
- I think there were
some weak links,
but I think there were some weak
links in the other team too.
At least this team's
all in drag.
- Coming up...
- You're gonna get lost,
'cause there's some
hungry bitches up here.
- This is Rupaul's Drag Race.
- Not Rupaul's Best Friend
Out Of Drag Race.
[laughing]
Ladies, this week
you worked as teams,
but tonight, you'll be judged
as individuals.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Honey Mahogany.
Ivy Winters.
Jade Jolie.
Alyssa Edwards.
Lineysha Sparx.
Lineysha, you're lucky
you have immunity.
Otherwise,
you'd be in the bottom.
The girls I've called forward,
you are all safe.
You may leave the stage.
Ladies, you represent
the very best
and the very worst of the week.
It's time for
the judges' critiques.
First up, Alaska.
- Hi.
- I love your dust bunny hair,
and I love your
pink splattered blood.
You are such an original.
- Tonight on the runway,
I love it.
I'm just concerned for you
with the boy-drag.
It is a drag show.
You know, I'm paying my $5.
I want to see Alaska.
- Next up,
Monica Beverly Hillz.
- I don't know if
during the Barnyard Bunch
you just got nervous,
but you need to project more,
or you're gonna get lost,
'cause there's some
hungry bitches up here.
- It's inside of you.
I could see that--
that Beverly Hills bitch--
when you walked out.
But then you kind of went
in your shell after a while.
- Thank you, Monica.
Vivienne Pinay.
- Tonight you look really cute.
It's unfortunate that
you created that character
and then that it
kind of fell so flat.
- You committed the number one
crime in showbiz--
you bored me.
- Moving on to...
Detox
- Your costume wasn't
my favorite part of you.
It was really just,
like, your jokes
and your mannerisms
and your volume.
- You rock the stage.
You rock it in acting.
I really like the shake
in the boobies.
Yeah, thank you.
- I know I had a lot of
competition up here tonight...
- Yes, right?
- Up next, Roxxxy Andrews.
- You float above the concrete.
- Thank you.
- I love it.
- Tasha salad was freaking
hilar.
- Jinkx Monsoon.
- Jinkx, you're the North Star
in your little group,
because they would've been lost
without you.
Looking like Glenn Close
in Fatal Attraction
for a kids' show?
I mean, that in itself
is completely demented.
- Coco Montrese.
- This was not your challenge.
I can't really tell you why.
- They wanted me
to be a marionette,
and I was just supposed
to answer the question.
And that's not me.
In the show in Vegas, I am the--
I'm the front. I'm the star.
- If you are good
at being in the spotlight,
you should know how to steal it.
- There's been a lot on my mind.
- What's on your mind?
- [tearful]
Alyssa's my friend.
We didn't talk for two years.
And...
Coming here and seeing her here
completely threw me off.
And I don't feel like
I'm showing you who--
who I really am,
'cause I'm better than that.
- I know there's distractions,
but, Coco, keep your head
in the game
and be Coco.
All right, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck in
the Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Okay, just between us "goyls,"
what do you think?
Starting with Roxxxy Andrews.
- She's absolutely a stunner.
The hair color.
J.Lo wishes.
- Yes.
What did you think of her
performance as Tasha Salad?
- There is nothing
more attractive
than seeing a beautiful woman
dare to be ugly.
- Uh-huh.
- I expect some good stuff
out of that one.
- Next up, Alaska.
Now, Michelle, you and I
both looked at each other
when Alaska came out
dressed as a man...
- Mm-hmm.
- And thought, "What the F?"
- It really was
just Pee-wee Herman.
- Yeah, that's true.
- And this is
Rupaul's Drag Race.
- Not Rupaul's Best Friend
Out Of Drag Race.
- Okay.
- Alaska, to me,
he doesn't stand out.
He's, like, someone I would
hang out with in high school.
- What high school
did you go to?
- Well, I mean, I was
a homeschooler, but, um...
[laughter]
- Monica Beverly Hillz.
- Who was she again?
- She played Fanny
the farm hand--sunglasses.
- Oh, well, see,
that's how memorable she was.
- Well, there you go.
- She was such a nervous wreck.
You can never let them
see you sweat.
- She's stopping herself.
- Exactly, the calls are coming
from inside the house.
Vivienne Pinay.
- Anita Bum was forgettable.
- Right,
'cause if she was Anita Bum,
she could've been really hyper,
like, you know, um, yeah, um--
She could've gone for it,
you know?
- When I see a Plain Jane,
kind of like her--
'cause she is boring--
I like to do them up.
- Turn her out.
- Turn her out!
That's what I love to do.
- Detox.
- Kids would love watching
Clucky the cock.
- I see Faye Dunaway had a child
with Anjelica Huston,
and then she lost
all her fashion sense
and started wearing clothes
with holes in them.
- Yes.
- Sorry, Coco.
[laughter]
- Jinkxy Monsoon.
- She got me in the mood.
Like, I was singing with her.
I was raising my hands.
- Oh, right.
- I was a little girl.
- She was the only reason
that team stayed afloat.
- Coco Montrese.
- She had an issue with,
you know,
not getting the right part,
but you have to take lemons
and make lemonade.
- Blaming your shortcomings
on somebody else?
- Mm-hmm.
- Please.
- And you know, Santino,
playing the dummy can be
a real scene-stealing role,
right, Michelle?
[laughter]
I mean--
- [guffawing]
- You know I love you, and I
only say it 'cause it's true.
- Yeah.
- I was just telling everybody
how much nicer
you were than Tyra.
[laughter]
- Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back...
[whispers] My girls.
[laughing]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Roxxxy Andrews,
your portrayal
of Tasha Salad was,
in a word,
[lisping] sensational.
You are safe.
Jinkx Monsoon.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Monica Beverly Hillz.
Your kidster character
was not after-school special.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
Detox, your Clucky the cock...
bl-bl-bl-blocked...
The competition.
Condragulations, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
[applause]
You've won a wig wardrobe
from new attitude wigs.
- I won the challenge!
Fantastic
- Alaska, your choice
to perform as a boy...
[sighs]
was a real drag.
You are...
safe.
Coco, your ventriloquist act
could have been hilarious,
but your performance was wooden.
Vivienne Pinay.
America's next drag superstar
has to be more than just pretty.
Much more.
Vivienne...
you...
are safe.
But consider this a warning.
Coco Montrese,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I cannot believe
I'm up for elimination.
Is this really happening?
I'm not ready to go home.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your
last chance to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
for you to lip-sync...
for your life.
- Bitch, win or lose, let's go.
- Good luck...
and don't [bleep] it up.
-  Boys call you sexy
-  What's up, sexy?
-  And you don't care
What they say
See, every time
You turn around
They screaming your name
-  Don't y'all
-  Now I've got a confession
Ha ha ha ha
When I was young
I wanted attention
Ha ha ha ha
- Mama ain't going that easy.
I gotta pull it out and let Ru
know why I should be here.
So here goes.
-  When I grow up
I want to be famous
I wanna be a star
I want to be in movies
- We're all kind of like,
"Oh, my gosh."
Coco's serving it up.
-  People know me
Be on magazines
When I grow up
Fresh and clean
Number one chick
When I step out on the scene
But be careful
- Monica doesn't seem
to have much energy.
She just didn't seem
to have that will
to lip-sync for her life.
-  I see them staring at me
Ooh I'm a trendsetter
Yes, this is true
'Cause what I do
No one can do it better
You can talk about me
'Cause I'm a hot topic
I see you watching me
Watching me
And I know you want it
When I grow up
I want to be famous
I wanna be a star
I want to be in movies
When I grow up
I want to see the world
Drive nice cars
I want to have boobies
But be careful
What you wish for
'Cause you just might get it
Get it?
[applause]
- [mouths words]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Coco Montrese...
Shante, you stay.
You may join the other girls.
- Thank you.
- Monica,
you came here with a secret.
And the secret is
you are fierce and talented.
Go share that with the world.
- [crying] Thank you
for believing in me.
Thank you for seeing something
in me that I never saw.
[sniffles]
- Thank you.
- I love you.
Thank you so much.
- We love you.
Now sashay away.
- I had a hard time
opening up to the girls.
I've always had that problem.
It did hold me back
in this competition.
But I am fierce.
And I need to just step back
and be okay with that.
- 11 queens, 1 crown.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen!
- All right,
now let the music play!