- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
We're throwing the first ever
Sugar Ball.
[all gasp]
Are you passionate about
becoming America's next drag
superstar?
- You're wrong, Jinkx,
on the lollipop.
- Roxxxy's grasping at straws
to try to shake me.
- Jinkx, your sweet 16 party
girl--16 going on 47.
- It's unfortunate that there's
a disconnect
and it makes me question
your taste level.
- Alaska, you're the winner
of this week's challenge.
- [squeals]
- Jinkx Monsoon...
shantay, you stay.
Detox, sashay away.
- [whimpers]
- Holy shit.
- Detox just went home.
This has been the hardest
elimination for me.
My baby.
- What giant lips she has.
- If I was
on that judges' panel,
Jinkx would have been gone.
Jinkx does not deserve
to be here.
No offense, Jinkx, but I know
what they were saying about
looking 70 'cause you did look
a little older.
- But that's how Jinkx Monsoon
would have looked.
She would have been 16
in the '70s.
I know Roxxxy is upset that she
doesn't get to go through this
last part of the competition
with her best friend.
But I'm not gonna stop fighting
for this
until the very, very end.
- One of the three of us is
going to win $100,000.
- How many challenges have you
won, Jinkx?
- Two. We've all won two.
- You've won two and I've won
two.
- Ooh, an even playing ground
except I've never lip-synced.
I'm coming right off winning
last week's challenge.
So I just say bring it on,
darling.
Alaska is back in full force.
- Alaska thinks she can just
slide right underneath the radar
and go for the crown.
But guess what, bitch.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Alaska, my dear, sashay away.
- Words you will never hear.
- The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a sickening supply
of Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip courtesy
of ALandCHUCK.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut vodka--
cocktails perfected--and a cash
prize of $100,000.
- Top three, fantasy.
- Top three,
fantasy.
Where my top three at?
- [sighs] Aw, look.
I have a note.
- Oh, my gosh.
A little note from Detoxy.
- It says, "Roxxxy, this was
such an amazing journey
and I'm so thankful to have made
it with you."
- Mine says, "Lasky, you're
fucking terrible.
I love you so much."
- And--and I didn't get a note.
[laughs]
- You didn't get a note?
- No.
- Well, here. I'll make one up
from Detox to you.
"Jinkx, you sent me home,
you fucking hot fucking mess."
[laughs]
[alarm blares]
- Ooh, girl.
You've got shemail.
Ladies, make a case why you
should be America's
next drag superstar and you
could be awarded
a judgment of $100,000.
And if you're really lucky,
you might even get a hung jury.
- What?
- Hello, hello, hello.
[all squeal]
- She has legs.
- And I know how to use 'em.
- [laughs]
- The final three!
Condragulations.
[all cheer]
RuPaul is getting some
last-minute cosmetic procedures.
So he asked me to tell you
all about your final challenge.
And it's a doozy.
This week, you'll be starring
with RuPaul
in the official music video
for The Beginning.
- [squeals]
- You'll be working with
choreographer Candis Cayne.
- Continental.
- And then, with director
Mathu Andersen,
you'll be shooting a dramatic
courtroom scene.
And each of you will be playing
defendant,
defense attorney,
and prosecutor.
All three parts.
And on the main stage, you'll
need to defend your life
and convince the judges and the
world why you deserve
to be America's next drag
superstar.
- If there's something
in this competition
that I've been waiting for,
it's to express to these judges
why I should be America's next
drag superstar.
- To help you build an ironclad
case, you'll each have
one-on-one time with mega
attorney Gloria Allred.
- [gasps]
- [laughs]
- And if that wasn't enough,
you're having lunch
with RuPaul too.
- Oh, my god.
- [laughs]
So don't fuck it up.
- Hello, girls.
all: Hi.
- Last year, I had choreography,
but to step it up,
I thought I would add a little
chiffonography.
Today, we're going for a
seductive, goddess-y theme.
A lot of fans, a lot of hair, a
lot of chiffon in the fan.
I want you to be sexy, soft,
beautiful.
- Okay.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- [squeals]
- Alaska, you're getting
nervous, it seems like.
And think about not turning in.
'Cause that's kind of not the
choreography.
- I'm making a fool of myself
in front of Candis Cayne.
- All right, girls.
We're gonna do some hairography.
Bring me my fan.
[all gasp]
The basic point of fan use is
all about flicking your hair.
The fast and then the slow.
Very good.
- I am definitely the most sexy.
I know how to work some
motherfucking hair.
And, uh, I like being blown.
- Give me goddess.
Try not to let your hair
in your face.
Uh...
This is challenging
choreography.
Think more Beyonce and less
Cousin It.
But, you know,
this is the top three
and I really need them
to step up.
Whip it.
- Bonjour.
- It's time for us to shoot a
music video
for RuPaul's The Beginning.
Nice car.
- [laughs]
- The basic idea here is that
you're driving into the wild
blue yonder
and you're going to fly
to heaven.
[all laugh]
- Wow.
- Action. Whoa!
Whoa!
And left.
- Oh!
- Okay, we have a tragedy.
- Oh, she trying to pull the
patch!
- [yelps]
Dear god, do I really have
to be attached to her now too?
- Drive, drive, stop!
[horn beeps]
- Whoa!
- What?
[all laugh]
- Jinkx kind of took over,
going crazy and having fun.
- [laughs]
- And here she is.
It's Mama Ru.
Oh, my lord.
Alaska, shake your hair out.
- Alaska, did you not get
the concept of hairography?
Afro?
- Okay, we've sped this song up
1 1/2 times
so that when we slow it down,
the effect will be lip-syncing
perfectly to the song.
Let the chipmunkery begin.
Cue the music.
[song sped up]
[rapid, high-pitched singing]
- What?
- And now we have to sell the
lip-sync at double the speed?
I feel like I'm going insane.
- ♪ It's a brand-new day ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
- Cut.
Let the chiffon drift.
Give me mystery.
- ♪ You decide ♪
♪ Change your mind ♪
♪ Miracles happen every-- ♪
- Cut.
- Alaska's movement
is a little awkward.
She had trouble
with the chiffonography.
- Cut.
- ♪ You decide ♪
♪ Change your mind ♪
- Beautiful.
- ♪ Miracles happen every day ♪
- Yeah! Spin!
- Roxxxy did great hair
movement.
- Give it a spin, Roxxxy!
- ♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
- She had her lip-sync down
really good.
- Yay!
- Nice.
- ♪ The beginning ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
- Good job, Roxxxy.
- Amazing.
All right, ladies.
- Give me goddess.
Hit it!
Six, seven, eight.
And one, look,
three, four, five.
Cut.
I need you to be on, Alaska.
It's about precision, precision,
precision.
From the top.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
Pick it up, Alaska.
Cut.
- The other girls are doing
really good
and their hair is flowing
and their chiffon is flowing in
the right places, and I'm, like,
terrible and this is awful.
- What are your winning
qualities?
- Um...
- You need to believe
in yourself.
- For you to just discredit
all my work--
- I know, you're the victim.
- I have done well
in this competition
and I love what I do.
- Huh?
[laughter]
- Hi.
- Hi, Alaska.
- Gloria Allred is a mega lawyer
who is known for
taking on really high-profile
cases.
- Make yourself comfortable.
- Tomorrow, we are going to have
to present
our final arguments
as to why we should be
America's next drag superstar.
- Let's go right to what your
case is gonna be.
What are your winning qualities
that are unique to you?
- I have star quality.
The "X" factor.
- That's not good enough.
Give me specifics.
What is your most important
strength?
- Um...
- Just lay it on me.
- Well, I mean, I guess we can
see which one
you think is the most impactful.
- Okay, but you need to believe
in yourself.
Now, when you go out there
to make your argument,
you're gonna need to make it
with confidence.
Do you think you can do that?
- Hello, Mother.
- Hi, Jinkx.
How's tricks?
- Tricks are for kids.
I'm a lady.
- [laughs]
Listen, I hope you have
an appetite.
- Oh, yes.
This looks more than I can
handle.
- Now, Jinkx, what do you think
your life's gonna be like?
What--what do you want to do?
- It's been my life dream ever
since I started doing drag
to do drag on Broadway.
- I could see you
as Blanche DuBois.
- I could see that too.
- So what was it like for you
growing up?
I know that you had to sort of
grow up really fast.
- Mm-hmm.
- Tell me about that.
- I had no real mother in my
house when I was a teenager
because of her alcoholism.
There were times where me and my
brothers wouldn't have
gone to school that day if I
hadn't gotten us up.
- What effect has that had on
who you are as Jinkx Monsoon?
- This is my way of making peace
with a dark childhood
and make light of the disheveled
kind of crazy, kooky mom.
And then I adapted into my
mature drag queen
from yesteryear character.
- Right, so--and so you're
saving the Britney Spears
part of your career for later.
- It never even occurred to me
before my lunch with Ru
that maybe the reason I do drag
as an older character
is because I never really
connected with my childhood.
- I think you're
a really bright star
and I'm so happy you're here.
- Thank you.
I'm happy I'm here too.
- [laughs]
- And I'm not gonna eat these.
I'm gonna make a necklace
out of 'em.
- Oh, good.
[laughs]
- What are your unique strengths
that should persuade the judges
and everyone else
to vote for you?
- My unique strengths are that I
have shown you
that time after time,
when presented challenges,
that I could succeed even when I
didn't believe I could.
And I learned that not being
perfect is being perfect.
- Okay, let's stop right now.
What you don't want is you don't
want kind of pageant babble.
- Okay.
- As the kids would say,
keep it real.
You think you can do that?
- Yeah.
- All right.
What are some of the obstacles
that you have faced
and how have you overcome those
obstacles?
- Actually before coming
to this competition,
I wanted to quit doing drag.
I was done.
I was done with the criticism
from the audience.
I was done with nobody
wanting to date me
because I'm a drag queen.
- Okay, but how did you
overcome it?
- Woman, can I speak?
- Remember, I want to...
- Yeah. I--well--
- Get the negative
into the positive.
- I overcame it by realizing
that God has given me a gift.
And I consider myself
a chameleon.
'Cause when the lights, camera,
action, that curtain opens
and you don't know
what's coming out,
that's the excitement of going
to a drag show.
- What would you say are some
of the weaknesses
of your competitors, Roxxxy?
- Jinkx needs to stop being
such a one-shtick kind of girl.
Alaska, in the kids' show,
came out as a boy.
This is a drag competition.
Where's the beauty?
Where's the creativity?
It pisses me off.
- You're showing passion,
so that's all good.
But how can you say this without
being too, kind of, catty?
- Hello, Alaska.
- Hi.
- [laughs]
Now, if you win,
what would it be like
to be part of drag's first
royal couple?
- Wow, I would feel just like
Kate Middleton.
I would rule the drag world
with dignity and grace
and lots of lace front wigs.
- [laughs]
Tell me something I don't know
about you.
What are you afraid of?
- I have a fear of dying.
- Why?
- Because I f--I've worked--
I've worked so hard to get so
many things in my life
that I'm so happy to have.
And I guess it's just a fear of,
like, losing that.
Like, my relationship
with Sharon.
It's like a castle that we built
and I don't want it to--
to go away by me dying,
you know?
It's a crazy love that Sharon
and I have
and it's something that I never
expected to happen.
She's my soul mate.
And I don't know that I've ever
had that before.
- Don't be afraid of that.
Just practice living
in this moment.
Think about how sweet it is
right now.
I am so proud of you.
Good luck, sweetheart.
- Thank you.
- What do you think
are your strengths
that are superior to your
competitors'?
- I'm a captivating performer
onstage
and I think comedy and the
ability to make people laugh
is such a huge and important
part of drag.
- But what about your
competitors?
I noticed you kind of shied away
from that.
- The thing that pushes me out
of my comfort zone the most
is when I have to talk poorly
about my other competitors
because I have a huge respect
for every drag queen.
- You sound like a person who
wants to be positive,
but in this competition...
- Yeah.
- You're gonna need to elevate
yourself up...
- Mm-hmm.
- And move them down.
- Well, hey, Roxxxy.
- Hi, Ru.
- You've done really well with
meeting the challenge head on
with this fearless attitude.
Have you always been that way?
- I've always been a competitor.
That's what drove me
to pageants.
- What do you want people to
take away from your experience?
- I came in here wanting to
represent for the big girls,
and, you know, a big girl has
made the top three.
And I think it's time to crown
a thick and juicy kind of girl.
Being a gay man
and being thicker,
it's harder, but I love it.
I'm representing
for the big girls.
I can't wait to make them all
proud of me and, you know,
let them know that,
hey, love yourself.
- You're an amazing queen.
- Thank you.
- You are an amazing queen.
- Oh, my god.
- Thanks, Roxxxy.
- Thank you, Ru, so much.
This isn't a joke to me.
I've had it.
I've fucking had it.
I'm ready to plead my case
on this runway.
[laughter]
- We're right about to do our
courtroom scene,
directed by Mathu Andersen,
in which we all
have to play three distinctly
different characters:
the witness, the defense
attorney, and the prosecutor.
- Ladies, you've been instructed
to create
different characters
for each role.
So blow me away.
Here we go. Action.
- All rise for the honorable
Judge Rudy.
- Order in the courtroom,
hunties.
- Judge Rudy,
the evidence will prove
that the accused is one
cold-blooded biatch.
- As the defense attorney, I
would like to submit my briefs.
- Cut.
Alaska, I 'd like to know what
your inspiration
and motivation for your
character at the moment.
- Her name is Peg Hollis.
She smokes two packs of Misty
Slim Menthol 100s
and she's a hard-ass.
She's going on 60.
40 years in the business.
Graduated law school at 20.
I don't know how that happened.
[all laugh]
- It's a miscarriage of justice.
[laughs]
- "I smoke 80 packs of Virginia
Slims every day."
I'm sorry, that's not funny
to me.
- Okay, and action.
- Those hideous, uh, drag queens
had it coming.
It was a murd--mercy murder.
- Cut.
- Sorry, I messed that up.
- Taking a deep breath,
and... action.
- If I'm guilty of being
anything up in "herrre,"
it's of being fierce.
- And cut. Roxxxy?
- Uh-huh?
- Who are you?
- I'm Roxxxy Andrews.
A ghetto bitch.
- Roxxxy's character of Roxxxy
is definitely Tamar Braxton.
- Where my people at?
Where my people at?
- Dot-com.
- Okay, ladies.
It's time to do musical chairs
and change into your next
character.
Hit the changing rooms.
So here we go.
Action.
- Judge Rudy, the prosecution
would like to submit
the murder weapon.
- Objection!
Reading the witness.
- You want answers?
- We want the "T," stupid.
- You can't handle the "T."
- Jinkx was the most solid
in her characterizations.
She has the leading edge
in this courtroom drama.
And cut.
Big change.
Next role.
Okay, ladies.
I see you're all in different
positions and ready to go...
on action!
- Those damn fucking drag queens
had it coming.
- I say, I say--
- Cut, cut, cut, cut.
One moment.
Just gonna back up a little bit
because, um...
- I said a bad word.
- You said naughty words.
Action.
- Those hideous drag queens
had it coming.
- Judge Rudy,
the evidence will prove
that the accused is one cold,
hard-blooded bitch.
Biatch.
- Cut.
Roxxxy, what's the motivation
for your character?
- Uh, actually just a bitch.
- Okay.
Jinkx Monsoon?
- Her name is Daisy A. Irwin
and she's a little older than
she tries to pass herself off as
and she's just a simple
Southern lawyer.
- Fantastic. Alaska?
- I hope I don't go to prison,
but if I do,
I hope it's a men's prison.
- [laughs]
Okay, really bring it.
I want to see Satan,
ancient crone, and...bitch.
Action!
- I say, I say, objection.
- And Alaska?
- What's the line?
- "I can't face it."
- I can't face it.
I can't face it.
[sobs]
- What is it you can't face?
- What did you just call her?
- Roxxxy, humor me.
Your spit take
was a bit overly long.
Try and get the water
out of your mouth
so you can get to your line.
- Okay.
What did you just call her?
- Spit takes are usually a bit
more, "Puh!"
Nnn!
- Am I still not doing it right?
- Tight.
It seemed a little bit
problematic for Roxxxy
with the old spit take.
I just need you to snort it out
like a, "Puh!"
"What did you say?"
- I didn't know you wanted me
to say the line.
- You can tell it's really
affecting her
when Mathu calls her out.
The frustration
has gotten to the point
where you can tell she's mad.
- Ladies, guess what.
That's a wrap.
- Whew.
- [groans]
- This isn't even my character
anymore.
I just literally
have the shakes.
This day has been so long.
- [laughs]
My brain is completely gone.
- Melted.
- Are you okay, Roxxxy?
- I'm perfectly fine.
- No, you're not. You're upset.
- You guys are comedy girls,
so your spit takes were fine.
Didn't know a courtroom scene
was comedic.
- Girl.
It's a courtroom scene
that's written to be funny.
This is not NCIS.
- I take what I do extremely
professional and real
and I don't make a joke
out of everything.
And they're gonna read me 'cause
I'm lost
because there's
so much bullshit going on.
So trying to sell comedy,
trying to sell comedy,
trying to outdo each other--
I know what I've done
and I've--
I-I'm ready to plead my case
on this runway.
I'm sick of the gimmicks.
I feel that America's next
drag superstar
should take her career a little
more serious
than completely joking
all the fucking time.
I'm so--I've had it.
I've fucking had it.
This isn't a joke to me.
- I don't think you--
- This competition
is extremely serious
and it's the rest of my life.
Girl, I'm over it.
Why do I have to make up a name
to who I'm doing?
I'm acting like an attorney.
A bitch.
Why do I have to have some kind
of fucking character?
"Well, I'm so and so.
And I do this
and I'm 80 years old."
No, you're not 80 years old.
You're Jinkx Monsoon
playing a character.
- Roxxxy has admitted
to me before
that she's lashed out at me
when she's felt insecure
with her performance.
And she's obviously
doing it again.
- I'm just frustrated with this
whole fucking competition.
- I'm sorry if you missed the
mark on this challenge,
but stop trying to blame
everyone else
when you don't do well.
- The time has come for you
to defend your life.
[laughter]
- Ah!
- It's the last time we're gonna
see this place.
It's the final day.
And I just want to soak up this
experience
for everything it's worth.
- How did you guys feel
about yesterday?
- Yeah. Um--
- You know--
- I know I had a breakdown,
but the buffoonery that was
going on in that room?
All of our characters
are not supposed to be funny.
- Yes, they are.
- I think they were.
- No, they're not.
- I love how you say, "comedy,"
like it's a bad thing.
- Well, honey,
not all drag is comedy.
- I take comedy very seriously.
Comedy is not poking fun
at drag.
Like, comedy's--
- Well, it's not funny to me.
And the fact that drag continues
to get insulted
in this competition
is not funny to me.
They're making fun of drag.
I take my drag very seriously
and I look good
from head to toe.
Not in the same shoes
since day one.
Not in the same wig
Sorry, I change it up.
- So what has been
your favorite moment
throughout this competition?
- Seeing you in the bottom two.
- I just don't get
what's so rewarding
about being hurtful like that.
- I'm not being hurtful.
I'm being truthful.
You asked me.
I gave you an answer.
You skated through this whole
competition.
- For you to just discredit
all my work,
it just shows how immature
and bitter you are.
- I can't hear you.
I'm blow-drying my hair.
- I would never discredit
your form of drag.
- Huh?
- It doesn't make me feel good
to talk to other people the way
you talk to me sometimes.
- I know, you're the victim.
Everybody hates you and nobody
gets you and--
- I'm not a victim.
I've been very strong throughout
this competition.
- Roxxxy's a pageant girl,
and those pageant girls
play some wicked mind games
backstage.
- I know it's gonna get under
her skin.
I want her going in tonight
bothered.
Jinkx is competition to me and
I'm gonna do anything to get her
off her track.
- Victims blame other people
when they don't do well.
- You're getting all angry and--
- I have done well
in this competition
and I love what I do,
so I am not angry.
- This was the gas that I needed
for tonight.
I'm ready to tell the judges why
these two jokes should go home.
They have no idea what's coming
to this runway.
I'm here to win America's next
drag superstar,
and I'm going for blood.
- Alaska, what's been your
favorite part
of this competition?
- Seeing you in the bottom two.
[laughs]
- [laughter]
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Hey, judges.
Tonight, it's just family.
Michelle Visage,
can I get a witness?
- Of course.
You got one right here.
- Santino Rice, any objections?
- Just one, Ru.
You are looking too damn fine
tonight.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- Objection!
Ass-kissing overruled.
- For their final challenge,
our queens starred
in the official music video
for my latest single,
The Beginning.
And tonight, they're ready
to hit the runway
in their very best drag
as they prepare
to defend their lives.
Are you ready for some justice
to be served?
- Bring it.
- Ready.
- Gentlemen, start your engines
and may the best woman win.
- First up, the queen
on everybody's lips,
Roxxxy Andrews.
- Ooh!
- Glamour.
- This is my last time walking
this runway
and I'm feeling
so good right now.
The dress is stone
from head to toe.
I'm giving them a little bit
of my hair.
I'm feeling absolutely
glamorous.
- Foxy Roxxxy.
- She must have just come
from Paisley Park.
- Where my Paisley at?
- [laughs]
- Next up, Jinkx Monsoon.
- Aww.
- Fairy tale come to life.
- Very Princess Bride.
- It is.
- I am exuding beauty
from within.
I want them to see how gorgeous
and proud I feel.
- Like, it's soft, earthy Jinkx.
- She's a real
Renaissance woman.
- What kind of sauce
is Renee sauce?
- Ooh, it's good
on some chicken.
- Mmm.
- Up next, 49th state, Alaska.
High fash-i-on.
- That's what she's giving you.
- Yes, she's giving some fear up
in here.
- I'm coming down the runway
and I'm looking like a high
fashion ghoul
and I feel lovely.
- Oh, she got some booty today.
- Oh, yeah.
That's what she got
from her mama.
She's wearing
a lace front dress.
[all laugh]
Welcome, ladies.
The judges' final critique
is now in session.
Let's take a look
at the evidence.
- As the defense attorney, I 'd
like to submit my briefs.
- The state accuses Roxxxy
Andrews
of deplorable acts
of slayin' bitches.
- I plead guilty of being
devastatingly beautiful.
- Those hideous drag queens
had it coming.
It was a mercy killing.
- The evidence
will prove beyond a doubt
that the accused is one
cold-blooded biatch.
- Objection!
Reading the witness!
- The prosecution would like
to submit the murder weapon.
A size three stiletto.
- But I wear a size 14.
- If the pup don't fit,
you must acquit.
- [laughs]
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
[laughter]
Ladies, it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Roxxxy Andrews.
- Tonight, you look fantastic.
And what's been really exciting,
Roxxxy,
is seeing you come in
as a pageant queen
and you leave as a fully
rounded--pardon the pun--queen.
- In that video,
you exuded sex appeal.
Your hairography was on point.
Then in the courtroom scene,
there was a point where
some of the characters started
to blend a little bit for me.
- Next up, Jinkx Monsoon.
- You gave so many different,
varied performances.
Tyler Perry better watch out.
- I think her head piece tonight
is adorable,
but the dress
is just not my favorite.
It's very prom-ish. Very '80s.
- But your face looks amazing.
And you moved like you feel
beautiful tonight.
- All right, next up, Alaska.
Hi-eee!
- Hi-eee!
- Tonight, I really loved this
look on you.
The courtroom, your characters
were realized,
thought out, and you may not
be the strongest dancer,
but I think you made it work.
I don't know if I would have
chosen an afro.
- You had a lot to live up to.
And I think now you're--you're
not in anyone's shadow.
You're standing as Alaska.
You're your own queen.
- You've made so many of my
dreams come true being here.
It means everything to me.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Ladies, now we are ready
for your closing arguments.
Convince me
and everyone watching
why you deserve to be America's
next drag superstar.
The time has come for you
to defend your life.
First up, Roxxxy Andrews.
- The reason I should be
America's next drag superstar?
What they don't have, I do have.
I have grace, I have beauty,
I have professionalism.
I want to be a person that kids
look up to.
I am a thick and juicy girl,
and that makes me so proud.
I could never let you down.
And I will be one hell
of a superstar.
- Thank you, Roxxxy.
Jinkx Monsoon.
- Growing up, I was continually
an outcast,
and in my teen years,
I discovered drag.
So even though I was hurting
at home, I was living onstage.
My whole life, I've danced
to the beat of a different drum.
And when I came here, I took
the critiques and I was able to
adapt and grow while still being
true to who I am as a performer.
And anything else was just water
off a duck's back.
- [laughs]
- Thank you, Jinkx.
- Um, can I say something else?
- What's on your mind?
- I said something to Jinkx
earlier today that I just--
it has nothing
to do with the runway,
but I want to apologize to her.
I really didn't mean that,
and I really do love you.
I love you.
- Thank you, Roxxxy.
Last, but not least, Alaska.
- When it comes
to pleading our case,
Roxxxy and Jinkx totally
copped out.
We're supposed to say
why the other queens
shouldn't be America's
next drag superstar.
My name is Alaska,
and I am hungry
to be America's next drag
superstar.
Not hungry.
I'm practically starving.
As for my fellow competitors
tonight, Roxxxy was faced
with a challenge of presenting
a 16-year-old girl.
What did she present?
A tawdry, 27-year-old tramp.
And Jinkx Monsoon.
During the Sugar Ball,
she failed not just one,
not just two, but three
different looks.
I am the queen who takes the
tragic and turns it into magic.
I take trash and turn it into
treasure.
And having never fallen
into the bottom two,
I am Alaska and I am America's
next drag superstar!
Thank you.
- Wow.
Thank you, Alaska.
And thank you, ladies.
While you enjoy an Absolut
cocktail in the Interior
Illusions Lounge, the judges
and I will deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
All right, now, just between us
girls, what do you think?
Let's start with Roxxxy Andrews.
- Roxxxy is the embodiment
of a superstar.
In the music video, she whipped
that hair.
- She a video ho.
- She's thick and juicy.
She--she owns it
and she's come up
with some pretty amazing looks
this season.
- She comes from the pageant
world of drag.
To go from that
to this competition,
she's a fully-rounded
entertainer.
Jinkx Monsoon.
- Unlike Roxxxy, Jinkx does not
care at all what she looks like
and will go completely
into a character.
- She's in love with her craft.
And you see it
in everything she does,
but her style is--is lacking.
- But if we saw Carol Burnett
out at a red carpet event
and she looked a hot mess,
are you even gonna care?
- She talked about dancing to
the beat of a different drummer
and that's something each of us
on this panel right now
can relate to.
Miss Alaska.
- The cards were stacked
against her.
I love that she's persevered
through that.
- Alaska's got a really great,
sick, twisted sense of humor.
I like that she was able
to drop down that wall.
Mr. Gorbachev,
knock down that wall.
- [laughs]
- And when she gave us more
vulnerability,
I loved her even more.
Her defend-your-life speech
was the best.
- Well, they worked
with Gloria Allred.
- But she was the only one
out of the three
that read the other two.
- Yeah.
- It was actually part
of the assignment.
- Yes.
- Alaska has evolved
understanding the power,
not only of drag,
but the power of Alaska.
They're all so different.
Let's just break it down.
This week, Roxxxy really rocked
the music video,
Jinkx excelled
at the courtroom scene,
and when it came
to defending her life,
Alaska had the upper hand.
Damn, this is a photo finish.
- Hell, yeah.
- Silence!
Bring back my girls.
[laughter]
Welcome back, ladies.
Only one of you will be named
America's next drag superstar
and walk away with a prize
package that includes a crown
designed by Fierce Drag Jewels
and a cash prize...
of $100,000.
Now, based on your performance
in this week's final challenge
and throughout the season,
each of you
has earned the right
to lip-sync for your life.
- I have never lip-synced
for my life before, and now
I have to lip-sync against two
other queens for $100,000.
Help me, Mommy.
- Three amazing queens
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and prove to the world
that you are America's
next drag superstar.
- This is the last chance
to show ourselves to Ru,
the judges, and the whole world.
- I'm so ready for this.
I'm ready to dance,
I'm ready to show them
why I should be America's
next drag superstar.
It's what I'm here for.
- Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
- ♪ This is the beginning of ♪
♪ The record you like ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Breaking up ♪
♪ Fading out ♪
♪ Holding on until tomorrow ♪
- Jinkx Monsoon represents
the awkward kids of the world.
Being America's next drag
superstar
means everything to me.
- ♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
♪ That was then ♪
♪ This is now ♪
- I just want to win this so bad
and it's what I love to do.
It's my passion, it's my art.
I am America's next drag
superstar.
- ♪ Miracles happen every day ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
♪ Change the world ♪
♪ Change your mind ♪
- I am a queen who takes trash
and I turn it into treasure.
You have to take whatever you
have and make the most of it.
This is the beginning
of the rest of my life.
This is it.
- ♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of your life ♪
- [laughs]
- Get it, girls.
- Wow. [laughs]
Ladies...
I have not made my final
decision.
The race is that close.
And like last year, the crown
could still go
to any one of you.
Now I need the help of Drag Race
fans everywhere.
Based on all the evidence,
who do you think
should be America's next
drag superstar?
Is it Alaska?
Jinkx Monsoon?
Or Roxxxy Andrews?
Tweet your top choice
to @rupaulsdragrace
using #dragrace.
Then go to the RuPaul's
Drag Race Facebook page.
Then go to Instagram, Tumblr,
Pinterest, the Wow Report
and GetGlue to make sure your
voice is heard.
And then turn off
your goddamn computer
and go walk, children,
in nature.
Next week, tune in
for surprising revelations
and unseen footage of the final
three, including the debut
of their music video,
The Beginning.
And in two weeks,
we will announce the winner
on RuPaul's Drag Race: Reunited.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get a "Amen" in here?
all: Amen!
- [laughs]
Now let the music play.