- Previously on
Rupaul's Drag Race...
You'll be creating kidster
television shows.
- I am ready
to toss your salad.
- I like a cheesy salad.
- Vivienne, if you can bring
your energy up to meet Roxxxy...
- You're gettin' lost.
- It was pure hell.
Fuck you, Alyssa.
- Coco is always the victim.
- You committed
the number-one crime.
You bored me.
- Detox, condragulations,
you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
Coco Montrese, shante, you stay.
Monica, sashay away.
- Monica Beverly Hillz.
- We're back in the workroom,
and Monica got sent home.
- I would have been incredibly
sad if Coco would have left.
I mean, she is my most closest
friend here.
I'm not going to be a yin yang
without my yin.
- So what was it like, girl?
- It taught me a big lesson
that, you know,
in this competition,
you have to focus
and concentrate
on what you're doing.
- Right.
- I haven't been focused.
In the whole competition,
Alyssa has been
a distraction for me.
I've got to shake this off
and move on.
- Vivienne, were you scared?
'Cause when you turned around,
Vivienne's face was like--
- I wanted to fucking throw up.
Are you kidding me?
I thought I was going to pull
a Willam.
I was so fucking scared.
You don't even know.
- Vivienne's critique
was basically
that she played little,
and I overshadowed her
in our scene.
She knows that she didn't shine
last week,
so she's got to shine
this week and pull through.
- At first, we were working
really well together,
and our script
was really good,
but once you get there...
At this point, I'm pissed.
I really felt like Roxxxy
overpowered me.
I think that she's
an attention whore.
- Oh, oh, my--ah!
Oh, my god.
- I personally think
that she's annoying.
I'm going to be honest.
I'd like to see Roxxxy go home.
- ♪ Rupaul's Drag Race ♪
- The winner of
Rupaul's Drag Race receives
a sickening supply of
Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip courtesy
of alandchuck.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut Vodka--
cocktails perfected--
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra-special guest judges,
Shaping Sound's Travis Wall
and Chaz Bono.
- ♪ Rupaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
- Another week.
[all speaking at once]
- It's a new week,
and I'm very excited
to find out what our new
challenge is,
because I have to prove
that I deserve to be here.
[siren wailing]
- Ooh.
- Oh, girl.
- You got shemail.
Hey, girls.
So you think you can dance?
'Cause America's next drag
superstar
needs to be one
singular sensation.
Girl, once you go Black Swan,
you never go back.
[cheers and applause]
Hey, hey, hey.
What's happenin'?
[cheers and applause]
For today's mini challenge,
I want to turn back time
and find out
who are the best dancers
at Rupaul's Drag Race.
all: Oh.
- It is time to bust some
classic moves with
a good, old-fashioned Soul Train
dance-off.
[cheers and applause]
Ready, set, wig out.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- This is going to be too much
fish for your nerves.
- Ooh, y'all don't want it.
- [laughs]
- All right, D.J., hit it.
[Rupaul's Jealous of my Boogie]
Coco Montrese.
- ♪ Hey, D.J. ♪
- Yeah.
- ♪ Love the way I lose ♪
♪ My inhibitions ♪
♪ When you stare ♪
- Ooh.
Lineysha Sparx.
Burn, baby, burn.
Jade Jolie.
Hey.
- Whoo!
- Get it, girl.
Yeah.
Alaska.
Ooh, you a stone gas, honey.
- I'm featuring
the Flailing Chicken--
not really a Funky Chicken,
more like a chicken
that smells funky.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
[laughs]
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
[laughs]
Honey Mahogany.
Get it, girl, yeah.
- Ow!
- That's right.
Show them what you
are working with.
- Honey dances like
a white chick.
[laughs]
- Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
- Whoo!
- That was interesting.
- Detox.
That's right.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
[laughs]
She's a super freak.
Ooh!
Vivienne Pinay.
- Go, Viv.
Go, Viv.
- Hey, that's right.
Ivy Winters.
Make that money.
- Ivy doesn't have one stitch
of rhythm in that body.
This is not for you.
- Jinkx Monsoon.
Oh, my fur.
Hey.
Oh, get it, girl.
Whoo-hoo!
[laughs]
No parking on the dance floor.
Alyssa Edwards.
Yeah, shake your groove thing.
- Get it.
- Whoo.
Yeah, turn it up.
Ooh, you're giving those
Andrew Christian undies
a workout.
- Come on.
Ooh!
- Look at those
matching outfits.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
[cheers and applause]
- All right, ladies.
The late, great Don Cornelius
would be proud,
but two of you
really brought the funk.
The winners are...
Jinkx Monsoon...
[cheers and applause]
And Coco Montrese.
All right, ladies, for this
week's main challenge,
you'll be debuting
an original
American drag ballet.
- Yeah.
- It's called No Rupaulogies.
[laughter]
- Oh, my god.
- And it tracks the highs and
lows of my illustrious career.
Think of it as the black
Swan Lake.
Why it gotta be black?
[laughter]
- Hallelujah, thank the Ru gods
for sending a challenge my way
that I could excel in.
This is what I do.
I'm a dancer.
- Now, Jinkx and Coco,
you won the mini challenge,
so you're team captains.
All right, Coco, you pick first.
- Alyssa Edwards.
[record scratches]
- What the fuck?
- Well, well, well, I would
have never expected that.
- I'm not no dummy, y'all.
Alyssa is the best dancer,
and she's going to be
on my team.
- Hi, Jinkx.
You go next.
- Ivy Winters.
- [laughing]
- Detox.
- [laughs]
- Lineysha.
- Honey Mahogany.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
- A-loose-ka.
- [laughs]
- Oh, wow.
All right, Coco.
- God, Jade is never going to
forgive me for this.
Roxxxy Andrews.
- Whoo.
- In the back of my mind,
I kind of felt that I would be
one of the first people
that she would choose.
It kind of was like a slap
to my face,
because we have been so close.
- All right, now, Vivienne
and Jade remain.
Jinkx, who do you pick?
- Jade Jolie.
- Jade Jolie goes to
Jinkx's team,
which leaves
Vivienne Pinay to Coco's team.
- Great.
I find myself again in a team
with a bunch of loudmouths.
- Now, remember, this week...
actions speak louder than words.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- All right, I would like to
read through the script
before we assign any parts.
I feel a ton of pressure being
team captain,
but I kind of
built myself up last week,
and I don't want to take
a step backwards.
All right, I'm thinking young Ru
and Diana Ross.
Then we have Lady Bunny
and gender fuck drag Ru.
- Yeah.
- Does everyone feel good
about this?
- I feel awesome about it.
- Okay.
- I've worked with
Lady Bunny before.
I've made a couple costumes
for her,
and I've gotten to know her
pretty well.
- Ru's mom, you're going to be
the comic relief
right from the get-go.
- I'm the first impression
in this ballet,
and I can't dance.
- Have you had
any formal dance training?
- [mumbles]
- [laughs]
- Can you krump dance, though?
- No, what is that?
- You know, the--
I know you can do that.
- This is--that's my
only dance move.
It's going to be a problem.
- Coming up...
- We'll make you big.
- But we can't make her
outshine Ru though, right?
- Trust me.
She ain't gonna outshine me.
- Oh. Oh.
- Fuck.
- [laughs]
- Today, our main challenge
is No Rupaulogies, the ballet,
which is the story
of Rupaul's life.
I picked Alyssa for my team.
This could go
really, really good,
or this could go way south.
- In the first scene, there's
a good Ru and a bad Ru,
so there are two Ru's.
- I think it will be good
if we played the good Ru
and the bad Ru.
Ru versus Ru.
- Oh.
Oh, I see where this is going.
- Scene three is
"All my legendary children,
Ru and
America's next drag."
You gonna do Ru?
- I guess.
That's fine.
I think Vivienne should be
America's next drag superstar.
- Okay, that's fine.
- Once again, I'm in a team
with Roxxxy Andrews.
I don't like being
paired with her.
I just don't.
I don't like her energy.
- We'll put big earrings
on you.
Jewels, jewels, jewels,
and just the dress
and the shoes and the--
we'll make you big.
- But we can't make her
outshine Ru, though, right?
- Trust me.
She ain't gonna outshine me.
- Oh. Oh.
- I feel like the team today is
really underestimating me.
I'm kind of just waiting for it
to blow.
- Hello, hello, hello, hello,
my private dancers.
all: Hello.
- Is everything beautiful
at the drag ballet?
all: yeah.
- Of course.
- I don't believe you.
[all laughing]
Team Jinkx, who have you
assigned the roles to?
- Well, we have Ivy
as the Lady Bunny.
We have Alaska
as Mama Ernestine.
- [laughs]
- I'm your mama.
- Yes, you are.
- And we have Jade
as little Ru.
I am playing gender fuck
21-year-old Ru.
- Oh, dear.
- Yes.
- And who is playing
'60s Diana Ross?
- That would be Miss Lineysha
here.
- Are you familiar with
Diana Ross and the Supremes?
- Um, not really, no.
- All right.
Now, Ivy, you have
history with Lady Bunny.
- I do.
- I've always wanted to know.
I know you make costumes
for her.
- Uh-huh.
- What is Lady Bunny's
real waist size?
- She's a 28.
[laughs]
- Ooh, you mean her thigh
is a 28.
[all laughing]
- Now, Ernestine is Alaska.
Where are you drawing
inspiration?
- Well, in the voiceover,
it's going to say that she had
a mouth like a sailor, so...
- Yes, she did.
Her favorite saying was...
"You pussy-mouthed
motherfucker.”
- [laughs]
- I'm going to attempt to
convey
with my flailing limbs
Ernestine's strictness,
her strength,
and a face that's like this.
- All right, kids.
I'm going to let you get back
to rehearsal.
Good luck.
all: Thank you.
- Hey, team Coco.
- Hi, Ru.
- How you doing?
Now, which Rupaul
are you playing?
- I am the good Ru,
and alyssa's the bad Ru.
- [laughs]
Now, is this a case
of life imitating art?
- Yeah.
- How did that come about?
'Cause I was pretty gobsmacked
when you chose Alyssa.
I thought that you guys
had a little thing.
- Well, this is a competition,
and like I said,
I'm playing to win.
- Now, who's playing
'90s supermodel Ru?
- Me.
- The glamazon.
I love it, and you're working
with '90s Diana Ross.
Have you ever done
Diana Ross before?
- I've been asked
and actually haven't--
I wasn't able to the one time
they asked me to do it, so...
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Now, Roxxxy,
you are today's Rupaul,
and you're working with
America's next drag superstar,
which would be Vivienne Pinay.
- She's just playing her
for the sketch.
She's not America's
next drag superstar.
[laughs]
- Yeah.
- Now, Vivienne,
you have been criticized
for playing it safe,
playing it small.
- Yes.
- How are you going to
overcome that?
- I, again, have a lot of
big personalities
in my--in my group.
- You absolutely do.
- After last week, I just have
to, fuck it, just be myself.
If people don't like it,
they don't like it.
- Vivienne has to step it up.
- Break a leg.
- I mean, Ru gave her
a warning last week.
I don't think he'll give her
another one.
- Gather around,
my sugar plum fairies.
Now, in a moment,
you'll be working
with two red hot
choreographers.
From Shaping Sound, Travis Wall
and Nick Lazzarini.
[clapping]
And tomorrow on the main stage,
you'll be making
your dance debut
in front of Travis and our
other extra special guest judge,
Chaz Bono.
all: Oh.
[cheering]
- Chaz.
I live for Chaz Bono.
Chaz Bono came out of
Cher's vagina.
- And opera ballet.
Come dressed in your most
diva-licious outfit.
Ladies, this production of
No Rupaulogies
could change the face of
contemporary dance forever.
So don't fuck it up.
- All right.
[classical piano music]
♪ ♪
- Wow.
We don't have to do that, do we?
- Hey, ladies.
- Hi.
- I'm Travis.
- I'm Nick.
- Both the choreographers
are very dreamy,
and we're in
solitary confinement right now,
and all the girls
are like cats in heat,
to be quite honest.
- We kind of want to see
what we're working with here,
so if you could, one at a time,
show me your best move.
- So I have a little bit of
this in me.
- Okay.
- Oh, gorgeous.
- So--and these.
- [laughs]
- Oh, we love a split.
- That was beautiful.
- Wow, fouettes
are very advanced.
- [laughs]
- Oh, black swan.
- Fuck.
- This one.
[scatting Macarena]
- Macarena.
- So you're going to
take your legs out,
and you're going to go
jump that way.
- Um...
- Jump off the right foot.
Right foot.
Almost.
And chaine out and turn around
and kiss her.
- Ah.
- A little bit more grander.
Remember, you're playing
Diana Ross.
- I'm playing the role
of Diana Ross,
and I know how to do it.
- You know who Diana Ross is?
- Lineysha's going to bomb
at this.
- All right, take your foot--
you ready for floor?
You're going to jump right,
left, right, right, back.
Back, back, back.
- That's tricky.
- Nick and Travis,
they were, like,
shooting this choreography
on me super fast.
I'm just trying to remember it.
It was so overwhelming.
- This one's really important
for timing,
so you guys have
a lot of work to do.
- If we miss a beat,
it throws off
the whole rest of the piece.
It's going to be a nightmare
if we can't get this perfect.
- Coming up...
- And jump, go.
- They're, like, hesitant.
They're just not willing to
trust each other.
- [squeals]
- Honey kind of sucks.
Watching her
was so uncomfortable.
Fuck my life.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
- Stretch and extend
all the way over.
Stretch that side.
Today's main challenge is,
we have to tell Rupaul's story
through the art of dance.
This is a very important
challenge to me,
because I own
and operate a dance studio.
Good, and straighten.
And fingers crossed
that everything
just falls into place.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go, they're coming.
One, two, three, four, second,
five, down, seven, up, eight,
back, one, two, three, four.
- The looks on their faces
were, like, "uh-oh."
- Oh, that's real fancy, girls.
And I about shit my pants.
- Bye, kids.
- Bye, guys.
- Psych!
And it worked.
all: Hi.
- Hey, ladies.
How are you guys?
- Good, how are you?
- Are you guys ready
to dance today?
- For sure.
- All right, so let's start
with scene number one.
- Ooh, good Ru, evil Ru.
This one's going to be good.
- After not speaking to Coco
for two years,
and the blow up last week,
and then being picked
for his team today,
I'm hoping that our chemistry
can be there
and we can really deliver.
- I think you should definitely
do the lift.
This is about
trusting each other.
Can you just take her around
this way?
And turn me and go, lift,
like, that way?
- Oof.
- Slide and jump, go.
Jump.
- Ah.
[squeals]
Owie.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Owie.
- Wait.
I feel like they're,
like, hesitant
'cause they're just not
willing to trust each other yet.
They definitely have the most
work cut out for them.
You'd run around her,
you grab her by the throat,
and then you
just let her go.
Go around, go around, go around,
go around, go around.
And then grab him by the throat.
You grab.
Mm, shake, shake, shake, shake.
- It felt so good.
- Grab her hands.
So you'll do six of these.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, passe, and right, left,
right, left, right, left, passe,
and--
- Travis decides to give us
some choreography
that's actually
a little complicated.
- Go.
Right, left.
- Down, down.
- Wait, you're holding wrong.
It's just six steps,
so as much as you can,
try to retain the choreography
just a little faster.
- Okay.
- Honey kind of sucks.
Watching her was
so uncomfortable.
Fuck my life.
- Next.
- What do you want, like--
- [laughs]
- Ooh.
- Wow.
- That's what I do.
- Roxxxy wants all the eyes
on her,
and I'm really waiting
for the moment
where she kind of
messes up,
even though she's
still in my group.
- Cue music.
Jump, jump.
Turn around, and jump.
- Shit.
- Jump.
Go over and around.
Turn, turn.
All right, cool, thank you.
- It's--yeah, it's getting--
yeah.
Roxxxy and Vivienne,
they're probably the weakest
dancers in that group,
so to have them
at the end
makes me a little bit nervous.
Remember, this is about
Ru's life.
Don't fuck it up.
[hip-hop music]
♪ ♪
- Ro.
- 'Laska.
- Tox.
- Rolaskatox, darling.
- So tonight,
the first time we have
a major performance
right on stage
in front of Rupaul
and the judges.
- Show me one of your steps,
Alaska.
I've been waiting to see.
- Um, it's like this.
It goes...
[trills]
- That's beautiful.
- We're all shitting our pants
a little bit.
Or a lot, in my case.
- You know, when I came back
from college,
my parents actually found
a picture of me in drag.
- Oh, my--oh.
- Like, that's
how they found out.
They basically sent me out of
the country,
'cause they were like,
"You need to get away
from your negative influences.”
- Oh, my God.
- They sent you away basically.
- They sent me to Africa.
Yeah.
I think being a gay person--
we go through things
that I think enable us
to grow in a way
that straight people
don't get to have
that experience.
- I just wish my dad
would have been
a little bit more supportive
of the whole dancing.
When you do something
that makes you so happy,
and other people
try to take your happiness,
it's sad.
We just didn't have
that father-son relationship.
It was very hard for him
to understand me.
I found myself
getting lost in music,
and that's when it sparked me
to become a choreographer.
- I think everything
that we've all gone through
has made us--
- Oh, every road.
- Absolutely.
- And for me to give back
what was given to me,
the gift of
dance and art--it's my world.
- I feel really bad about Jade.
Not picking her right away.
Oh, she didn't even--
she just walked by me
like I wasn't even here.
She's really funny with me
right now.
I got to talk to Jade.
I've been trying to talk to you
all day,
and you've just been
avoiding me.
- Girl, I'm just focused on
my challenge and being here,
just like you're focused
on being here.
My feelings were hurt that Coco
didn't pick me.
Maybe she thought that I wasn't
a strong enough player
as the other girls.
I'm very happy that you picked
the team that you wanted,
and I'm very happy with the team
that I got.
So everything worked out.
Being in the bottom two
every week
just seems to work out for me.
- Oh, girl, I don't need
this today.
I need to get ready.
- Alyssa's most known
for her faces that she makes
in the mirror.
- The weird faces,
that's my favorite part.
- Playing
the ugliest face game?
- Yeah.
- So that's what you do on
the runway, Alyssa?
all: Ooh!
- [laughs]
Just pull it all in.
[Rupaul's Cover Girl
(Put the Bass in Your Walk)
♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what ♪
- Ooh.
- Welcome to the main stage of
Rupaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
may I have this dance?
- For the rest of your life.
- [laughs]
Santino Rice, how about some
dirty dancin'?
- Nobody puts baby Ru
in a corner.
- Ever!
- [laughs]
- And now, a man
with all the right moves,
Travis Wall.
How did my dolls do?
- They were absolutely fabulous
this week.
- Chaz Bono, welcome.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Tonight, we are dancing with
the drag stars.
- Can't wait.
- [laughs]
This week, our queens
were challenged
to dance their padded asses off
in an original drag ballet,
No Rupaulogies:
An American Dance Odyssey,
based on my life.
Or, as I like to call it,
the greatest story ever told.
[laughter]
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Coming up...
- Talk about not delivering.
- I just feel like
it's forgettable.
- The "it" thing
that you've got,
I didn't see up on the stage.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
[triumphant classical music]
- Act one of No Rupaulogies,
starring team Jinkx Monsoon.
[Vivaldi's spring]
I was born a poor black child.
[baby crying]
My mama, Ernestine,
swore like a truck driver.
"His name is
Rupaul Andre Charles,
and he's gonna be a star,
'cause ain't another
motherfucker alive
with a name like that."
And damn it, maybe, just maybe,
mama was right.
I loved playing dress up
as a kid.
Then, one day,
I saw The Supremes on
The Ed Sullivan Show.
My eye went straight to
the girl in the middle.
I couldn't stop watching her.
She was my idol,
and I've been singing
Diana Ross songs
in the mirror ever since.
[William Tell Overture playing]
At 21, my pal,
Lady Bunny, and I
ran away to New York City.
With a pussycat wig,
a pair of cha- cha heels,
and a dream,
we became the toast
of the town.
Well, at least
the lower east side.
And we partied
like there was no tomorrow,
and there almost wasn't.
- [laughs]
[laughter and applause]
- The next team better not
slip on
all that pee on the stage,
because we pissed
all over this competition.
[Tchaikovsky's Swan Theme]
- Act two of No Rupaulogies,
starring team Coco Montrese.
I can't wait to see
how this turns out.
[Beethoven's Symphony #5]
♪ ♪
Super stardom was so close
I could taste it,
but there was a war raging,
a battle between me and myself.
I hit rock bottom.
I had two choices,
to die or die trying.
Ah.
[all applauding]
Brava.
[Mozart's overture to
The Marriage of Figaro]
Flash forward.
The '90s.
You better work.
Supermodel, TV, films,
and then my forever came today.
My idol, Diana Ross,
invited me to work with her.
It took me a lifetime
to get here,
and, honey,
I wasn't going anywhere.
[applause]
- Honey was just kind of dead,
and I was carrying around
some extra blubber.
- All my dreams have come true,
so I've decided to spread
the love,
and to find America's
next drag superstar.
The charisma,
uniqueness, nerve,
and talent is overflowing.
[Beethoven's Ode to Joy]
♪ ♪
[all applauding]
[Handel's Hallelujah Chorus]
- ♪ Hallelujah ♪
- As I watch over
my legendary children,
mama is watching over me...
- [laughs]
- Whispering in my ear,
"Good luck, baby,
and don't fuck it up.”
- ♪ Hallelujah ♪
- Brava.
Brava!
Coming up...
Who do you think deserves
to go home tonight and why?
[laughs]
[Rupaul's I Bring the Beat]
- ♪ Commence shake down ♪
- Alaska!
Jade Jolie.
Lineysha Sparx.
Jinkx Monsoon.
Ivy Winters.
Alyssa Edwards.
Coco Montrese.
Detox!
Honey Mahogany.
Vivienne Pinay.
Roxxxy Andrews.
Welcome back, ladies.
This week, you worked in groups,
but tonight, you'll be judged
as individuals.
Jinkx Monsoon.
Ivy Winters.
Alyssa Edwards.
Vivienne Pinay.
Roxxxy Andrews.
Honey Mahogany.
The rest of you are safe.
You may leave the stage.
Ladies, it's time for
the judges' critiques.
First up, Jinkx Monsoon.
- I'm not crazy about the hair
and makeup.
It's not my favorite.
What's on your head?
- It is just a little, um,
head piece.
- I know you are filled
with lots of characters,
but I want to see some glamour.
I want to know if you've got
that in you.
- I believed in
all the debauchery
that you were creating up there
on stage
as young 21-year-old Ru.
- You were so entertaining,
and it was so much fun.
I really had a great time
watching you dance.
- All right, next up,
Ivy Winters.
- I love this outfit.
I'm a big Victor/Victoria fan,
so I think that this is great.
- You make everything
that you wear.
- I do, yeah.
- You're mind-blowingly
talented.
- Thank you.
- And your Lady Bunny
was so much fun.
- If anything,
your Lady Bunny was maybe
a little too skinny
and too pretty.
all: Ooh.
- That's a read!
- [laughs]
- Ooh!
- All right, next up,
Roxxxy Andrews.
- This look tonight--
there is something
not quite right
in the waist and hips area.
I don't think it's as flattering
as it could be.
You're not as curvy this week.
- I certainly know
what it's like
to not be the lightest
on one's feet.
You have to kind of
make up for it
with attitude and everything,
and I thought that's where
you could have elevated
your performance.
- Next up, Vivienne Pinay.
- Hi, Ru.
- Tonight, you faded into
the woodwork again.
It's a tad pedestrian.
- Look around
at your competition
and what they're wearing.
This is really low-key.
- I think you're actually one
of the most
beautiful queens
I've ever seen in person.
I think--
- Hey, wait, hold up a minute.
[laughter]
- I go back to thinking about
your performance
and, just, I feel like
it's forgettable.
- Next up, Honey Mahogany.
- You look like you must have
a lovely body.
This is just covering it up
and not doing anything for you.
- What is with you
and the kaftan collection?
Why don't we get to see
your figure?
And we need to talk about
your Diana Ross.
- I--you know, I've never done
Diana before.
- Clearly.
- [laughs]
- Alyssa Edwards.
- Tonight is ri-donk-culous,
and I've not seen a queen grand
jete across the stage before.
Fierce.
- You embodied everything
of the evil Ru,
and I don't think
the evil Ru lost.
- No.
And it didn't lose.
- Hello.
- If you walk into every
challenge this confident
as you were with this challenge,
I think you'll go a very long
way in this competition.
- Ladies, one last question
before you go.
At this point, you're all
getting to know each other.
Who do you think deserves to go
home tonight and why?
[thunder]
Jinkx Monsoon.
- Vivienne,
only because it seems like
she's repeating the same notes
that you guys are giving her.
- Ivy, what about you?
- I would have to say Honey.
- Roxxxy?
- Vivienne.
- Vivienne?
- I would say Honey.
- Honey?
- I would say Vivienne.
- Alyssa?
- The one that I would want
to send home
is not in this lineup.
- Who is not in the lineup
that you want to send home?
- Charisma, uniqueness, nerve,
and talent--
um, I don't see Jade
at the same level.
She's kind of a little
hokey pokey.
This is a drag queen
competition.
- Well, my queens,
I think we have heard enough.
While you untuck in
the Interior Illusions lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All righty.
Just between us dancers...
[laughter]
Let's talk.
What do you think?
Starting with Jinkx Monsoon.
- I do want to see other sides
to Jinkx
that I don't think
we've gotten to yet.
- If she can pull off
the glamazon,
we've got a real contender
on our hands.
- Her dancing wasn't
phenomenal,
but I think she
really made up for that
with committing
to her character.
- Ivy Winters.
- Nobody's more in on the joke
than Bunny,
and Ivy really
played that well.
- Did Lady Bunny ever lift you
up like that, Ru?
- Usually I saw her going down.
[laughter]
Roxxxy Andrews.
- She's out there playing you.
Honest to God, it's been so long
since I've seen you go out
in a leotard.
- She had a tall order
to play you now,
and the "it" thing
that you've got,
I didn't see up on the stage.
- All right, up next
is Honey Mahogany.
Now, here she is, playing
my idol, Diana Ross.
- I found myself watching
Detox the whole time.
- Tonight,
she comes up here again
with a sequin kaftan,
and this, you know, hodge podge.
It was all just whatever.
- Alyssa Edwards,
who is a trained dancer.
Regardless of her technique
and her background as a dancer,
she had the story in her head,
and we could see that.
- I mean,
she just looked so hot,
and I love her walk.
- She danced from head to toe,
between her hands and her toes.
Everything, she articulated
through her entire body,
and it was amazing.
- All right, moving on to
Vivienne Pinay.
- Talk about not delivering.
Even being the crowned drag
superstar--
No, you weren't.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- You were just a regular girl
putting a crown on at the mall.
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
[laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
This week,
you were all dance troupers,
but one of you stood out
as the prima drag ballerina.
The winner of this week's
main challenge is...
Alyssa Edwards.
[all applauding]
You've won a custom feather
piece from Mother Plucker,
and you'll receive immunity
from elimination next week.
- I'm at a loss for words,
and that doesn't happen much.
I'm just very thankful.
- Ivy Winters...
you're safe.
- Thank you all.
- Jinkx Monsoon.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Honey Mahogany,
as Diana Ross,
we were not swept away.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you're up for elimination.
Roxxxy Andrews, we challenged
you to step it up,
and you fell short.
Vivienne Pinay,
you are making progress,
but this week,
it was not measured
in leaps and bounds.
Roxxxy Andrews...
you are safe.
- Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
- You may join the other girls.
- Vivienne Pinay,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come.
You need to lip sync
for your life.
- The anger that I have
is preventing me
from being nervous.
Fuck it.
I'm going to do it
to the best of my ability,
because I owe it to myself.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ I think I did it again ♪
♪ I made you believe ♪
♪ We're more than
just friends ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ It might seem like a crush ♪
♪ But it doesn't mean ♪
- I can sing live,
and I'm really able
to deliver a lip sync.
This competition is mine.
- ♪ 'Cause to lose ♪
♪ All my senses ♪
- I'm really trying to look
the judges right in the eye,
and give them a reason
to keep me here.
- ♪ Oops, I did it again ♪
♪ I played with your heart ♪
♪ Got lost in the game ♪
♪ Oh, baby, baby ♪
♪ Oops, you think I'm in love ♪
♪ That I'm sent from above ♪
♪ I'm not that innocent ♪
♪ You see, my problem is this ♪
♪ I'm dreaming away ♪
- They're both lacking energy.
It's Britney Spears.
Bring it.
- ♪ Oops, I did it again ♪
♪ To your heart ♪
♪ Got lost ♪
♪ I'm not that innocent ♪
[clapping]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Honey Mahogany.
Vivienne Pinay.
I'm sending you both home.
I'm sorry, my dears.
Neither one of you showed me
the fire it takes to stay.
- In the history
of Rupaul's Drag Race,
there has never been
a double elimination.
- Double elimination?
Of course, it is.
Why wouldn't it be?
- Now, ladies, sashay away.
- I do have talent,
and I do have,
I think, what it takes
to be a performer.
If I could do something
differently,
I would have not worn
this kaftan.
Maybe I just need to
hire a stylist.
- I'm upset, obviously,
because I want to be here
to the end,
but I am beautiful,
and nobody can
take that away from me.
I will always be
the fishiest queen.
Today, tomorrow, next month,
the past seasons,
and the next seasons to come.
- Ladies, from here on out,
I will not tolerate
no half stepping.
Bring me your best.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get a amen up in here?
all: Amen.
- [laughs]
Now, let the music play.
[Rupaul's The Beginning]
♪ ♪