- Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be competing
in the RuPaul roast.
- Ru, you're acting to me, um--
[clears throat]
- What do you call it
when you flatline?
- Fuck.
- I'm not acting when I say
I'm insecure about things.
- It's all bullshit.
- Girl, you look like
the black Pee-wee Herman.
[laughter]
- RuPaul's next...
[microphone feedback]
Drag queen of the year--
- Coco Montrese,
you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
Condragulations.
- [cries]
- What's going on?
- My mother
left my sister and myself
at a bus stop when I was three.
It just hurt that I was left.
- As gay people,
we get to choose our family.
We are family here.
What you two did on this runway
is the passion I am looking for.
Shante, you both stay.
- Oh, my god, my god, my god.
My god.
- Oh. Are we all a mess?
- So we're walking
back into the workroom,
and I just finished
having the breakdown of my life.
I know y'all don't understand
what I was saying
'cause I was crying so much,
but it all just hit me.
I have never cried
about being left by my mom.
- Ever?
- Ever!
I was left at a bus stop
by my real mother,
and I was sent to an orphanage.
I've always felt rejection.
Part of me comes off
as such a strong character.
You know, like
when y'all were reading me,
you and Jade and stuff like--
that comes from being rejected.
The way I tend
to react to rejection
is getting very angry.
I was angry, and the easiest
target was Jinkx.
I totally took it out on her.
And that's not fair.
And Jinkx, I'm sorry.
- After seeing what Roxxxy
went through tonight,
I can't stay mad at her,
you know.
We have all been through so much
shit in our lives.
- Roxxxy Andrews is my sister,
and I'm so happy
that she's still here.
But it's still top seven
and not top six.
And I know I'm annoyed.
And I think a lot
of other girls are annoyed.
- This has been rough
fucking day.
I still am the one queen
who hasn't won a challenge.
- I can't believe I got it
with you two in the room.
What the hell?
The two comedy queens of
oh, my god.
I won?
What happened
to the funny girls?
Jinkx, Alaska.
- I just really
want to win a challenge.
- This was a challenge
right up your alley.
Do you feel, like, Coco,
you know--
- These other queens don't think
that I'm a force
to be reckoned with.
Good.
It's called a sneak attack.
I'ma get you, girl.
- The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race receives
sickening supply
of colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip
courtesy of alandchuck.travel,
headline logo's Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut vodka,
cocktails perfected.
And a cash prize of $100,000.
And tonight,
extra special guest judges
Aubrey O'Day
and Joan Van Ark.
[tires screeching]
- Oh, girl.
- Whoo.
[overlapping chatter]
- Today, I'm feeling
a little on edge.
Me and Roxxxy
both are still here.
But I think that the girls
wanted one of us to go home.
- Finally, the top six.
Oh, wait.
- [laughs]
- Nope. Alyssa's still here.
- Aw, man.
[siren wails]
all: Ooh!
- Ooh, girl, you got shemail.
Hey, ladies.
Can you smell me?
Mm.
It's the sweet
smell of success.
Remember,
America's next drag superstar
needs to follow her nose
wherever it goes.
Good luck.
And don't funk it up.
- What?
- Smell?
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hello.
- Now at this point in the race,
you must be getting
a little homesick
or lonely for boyfriends
or just miss having
a little sexy fun.
- [chuckles]
- Well, I have just the remedy.
Oh, pit crew.
- Oh!
- Come on.
[all cheering]
- Mmm.
- What?
- What the hell?
[squeals]
- [wolf whistle]
- Oh, my god, it doesn't stop.
- Oh.
- Say hello to designer
Andrew Christian.
Andrew, thank you
for keeping the pit crew
looking so hot all season.
- I'm very dedicated to my work.
- I bet you are.
Now, ladies,
Andrew has brought his models
to play a little game
of whatcha packin'?
- You know
what I'm talking about.
- [laughs]
- You ask a model to drop trou
and reveal
his Andrew Christians.
- Oh!
- Your job is
to find the matching pair.
[laughter]
Now, the queen that makes all
the matches the fastest wins.
- Oh, my god.
- First up, Ivy Winters.
- [laughs]
- The rest of you,
wait outside for your turn.
All right, Ivy, choose a model.
- Number 9.
[laughs]
- Oh.
- 14, please.
[buzzer]
- Not a match.
Next pick.
- Number 10.
- Damn.
You're gonna put somebody's
eyes out with that thing.
- 18.
[ding]
- We got a match.
How did we end up
in the meatpacking district?
- [laughs]
- Number 6.
both: Red.
- Now wait a minute.
- Wait. Oh, no.
I forgot what one was red.
- [laughs]
- I'm so distracted.
[laughs]
I am trying to memorize what boy
has got what underwear on.
And at the same time,
I'm just thinking,
god, this guy's really hot.
- Pick a model.
- 22.
- Ooh, pretty in pink.
- Oh, my god.
[shrieks]
I could play this game all day.
- It's like the Rockettes
only a lot more cock.
- 6.
9.
- Not a match.
- 11.
21.
[buzzer]
- No match.
- I was so close.
- I know,
you were about this close.
[laughter]
- 2 and 5.
[buzzer]
Son of a bitch.
17.
- Ooh.
- Oh.
- Seen that color before
somewhere.
- 8.
[buzzer]
Oh, wait.
Son of a bitch.
- Oh, damn it.
- Take them the fuck off.
I've had it.
- [laughs]
- Number 6 and number 7.
[buzzer]
- Ooh, not a match.
Alyssa, you're not doing
very well here.
- No, I'm doing very well.
I'm just not making any matches.
- Exactly, exactly.
- 15 and 7.
[ding]
- We got a match.
I don't know why
but I'm craving a corn dog.
The winner of today's
mini challenge is...
every straight woman
and gay man in America.
[laughter]
But one of you de-pants
these boys in record time.
The winner is...
Ivy Winters!
- [laughs]
Yay.
[laughs]
- You've won a phone call home.
- [gasps]
- Oh.
- I'm so happy I won
the mini challenge.
I'll be able to call my mom.
- Ladies, you know
you've reached the height
of superstardom when you have
your own fragrance.
For this week's main challenge,
you'll be creating and marketing
your own signature fragrance.
- [gasps]
- You'll come up with the scent,
a name, a package, and then
film your own commercial.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman...
[magical tone]
Win.
- Damn it, I wanted that.
You cunt.
- I'm so excited.
We've been doing
comedy after comedy.
A perfume ad
is something that me,
a pageant girl,
would like to do.
[bottles clatter]
- [gasps]
- Shit.
- How many did she--
drops did she say goes in?
- It depends on how you make it.
- Alyssa doesn't even
notice that
she's knocked a whole
bottle of oil all over me.
Yeah, I got to start over again.
Alyssa just doesn't think
past her own wig.
You know, it's all about Alyssa.
And it's pissing me off.
- My fragrance
is called Ruanimale.
- Does it smell like me
or does it smell like you?
- It smells like food
and maple and--
- Yeah, it smells like IHOP.
[laughs]
- [laughs]
- For the main challenge,
we have to create a scent...
- Ugh.
[coughs]
- Design a slogan,
the perfume bottle,
and shoot a commercial.
- Does everyone have an idea
of where you want to go?
- Kind of.
I think I've got like
a general idea.
- And what are you
gonna call it?
- Ivy winter's Poison Rosebud.
- [laughs]
That's cute.
- I've always been interested
in making my own perfume.
I've thought about
going to school for it.
I think I'm creative enough
to come up with
a really delicious perfume.
- Oh, it's so good,
I just want to
spray it all over my body
right now.
- [laughs]
- I haven't won a challenge yet,
so it's do or die.
I'm taking my gut reaction
and just running
straight forward with it.
Did somebody get fresh dirt?
I'm using things like dirt,
leather--
earthy and dirty,
which is totally my brand.
Oh, my god.
I love it.
- Mm, what you got going on?
- It's gonna start
like it's the morning after.
- Yeah.
- And have the pit crew
and me, like,
laying on a sofa or something
as if we had a threesome.
- That's a cute idea.
- I've been told continuously
in this competition,
"Girl, I don't get you."
But there's one person
who always gets who I am
and what I'm doing.
And it's Ivy.
- What about you?
- I'm doing a poison rosebud.
[both laugh]
- You know, a rosebud
is a synonym for asshole.
- I know,
that's why I'm using it.
- Just checking.
- Jinkx is amazing.
I feel like
I can relate to her a lot,
and the other girls
are totally threatened,
so that's why they're
all kind of nitpicking at her.
- Any help from me at all,
just let me know.
- Okay, honey.
I got to get back
to my rosebuds.
- Go prune the roses.
- [laughs]
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hi, Ru.
- How are my little stinkers
doing?
[laughter]
- Alaska.
- Hi.
- Is your fragrance gonna
represent Alaska?
- It is.
It smells delicious,
but it's also a little weird.
- Huh.
- Do you want to smell it?
- Yeah, I would love
to smell it.
It's not gonna make me sick,
is it?
- Well, I hope not.
You're the first guinea pig,
so--
- [inhales deeply]
[groaning]
Ooh, yeah, yeah, ooh, yeah,
yeah.
- My fragrance is called Red.
- Has Red been used before?
- Oh.
I think he's right.
Which means
I have to make up a tagline.
- All right, Alaska.
Good luck, and I can't wait
to smell you.
- Thank you, Ru.
- All right.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
Look at that bottle.
- Hi, Ru.
- What's the name
of your fragrance?
- My name of my fragrance
is Thick &amp; Juicy.
- Oh, my goodness.
- It's all about confidence.
And you have to embrace
and love yourself.
And like I told you guys,
I've embraced myself
with how I look,
and I want to
share that with everybody.
And wearing this is gonna
help you get confidence.
- Can I smell it?
- The smell is delicious.
It smells like food and maple
and jasmine at the same time.
- Oh, my goodness, yes.
It smells like IHOP.
Ooh, your country breakfast
is ready.
Y'all hungry?
Listen, you have
a lot of work to do here
'cause you know,
you were in the bottom two
last week,
so this has really
got to pop for you.
I'll see you then.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hey, Coco.
- Hi, Ru.
- Tell me about your fragrance.
- My fragrance is called
Ruanimale by Coco.
- Ooh.
Does it smell like me
or does it smell like you?
- It smells like me.
- Do you think the title
is a little confusing
for the consumer?
- No, because it says
Ruanimale by Coco.
- Ru is a little concerned
about the name.
But every perfume line
has a spokesperson.
- Okay, all right.
I'll have to check
with my lawyer.
I can't wait
to see the campaign.
See ya.
Alyssa Edwards.
- Hello, Ru.
- This sounds like a challenge
right up your alley.
- Something like that.
[laughs]
- Okay, tell me about your
fragrance.
- My fragrance is called
Alyssa's Secret.
- What is Alyssa's Secret?
- Um--
Son of a bitch.
Well, my secret to what?
- Here's Alyssa's secret,
darling.
The secret is, she don't know
what the fuck she's doing.
Here's the secret.
You can't tell Alyssa anything.
Here's a secret.
You can't get Alyssa
in front of a mirror
without taking four hours.
I've had it.
- I would have to really think
what my secret is,
because I wanted the secret
to be left for the imagination.
Ru is definitely not buying
what I'm trying to sell,
so this concerns me.
- Clarify your message, okay?
- Thank you.
Okay.
- Ivy Winters.
- Hi.
- Tell me about your fragrance.
- My fragrance is called
Ivy Winters' Poisoned Rosebud.
- Wow, that's a mouthful.
What are you
patterning it after?
- I really wanted to be able
to give women confidence,
to be classy, to be powerful.
- Well, that sounds like
a lot of fragrances.
- That is a lot of fragrances,
yeah.
- As this performer, you have
to be a marketing person too.
And actually break it down,
like, who is Ivy Winters?
And you think, okay.
You put together outfits.
You think, the circus performer.
You think of wacky, young.
But what I'm hearing is,
you're designing this
for a woman 45 and older.
- I completely missed the mark
with this rosebud.
Talking to you, I realize that
this is not really me.
Oh, what am I doing, Ivy?
I gotta get it together.
I'm just, like, thinking,
like, crazy.
I gotta make it happen.
Make it work.
- All right, listen up, ladies.
In a moment, you'll be shooting
your perfume commercials.
You'll be directed
by Michelle Visage
and our extra special
guest judge,
the enterprising singer
Aubrey O'Day.
- [gasps]
Yay.
- What?
- And this week
on the main stage,
come dressed
for your fragrance launch,
where we'll be joined by
one of my absolute favorites,
Joan Van Ark.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Ladies,
I expect you to come out
smelling like a rose.
So don't fuck it up.
- Remember it's perfume.
- I feel like I'm watching
The Lion King right now.
- [laughs]
[lion roars]
- Jinkx Monsoon.
- Guten morgen.
This week's main challenge
is to create a perfume
and star in a commercial.
- Hi, love.
Meet Aubrey O'Day.
- Hi.
- All right, boys.
You guys are asleep
the whole time.
Which just had a kinky
three-way.
Eiffel tower, all that stuff.
My perfume is Delusion
by Jinkx Monsoon.
Does this look like we had sex?
- Looks like something.
Action.
[laid-back music]
♪ ♪
- Her legs are really open
for selling perfume.
- Cut.
Remember it's perfume,
not a dildo ad.
So you might want to
take it down just a notch.
- Okay.
- Action.
- Nothing about her
felt like a lady.
Her legs were spread open,
her arms were awkward.
It felt kind of messy.
You look like this.
- Show me, show me, Aubrey.
- Hold on, let me just do
a couple--a little bit longer.
[laughter]
Something like this.
- Ivy Winters.
- Hello.
- Can we see your background
palette thingy?
- New York city.
- Oh, New York City.
Okay, home for you, yeah?
- Home for me.
- Uh, you know that's Tokyo.
- Oh, is it?
[laughs]
Dress Code for the glamorous
girl on the go.
- And cut.
There's a lot of jerking around,
a lot of movement.
- You're gritting your teeth
a lot
when you're
doing your sexy face,
like you have to go
to the bathroom or something.
- And action.
- Dress Code by Ivy Winters.
The smell
that changes your style.
- Cut.
- Remember it's scent,
not smell.
- Not only does it--
not only--excuse me.
Aubrey O'Day, her eyes are
a little intimidating.
- Feel it, girl.
- Ivy Winters, Dress Code.
Oh, shit.
Sorry.
- What's the name
of your fragrance, Coco?
- Ruanimale by Coco.
- Blue animale?
- Ru.
- Boo?
- Ruanimale?
- Ruanimale.
Yes.
- And you're wearing leopard
and you're performing
in front of leopard.
- Yeah.
- Coco--damn,
she gave me a headache.
There was so much leopard
happening.
The outfit, the hair--
it felt like a bad, cheesy porn.
- Ruanimale by Coco.
The wild exotic essence
of a woman.
[lion snarls]
- Cut.
- You have so much going on,
especially with your background.
So I would try your hardest
to keep your face
as soft as you can.
- Because everything else
is gonna be so animale.
- Yeah.
- Action.
[lion snarling]
- I feel like I'm watching
The Lion King right now.
- [laughs]
[elephant trumpets]
- I just don't know how well
she's gonna be able to recover
from all that leopard.
- It's Detox.
- Hi.
- First of all, what's the name
of your scent?
- Heroine.
- Hmm.
- It's kind of a double entendre
of the drug heroin
because my name is Detox
and a heroine,
which is a really strong
female figure.
And I feel like I embody
all of that.
- And action.
- Detox.
[whispers]
Sexy.
[deep voice]
Heroine.
[whispers]
Seductive.
[deep voice]
Heroine.
[whispers]
Get high.
[inhales]
Ah.
- [giggles]
- And cut.
- I don't think whispering
always means sexy.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's trying too hard.
Just mean the word.
- Okay.
- Detox is beautiful,
tall, great hair,
but I don't really
remember the commercial at all.
- Alyssa Edwards.
Action.
- Every woman has a secret.
Mine happens to be
a little bigger.
- Wha--what did you say?
- [laughs]
Oh, girl.
My secret--
[laughs]
I'm a man.
A scent sophisticated
for the everyday woman,
yet strong enough
for the career lady.
- And cut.
- You're real hard right now.
Make me like you.
Right now I'm like, ugh.
She's real pretty,
but her personality is crazy.
- Every woman has a secret.
Um...
uh, what was my next line?
Oh, let me start again.
Sorry.
I just feel so damn tense.
- You look it.
- I can talk to people
all day long,
but the minute someone says,
"Here are the lines,
say it," game over.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Hi.
- So, what's the name
of your scent?
- My scent, just like me,
is Thick &amp; Juicy.
- Action.
- Thick &amp; Juicy,
for the girls that are a little
thick and juicy.
And it smells just like food.
- Cut.
- Okay, we're gonna
do that again.
- [inhales]
Mmm. And tastes
just like my favorite foods.
Maple, chocolate,
and a little bit of everything.
- Cut.
- And smells
just like maple syrup,
chocolate, and watermelon.
- Cut.
I feel like you're making up
your words.
What did you plan to say, Rox?
- I planned to say that
it smells so good
you can eat it,
but then I was, like, "Hold on.
Perfume, you can't eat it."
- Okay.
So, you ended up with,
"I don't know"?
All right.
- Hi, Alaska.
Tell us the name of your scent.
- Red for filth.
- Oh, work!
- Okay, do you have any modeling
or scene work or anything?
- For dangerous, flawless,
seductive, and overpriced.
She's gonna be,
like, turning around and,
like, catching the camera.
And then it cross-fades.
And then turn around.
- Girl.
- Let's do this.
All right.
- Seductive.
Overpriced.
Those all look kind of the same.
- Uh-huh.
- Maybe you should just do it
one right after the other
like Wonder Woman.
Just keep spinning.
- Okay.
- And don't stop.
Dangerous.
Spin!
Seductive!
Overpriced!
[laughter]
- I love Red to filth.
She knew exactly
what she wanted to do,
and she took control.
And at the end of the day,
that's more impressive
than any win you can get.
- I think we've got it.
- Okay.
- That's a wrap, Ms. Alaska.
- Thank you, guys.
- Good job.
- Can I open up to you about
something?
- Mm-hmm.
- I have a crush on Ivy Winters.
- [gasps]
- I love you.
[crying]
- [laughs]
[overlapping chatter]
- Here we are, again.
Today is elimination day.
And like usual,
I'm scrambling around
and trying to get a really good
runway look together.
I'm going through my suitcases,
and I completely forgot that
I packed this photo book.
I have to show you guys
something.
This is my friend Caldwell's
photo book
chronicling the House of Haute.
- Oh, how much fun is that.
- Oh, my gosh, how neat.
Are you really onstage naked?
- Girl, we do some shit, girl.
With all of, like,
my family and my friends.
That's in the airport
the day Sharon came back
from RuPaul's Drag Race.
Getting to, like, see this book
that I totally forgot
that I had,
was like a huge,
like, shot in the arm.
[crying]
It was just so, like,
encouraging.
And it just makes me feel
renewed completely.
- I won the mini challenge,
and my prize
is getting to call to my mom.
Hi.
I'm so happy.
[laughs]
- I'm just so happy
to see your face.
[laughter]
- Seeing all the girls having
such tragic stories
with their families,
it made me really start thinking
about how special
you guys are to me.
- Aww.
- And I'm so blessed
to have such an amazing family.
- Yeah.
[laughing, crying]
When I was little,
I did a lot of theater,
and I was always nervous.
And she'd always,
like, squeeze my hand,
just to let me know
that everything
was gonna be all right.
And you know, she's proud of me.
Hmm.
I love you.
- Bye-bye.
- Mwah.
- Can I open up to you
about something?
- Mm-hmm.
- I have a crush on Ivy Winters.
- [gasps]
- I definitely can sense
those kind of feelings
bubbling up.
My biggest fear
is that this is gonna be done,
and she's gonna go back
to New York.
And I'm gonna
go back to Seattle,
and I'm gonna be like, "mm."
[snorts]
- You little scamp, you.
- I don't want to lose my head
or anything.
- Well, you know, that's cute.
- I don't know
how to describe it in words
how much Ivy means to me.
I almost think
that this could be
the beginning
of a relationship.
I'm really excited about that.
- Ivy.
- How was it, Ivy?
- It was so special.
- Oh.
- [laughing]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
- My citrus queen.
- [laughs]
- Shake the old spice
and steal the rice.
It's Santino.
- These have always
brought me luck.
- [laughs]
Joan Van Ark,
I am so thrilled you're here.
- You look like
a hot dream-sicle.
- [laughs]
And Aubrey O'Day.
Did my girls
pass the smell test?
- Some of them did.
Some of them didn't.
- Oh, my goodness.
This week,
we challenged our queens
to create their own
signature fragrances.
And tonight,
they're ready to mark the runway
with the scent of a drag queen.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
[upbeat music]
- First up, Coco Montrese.
Panther on the runway.
- Zebra on the runway.
- Okay.
- I'm serving animalistic
evening gown down.
I feel exquisite.
- I almost wore that outfit.
- [laughs]
- Up next, Alaska.
Lady in red.
A head for business
and a body for sin.
- Yes.
- I'm giving
crazy red executive dreams.
If this look
isn't changing it up,
I'm not really sure what is.
- I own 51% of this company.
- [laughs]
- Ivy Winters.
- The flounce and the bounce.
- I'm trying to move
as much as possible,
so every little
sparkly rhinestone
just twinkles in their eye.
[laughs]
- She's a Ziegfeld girl.
- Is she getting too old
for that whorey look?
[laughter]
- You're never too old for that.
- No.
- Detox.
- Ooh.
- High fa-shi-on.
- Oh, yeah.
- I see London, I see France.
- You can't fucking
take this body.
You have no choice but to get up
into my cakes and my lingerie
and love every little bit of it.
- Between love and madness
lies Detox.
- [laughs]
- Then of course, rehab.
- Alyssa Edwards.
Dallas meets Dynasty meets
Knots Landing.
I am giving 2013 businesswoman,
and I am living
for my gig today.
- Ah, the smell of it.
- Ah, yes.
- Does this skirt
make my damask look big?
- Mm.
- Jinkx Monsoon.
She works for MGM by day
and FOX all night.
- I am floating
down that runway,
and I am just
being cute and lovely.
- Oh.
- And 100% Jinkxy.
- No animals were harmed.
- No animals were harmed, yes.
Roxxxy Andrews, cat suit.
I could read her lips.
- [laughs]
- I turn this corner,
and they're gonna get a load
of this back.
Ow, eat it, bitch.
- Roxxxy Andrews,
the other white meat.
- She can bring home the bacon,
fry it up in a pan,
and serve it.
- There wasn't much going on,
idea-wise.
- I don't even know what you're
selling me,
but I don't want this.
- The perfume smells like
grandma's vag.
- [laughs]
- Welcome, ladies.
Coco Montrese, let's see your
fragrance commercial.
- Ruanimale by Coco.
Wild.
[lion snarls]
Exotic.
Essence of a woman.
- Ooh!
- As far as the video goes,
too much leopard,
and the guy with the headpiece
makes it gimmicky.
- Tonight, probably
one too many accessories,
but I think
this dress is gorgeous.
- Next up, Alaska.
- Dangerous, flawless,
overpriced.
Whether you're getting
read the house down...
- Your makeup is terrible.
- [laughs]
- Or just ready to go down.
The exciting new fragrance.
Red for filth.
Are you red..."e" for me?
[laughter]
- Absolutely loved it.
The only thing,
when you went south,
I wanted to see a big fat smile
on his face.
- [laughs]
- Ivy Winters.
- Dress Code by Ivy Winters.
For the glamorous girl
on the go.
Not only does it smell good,
but it changes your style.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Dress code by Ivy Winters.
The scent that
changes your style.
- Oh, dear.
- There wasn't much going on,
idea-wise.
- There were a lot of
awkward moments,
and as far as
the outfit tonight,
it's ice skater-y.
You're all about a dress code.
- Detox.
- Seduction, addiction,
heroine.
- [laughs]
- Sexy, sultry.
Heroine.
- [laughs]
- The new addiction
for an addictive woman.
Available at the clinic.
[laughter]
- The commercial was so brave
and so out there.
And the voiceover part.
Bravo to you.
- Tonight, something
looks a little unfinished.
It's not quite pushing it
as far as you normally do.
- Alyssa Edwards.
- Every woman has a secret.
And my secret happens to be
a little bigger.
And what exactly is my secret?
[laughs]
Why, it's Alyssa's secret.
For the desired
and the inspired.
- I don't even know
what you're selling me,
but I don't want this.
I want to change the channel.
- You do this thing
with your eyes
and it's like this sexy,
like, open 'em
and then close 'em.
I've gotten this note
a million times
which is why I'm just
passing it your way.
Less is more
'cause it almost gets
a little serial killer-ish.
[laughter]
- Jinkx, are you all right?
- Oh, yeah.
[laughs]
I'm just saying, "Water
off a duck's back" to myself.
Um, before my critiques.
- That's a great mantra.
- Words can't hurt you.
Only your own perception
of those words.
- Let's see your
fragrance commercial.
- For the girl
who lives above her means.
For the girl
who just won't give up.
For the girl with a dream.
Delusion.
[laughs]
Convince yourself.
- [laughs]
- I thought
it was the best concept.
No tea, no shade, hunty,
but I think it's my favorite.
- I'll have what she's having.
- [laughs]
- I don't even have enough words
for how happy I am tonight
with your look.
- Thank you.
- All right, Roxxxy Andrews.
- Thick &amp; Juicy.
For the girls who are like me.
Thick &amp; Juicy.
For the girls that like to eat
and don't worry
about being petite.
[inhales]
Mmm.
- Tonight on the runway,
I'm not in love
with that bow placement
right in the front.
When you turn to the side,
it's really kind of
sticking out.
- Roxxxy is another one
who came in with not much
of a concept.
You didn't have anything
written down.
You were just kind of
winging it,
which made it different
kind of each time.
- I know it kind of
seemed confusing to you
when I kept switching my words.
- It wasn't confusing.
It was unprofessional.
- Oh.
- I think we've heard enough.
While you enjoy
an Absolut cocktail
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right.
Just between us girls,
what do you stink?
We're gonna start
with Alyssa's secret.
Ooh.
- Right?
- It smells like
a Kardashian sex tape.
- If you ask her,
"What's your secret?"
And she's, "Well, I don't know.
I don't know."
She's not delivering her brand
and, therefore, her secret.
- Coco Montrese.
- Ruanimale is by far the worst.
- It smells like mating time
at the zoo.
- Not only is it
kissing your ass,
which I normally
don't have a problem with--
- [laughs]
- But they were supposed to be
expressing themselves
in their fragrance.
- Right.
I think her campaign,
and her in general,
is obvious, unoriginal,
and overdone.
- Ooh, okay.
- Ooh.
- Let's go next to Alaska.
- I enjoyed the commercial,
and I loved her outfit
on the runway
carrying the red theme through.
- I love the perfume.
Hers is the only one
that I would wear.
Everything else
smells like grandma's vag to me.
- [laughs]
- Dress Code by Ivy Winters.
- I think she missed everything
completely.
- I'm just clocking that bottle.
It does look like
a Christmas ornament.
And I think
it smells like something
my housekeeper used yesterday
in the bathroom.
- Or did in the bathroom.
- Oh, my goodness!
All right.
Heroine by Detox.
Joan Van Ark,
what'd you think of Detox?
And not your own
personal experiences--
- [laughs]
With it?
I don't share that with you?
Her Detox commercial I loved
because it was very brave
and upfront
and right out there.
- This week,
I wasn't feeling her look.
It looked a little homemade.
- Jinkx Monsoon's Delusion.
- She looked so beautiful
tonight.
I was so very proud of her.
- She had one of the best
commercials,
but it felt very, like,
vaudeville-y.
- All right, let's move on
to Roxxxy Andrews'
Thick &amp; Juicy.
- On the runway,
I wasn't in love with her look.
She had a bit of an open back,
but it wasn't cut out
nearly enough
to save the front of that look.
- The whole thing was tacky.
The outfit tonight was tacky.
The commercial was tacky.
I-I can't.
- [laughs]
- [claps]
Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
- [laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Jinkx Monsoon.
You're safe.
Detox.
Alaska, this week, girl,
you caused quite a stink.
Condragulations.
You're the winner
of this challenge.
- Ha ha!
- You've won a selection
of handcrafted corsets
from corsetconnection.com.
- [laughs]
I'm so happy.
I can't say this win is overdue,
but it's right on fucking time.
- Ivy Winters.
In your commercial,
your dress code
was not strictly enforced.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I did not expect
to be lip-synching.
I can't believe
this is actually happening.
- Coco Montrese.
Safari, so goody.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Alyssa Edwards, this week
you were not as inspired
as we desired.
Roxxxy Andrews,
your Thick &amp; Juicy
was a bit too loosey-goosey.
Roxxxy Andrews...
you're safe.
You may join the other girls.
- Thank you.
- Alyssa, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I'm disappointed, of course.
I don't want to be known
as being in the bottom
two times in a row.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lip-sync
for your life.
- I have a lot to prove.
A lot is riding
on this performance.
- Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Bill collectors ♪
♪ At my door ♪
♪ What can you do for me ♪
♪ No romance without finance ♪
♪ ♪
- I'm not gonna be meandering
all over the stage.
I want them to focus on my mouth
and hope that what I do is
better than what she's doing.
- ♪ Nothin' in life is free ♪
♪ That's why I'm asking you ♪
- I am giving my life.
This is my second opportunity
to give a better representation
of who Alyssa Edwards is.
- ♪ Oh, life is just serious ♪
♪ Love's too mysterious ♪
♪ A fly girl like me ♪
♪ Need security ♪
♪ 'Cause ain't nothin' ♪
♪ Goin' on but the rent ♪
- Ivy is owning
that part of the stage.
She's not moving around a lot,
but she's using
every bit of that costume.
- ♪ Ain't nothin' goin' on ♪
♪ But the rent ♪
♪ You got to have a j-o-b ♪
♪ If you want to be with me ♪
♪ Oh, you look good to me ♪
♪ Your silky words are sweet ♪
- Alyssa is
doing her dance moves,
and she's dressed like
a businesswoman of the '80s
who doesn't want romance
without finance.
- ♪ Ain't nothin' going on ♪
♪ But the rent ♪
[applause]
- Ladies, I've made my decision.
Alyssa Edwards...
shante, you stay.
You may join the other girls.
Ivy, I'm going to miss
your style, grace,
and I'm going to miss saying...
Ivy Winters!
I love you, Ivy.
- I love you too.
- Now, sashay away.
- Thank you, guys, so much.
- Oh.
I'm so sad to see Ivy go.
For a while now, I feel like
she's one of the only people
who have tried
to fully understand me.
- I made amazing friends
along the way.
I'm--I'm very happy with what
I've put out to the world.
I'll miss Jinkx the most,
but we'll be
seeing each other soon.
That, I'm not worried about.
It's just so sad.
[laughs]
I'm crying because they're all
gonna miss me so damn much.
[laughs]
- My sickening six, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
all: Amen.
- All right.
Now, let the music play.
[RuPaul's The Beginning]
♪ ♪