- Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
- Alyssa has been
a distraction for me.
I've got to shake this off
and move on.
- You'll be debuting
an original drag ballet.
- I can't dance.
- Coco, you pick first.
- Alyssa Edwards.
- What the fuck?
- Here's what I want from you,
Jinkx.
I want to see some glamour.
- The winner is Alyssa Edwards.
- [exhales with relief]
- Honey Mahogany,
Vivienne Pinay,
I'm sending you both home.
Now, ladies, sashay away.
- Girl.
- After the double elimination,
every girl knows Ru is not
playing the radio.
- Girl.
- Crack.
That's a sign of don't get
too comfortable.
- That was the closest I ever
want to get to the bottom.
To be in the bottom three has
lit a fire under my ass.
Never again.
- I think everyone is just
shocked that Roxxxy Andrews
is in the bottom three.
But I'm not shocked.
She's part of Rolaskatox, and
they've convinced themselves
that they're invincible.
- But you won.
- I wish she would have sent
all y'all bitches home.
[laughter]
- I want you to go home too,
bitch, so you don't throw me
in the bottom again.
Alyssa wanted to act
like she's so real,
but I think it was a pretty
bitchy-ass move to call
me out onstage.
- The one that I would want to
send home is not in this lineup.
I don't see Jade
at the same level.
If she would've asked me who
needed to go,
I would have said that,
because from the view
that I was getting,
it looked like a sausage
squeezed into a two-piece.
It was not pretty.
- You can't take it personal.
- You're a dirty bitch.
- It's not dirty.
I kept it real to your face.
If I wanted to be dirty, I would
have really, really read you.
Ha.
- Well, girl, if you read me,
I would have read you
right back.
- That's a part of the game,
baby.
Welcome to drag.
I knew coming into this
competition that the claws
would come out.
I don't want to scratch
anybody's eyes out.
I just want to scratch my way
to the top.
'Cause I'm what?
Sickening.
- The winner of RuPaul's Drag
Race receives a
sickening supply of
Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip courtesy of
ALandCHUCK.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race Tour,
featuring Absolut Vodka--
cocktails perfected--
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And tonight,
extra special guest
judges Julie Brown
and Downtown Julie Brown.
both: Rolaskatox.
- [laughs]
- It's a new day
in the workroom.
There's two less girls
in the competition now.
And the more that are gone,
the better.
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl.
You got shemail.
Ladies, stars aren't born.
They're made.
And then we destroy them.
But eventually,
those fallen stars
get their own reality shows
and become famous
all over again.
Ladies, get ready, because
your 15 minutes starts now.
- Uh-oh.
- Hello, hello, hello, ladies.
all: Hi.
- Well, well, well...
for today's mini challenge,
we're ripping a page
from Us Weekly
to find out who wore it best.
And we're going to do it
Drag Race style.
Now, you'll have just 30 minutes
to turn these cuddlers...
- Ooh.
- Into something
red carpet worthy.
I'll decide who wore it best.
Ready, set, style.
[all shouting, laughing]
- Damn.
- How am I supposed to wear
something so goddamn ugly?
- It'll be like everything else
you wear.
- How dare you?
- Oh, really?
- All right, ladies.
Time's up.
[camera shutter clicking]
To help me make this sartorial
decision,
I've invited an expert.
From Us Weekly magazine,
please welcome senior editor
Ian Drew.
[all cheering]
- Uh, Ru?
Is that a Klein Epstein &amp; Parker
suit that you're wearing?
- Why, yes, it is.
What do you think?
- Well, I think, in this case,
Ru wore it best.
- Aw.
[laughter]
All right.
First up, wearing zebra,
Coco Montrese.
You want some Coco
in your Cocoa?
Next up, Ivy Winters.
Girls gone wild kingdom.
Detox.
She's pairing it with some
DayGlo.
[imitates camera shutter
clicking]
[laughter]
All right, Ian.
- Yes.
- Who wore it best?
- I'd have to say Detox.
- Ah, Detox.
- Yay.
- Next up, wearing giraffe,
Lineysha Sparx.
[imitates camera shutter
clicking]
Ooh, look at that manicure.
Roxxxy Andrews.
Jet magazine, this way.
- [laughs]
Next up, Alaska.
Dear Lord.
African Vogue, this way.
- I think it was the best makeup
she's worn all season.
- So, Ian, who wore it best?
The name on everybody's lips has
got to be Roxxxy.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
First up wearing pink,
Alyssa Edwards.
Who are the jewels by?
- They're rented.
[laughter]
- A night at the opera.
Jade Jolie, a vision in pink.
- [laughs]
- Thank you, Jade Jolie.
Jinkx Monsoon.
Oh, my.
- The missing Olsen twin.
- Uh-huh.
- She just woke up.
- This way, Jinkx.
- I don't think Jinkx did
anything with the blanket.
She just put the blanket on
and gave it a character...
what she does best.
- All right, Ian.
So who wore it best?
- It is a stiff competition,
I will say.
- Oh.
- But it has to be
Alyssa Edwards.
- All right, Alyssa Edwards.
Well, condragulations
to our best dressed queens.
You've each won an Us Weekly
swag bag.
Now, Ian...
- Yes.
- I'm about to give you
a Drag Race exclusive.
For this week's main challenge,
we're going to play...
wait for it, wait for it...
Snatch Game.
[all cheering]
- This is what I came here
to do.
- Time to break out your best
celebrity impersonations.
Be fabulous, be a star, and,
most importantly, be funny.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- So what's everybody doing?
What you doing?
- You doing Katy?
- I'm doing Ke$ha.
- [laughs]
- Who are you doing, Alaska?
- Lady Bunny.
- Oh.
It's risky.
- And she just did Lady Bunny
in the last challenge.
- That's very risky.
- Who are you doing, Roxxxy?
- Tamar Braxton, honey.
- [laughs]
- Who?
- Tamar Braxton,
Toni Braxton's sister.
If you don't know her,
you're going to know her.
- Oh, is she coming to life
today?
- She coming to life tonight.
Tonight!
- This is something you should
be strong at, right?
- I'm hoping.
- What are you going to do?
- I'm going to do Little Edie
from Grey Gardens.
- Who--what?
- Little Edie from
Grey Gardens.
- Grey Gardens?
Who is that?
- Who is it?
- So Jackie O. has this cousin
and this aunt
who went bankrupt
and became shut-ins,
living in a big,
dilapidated mansion.
Little Edie had alopecia and
lost all her hair out of the
stress,
and then she became a big
fashion icon
years after she died.
- Do you think a lot of people
are going to recognize
that character?
- Little Edie is a risky
character.
Not everyone's going to know
who she is.
But I think people should know
Here's your pate, mother,
darling.
At least, I think it's pate.
The label's faded.
[both speaking Spanish]
- When you're dealing with
people judging what you do,
you just have to let it roll off
like water off a duck's back.
All right.
- Coming up...
Who are you doing?
- Michelle Obama.
- Michelle Obama?
Okay.
- This about to get real ugly.
- Girl, look how orange you
fucking look.
- I'm not joking, bitch.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
- Our main challenge today is
to pick a celebrity character
and play them on
The Snatch Game.
- Freaking out.
- Are you scared you can't make
Ke$ha funny?
- I think I can make her funny.
- Snatch Game challenges your
improv skills, your wit,
and your impersonation skills.
Without these three things, a
drag queen might as well not
call herself a drag queen.
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi.
- Ivy Winters.
- Hey, mama.
- Ah, who are you doing?
- Miss Monroe.
- Marilyn Monroe?
- Yes.
- How are you going to make
Marilyn Monroe funny?
- That's a good question.
[laughs]
Um, I think it's just relating
a lot to her movies.
Um...
- Yeah.
What about the funny part?
- I just have to be big
and blonde.
- Well, the tricky thing with
Marilyn, too,
is that she was
the smart dumb blonde.
So that sort of nuance
is not easy to do.
Get it going and make me laugh.
- I will.
- All right.
Alaska.
- Hi.
- 49th state.
- The biggest state.
- Oh, that's right.
It's like its own country.
- I'm my own continent.
- Oh.
- I'm incontinent, though.
- [laughs]
So who are you doing?
- I'm doing Lady Bunny.
- Ex-squeeze me?
Bunny is hilar--
I think she's actually the
funniest person I've ever met.
It's a tricky one.
I want you to be funnier
than Bunny.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- All right.
I'm scared shitless.
How the fuck am I supposed
to measure up to that?
- Hey, Coco.
- Hi, Ru.
- Now, okay, I'm getting
psychic feelings.
Um...
let me guess.
Margaret Thatcher?
- No, Ru.
Janet Jackson.
- I love me some Janet.
Now, what made you decide
to do Janet?
- I do Janet six nights a week
in Vegas.
- Really?
Six nights a week?
- Yes.
I really actually studied
everything about her onstage
and offstage.
So, if I don't know this
character,
then I shouldn't be doing drag.
- You got to bring the funny.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hi, Detox.
- Hi, Ru.
- I don't know who that could
be.
Let's see--Rachel Zoe
after a fire?
- No, I'm going to do my friend
Ke$ha.
- You're friends with Ke$ha?
- I've worked with her a few
times,
and I've done a bunch of her
music videos.
And, yeah, she's a lot of fun.
- Since you actually know Ke$ha,
how are you going to not sort of
hold back?
- I don't want to, like,
slander her too much.
- Well, that could be a problem.
You got to be willing
to make a fool
out of the person you're doing.
When the camera lands on you,
you have 30 seconds, from the
waist up, to make it happen.
Get back to work.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Hi, Jinkxy.
- Hi.
You caught me
with one eyebrow on.
- You are a quirky character.
I am just dying to find out...
who are you playing?
- Her name is
Little Edie Bouvier Beale.
- Jackie Kennedy's cousin.
- Yes.
- I love her.
But are you a little worried
that the audience at home
won't know who she is?
- It's a concern I had, but I
kept tossing around, you know,
pop icons I could do, and just--
none of them speak
to me the same way.
I landed on Little Edie because
I really relate to her,
and since I started in this
competition,
I feel even more connected
with her right now.
She's a little misunderstood.
- Yes, well, just make sure you
make Little Edie pop
for the unwashed masses.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right, well, listen,
you got a lot of work to do.
I'm going to let you get to it.
All right.
Lineysha Sparx.
- Hello, RuPaul.
- Who are you doing?
- I'm going to do
Michelle Obama.
- Michelle Obama?
- Yes.
- That's an interesting choice.
What made you decide to do
Michelle Obama?
- Because I think that I can
look like her, and--
- It's more than just looking
like the person.
They have to be funny.
Can I hear a little bit
of your Michelle Obama?
What did you serve Obama
for breakfast this morning?
- French fries.
- Um...
french fries.
Yeah.
Michelle Obama,
how are your daughters?
- [laughs]
Aw.
- Who are your other choices?
- I really--
I was thinking Celia Cruz.
- Is a good choice.
- But...
right now I got this choice.
I think it's better.
Celia Cruz--she's the queen of
the salsa,
but I really know that I can
look like Michelle Obama,
so I'm not going to change.
- It's a tough sell--
Michelle Obama.
Just be funny.
Be funny.
- I'm Michelle Obama,
and I approve this message.
- Ladies, gather round.
Now, I'll see you on the set,
with our extra special
guest judges...
MTV royalty Julie Brown
and Downtown Julie Brown.
[all cheering]
Don't fuck it up.
all: Bye, Ru.
- Julie Brown!
- Girl, which one do you think
I should do--Katy or her?
Miss Kim--this is not Kim.
This is too platinum.
I'm not 100% sold on Katy Perry.
I'm really thinking I should
probably switch to Kim from
The Real Housewives of Atlanta.
Celebrity impersonation is not
part of my gig,
and that makes me second-guess
myself
and what is the right character
for me.
- I have my makeup
like Michelle Obama.
I have my wig.
But I have in my mind the voice
of RuPaul.
- Do you know enough about
Michelle Obama to make it funny?
Celia Cruz?
- Mm-mm.
My other option is Celia Cruz,
but I don't have the clothes.
I don't have the right wigs.
So...
I don't know.
- I'm worried about Lineysha
because I don't think she knows
what she's doing at this point.
She needs to get it together.
- Coming up...
Welcome to The New Snatch Game.
- Get your life.
- I don't have a single idea
who any of these people are.
[laughter]
- [laughs]
[laughs]
Welcome to The New Snatch Game.
Today it's a battle
of the Browns.
She put the "wubba" in
"wubba, wubba, wubba."
Downtown Julie Brown!
And she's, like, totally
the original valley girl--
Julie Brown.
May I call you
"Uptown Julie Brown"?
- I prefer "just say Julie."
- [laughs]
Now let's meet
our celebrity panel.
Direct from Grey Gardens,
it's Little Edie Beale.
- Oh, hi, RuPaul.
- How is Big Edie doing?
- She's always begging for the
pate, but the label is faded.
I can never tell if it's pate or
if it's giblets for the cats.
[laughter]
- Next, don't break up with her
because she'll write a song
about it.
It's Taylor Swift.
- I can't believe I'm here.
This is so exciting.
[giggles]
- Next, my old, old, old, old,
old friend, Lady Bunny.
- You know, the last time I had
a battle of the Browns was about
ten minutes ago
in my dressing room.
- [laughs]
- Hey, Ke$ha.
- I just woke up here.
- You're at The Snatch Game,
honey.
- What's that?
- Now it's the president of the
rhythm nation, Janet Jackson.
- Hi, Ru. How are you?
- What have you done for me
lately?
- I haven't put out a hit
in a while.
- Next, she's my teenage dream.
Hey, Katy Perry.
Oh, is that your fragrance?
- It is.
Would you like to try some?
- No.
- Okay.
- Good-bye, Norma Jean.
Hello, Marilyn Monroe.
- Hello, Ru.
- Now, is it true that gentlemen
prefer blondes?
- Oh, they do.
You know it.
- Fabulous.
Next up, it's the queen
of salsa, Celia Cruz.
Hola!
- I'm very fine here.
My English is
no very good-looking.
- Last but not least, it's
Braxton family bad girl...
Tamar Braxton.
- Get your life!
- What's Toni really like?
- Girl, who cares?
This is my first gig without
Toni, and I am so excited.
Boom!
[laughter]
- Okay, here's how the game
works.
I ask the question.
Our celebrity panel fills
in the blanks.
And you give an answer that you
think will match.
First question for Julie Brown.
Lady Bunny is so over politics.
When she steps into the voting
booth, she just blanks.
- Pleasures herself
with the voting wand.
- Let's hear what our
celebrities have to say.
- Little Edie?
- Well, I don't know her
personally,
but she looks older than mother
darling, so I said,
when she steps into the voting
booth, she just seizures.
Spelling?
- Seize--[laughs]
[laughter]
Not a match.
Moving on to Celia Cruz,
the queen of salsa.
Lady Bunny is so over politics.
When she steps into the voting
booth, she just...
- Flip her hair back and forth.
- I think it's "whip your hair
back and forth."
- Uh-huh.
- Si.
- Uh-huh, si.
- No el match-o.
- No match-o?
- No.
All right, we're going to the
original material girl,
Marilyn Monroe.
- She passes out.
I think if it was me, it'd be
the hard decision-making.
I get a little bit light-headed
sometimes.
- Now, you're into politics,
aren't you?
Presidents and...
- Ivy totally didn't get the
joke.
It was an awkward moment.
- Quite the scandal, actually.
[laughter]
With my cousin-in-law, really?
- [laughs] Yes.
- It was in all the magazines
at the time.
[laughter]
- All right, next question is
for Downtown Julie Brown.
- Yes.
- Heather the hoarder is such
a mess.
When she opens her blank, her
personal massager falls out.
- When she opens her box.
- Let's see if we get a match
from Taylor Swift.
When she opens her blank, her
personal massager falls out.
- Falls out of her Taylor Swift
lunchbox.
- Oh, that's a match!
She's got box!
All right, let's move on
to Katy Perry.
- Hi, Ru.
- Did you really kiss a girl?
Have you ever kissed a girl?
- [gasps] Ru, never.
- But--uh, yeah.
Have you ever fucked
a black guy?
[laughter]
Okay, okay.
Heather the hoarder
is such a mess.
When she opens her blank, her
personal massager falls out.
- Her clutch.
- Sorry.
Not a match.
- I think that immunity for
Alyssa is gonna come in real
handy this week.
- Lady Bunny, same question.
When she opens her blank, her
personal massager falls out.
- Well, Julie,
I just wrote "anus."
[laughter]
- Same neighborhood--
not a match.
[all awwing]
Next question is
for Julie Brown.
Lady Gaga has finally gone
too far.
She wore a dress made of blank.
- Madonna's leftovers.
- Madonna's leftovers!
Let's go to the stars.
Ke$ha, she wore a dress made
of blank.
- I said "her stupid monsters,"
'cause my animals
are fucking badass.
- Oh, right, that's what you
pop stars call your fans.
- Yeah.
- Let's move on to the queen
of salsa, Celia Cruz.
- Hey, hey.
- She wore a dress made
of blank.
"A can of tomato salsa."
- Like a big can.
- [imitates buzzing]
Flat.
- All right.
- [scatting]
- Tamar, Lady Gaga's finally
gone too far.
Last week she wore a dress made
of blank.
- Boom!
Who cares?
I'm so sick and tired of hearing
about that bitch.
[laughter]
Tamar's world.
- That's right.
Moving on--this one's for
Downtown Julie Brown.
Paula Deen is out of control.
This morning she put a stick
of butter on her blank.
- On her toothbrush.
- On her toothbrush!
- [laughs]
- Miss Janet Jackson.
- I think she put it
in her panty liner.
- Panty liner.
- I did too.
You want to see what happened?
- Yes.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my goodness!
- Oh, my God, it's so thin.
- That's impressive.
- Coco's voice as Janet
was so perfect.
But she wasn't able
to make it funny.
- Ru, may I ask you why you
couldn't have gotten me real
celebrities for this game?
- Well...
- I don't have a single idea
who any of these people are.
You could have gotten
Leslie Caron or Audrey Hepburn
or any one of them.
Instead you got ketchup.
- Ketchup?
- And that must be
Janice Jickson?
- Can I ask you a question, Ru?
- Yes, you can ask me
a question.
- What's a Little Edie?
- Little Edie is a star of
a movie, Grey Gardens.
- Okay, well,
she's not that little.
Who the hell is Little Edie?
I didn't know what that is.
- Okay, moving on--
[singsong] Tamar Braxton.
- Get your life!
- Now, Paula Deen
is out of control.
This morning she put a stick
of butter...
- On her--boom--Louboutins,
'cause her fat-ass feet
don't fit in 'em.
[laughter]
- I really have to pee.
[record scratches]
Can I pee?
- Just a--in just one second.
We're get--we're almost done.
- I'm gonna go ahead and pee
over here by Tamar.
- She's gonna go pee in the
corner.
- [laughing]
[liquid rushing]
Ke$ha!
- Do you have toilet paper?
- Yeah, I'll get somebody
to clean that up.
- Thanks, Ru.
- Detox bathroom break?
[mouthing] Gross.
- All right, I'm afraid we've
run out of time.
And the winner is...
who cares?
[laughter and applause]
Thanks for joining us, everyone.
Until next time, RuPaul out.
Say good night, stars!
both: Good night, stars.
- Coming up...
- I don't understand why you're
really trying to, like,
come for me.
- Girl, you came for me.
- It just came off as
"annoying skank."
- [laughs]
[laughs]
- Ro...
- Laska...
- Tox.
- It's elimination day, and
with a challenge
like The Snatch Game,
it's definitely a lot more
intense.
- Alyssa, are you glad you had
immunity?
[all oohing]
- I don't do characters.
I mean, this was going to be the
hardest challenge for me,
period.
- At this point, we know Snatch
Game is gonna happen.
- Right.
- You should already have a plan
from the moment you audition.
- America's Next Drag Superstar
is not going to travel the
country being a comedian.
She needs to be sickening.
Do the math.
Jinkx, on the runway, I think
you should've prepared more
than one look.
- Honey, all your outfits
haven't been that clean either.
What you wore--that gold the
other day--
some people shouldn't come down
to wear a two-piece,
because the view that I had in
the safe zone was not too cute.
- I don't understand why you're
trying to, like, come for me.
I mean--
- Girl, you came for me, right
out there,
threw me under the fuckin' bus.
- You're still mad about that,
girl?
I mean, are you intrigued
or something?
- No, honey--
- Obsess much?
- That's one thing I ain't.
One thing I'm not is intrigued.
- Jade, I can speak up
for myself.
Alyssa, every week I've done
a different look.
Like, one time I was space age.
The next time I was
Marie Antoinette.
- No, no, no, no, some people
are coming down the runway
in complete bullshit.
Had I pulled that on the runway,
they would have ripped me
to shreds, and y'all know it.
Jinkx--she's all comedy
and no glamour.
I don't think from day one,
she's put anything on the runway
worth looking at.
- I have dealt with this my
entire drag career, you know?
It's getting frustrating to have
to defend a style of drag
that's completely valid.
When I first got to Seattle,
because I'm kind of quirky,
not a lot of queens took me
very seriously.
- Girl, what if I just went out
there
and not even brushed its hair?
I'ma say, "Well, I was trying
to make it funny.
Everything got to be funny,
right?"
- [voice breaking] Every time
I step into something new,
I have to fight this fight
again.
I don't want to have to keep
explaining myself.
- Miss Coco, you're gonna have
to do a little bit more pink
in the eye.
- You concerned about what's
going on over here when
you need to be worried about
what's going over there with
that same makeup you've been
running on the runway
every single time.
- Girl, look how orange you
fucking look, girl.
- Don't start with me.
- You're used to being my
runner-up and being behind me.
Don't switch the game up now,
mama.
- Okay, now, miss Alyssa...
[others whooping]
- Now you pushed it.
- Miss Coco, you're taking it
personal.
I'm joking with you.
- Oh, now I'm not joking, bitch!
You gonna call me a runner-up?
- You ain't never won nothing.
By default, mama--
you take that picture
by default.
- No, I took that picture
'cause you couldn't do the job,
bitch.
- I got that moment, though.
- She got the crown
put on her head.
She got to feel the emotion
of that moment.
She took that away from me.
I'll be damned if I let her take
that away from me here...
not without a fight.
This about to get real ugly.
- You know what's ugly?
Poverty.
[laughter]
- The Jade!
- The Jade of it all.
- And what?
[light applause]
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
are you ready to play?
- Always.
- Santino's in the house.
- You are looking snatchtacular
tonight, Ru.
- [laughs]
- Downtown Julie Brown,
do you feel lucky?
- Very lucky.
- And the hilarious Julie Brown.
Did you have fun yesterday?
- I had such a great time.
- Tonight the queens are
serving their own girlish
glamour on the runway.
Category is...
deadliest snatch.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[electronic beeping]
Commence shake down.
First up, Ivy Winters.
Goldfish.
- It's little she-mo!
- I'm strutting down the runway,
and I could feel my little fin
flopping.
I felt very fishy.
- Now, that's a catch.
- But still very "koi."
[laughter]
Detox.
Ooh, she's a power pouf girl.
- Or a cupcake.
- I'm serving killer jellyfish
realness,
and I'm living for it.
- You know,
you could shoplift in that.
She could steal a ham.
- Jade Jolie.
Chain, chain, chain!
- I'm serving up some bondage
bombshell fish fierceness,
and I am loving it.
- She spent a lot at Home Depot
for that one.
- Yes.
- [laughs]
- Roxxxy Andrews.
It's like a blazer
and no trousers.
- Blazer!
- Miss Thang, I am walking down
this runway like I am
$10 million.
Pose, pose, pose.
- Roxxxy, your pussy is on fire.
- [laughs]
- Jinkx Monsoon,
chicken of the sea.
- I am serving up Seattle boho
chic
with a flair of day out
at the beach.
[giggles]
- She's like a flying fish.
- Brackish, actually.
- Now there are 102 ways
to wear a scarf.
[laughter]
Ooh, Coco, girl.
- All right, little Coco Minaj.
- I am turning it out.
This is my runway.
Thank you, Ru, for letting me
borrow it.
- Those boots are made
for stomping.
- Or wading through a river.
[laughter]
- Alyssa Edwards.
The little mermaid's
all grown up.
- I am the definition
of fishy glamour.
Always and forever,
Alyssa Edwards.
- Mm.
- What's her net worth?
- [laughs]
She has a date with Moby Dick.
- Lucky.
- Lineysha Sparx.
- That is Sheila E. realness.
- If a girl answers,
don't hang up.
- I am serving bawdy,
bawdy, bawdy,
and just a little bit of bitch.
- You know, she's got a leg up
on the competition.
- She does.
- The 49th state, Alaska.
- Something smells fishy.
- I'm holding a brook trout
my grandfather
caught in Lake Erie.
Grandpa would be so proud
and completely horrified.
- Would you like a mint?
- That outfit would go great
with some tartar sauce.
- Mmm.
- Coming up...
- It's rather pedestrian.
- I do think we have a slightly
different aesthetic.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
Welcome, ladies.
Based on your performances in
The Snatch Game
and your presentation
on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Jade Jolie...
Coco Montrese...
Alyssa Edwards...
Alyssa, this week you let down
Katy Perry.
I want you to tweet an apology
to her tonight--
#RuPaulogy.
- Yes, ma'am.
- But last week you won immunity
from elimination.
The three of you are safe.
- Katy Perry's fans
are gonna slay me.
It was an embarrassment
to my career.
- Ladies, survey says you
represent the best and the worst
of the week.
It's time for the judges'
critiques.
First up, Detox.
- The problem is, Ke$ha's not
really that much fun.
It has to be somebody
who's kind of fun.
I just don't want to hang
with Ke$ha.
- Tonight on the runway,
your side silhouette is huge...
like a ball with legs.
- The first thing I thought of
when I heard fishy fierceness
was a jellyfish.
- Really? That's the first thing
you thought of?
You're fiercer than that.
- Next up, Roxxxy Andrews.
- I thought you did
a wonderful job
with your portrayal of Tamar.
I had a lot of fun and giggles
with you.
- Tonight your boobs
look amazing.
I love a bedazzled muffin.
- The hair is interesting, but
I wish it was a little more
coiffed.
- Next up, the 49th state,
Alaska.
- Hi.
- Your Lady Bunny, for me,
was absolutely hilarious.
You have incredible timing.
Absolutely fantastic.
- One thing that was kind of
missing from Bunny
was her voice.
She--it sounded more...
[deep, raspy voice] Like Roz,
you know, than it did--
[high-pitched voice]
Bunny's up here.
[high-pitched cackle]
- Next up, Ivy Winters.
- Your dress tonight I loved.
I mean, I loved the fun
and camp value
that we got with Nemo
eating you.
- [laughs]
- But with Marilyn Monroe,
you lost an icon.
What is the first thing
you think about?
[breathily]
You think about that.
[normal voice] You know...
- I think doing Marilyn Monroe
is next to impossible.
Everybody's done it.
You have to find something that
we haven't seen done to death,
in a way.
- Next up, Lineysha Sparx.
- You look absolutely stunning
tonight.
Love the hair and the choker and
the glam rock with the chains
going down.
- Celia Cruz was really generic.
- It's very hard make comedy
in other language.
It's more comfortable for me
make somebody Latino.
- I think you have the skills,
but you just didn't pull it out
of that character.
- All right, next up,
Jinkx Monsoon.
Michelle Visage?
- Jinkxy, I am starting to give
up here.
It's rather pedestrian.
I'm not getting glamour.
- To me, this looks glamorous.
I have big blonde hair--
- This, to me,
is not big blonde hair.
- I do think we have a slightly
different aesthetic.
[laughter]
- We do?
- You ruled The Snatch Game.
- [giggles]
- I thought it was absolutely
brilliant,
and I think anybody
who ever does The Snatch Game
should watch what you did.
- Thank you, Jinkx.
Well, ladies,
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck in
the Interior Illusions Lounge,
the judges
and I will deliberate.
[engine turning]
All right, kids,
just between us girls...
what do you think?
Let's start with Detox.
- She looks like a blob,
and I was not happy tonight.
- I disagree.
I thought it was quite
a nice jellyfish.
- To me, it looked like two
giant shower caps--
not hot in any way.
- Did she make you laugh--
Detox?
- It just came off
as annoying skank.
- Roxxxy Andrews...
- Roxxxy nailed that modern take
on Liza with a "Z."
- As Tamar, Roxxxy rocked it.
- [laughs]
- [snaps fingers] Okay?
- Let's go way up north
to Alaska.
Santino, I thought that Alaska's
jokes were crude, rude,
offensive.
She nailed Bunny completely.
- Right on the head.
Yes, the voice was not there,
but she was consistent with her
own made-up voice for Bunny.
- I actually liked her little
fish wiggle on the runway, and,
uh, she's got the tiniest butt
I've ever seen.
- Ivy Winters.
- With someone like Marilyn
Monroe,
you really have to have
the voice down.
- I just don't know
why you'd pick Marilyn.
It seems crazy to me
that you'd pick it
if you can't do the voice
or the character.
- Lineysha Sparx.
- She's a sex shooter.
She's getting phone calls from
Prince right now
to get in his new girl group.
- Or get his outfit back.
- [laughing] Yeah.
But her Snatch Game was lost
in translation.
- It actually reminded me of my
grandma at Christmas with too
much eggnog with a karaoke mic.
- Jinkx Monsoon.
- She was like the Meryl Streep
of drag queens.
- 'Cause that bitch turned it
out.
- Completely committed.
Should be committed.
- [laughs]
- I was just wondering if we'll
ever be able to get to see that
ultra-glamazon thing
from Jinkx once.
Not that this is ugly.
She's adorable.
- Who Jinkx reminds me
of is Pandora Boxx.
- Yeah.
- I actually like that dress.
It was just the way
it was styled,
the way she paired the things,
and these are things you can
learn.
- She thought that was big hair.
[laughter]
- [claps]
Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back...
[sighs]
[whispering] My girls.
[laughs]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Roxxxy Andrews...
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Jinkx Monsoon...
you gave us 50 shades
of Grey Gardens.
Condragulations, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
[applause]
You've won a custom jewel
package from Fierce Drag Jewels.
- I won Snatch Game!
A life dream is coming true
today.
- Alaska...
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Lineysha Sparx,
as the queen of salsa,
you lacked spice.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- To be in the bottom two
is very hard for myself.
But I don't want to go home.
- Ivy Winters,
your Marilyn Monroe was
one bland bombshell.
Detox, your Ke$ha was,
in a word...
blah, blah, blah.
Detox...
I'm sorry, my dear, but you
are up for elimination.
Ivy Winters, you are safe.
- Thank you.
- You may join the other girls.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
for you to lip-synch
for your life.
- I'm really well-known for
my unique style of lip-synch.
I'm ready to send
Lineysha packing.
- Good luck...
and don't fuck it up.
-  Take me home
Take me home
Want to feel you close to me
With you is where I wanna be
Wrapped in your arms tonight
Just making love
Music and candlelight
- I feel sexy.
I feel powerful.
I feel strong.
I want to win this lip-synch.
I don't want to give it up.
-  I'm in heaven
Seems like heaven
So much in heaven
- Whoo!
-  Take me home
-  One night with you
Lying here next to me
It's the right...
- I think Lineysha's heart is
really coming out,
and Detox is selling it.
It's gonna be a close call.
-  So much in heaven
[laughter]
Take me home
- Whoo!
-  I'm in heaven
Seems like heaven
- [blabbering]
-  I wanna get next to you
I wanna get next to you
-  Hold me, baby
Won't you hold me?
Take me, take me home
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies...
I've made my decision.
Detox...
shantay, you stay.
You may join the other girls.
Lineysha, your beauty transcends
language,
and there's no barrier
to how far you will soar.
Now sashay away.
[applause]
- [smooching]
- I love you, mami.
- This is the end for me
in this competition,
but I feel very proud to be one
of the family of Drag Race.
[speaking Spanish]
- Condragulations,
my crazy eight.
And remember, if you can't
love yourself,
how in the hell are you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
all: Amen.
- All right, let the music play.