&gt;&gt; Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
Welcome to the new Snatch Game.
&gt;&gt; Get your life!
&gt;&gt; I can never tell if it's pâté
or if it's giblets for the cats.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; I just wrote "anus."
&gt;&gt; Flip her hair back and forth.
&gt;&gt; You're at the Snatch Game,
honey.
&gt;&gt; What's that?
&gt;&gt; This is about to get real
ugly.
&gt;&gt; Girl, look how orange you
fucking look.
&gt;&gt; I'm not joking, bitch!
&gt;&gt; I'm not getting "glamour."
&gt;&gt; To me, this looks glamorous.
&gt;&gt; Celia Cruz
was really generic.
&gt;&gt; Jinkx Monsoon, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
&gt;&gt; Thank you very much.
&gt;&gt; Detox, shante, you stay.
Lineysha, sashay away.
&gt;&gt; [groaning]
&gt;&gt; We see Lineysha's message,
and we're all really sad.
We're gonna miss her.
&gt;&gt; "Latino shade!"
&gt;&gt; Beautiful, crafty lady.
both: She was.
&gt;&gt; Detox, how did it
feel up there?
&gt;&gt; Girl, you don't even
want to know.
I will never be
in the bottom two again.
Just makes me want to step my
game up even more.
Jinxalicious.
&gt;&gt; It was an amazing
performance.
Congratulations.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Don't count out Tamar,
bitch!
&gt;&gt; What about Tamar?
&gt;&gt; [singing]
&gt;&gt; Even though I'm doing well,
I'm not really getting the same
kind of emphatic reaction
from the rest of the queens
that members
of Rolaskatox get
when they do well.
&gt;&gt; Rolaskatox is firmly intact
and ready for the kill.
&gt;&gt; Oh, here we go with that
shit again.
&gt;&gt; I am in it to win it.
To dismiss me, right now,
would be a bad move
on their part
because you should be
taking me as a threat.
[snores]
&gt;&gt; The winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race receives
a sickening supply of
Colorevolution cosmetics,
a luxury trip courtesy of
alandchuck.travel,
headline logo's Drag Race tour
featuring Absolut vodka--
"cocktails perfected"--
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And tonight, extra-special
guest judges
The Pointer Sisters
and La Toya Jackson.
&gt;&gt; ♪ RuPaul Drag Race ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ May the best woman ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Best woman win ♪
&gt;&gt; Ro!
&gt;&gt; 'Laska.
Rolaskatox!
&gt;&gt; Jinkx!
&gt;&gt; Jade!
&gt;&gt; We're back in the workroom,
and we're down to eight.
&gt;&gt; At this point,
it's all or nothing.
It's balls to the walls,
literally.
[siren wails]
&gt;&gt; Ooh, girl!
You got shemail.
My queens...
a ladyboy needs to give
till it hurts.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; So whether you're saving
the whales
or saving face,
America's next drag superstar
needs to get by with a little
help from her friends...
with benefits.
all: What?
&gt;&gt; Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi.
&gt;&gt; Now,
in my illustrious career,
I've had to put on my makeup
without a mirror
or during a power blackout.
So for today's mini-challenge,
you have to apply your makeup
in total darkness.
[laughter]
&gt;&gt; I am losing confidence
in myself doing makeup
in the light.
[groans]
&gt;&gt; Oh, and ladies,
thanks to these
night vision goggles,
I'll be watching
your every move.
all: Oh!
&gt;&gt; Lights out.
&gt;&gt; Oh, my god.
&gt;&gt; Oh!
&gt;&gt; A table.
&gt;&gt; What is this?
&gt;&gt; Oh, my god. Ow.
&gt;&gt; Whoop, that went into
my eyeball.
&gt;&gt; It's all fun and games
till the looting starts.
&gt;&gt; Miss Coco, how are you going
to blend your powders?
[laughter]
&gt;&gt; Oh, really, Miss Detox?
&gt;&gt; I'm certain that,
whether it's light or dark,
Alyssa is still making this face
in the mirror.
&gt;&gt; Ladies, I'm watching you.
&gt;&gt; Hmm, interesting.
Very interesting.
All right.
[clapping hands]
Lights up!
[all sighing]
&gt;&gt; Ooh!
&gt;&gt; Do you remember
where we parked the car?
&gt;&gt; All right, first up,
Jinkx Monsoon.
Oh, dear god!
&gt;&gt; [mock crying]
&gt;&gt; Are you ready to take a peek?
&gt;&gt; I think I'm ready
for a funeral.
&gt;&gt; Whose?
&gt;&gt; My career's.
&gt;&gt; Oh.
Next up, Detox.
Ooh!
Actually, you look
kind of gorgeous.
I bet you get dressed
in the dark a lot.
Alyssa Edwards.
all: Ooh!
&gt;&gt; It's kind of gorgeous.
Alyssa, we're still here, hon.
Over here.
Ivy Winters.
[gasps]
Wow.
It's very drama-filled.
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Roxxxy Andrews.
Nice, take a look.
&gt;&gt; Oh, no, ma'am.
&gt;&gt; Jade Jolie.
Ooh!
Young boy, first time in drag?
Miss Coco Montrese.
You've got that highlight under
those eyes, don't ya?
&gt;&gt; That's bad, Ru.
&gt;&gt; Well...
laughs]
&gt;&gt; Girl, what was those colors?
&gt;&gt; Alaska.
[both screaming]
No, it looks perfect to me.
[laughter]
The winner is...
Detox.
Face, face.
Ladies, it's always darkest
before the dawn,
and now it's time to share
your light with the world.
Now back in the '80s,
music's biggest superstars
formed super-groups,
like "Band Aid"
and "USA for Africa."
They lifted spirits
and raised money.
So for today's main challenge,
you'll be writing and recording
the newest inspirational anthem.
Can I get an amen?
all: Amen.
&gt;&gt; No, I mean, actually
that's the name of the song:
Can I Get an Amen?
[laughter]
Yeah.
Now, you'll be writing lyrics
in three teams.
Detox, since you won
the mini-challenge,
you get to decide the teams.
[laughter]
So who's your first
team of three?
Alaska and Roxxxy,
get your asses over here.
&gt;&gt; Rolaskatox formation.
&gt;&gt; Formation.
[laughs]
Okay, and I think
that the rest of the groups
are already
paired together...
&gt;&gt; Oh.
&gt;&gt; The way that I want them.
&gt;&gt; Oh, oh.
&gt;&gt; So we have Jade, Ivy,
and Jinkx.
And we've got Coco and Alyssa.
&gt;&gt; You are a shady bitch.
Me and Alyssa had a very heated
argument,
and these girls know that.
&gt;&gt; I'm a little thrown.
Once again, here we go.
&gt;&gt; You can see
the storm clouds gathering.
[imitates cat hissing, snarling]
&gt;&gt; All right, ladies.
Later, you'll be recording with
my producer, Lucian Piane.
[cheers and applause]
&gt;&gt; And the dress code?
Flashback, '80s ladies.
[cheering]
All right, gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; Do we want to start it off,
olr do we want...
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; If Coco's gonna act like that
when I give her a team,
then show me what you can do
with this fucking first verse.
Have at it.
Okay, so Alyssa and Coco,
you guys are gonna do verse one.
Jinkx, Jade, and Ivy,
you guys are gonna do verse two.
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; And then, Rolaskatox,
we're gonna be doing the bridge.
Listen to this a few times
and get to work.
That's all.
&gt;&gt; "You guys are
the first verse."
Which means we'll be
the first take.
I'm so over these girls.
I'm done.
&gt;&gt; What's the "T"?
&gt;&gt; I don't need y'all
to gang up on me.
You, you, or you.
&gt;&gt; I wasn't instigating shit.
&gt;&gt; [giggles]
[laughs]
&gt;&gt; The challenge for this week
is to write lyrics
to a "save the world"-inspired
drag anthem.
We have to have an '80s look
put together,
and we have to perform the song
in front of Lucian.
It's a doozy.
I'm gonna alter
some of these words.
&gt;&gt; ♪ And some buffoonery ♪
Can I get an amen?
That would make it funny.
&gt;&gt; No.
This--oh, this is horrible.
I need to finish this.
&gt;&gt; I feel like Coco's over it.
And it's kind of
wearing me down.
I'm trying to overcompensate
for not having a voice,
and I'm really channeling
my inner Glee personality.
♪ How in the hell ♪
♪ You gonna love
somebody else ♪
♪ Amen ♪
&gt;&gt; Let's start throwing out
some--
just, like,
some one-liners.
♪ If your feet are sore ♪
♪ The beard grew back again ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Stealing ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Girl, that's okay ♪
♪ Just keep on shaving ♪
&gt;&gt; I like the "rhinestones are
a girl's best friend."
Then you say, "They're cheap."
♪ So you don't
have to be stealing ♪
&gt;&gt; Um...
I need my headphones.
I would have been really fine
if it was just Jinkx and myself.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; Lately, like,
I've been feeling like Jade
just needs to
step it up a little bit.
&gt;&gt; Just keep your head up
and you can achieve.
&gt;&gt; It's so close.
&gt;&gt; We don't have to rhyme
the last line with anything.
&gt;&gt; Oh, it doesn't?
&gt;&gt; No.
&gt;&gt; When your own friends
don't believe in you,
it makes you just kind of,
like, second guess yourself.
So I'm just feeling
a little underestimated again.
&gt;&gt; ♪ It'll get better someday ♪
&gt;&gt; I'm not worried whatsoever
about myself
or Rolaskatox.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; [scat singing]
&gt;&gt; We're gonna fucking
nail it.
I have an idea for a line
that I think
we should put in somewhere.
♪ And you can ♪
♪ Follow your dreams ♪
♪ Just get some shaving cream ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Yeah-heh ♪
[laughter]
&gt;&gt; ♪ I want an amen ♪
[wails]
&gt;&gt; I love Roxxxy and Detox
as friends...
&gt;&gt; ♪ Ah ♪
&gt;&gt; But the importance of me
sticking out from the pack
is extremely huge
right now
because I'm the only part
of Rolaskatox
who hasn't won a challenge.
&gt;&gt; Can I get an amen?
&gt;&gt; Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hello!
&gt;&gt; How are my little
singer-songwriters doing?
&gt;&gt; ♪ Yes ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
&gt;&gt; All right.
Coco and Alyssa.
&gt;&gt; Hi, Ru.
&gt;&gt; Cocolyssa.
Now, who sings?
&gt;&gt; I'm gonna try to take it to
church a little bit.
&gt;&gt; All right, what about you,
Alyssa?
&gt;&gt; I don't know if I'm gonna be
able to take it to church.
I may take it down the street
to the Jack in the Box.
&gt;&gt; Can I hear a little bit?
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; Yeah, you can.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Amen ♪
&gt;&gt; Whoa, okay.
&gt;&gt; We got auto-tune?
&gt;&gt; All righty, then.
&gt;&gt; Can we get auto-tune?
&gt;&gt; Alyssa in
a dancing challenge,
she's bringing home the trophy.
Alyssa in a singing challenge...
she ain't bringing home shit.
&gt;&gt; Now how is this gonna
inspire people
in the context of your song?
&gt;&gt; We did ours kind of towards
straight people, you know?
&gt;&gt; Oh.
both: "Lost and confused.
"I had to smile deep within.
When I realized
these women were men."
&gt;&gt; Um, look at those
lyrics again
and put some fun in there.
All right, kids,
you get back to work.
I cannot wait to hear
the finished product.
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; Ivy, Jade, and Jinkx.
[overlapping greetings]
&gt;&gt; It's like Wilson Phillips is
back together.
Now, who sings in the group?
&gt;&gt; I grew up singing, doing,
like, classical music.
I was classically trained.
&gt;&gt; I sing professionally,
actually.
&gt;&gt; What about you, Jade?
&gt;&gt; I sing in the car.
I think I'm just gonna have to
freestyle it and just...
&gt;&gt; Well, this is a competition.
You know, you got to plan
something out.
&gt;&gt; Jade?
She's just kind of floating by.
&gt;&gt; Jinkx, you and Michelle
aren't coming together
on a style angle.
What do you think that's about?
&gt;&gt; I think we used the word
"glamour" in different ways.
But I think this next runway,
I'm going to get right on there.
&gt;&gt; There's a lot
of show-stopping queens
around here.
You need to steal the spotlight.
All right, get back to work,
and I cannot wait to see you.
&gt;&gt; [sighs]
&gt;&gt; Rolaskatox.
&gt;&gt; What's going on?
&gt;&gt; Hey.
You're doing the bridge
and the last chorus.
What message have you
all written?
&gt;&gt; ♪ If you can't get a gig ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Go ahead and buy ♪
♪ A lace-front wig ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ So just tuck your junk ♪
♪ And hit that fucking runway ♪
&gt;&gt; Now, you're gonna make this
the g-rated version, right?
All right,
get back to work,
and we'll see you out there.
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Ru.
&gt;&gt; All right.
All right, ladies,
gather around, my children.
Tomorrow, on the main stage,
we will debut your
Can I Get an Amen?
music video.
And our extra-special guest
judges will be
three amazing women
who appeared on the original
We are the World:
Anita and Ruth,
the Pointer Sisters.
[cheers and applause]
And La Toya Jackson
will be here.
&gt;&gt; La Toya!
&gt;&gt; Oh, my god.
So excited to have them here
when I know I'm
on top of my game.
&gt;&gt; And for the runway, I want
you to put together a look
that shows off
your favorite body part.
&gt;&gt; Oh.
&gt;&gt; 'Cause, honey, if you can't
love your body part,
how in the hell you gonna--
well, you get
the picture.
Just don't fuck it up.
Okay?
All right.
I'll see you later.
&gt;&gt; Coco, there's a lot of
pressure on you
to start this out.
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
It's great.
Thanks, Detox.
&gt;&gt; For what?
&gt;&gt; [giggles]
[laughs]
&gt;&gt; Ooh.
&gt;&gt; Amen.
&gt;&gt; The main challenge
for this week
is to record a song about
how drag can save people's lives
and change the world.
&gt;&gt; Hello, ladies.
all: Hi.
&gt;&gt; Okay.
We're recording the track,
and we're recording
a live video.
Coco, there's a lot of pressure
on you to start this out.
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt; It's great.
Thanks, Detox.
&gt;&gt; What, honey?
&gt;&gt; I said, "Thank you."
&gt;&gt; For what?
&gt;&gt; Nothing.
Go ahead.
&gt;&gt; Is something wrong?
&gt;&gt; No. Not at all.
&gt;&gt; Well, apparently there is.
What's going on?
&gt;&gt; We're ready.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I'm pissed off.
I'm the first one up.
I'm nervous as hell.
&gt;&gt; Cue track.
[lyrical music]
&gt;&gt; ♪ I lost all hope today ♪
&gt;&gt; You lost all hope there,
didn't you?
You literally did.
Okay.
&gt;&gt; ♪ So I went to a local bar ♪
&gt;&gt; Coco, remember to use your
headphone in the other ear.
For the camera.
Got to see your beautiful face.
[lyrical music]
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; Uh, missed my cue, sorry.
[laughs]
&gt;&gt; Just catch up.
&gt;&gt; ♪ When I realized
these women were men ♪
&gt;&gt; Coco, what's going on?
&gt;&gt; I'm good.
&gt;&gt; Coco and Alyssa had
very strange chemistry.
They seemed like
they were on different planes.
Let's move on.
[lyrical music]
&gt;&gt; ♪ Your beard ♪
♪ Grew back again ♪
♪ Girl, that's okay ♪
&gt;&gt; Why are you looking down
and, like, not performing?
&gt;&gt; Sorry.
[laughs] I was just trying
to focus on the words.
&gt;&gt; Confidence and owning it
is a good idea.
&gt;&gt; ♪ All your dreams
in front of you ♪
♪ Just don't sashay ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ No misbehavin' ♪
&gt;&gt; That was awesome.
Ivy, great job.
Ivy's got the energy,
the performance,
and the voice.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; I feel that Jinkx
is the weakest
because all these girls
with the gimmicks
are getting by, and it's kind of
pissing me off.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Amen ♪
[glass shattering]
&gt;&gt; You guys have the bridge,
so you know this is, like, the
most inspired part of the song.
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh.
&gt;&gt; ♪ When life is ♪
♪ Bringing you down ♪
♪ Put on a shiny
sequinsed gown ♪
&gt;&gt; Are you saying "sequin" or--
&gt;&gt; Sequinsed dress.
&gt;&gt; "Sequin dress," I think is
what you mean.
&gt;&gt; I say "sequinsed dress."
"Sequinsed" is more than one
sequins.
A "sequins" is one little
circle shiny little sequins.
Is it wrong English?
Sequin?
A sequin is one.
Sequins is plural?
Sequinsed.
&gt;&gt; ♪ If you can't get a wig ♪
Oh, fuck.
♪ So--a lace-front wig ♪
&gt;&gt; Detox, don't swear during
a recording take.
all: ♪ Can I get ♪
♪ Oh, can I get an amen? ♪
♪ Can I get ♪
♪ Oh, can I get an-- ♪
♪ Oh-oh ♪
♪ Somebody else ♪
&gt;&gt; We'll stop there.
Both of you are doing what,
right there?
&gt;&gt; The second part.
&gt;&gt; No, are you crazy?
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; You guys changed keys
before the song changes keys.
Just--ugh--a train wreck.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; Detox and Roxxxy
are joking around too much,
not taking it seriously.
That's unacceptable.
&gt;&gt; So now it's time to do
some freestyling
over the choruses, ladies.
Do whatever you think works.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; I'm going Beyoncé
on Destiny's Child.
I can't be Kelly Rowland.
♪ Can I get a wha-oo? ♪
♪ Ooh, can I get an aah ♪
[wailing]
&gt;&gt; Next.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Where my people at? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ How you gonna ♪
♪ How you gonna love
♪ someone else ♪
♪ Beside yourself? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ A-A-amen ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
♪ Just love yourself ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Love someone ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get a, get an amen ♪
&gt;&gt; Give yourself a big round
of applause.
That's a wrap, ladies.
&gt;&gt; Ah!
&gt;&gt; Whoo!
&gt;&gt; "Love yourself."
&gt;&gt; That was so much fun.
&gt;&gt; Girl, I thought you was about
to go off.
&gt;&gt; No, girl.
&gt;&gt; Do you feel like
she was instigating it?
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
And then try to play like,
"Oh, I didn't do anything."
&gt;&gt; What's the "T"?
&gt;&gt; I'm fine.
I'm totally fine.
&gt;&gt; Well, I was thinking if
you're gonna say my name,
you've been throwing
dust and shade.
&gt;&gt; I said, "Thank you."
All I said was,
"Thank you, Detox."
&gt;&gt; Well, thank you for
what though, miss thing?
&gt;&gt; Well, she feels like
you were instigating.
&gt;&gt; I wasn't instigating shit.
I'm not trying to be dusty.
I'm not trying to sabotage
anybody in this competition.
If you feel that way,
I'm sorry you feel that way,
'cause that's not the case.
&gt;&gt; I'm giving dust,
I'm giving this.
I ain't said a word.
I'm just standing here.
&gt;&gt; You haven't said a word,
but you said a lot to Alyssa
this whole--
&gt;&gt; I don't need y'all
to gang up on me.
You, you, or you.
&gt;&gt; Miss thing, I'm not ganging
up on anybody.
&gt;&gt; I don't need that.
&gt;&gt; I'm not ganging up
on anybody.
&gt;&gt; I said what I had to say.
&gt;&gt; When you're on stage
and you say,
"Thank you, detox,"
snotty like that--
when I see this and I see
eyeballs flying at me,
I'm gonna fucking say something.
&gt;&gt; Girl, I didn't even
look at you.
Who eyeballs were flying at you?
'Cause my eyeballs
didn't fly nowhere.
&gt;&gt; Coco always wants to say
that she's very positive
and looks at the best
of everything.
&gt;&gt; Oh, my god.
&gt;&gt; Yet she's been
playing the victim
the last couple of weeks,
and I'm just
pretty much over it.
&gt;&gt; Ro!
&gt;&gt; Laska!
&gt;&gt; Tox!
&gt;&gt; ♪ Elimination day ♪
&gt;&gt; The theme for today's runway
is "best body part."
It's imperative for me to burn
the building with the look,
because Coco wasn't herself,
I'm not a singer,
and I didn't come to
this competition
to be in the bottom three.
&gt;&gt; What are you featuring today?
&gt;&gt; I'm gonna show off
my whole body.
I've had so much done
to my body,
I might as well show it off.
&gt;&gt; What all have you had done?
&gt;&gt; I have had a little bit
of plastic surgery
here and there.
I've had my hips
and my ass done.
I've had my pecs done.
Underneath my eyes done
and my brow area done.
My six-pack done.
&gt;&gt; You've had a six-pack done
with silicone?
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh.
My cheeks done and my lips done.
My chin done,
and my jawline done.
My shoulders, I've had--
&gt;&gt; Your shoulders?
&gt;&gt; My muscles are all silicone.
And then I've had a little bit
done on my bicep here.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
You're a silicone maniac.
&gt;&gt; The only thing I haven't
had done
is my knees and my nose
and my big toe.
I'm like walking tupperware,
girl.
I'm part of the Glad family
of products.
[laughter]
&gt;&gt; How do I feel about queens
who've had plastic surgery?
Jealous.
If I had my way,
my upper lip would
look like this.
&gt;&gt; It wasn't
the most pleasant experience
for coming out for me.
[laughs]
&gt;&gt; Did you have anyone
in your family
who was supportive of you?
&gt;&gt; It really, like, ruined
my world for a while.
I had, like, really
dark times as a kid.
I parted from my family.
We parted on bad terms,
and I really just
didn't have anyone.
I didn't have any friends.
I didn't have anybody.
I was just very lost.
And I wasn't happy with myself.
&gt;&gt; You don't need to waste time
trying to impress the people
who aren't gonna accept you
for who you are.
&gt;&gt; Right.
And I think when you get older,
you just really appreciate
things so much more.
You know what I mean?
Like, I'm glad that--you
know, I don't regret anything.
I pride myself on
where I'm at now
and the person that I've become.
I'm much stronger,
and I love myself much more.
You know, when Ru says,
"You have to love yourself",
you definitely do, so...
'cause if you don't love
yourself,
how the hell are you gonna love
anyone else?
[laughs]
&gt;&gt; I thought that Detox
was trying to be
a little malicious
when she put us together.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
[RuPaul's Cover Girl]
&gt;&gt; ♪ Cover girl ♪
♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
♪ And what? ♪
&gt;&gt; Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
can drag change the world?
&gt;&gt; Yes, just you and me.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
Santino Rice?
&gt;&gt; We're gonna make music
her-story tonight.
&gt;&gt; ♪ I cannot wait! ♪
It's Anita and Ruth,
the Pointer Sisters.
"I'm so excited."
&gt;&gt; Oh, and you better
not hide it.
&gt;&gt; And my queen,
Miss La Toya Jackson.
Third time as a judge.
&gt;&gt; That's right, three times.
And it never gets a dull moment
when I look at you.
&gt;&gt; How's life with La Toya?
&gt;&gt; You'll see.
&gt;&gt; Good.
This week,
our queens were challenged
to record and perform
an inspirational anthem.
And tonight,
they're ready to wow us
with their favorite body part.
Ooh.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
Commence shakedown.
First up, Coco Montrese.
It takes a lot of guts to wear
that outfit.
&gt;&gt; I'm giving them a Coco
they've never seen.
I'm showing off my heart.
&gt;&gt; She's got a "heart on"
for you.
&gt;&gt; I love that little shy thing
she does like Prince.
[laughs]
&gt;&gt; Alyssa Edwards.
She's showing off her poochy.
She's not ashamed.
&gt;&gt; I'm showing off my legs,
and they are wearing
the runway out.
&gt;&gt; That's how you wear
that caftan dress.
&gt;&gt; That's what I'm saying.
Take that, Honey Mahogany.
&gt;&gt; Jade Jolie, rainbow bright.
&gt;&gt; I'm featuring my arms.
I try not to carry over
5 pounds,
so I'm very proud to have
the petite arms that I have.
&gt;&gt; She forgot to shave.
[laughs]
&gt;&gt; Ivy Winters.
&gt;&gt; Ivy's a real pinup.
&gt;&gt; I decided to make a dress
completely out of paper,
pictures of my face.
[laughs]
&gt;&gt; I love that dress!
Just don't get near
the shredder.
&gt;&gt; No.
&gt;&gt; Or an open flame.
&gt;&gt; Jinkx Monsoon.
&gt;&gt; It reminds me of
the really old Hollywood movies.
The glamour movies.
&gt;&gt; My look tonight
is rich, white bitch.
And my attitude tonight
is so over it.
&gt;&gt; Waiter, can you wrap
that ass to go?
[laughter]
Roxxxy Andrews.
&gt;&gt; Bam!
&gt;&gt; Oh, hey!
&gt;&gt; An element of surprise.
&gt;&gt; Give me body.
&gt;&gt; I've learned to love
every single piece of my body,
and I want them to see it.
&gt;&gt; She's so shy.
No, she's not.
&gt;&gt; Ooh.
&gt;&gt; Alaska.
&gt;&gt; That sweet little girl
who caught our eye.
&gt;&gt; Well, I was going to come out
in ass-less chaps,
but they were at the cleaners.
So I'm showing off
this bone right here.
&gt;&gt; There is purple ice
in Alaska.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Hi.
Detox.
It's just so simple and elegant.
&gt;&gt; I know.
&gt;&gt; It's a simple--
all: Oh!
&gt;&gt; Say "yes" to crack.
&gt;&gt; The minute I turn around
and show them that ass, honey,
it was
♪ Over ♪
Body-ody-ody realness.
&gt;&gt; She got that dress
from her crack dealer.
&gt;&gt; Peek-a-ru!
I see you.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; Welcome, ladies.
It's my honor to present
the world premiere of
Can I Get an Amen?
[synthesizer fanfare]
♪ ♪
[piano music]
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
♪ If you can't love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell you gonna ♪
♪ Love somebody else? ♪
♪ Say amen ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ I lost all hope today ♪
♪ My car broke down ♪
♪ I'm empty ♪
♪ So I went to a friendly bar ♪
♪ There was a show ♪
♪ This one's different ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Lost and confused ♪
♪ I had to smile from within ♪
♪ When I realized ♪
♪ These women were men ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Your beard ♪
♪ Grew back again ♪
♪ Girl, that's okay ♪
all: ♪ Just keep shaving ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ All your dreams ♪
♪ In front of you ♪
♪ Just don't sashay ♪
all: ♪ No misbehavin' ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Don't let ♪
♪ The weight of the world ♪
♪ Flatten your weave ♪
all: ♪ Just tease it out ♪
♪ Turn Adam to Eve ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ When life pulls you down ♪
♪ Put on a shiny ♪
♪ Sequinsed gown ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ If you can't get a gig ♪
♪ Go buy yourself
a lace-front wig ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Just tuck your junk ♪
♪ And hit that runway ♪
all: ♪ It'll get better ♪
♪ Some day ♪
all: ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get ♪
♪ Oh, can I get an amen? ♪
♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
all: ♪ If you can't ♪
♪ Love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell ♪
♪ You gonna love ♪
♪ Somebody else? ♪
♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
all: ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Where my people at? ♪
♪ Where my people at? ♪
&gt;&gt; all: ♪ If you can't ♪
♪ Love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell ♪
♪ You gonna love ♪
♪ Somebody else? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Love somebody else ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Amen ♪
all: ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
all: ♪ If you can't ♪
♪ Love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell ♪
♪ You gonna love ♪
♪ Somebody else? ♪
♪ A-amen ♪
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; Nice work, ladies.
The single is available
on iTunes.
And a portion of the proceeds
will go
to the L.A. Gay &amp; Lesbian
Center's
homeless youth services.
Yes.
Now it's time for
the judges' critiques.
&gt;&gt; How do you tuck your junk?
[both laugh]
&gt;&gt; No!
Worry about you!
&gt;&gt; [giggles]
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
Ladies, this week
you worked as teams,
but tonight you'll be judged
individually.
Starting with Coco Montrese.
&gt;&gt; I was a little confused
with the top.
I wasn't sure what it was
showing me.
&gt;&gt; Coco, we lost you
in that number.
&gt;&gt; I know that the two of you
have had your differences
in the past.
What was it like working
together as a group?
&gt;&gt; I thought that Detox
was trying to be
a little malicious
when she put us together.
&gt;&gt; Truly, I was not.
I just think that you got
in your head
a little bit too much
yesterday.
&gt;&gt; Coco, you have to stay
grounded in your own foundation.
All right.
Alyssa Edwards.
&gt;&gt; You are absolutely gorgeous.
Your singing...
[laughs]
That's kind of a bit different.
[both laugh]
&gt;&gt; It's clear you do not sing,
but that did not stop you.
You were very funny
and still in it.
&gt;&gt; Next up, Jade Jolie.
&gt;&gt; The singing, it was a little
bit of a let down.
&gt;&gt; It was almost as if you were
dying for this song to get over.
&gt;&gt; I don't know what's going on
here,
hair coming out of the hips,
hair coming out of a boob.
What?
&gt;&gt; Next up, Ivy Winters.
&gt;&gt; Hi, mama.
&gt;&gt; I love your dress.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Are those your pictures
on there?
&gt;&gt; They're all my face,
body shots.
&gt;&gt; Oh, that is so clever.
&gt;&gt; You can carry a tune as well.
I liked your harmonies the best.
You stood out.
&gt;&gt; Next up, Jinkx Monsoon.
&gt;&gt; I love the way you held that
long note.
That just put all the icing
on the cake for me.
&gt;&gt; Look, I'm gonna give you
a tip.
You don't need to contour
so hard.
Though we have
a touch of crazy in us,
you don't need to
look it.
&gt;&gt; Next up, Roxxxy Andrews.
One question.
Is that your skin color?
Is that all painted on?
&gt;&gt; That's peanut butter.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Peanut butter.
&gt;&gt; Peanut butter, peanut butter.
&gt;&gt; It was so hot from the moment
you stepped out there.
And when you threw that
cape off, it was on, honey.
&gt;&gt; In the video, as a group,
it was rough, because
no one was harmonizing
and it got
a little monotonous.
&gt;&gt; What's going on with you
and Detox?
&gt;&gt; Rolaskatox.
&gt;&gt; You got this little sisterly
thing going on?
&gt;&gt; We're just becoming
best of friends,
and Alaska as well.
&gt;&gt; Remember, this is
a competition.
Cliques can be dangerous.
&gt;&gt; All right, next up, Detox.
&gt;&gt; Stunning shape tonight,
and a real payoff
when you turned around.
&gt;&gt; I get worried about you
relying on crutches.
Last week you lip synched for
your life,
and you did
your little jaw thing,
and it's funny.
Let's not kill it.
&gt;&gt; All right.
Who's gonna ask her?
Al-as-ka!
&gt;&gt; Hi.
&gt;&gt; I loved the lyric
when you said,
I think it was,
"tuck my junk"?
Yeah, I--
How do you tuck your junk?
&gt;&gt; After the show,
I can show you.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; I'm almost getting bored.
Something's missing, Alaska.
In your singing performance,
you were hiding behind glasses,
almost so we don't
get to see you.
I don't know why
you're holding back.
Don't worry about your group,
whoever you're with.
No!
Worry about you!
We want to see what Alaska has.
Bring it.
&gt;&gt; I get a sense that you hide
behind shticky character.
There's a level of vulnerability
that you're not allowing us
to see.
You are in a relationship with
Sharon Needles,
and she's got the shtick,
but there is a heart there.
And I want to get to the heart
of Alaska.
Are you hearing any of that?
&gt;&gt; I'm...
um, I need to show you
the real me
and--and show that
to you every time.
To hear that I don't have
a heart,
and I don't have vulnerability,
that's extremely hard
for me to hear.
&gt;&gt; All right, ladies,
while you untuck
in the Interior Illusions
lounge,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right.
Just between us siblings,
what do you think?
Let's start with Coco Montrese.
&gt;&gt; Child, that highlighter
was higher and lighter
than I've seen in many a time.
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; I don't think she's focused,
and that's her problem.
The stronger people are gonna
take over
and win at the end of the day,
and that's what's happening
right here.
&gt;&gt; Alyssa Edwards.
&gt;&gt; I loved her look tonight.
She was showcasing legs
and face.
&gt;&gt; She does that walk.
Every time she goes somewhere,
she points to the...
&gt;&gt; Yes.
&gt;&gt; Spot she's gonna go to.
&gt;&gt; "I'm going over here."
"Now I'm going over here."
"Back here."
&gt;&gt; I love it.
&gt;&gt; Her singing was
a little off balance.
&gt;&gt; She's not a great singer.
Don't judge me!
&gt;&gt; But I think she compensated
for that with her movement.
&gt;&gt; Let's move on to Jade Jolie.
Oh, my goodness, that outfit.
&gt;&gt; It just was a miss
on so many levels.
I don't even know
where to begin.
&gt;&gt; I don't really remember
her vocals.
I guess I wasn't impressed.
&gt;&gt; Forgettable.
Just forgettable.
&gt;&gt; Moving on to Ivy Winters.
&gt;&gt; Tonight, on the runway,
was very creative.
&gt;&gt; I like when she added
the harmony to the song.
I thought that was very good.
&gt;&gt; The girl can sing.
She really surprised me.
&gt;&gt; Jinkx Monsoon.
&gt;&gt; There was, like, 20 different
eras going on tonight
in this glamour.
The belt was from the '80s,
the dress was, like, the '50s.
There are so many things
that are consistently a mess.
&gt;&gt; But she can sing.
Jinkx has some pipes.
&gt;&gt; Very strong and powerful.
Liked it very much.
&gt;&gt; Roxxxy Andrews.
&gt;&gt; When it comes to sexy,
she was the top for me.
&gt;&gt; She could not sing a lick,
and that did not stop her.
She was hilarious.
&gt;&gt; Moving on to Detox.
&gt;&gt; She kind of phoned it in
in the song department.
&gt;&gt; Can't remember
the performance.
The dress just
took my mind away.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; Crack is back,
and that was that.
&gt;&gt; Alaska.
&gt;&gt; Every time
she comes out here,
she's got the same
little wiggle,
the same little, "Hi."
I'm bored.
&gt;&gt; I think, truthfully,
that she's given us all she has.
Michelle, this is probably it.
Remember,
we're paring everybody off,
and the competition's getting
really strict and hard now.
&gt;&gt; Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls,
and, uh, can I get an amen?
all: Amen.
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get an amen? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Where my people at? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Bring back my girls ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ love yourself ♪
♪ How in the hell you gonna ♪
♪ love somebody else? ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Can I get a gay-men? ♪
[giggles]
[laughs]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
This week's winner is...
Ivy Winters.
[applause]
You've won a Flight 001 package.
Luggage for the queen on the go.
&gt;&gt; Thank you so much.
I'm so excited that I won
this challenge,
and I proved to the judges
that I am here for a reason.
&gt;&gt; Jinkx Monsoon, you're safe.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Roxxxy Andrews.
You are safe.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Detox.
You're safe.
But--
and it's a big butt--
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; We expect more from you.
You may join the other girls.
Alaska, you've been coasting
on kooky,
and we want you to go deeper.
You're safe.
Coco Montrese,
this week you wore your heart
on your sleeve
but your mind got
the better of you.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Alyssa Edwards, your singing
proved you are...
an amazing dancer.
&gt;&gt; [laughs]
&gt;&gt; Jade Jolie, you light up
our lives,
but this week, you let the other
queens outshine you.
Jade Jolie,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Alyssa Edwards, you are safe.
You may join the other girls.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip-synch performance of
I'm So Excited
by the legendary
Pointer Sisters.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come for you to
lip-synch for your life.
&gt;&gt; Everything that I didn't give
in that video,
I have to pull it
and give it right now
'cause this is my last chance.
&gt;&gt; Good luck.
And don't fuck it up.
[disco music]
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ Tonight's the night ♪
♪ We're gonna make it happen ♪
♪ We're going for ♪
♪ Those pleasures
in the night ♪
♪ I want to love you ♪
♪ Feel you ♪
♪ Wrap myself around you ♪
♪ I want to squeeze you... ♪
&gt;&gt; I'm spinning, I'm kicking.
I'm high energy and fun.
I'm just laying everything
on the table.
&gt;&gt; ♪ I'll let it go ♪
♪ I'm so excited ♪
♪ And I just can't hide it ♪
♪ I'm about to lose control ♪
♪ And I think I like it ♪
&gt;&gt; I can't underestimate Jade.
She wants this just as bad
as I do.
I've got to give this my all.
&gt;&gt; ♪ I know, I know, I know ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ I think you get to me ♪
♪ I've got to give it up ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
&gt;&gt; Whoo!
[applause]
&gt;&gt; Yeah!
&gt;&gt; Ladies, I've made
my decision.
Coco Montrese,
shante, you stay.
You may join the other girls.
Jade, I'm so proud of you.
&gt;&gt; Thank you so much.
This has been the most amazing
experience in my life.
[cries]
&gt;&gt; Keep being tres jolie.
&gt;&gt; Girl, I will.
&gt;&gt; Now, sashay away.
&gt;&gt; Thank you, guys.
I gave it my all,
and if anyone was gonna
send me home,
at least it was a close friend.
This has been so amazing,
and I'm just gonna keep going
and be more fabulous
than I've ever been.
&gt;&gt; My drag-nificent seven,
remember.
If you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
all: Amen.
&gt;&gt; All right.
Let the music play.
[RuPaul's The Beginning]
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ Of the rest of ♪