- PREVIOUSLY
ON "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
- WHEN I WAS 17,
I APPEARED ON "AMERICAN IDOL."
- I WAS A FINALIST
ON THE FIRST SEASON
OF "AUSTRALIAN IDOL."
- OH, WE'RE PLAYING THAT
THIS YEAR, BITCH?
- FOR THIS WEEK'S MAIN
CHALLENGE,
YOU'LL BE SCREEN TESTING
FOR "DRAG RACE ME TO HELL."
- ACTION.
- [SCREAMING]
- DID YOU GUYS REHEARSE
AS A TEAM BEFORE YOU CAME ON?
- YEAH.
- LIZA MINNELLI LIES.
- DARIENNE LAKE,
YOU ARE THE WINNER
OF THIS WEEK'S MAIN CHALLENGE.
- WHAT?
- APRIL CARRION,
SHANTE, YOU STAY.
VIVACIOUS, SASHAY AWAY.
- OOH, THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- I KNOW, GIRL.
- UGH!
VIVACIOUS JUST GOT ELIMINATED
AND I'M FUCKING GLAD
TO GET ANOTHER BITCH
OUT OF HERE,
BECAUSE, HONEY,
WE NEED TO START
KNOCKING THEM ONE BY ONE.
- THANK YOU, MISS VIVACIOUS.
YOU WILL BE MISSED.
I'M DETERMINED TO SHOW RU
THAT I AM WORTHY OF BEING HERE.
THESE BITCHES BETTER GET READY
BECAUSE I'VE JUST GOTTEN
A WAKE-UP CALL.
- PARTY.
- [GROANS]
- OY, MAMI, OY.
- [MOANING]
- YES, WHO'S SERVING?
- ARE YOU IN
A WHITE SNAKE VIDEO?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OVER THERE?
- I'M FEELING MY OATS.
LET ME FEEL MY OATS.
- WHEN I FIRST MET GIA,
I DIDN'T LIKE HER.
- YOU LADYBOY?
YOU LADYBOY?
- NOW, SHE'S KIND OF
GROWN ON ME,
LIKE A RASH.
BEING FISH IS NOT GOING TO WIN
THIS COMPETITION.
- DON'T BE COMING
OVER HERE, NOW,
BECAUSE YOU ALL SAFE AND STUFF.
NOW, YOU'RE THROWING IN
MY MOTHERFUCKING PIT.
- SUBTITLES.
SHE'S FISH,
BUT SHE'S GONNA BE FLOATING
ON TOP--
DEAD.
- ♪ RUPAUL DRAG RACE ♪
- THE WINNER
OF "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
RECEIVES A SICKENING SUPPLY
OF COLOREVOLUTION COSMETICS
AND A CASH PRIZE OF $100,000.
WITH EXTRA SPECIAL GUEST JUDGES,
LUCIAN PIANE
AND SHERYL LEE RALPH.
- ♪ RUPAUL DRAG RACE ♪
♪ MAY THE BEST WOMAN ♪
♪ BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
- OH, YES, HONEY,
CLAP FOR THE KIDS.
- AH!
- IT'S A BRAND NEW DAY
IN THE WORKROOM.
EVERYBODY'S FEELING
OUR OATS, GRAINS,
WHEATS, THINS,
EVERYTHING.
WE'RE READY FOR ALL THE TWISTED
AND SICK LITTLE CHALLENGES
THAT RU HAS IN STORE FOR US.
- SO, WHO'S EXCITED FOR TODAY?
- ME, ME, ME.
- I WAS UNTIL I HEARD
YOUR VOICE.
- OH, BITCH,
HERE SHE GOES.
[SIREN WAILS]
- OOH, GIRL.
HEY, DREAM GIRLS.
NOW THAT YOU'VE HAD
YOUR SPRING AWAKENING,
IT'S TIME TO STRAP ON
YOUR KINKY BOOTS
AND FORM A CHORUS LINE.
AND IT BETTER BE WICKED GOOD.
OTHERWISE,
IT'S BYE-BYE, BIRDIE.
[GIGGLES]
- COME ON, MUSICAL THEATER!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- YES!
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO.
- HI!
- NOW, THIS WEEK,
IN THE MOST AMBITIOUS CHALLENGE
IN "DRAG RACE" HISTORY,
YOU'LL BE PERFORMING LIVE
IN THE ORIGINAL
PRODUCTION OF...
"SHADE, THE RUSICAL."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- I LOVE MUSICAL THEATER.
IT'S JUST SO CAMPY
AND CHEESY AND--ME!
- NOW, YOU'LL BE WORKING
IN TWO GROUPS.
BENDELACREME AND ADORE DELANO,
YOU GET TO CHOOSE
YOUR CASTMATES
AND ASSIGN THE ROLES--
BACK ROLLS.
[LAUGHTER]
- I'LL START OFF
WITH MISS COURTNEY.
[GASPS]
- I'M GONNA GO WITH MILK.
- MISS HOW-TO-
SUCCEED-IN-BITCHINESS-
WITHOUT-REALLY-TRYING,
MISS BIANCA DEL RIO.
- AH, YOU'RE SO CLEVER.
- MISS LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- EVERYTHING'S COMING UP ROSES,
DARLING.
- DE LA?
- MISS DARIENNE LAKE.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- MISS JOSLYN FOX.
- GIA, MY PET.
- YEAH!
- MISS APRIL.
- AND THAT MEANS
TRINITY K. BONET,
YOU'RE WITH
BENDELACREME'S TEAM.
[APPLAUSE]
- YAY, I GOT PICKED
LAST AGAIN.
NO BIGGIE,
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
- LATER TODAY,
YOU'LL BE WORKING
WITH THE COMPOSER
OF "SHADE, THE RUSICAL,"
LUCIAN PIANE.
[APPLAUSE]
LADIES, I EXPECT PERFORMANCES
WORTHY OF THE GREAT WHITE WAY.
BUT THEN AGAIN,
WHY IT GOTTA BE WHITE?
[LAUGHTER]
THEATER PEOPLE,
START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN.
- ALL RIGHT, LADIES,
LET'S MAKE SOME MAGIC.
MY GOAL AS A LEADER
IS TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO UTILIZE
EVERYONE IN THE GROUP BEST.
INGENUE QUEEN, PENNY.
WE'RE JUST ALL ASSUMING
YOU'RE PENNY, RIGHT?
I MEAN, THAT'S WHAT--
[LAUGHS]
- I'M HAPPY TO PLAY PENNY.
- COURTNEY'S THE OBVIOUS PENNY.
THAT'S JUST WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
PAGEANT QUEENS, COMEDY QUEENS.
I JUST KEEP THINKING
IT WOULD BE HYSTERICAL
TO SEE YOU PLAY
A PAGEANT QUEEN.
- NO, THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
- TRINITY, DOES BEING
A PAGEANT QUEEN
OR A COMEDY QUEEN SEEM
INTERESTING TO YOU?
- NO, I DON'T WANT
TO BE THE FUCK-UP,
SO I'D RATHER JUST
KIND OF PLAY IT SAFE.
- YOU PREFER TO BE
A PAGEANT QUEEN?
- YEAH.
- YEAH, OKAY.
- TRINITY,
SHE ALWAYS SEEMS OVER IT,
NOTHING EXCITES HER.
- DO WE WANT TO HAVE
A SING-THROUGH?
- YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
- OKAY.
♪ WELL, I'M GONNA BE
THE GREATEST STAR ♪
♪ AND NOTHING AND NO ONE
WILL KEEP ME DOWN ♪
- ♪ JUST A MIRACLE
IN FRONT OF YOU ♪
- THERE'S A BIT OF PRESSURE
BECAUSE ADORE
IS A SINGER, AS WELL.
- ♪ I WILL SHOW YOU
I'LL TEACH YOU ♪
- ♪ LET ME BE YOUR STAR ♪
- ♪ BE ♪
- ♪ AHH ♪
- BOTH ADORE AND COURTNEY
ARE AMAZING SINGERS.
"SHADE, THE RUSICAL"
HAS NOW BECOME
THE BATTLE OF THE IDOLS.
- ♪ WHEN YOU LOVE ME ♪
- I'M GONNA TAKE HER DOWN.
- COMING UP--
- GIA, HER VOICE IS LIKE
NAILS ON A CHALKBOARD.
- ♪ WE ARE THE COMEDY QUEENS ♪
- EEHH!
- TRINITY IS GETTING
A LITTLE RUDE.
- CAN WE DO IT?
BECAUSE IT'S A LOT DIFFERENT.
- CALM DOWN, BEYONCE.
- [LAUGHS]
- ♪ AND WE ARE THE QUEENS ♪
OUR CHALLENGE IS TO PERFORM
IN THE WORLD PREMIERE
OF "SHADE, THE RUSICAL."
WE HAVE TO ACT,
SING, AND DANCE,
AND DO IT ALL LIVE, MAMA.
- OKAY, NOW WE CAN GO THROUGH,
LIKE, WHO'S WHO.
- THAT SAYS "GOOD PENNY"
AND "BAD PENNY."
- "FISH OIL HAS TURNED PENNY
INTO A HORRIBLE DIVA BITCH."
BAD PENNY IS CLEARLY ME.
COURTNEY IS DEFINITELY
GOOD PENNY.
SHE'S VERY DISNEY,
AND I'M VERY COURTNEY LOVE.
AMANDA, PRETTY BUT BUTCH QUEEN.
- I DON'T WANT TO BE
A BUTCH QUEEN.
- OKAY, I DON'T WANNA MAKE HER
A BUTCH QUEEN AGAIN.
- I COULD BE BERTHA,
BUT BERTHA IS LIKE A BIG GIRL,
SO, WOULD I--I DON'T KNOW,
JUST PAD MYSELF, I GUESS?
- JUST PAD YOURSELF
TO HIGH HEAVENS.
- I AM HAPPY BECAUSE
I DIDN'T GET THE BUTCH CARD,
SO THANK GOD FOR THAT,
"DIOS MIO," YEAH.
- ♪ WE ARE THE COMEDY QUEENS ♪
♪ HUMOR ALWAYS
JUSTIFIES THE MEANS ♪
- GIA, HER VOICE IS LIKE
NAILS ON A CHALKBOARD.
- ♪ WE ARE THE COMEDY QUEENS ♪
- GIA'S VOICE IS KIND OF LIKE
IF FRAN DRESCHER
GOT STEAMROLLED
BY, LIKE, A DYING DUCK.
EEHH!
- [SINGING OUT OF TUNE]
♪ ME, EE, EE ♪
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO.
- HI!
- HOW ARE MY MUSICAL
THEATER QUEENS?
- FABULOUS.
- WELL, TEAM BENDELACREME,
WHO'S PLAYING WHO?
- WELL, OUR INGENUE PENNY
WILL BE PLAYED
BY MISS COURTNEY ACT.
- YOU'RE GOOD PENNY.
- YEAH.
- ARE YOU PREPARED TO SING
THE CRAP OUT OF THIS PART?
- I AM.
MY LATEST THING
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON
IS WHISTLE TONE.
- OH, LIKE MARIAH.
- YEAH.
[SCREECHES]
- NOW TRINITY,
YOU SEEM QUIET.
HAVE YOU DONE
MUSICAL THEATER?
- UH, IN JUNIOR HIGH.
- YEAH, BUT SHE PLAYED
A TREE, SO.
- OH, OKAY.
- JUST LIKE THE ACTING
CHALLENGE, YOU KNOW,
THIS IS NEW FOR ME, TOO.
SO, YOU KNOW,
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT
MY BEST AND--YOU KNOW.
I'M A DRAG QUEEN.
I LIP-SYNC,
I DON'T SING LIVE.
- THIS IS REALLY
ONE OF THOSE CHALLENGES
WHERE YOU HAVE
TO WORK TOGETHER,
AND AT THE SAME TIME,
STAND OUT AS THE STAR
THAT YOU ARE.
- YES.
- SO, GET TO IT, LADIES.
- THANK YOU, SIR.
- THANK YOU.
- WELL, TEAM ADORE, HELLO.
- HELLO, HELLO!
- I'M SO EXCITED.
- IT'S GONNA BE A PARTY.
- NOW, ADORE, WHAT CHARACTER
ARE YOU PLAYING?
- I AM PLAYING BAD PENNY.
- NOW, THAT'S A BIG
SINGING ROLE, ISN'T IT?
- IT IS.
- THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD EXCEL AT.
- IT SHOULD BE COOL.
- WELL, WHY DO YOU
DOUBT YOURSELF LIKE THAT?
LAST WEEK,
THE NOTE FOR YOU
WAS TO BE PREPARED
WHEN YOU HIT THE SET.
YOU HAVE TO DO YOUR HOMEWORK.
- I'M PRETTY NERVOUS,
BECAUSE I REALLY, REALLY
WANT THE JUDGES
TO SEE THAT I'M NOT
A FILLER BITCH.
- SO, YOU 3 ARE
THE SHOWGIRLS.
- YES.
- NOW, WHO ARE YOU PLAYING?
- I'M THE BUTCH QUEEN.
- YOU'RE A BUTCH QUEEN?
WHERE ARE YOU GONNA
DRAW YOUR INSPIRATION?
- BIANCA DEL RIO.
- [LAUGHTER]
- WHOO!
- YES, MA'AM!
- QUEEN DOWN.
- OKAY!
- I CANNOT WAIT TO SEE IT.
ALL RIGHT,
GATHER ROUND, THESPIANS.
PEOPLE, PLACES, PEOPLE.
TOMORROW, AFTER
YOUR MUSICAL DEBUT,
THE DRESS CODE
FOR THE MAIN STAGE IS...
TONY AWARDS GLAMOUR.
- YEAH!
NOW, AS WE SAY
IN THE THEATER, DARLING,
BREAK A LEG,
AND DON'T FUCK IT UP.
- ALL RIGHT.
- IT'S OUR TEAM'S TURN
TO COME IN
AND REHEARSE WITH LUCIAN.
I HAVE DONE SOME MUSICAL THEATER
IN MY PAST,
SO, PIECE OF CAKE.
- HELLO, LADIES.
- HI.
- THIS IS DENISE.
- HEY.
- SHE'S OUR CELEBRITY
CHOREOGRAPHER
AND MY SISTER.
AND OVER HERE,
WE HAVE OUR LADY J,
TRANS ICON
AND PIANIST TO THE STARS.
- HI, GUYS.
- HI.
- OKAY, SO, WHY DON'T YOU
SING OUT A LITTLE BIT, OKAY?
HERE WE GO.
- ♪ AND YOU, AND YOU
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE ME ♪
♪ YOU'RE GONNA LOVE ME ♪
- OKAY,
THERE AT THE END,
MAKE SURE YOUR LAST NOTE
IS THE MOST IMPRESSIVE ONE.
YOU CAN MAKE IT
YOUR MOMENT, YOU KNOW?
- I THINK I'M GONNA BE HELD TO
A HIGHER STANDARD ON THIS ONE,
AND WHEN YOU'RE LIVE ON STAGE,
YOU'VE GOT ONE CHANCE.
DON'T FUCK IT UP.
- ♪ WE ARE THE COMEDY ♪
- ♪ WE ARE THE COMEDY QUEENS ♪
- OH, CUTE.
- ♪ DON'T LISTEN TO THEM BECAUSE
THEY'RE ALL FULL OF BEANS ♪
LITERALLY.
- CUT, CUT, CUT.
WHEN YOU SAY "LITERALLY,"
YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT THE JOKE IS, THERE?
- UM, NOT REALLY.
- IT'S A FART JOKE.
IT'S BECAUSE IT SMELLS--
SMELLS BAD, SO, UH...
IF YOU CAN PLAY UP
THE COMEDY OF IT,
THEN THAT WILL SELL.
YOU GUYS RIGHT NOW
ARE NOT REALLY
FUNNY AT ALL.
- FUCK.
- OKAY, REAL QUICK--
SO PAGEANT QUEENS,
CAN I SHOW YOU
YOUR MOVEMENT REAL QUICK
FOR THIS SECTION?
OKAY, YOU'RE GONNA
STEP FORWARD
ON THE LEFT LEG
TO STRUT, OKAY?
- I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY,
I'M SORRY, I NEED TO KNOW,
WHEN SHE SAID--WHEN SHE SAID
"WHO ARE YOU?"
- WE ARE THE PAGEANT QUEENS.
- DOES THAT MAKE SENSE?
- CAN WE DO IT?
BECAUSE IT'S A LOT DIFFERENT
WHEN YOU'RE TRYING TO--
AND THEN FALL BACK INTO IT.
- WELL, THAT'S HOW WE GET TO
RUN IT SO THAT YOU CAN TRY IT.
- TRINITY IS GETTING
A LITTLE RUDE.
IT AIN'T DENISE'S FAULT THAT
TRINITY CAN'T GET THE MOVES.
CALM DOWN, BEYONCE.
[WHISPERING]
SO, TURN, YOU KNOW--
- WE'RE GOING DOWN,
AND NOT IN A GOOD WAY.
- SORRY, IF I SUCK, I SUCK.
- COMING UP--
- ♪ AND FINALLY
I'M THE STAR ♪
- ♪ NO, I'M THE STAR ♪
- TAKE A SECOND AND CALM DOWN.
- BECAUSE YOU DON'T DO
ANYTHING WRONG.
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT, BITCH.
- [LAUGHS]
- THIS WEEK'S CHALLENGE
IS TO PERFORM
IN "SHADE, THE RUSICAL."
- HELLO, LADIES.
- HI.
- ALL RIGHT, SO LET'S GO.
- ♪ JUST A MIRACLE
IN FRONT OF YOU ♪
♪ OH ♪
- WHY ARE YOU AFRAID?
AREN'T YOU THE SINGER?
- SPIT IT OUT, ADORE.
- IT'S REALLY INTIMIDATING
TO HAVE THE PERSON
WHO ACTUALLY WROTE THIS
IN FRONT OF YOU WHILE
YOU'RE BUTCHERING THE LYRICS.
- I KNOW THAT ALL THOSE WORDS,
THAT'S A LOT.
YOU HAVE TO GET
ALL THAT DOWN,
BECAUSE WHEN YOU GET LOST,
IT IMMEDIATELY SHOWS
IN YOUR EYES.
- I KNOW.
- YOU LOOK ABSOLUTELY TERRIFIED.
- THIS IS THE CHANCE, BASICALLY,
FOR ME TO PROVE MYSELF,
SO, I GOT TO GET IT TOGETHER.
- ♪ AND FINALLY, I'M THE STAR ♪
- ♪ NO, I'M THE STAR ♪
[GIGGLES]
- YOU HAVE A VERY UNIQUE TONE
TO YOUR VOICE.
- I'VE BEEN TOLD THAT.
I LIKE TO THINK THAT I HAVE
A RATHER DISTINCTIVE VOICE.
[LAUGHS]
I'VE EMBRACED IT.
- 2, 3, 4.
- ♪ WELL, I'M NOT GOING
TO STICK AROUND ♪
♪ AND BE A PART OF HER SHOW ♪
- OKAY, STOP FOR ONE SECOND.
THAT SORT OF RHYTHMIC
TALK-SINGING
THAT YOU'RE DOING RIGHT NOW
IS NOT COMING OFF THAT GREAT.
- AY, DIOS MIO.
- ♪ CENTER STAGE ♪
- ♪ AND FINALLY I'M THE STAR ♪
- APRIL, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO NECESSARILY SCREAM IT OUT--
- ♪ AND FINALLY I'M THE STAR ♪
- WELL, YOU JUST
WENT UP AGAIN.
- I NEED TO PROVE
THAT I CAN PULL THIS
FOR ME AND FOR MY TEAM,
SO, I CAN'T BE
A DOWNWARD DEBBIE--
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HER NAME IS.
- SHOWGIRLS,
YOUR ACT IS GOING TO BE
THE SINK-OR-SWIM THING
OF THIS WHOLE TEAM.
- THIS IS A HUGE CHALLENGE.
LIKE, ONE PERSON'S OFF,
WE ALL FALL LIKE DOMINOES.
- TRINITY IS DEFINITELY
NOT 100% HERE,
IS SHE FRUSTRATED SEXUALLY?
I HAVE NO IDEA,
BUT GUESS WHAT?
WE HAVE ABOUT THIS MUCH TIME
AND ABOUT THIS MUCH WORK TO DO,
SO, BITCH, GET INTO IT.
- ALL RIGHT, FROM THE TOP.
- TURN AROUND.
- NO, YOU'RE COMING
WITH ME, MISSY.
BOOM.
- I'M YOU.
DO YOU SEE THE DIFFICULTNESS
IN DOING IT BACKWARDS
AND THEN TRYING TO TURN AROUND
AT THE SAME TIME?
IT'S REALLY, REALLY FAST.
- SHE HAS TO BE HERE.
- IT TOOK YOU TOO LONG TO MOVE,
I'M TELLING YOU,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO HIT IT.
YOU HAVE TO TRY TO--
- CONSIDERING THIS HAS BEEN
YOUR PROBLEM AREA,
TAKE A SECOND AND CALM DOWN.
I WALK TO HER,
AND I SAY "TURN AROUND."
I WOULD SUGGEST YOU FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOU NEED TO DO
PRIOR TO TELLING ME
WHAT I'M NOT DOING RIGHT.
- YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT,
BIANCA,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T DO
ANYTHING WRONG.
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT, BITCH.
- I APOLOGIZE THAT I OPENED
MY MOUTH, AND THAT'S WHY
I DON'T SAY ANYTHING
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- COVER GIRL,
PUT THAT BASS IN YOUR WALK,
COME ON!
- COME ON, GIRL.
- TODAY, ON THE MAIN STAGE,
OUR RUNWAY LOOK
IS TONY AWARDS GLAMOUR,
AND WE'RE PERFORMING
IN "SHADE, THE RUSICAL."
WE HAVE TO SING LIVE,
ALTHOUGH YOU'VE SEEN
SOME OF THE PEOPLE
IN MY GROUP.
- YOU READY TO SERVE
SOME PAGEANT REALNESS OUT THERE?
- YES, GOD, BITCH, UGH.
- OKAY?
- I'M GOING TO GET ME
A TONY TONIGHT.
- WHAT'S A TONY?
- SO, YOU WERE ON THE IDOL
OF THE AMERICAN.
- YES.
AND YOU WERE ON THE IDOL
OF THE AUSTRALIAN.
- I WAS.
I WENT ALONG
THE FIRST DAY AS A BOY
AND I GOT KNOCKED BACK,
AND SO THEN I WENT BACK
THE NEXT DAY IN DRAG,
AND I MADE IT THROUGH
TO THE FINALS.
- HOLY CRAP.
- I WAS THE FIRST OUT GAY PERSON
AND THE FIRST PERSON IN DRAG
TO BE ON ANY IDOL FRANCHISE
ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.
- I WISH I COULD'VE DID THAT.
- YEAH, BUT ADORE,
DON'T YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU WERE SORT OF
THE AMERICAN COUNTERPART OF,
LIKE, THE FIRST REAL SORT OF
GAY PERSON ON "AMERICAN IDOL?"
- YEAH, BUT I WAS
KIND OF ADVISED
TO JUST NOT BE SO OUT THERE.
- SO, YOU ACTUALLY HAD TO, LIKE,
KIND OF KEEP YOURSELF--
- TONE IT DOWN A LITTLE.
- YEAH.
- RIGHT.
- SOME PEOPLE WEREN'T LIKING IT.
- MY MOM TOLD ME TO BUTCH IT UP
BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T WANT THEM
MAKING FUN OF ME.
SHE SHOULD'VE JUST LET ME
GO OUT THERE WITH PINK HAIR.
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN COOL.
- GIA, WHAT WERE SOME
OF YOUR TALENTS AS A CHILD
BESIDES TUCKING YOUR WEENIE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT?
[LAUGHTER]
- I ACTUALLY WAS DOING
THE DANCE FORM OF KABUKI THEATER
SINCE I WAS 5 YEARS OLD.
IN JAPAN, KABUKI THEATER
IS ALL MEN,
BUT WE WOULDN'T, LIKE, GET
TUCKED AND, LIKE, PUT BOOBS ON
AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
IN MY CULTURE,
IT'S NOT A GAY THING,
SO EVEN STRAIGHT MEN DO IT.
IT'S AN ART.
THIS IS LIKE WHEN I WOULD DO,
LIKE, THE BOY ROLES.
AND THIS IS ONE I WOULD DO
THE FISH ROLE.
- NO WAY!
- LOOKING GOOD.
- WITH MY THEATER BACKGROUND
IN KABUKI,
I DEFINITELY HAVE
A GOOD SENSE
OF STAGE PRESENCE
AND THE CHOREOGRAPHY,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I'M REALLY HOPING
FOR THE BEST,
BECAUSE SOME OF US
AIN'T SINGERS, WE DANCERS.
- ♪ COVER GIRL
PUT THE BASS IN YOUR WALK ♪
♪ HEAD TO TOE
LET YOUR WHOLE BODY TALK ♪
♪ AND WHAT ♪
- WELCOME TO THE MAIN STAGE
OF "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE,"
STAR OF "BREAST SIDE STORY,"
MICHELLE VISAGE.
- YES, AND AREN'T YOU AMAZING
IN TECHNICOLOR?
- AND FROM "THE BOOK OF MORON,"
SANTINO RICE.
[LAUGHTER]
- MY POSSE'S ON BROADWAY, RU.
- WELL, MY POSSE'S ON FIRE.
[LAUGHTER]
AND OUR VERY OWN MUSIC MAN,
LUCIAN PIANE.
HOW WAS IT WORKING
WITH MY BROADWAY BABIES?
- YOU ARE SURE IN FOR A TREAT.
- I'LL BE THE JUDGE OF THAT.
[LAUGHS]
AND THE LEGENDARY STAR
OF STAGE AND SCREEN,
THE OG DREAM GIRL,
SHERYL LEE RALPH.
- DARLING, LOOK AT YOU.
I LOVE EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU.
- I AM SO EXCITED
TO HAVE YOU HERE.
THIS WEEK, WE CHALLENGED
OUR LEADING LADIES
TO TREAD THE BOARDS IN A MUSICAL
COMEDY EXTRAVAGANZA,
"SHADE, THE RUSICAL."
NOW, THEY'RE READY TO MAKE
THEIR OFF-OFF-OFF-OFF-OFF-
OFF-BROADWAY DEBUT.
GENTLEMEN, START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN.
COMING UP--
- YOU GOT A LITTLE LOST.
- YOU WERE WAY OFF.
- IT'S LIKE YOU HAVE A BEARD
ON YOUR FOREHEAD.
- [LAUGHS]
- ACT ONE,
"SHADE, THE RUSICAL."
LET'S GO.
- IN THE CITY
OF DRAG QUEENS,
THERE'S A FINE LINE
BETWEEN BEING SHADY,
AND BEING A LADY.
THIS IS PENNY,
WHICH WILL SHE CHOOSE?
- ♪ I JUST GOT OFF THE BUS ♪
♪ I DON'T DRINK OR EAT OR CUSS ♪
- ♪ YOU'RE NEW IN TOWN ♪
- ♪ IT'S TIME TO KNUCKLE DOWN ♪
- ♪ START SWIMMING TO THE TOP
BEFORE YOU DROWN ♪
- WHO ARE YOU?
- ♪ WE ARE THE PAGEANT QUEENS ♪
- OH, FANCY!
- ♪ WE'RE ELEGANT MACHINES ♪
♪ IN GOWNS WE STRUT ♪
♪ WE DON'T NEED CORNY SMUT ♪
- WHAT?
- ♪ LET'S HOLD BACK
AND SEE WHICH WAY SHE LEANS ♪
- WHO ARE YOU?
♪ WE ARE THE COMEDY QUEENS ♪
- OH, CUTE.
- ♪ HUMOR ALWAYS
JUSTIFIES THE MEANS ♪
- ♪ WHILE SHE'S THERE
TELLING A JOKE ♪
- UGH!
- ♪ I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU, POKE ♪
- OH!
- ♪ DON'T LISTEN TO THEM ♪
♪ BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL
FULL OF BEANS ♪
- LITERALLY.
- WHO'S THAT?
- WAIT!
♪ SHE'S THE SHADY QUEEN
HORRID QUEEN ♪
♪ NO ONE WANTS TO SEE HER ♪
- ♪ ON HER OWN
ALL ALONE ♪
♪ NO ONE WANTS TO BE HER ♪
- ♪ LISTEN UP, PRETTY PUP ♪
- ♪ SHE'S ON HER WAY
TO 6 FEET ♪
- ♪ UNDERGROUND ♪
- ♪ YES, AND NOTHING NICE
NOTHING GOOD ♪
♪ EVER GOES HER WAY SO ♪
- MISS OFF-A-BUS
LIVES WITH US ♪
♪ EVEN RU WOULD SAY SO ♪
- WHO?
- [GASP]
♪ RUPAUL ♪
-OH.
- ♪ TURN AROUND ♪
♪ WE ARE THE BETTER QUEENS
THE SAFER QUEENS ♪
♪ THE LIGHTER QUEENS
THE BRIGHTER QUEENS ♪
♪ THE WISER QUEENS
ADVISOR QUEENS ♪
♪ THE ONES WHO
YOU SHOULD STICK WITH ♪
- PENNY, YOU REALLY WANT
TO BE A STAR?
- YEAH, I DO.
- NO!
- DON'T DO IT.
- DON'T GO.
- SHE'S A MAN
WITH ONE EYE!
- ♪ THERE'S A HOLE
IN YOUR HEART ♪
♪ THERE'S A PLACE
IN YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ A PASSION SO STRONG
IT MAKES YOUR BLOOD BOIL ♪
♪ ALL YOUR DREAMS COME ALIVE ♪
♪ ALL YOUR WISHES WILL GROW ♪
♪ IF YOU TAKE A SWIG
OF THIS FISH OIL ♪
DRINK FOR ME.
- OH, I'D REALLY LIKE TO,
BUT I SHOULDN'T, I--
- DRINK FOR ME!
- I DO WANT TO BE A BIG,
BIG STAR.
- DRINK FOR ME!
- ♪ DON'T DO IT
DON'T DO IT ♪
- ♪ DRINK FOR ME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL LOSE IT
YOU'LL LOSE IT ♪
- ♪ WELL, I'M GOING TO BE
THE GREATEST STAR ♪
♪ AND NOTHING AND NO ONE'S
GONNA KEEP ME DOWN ♪
♪ AND YOU AND YOU
AND ALL OF YOU ♪
♪ I'LL MAKE YOU LOVE ME ♪
- ♪ DON'T DO IT
DON'T DO IT ♪
- OH, I CAN'T GET IT OPEN.
- HERE.
- ♪ DON'T DO IT
DON'T DO IT ♪
- ♪ WATCH ME BE YOUR STAR ♪
- ♪ NO "T," NO SHADE ♪
[APPLAUSE]
- OH, ACT TWO
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
- THANKS TO FISH OIL,
OUR GOOD LITTLE PENNY
BECAME ONE BAD PENNY,
BUT SHE GOT HER FAME.
- ♪ BECAUSE I'M
THE BIGGEST STAR ♪
♪ AND I'M GOING FAR ♪
♪ JUST A MIRACLE
IN FRONT OF YOU ♪
♪ OH, AND IF YOU
DON'T BELIEVE ♪
♪ I WILL SHOW YOU ♪
♪ I'LL TEACH YOU
I'LL SCHOOL YOU ♪
♪ I'LL BEAT YOU
AND PUNCH YOU ♪
♪ AND CRUNCH YOU
I'LL TAKE YOU ♪
♪ AND MAKE YOU THANK ME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOVE ME ♪
- THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT,
BACK ROLLS.
[LAUGHTER]
- ♪ DO YOU SEE
WHAT SHE SAID TO ME? ♪
- BACK ROLLS.
- HEARD IT.
- ♪ CAN YOU BELIEVE
CAN YOU BELIEVE ♪
♪ SHE EVEN SAID THAT? ♪
- ♪ YES, SHE REALLY DID ♪
- ♪ OH, YEAH, SHE REALLY,
REALLY WENT THERE ♪
- ♪ WELL, I'M NOT GONNA
STICK AROUND ♪
♪ AND BE A PART OF HER SHOW ♪
- BUT YOU HAVE TO.
- GIRL, THE PAYCHECK.
- OH, RIGHT.
- MM-HMM.
♪ NO, I'LL NEVER LOVE
ANYONE ELSE ♪
♪ LIKE I LOVE MYSELF ♪
♪ OH, NO, NO, NO ♪
♪ I'LL NEVER LOVE
ANYONE ELSE ♪
- AY, DIOS MIO,
SHE'S GOING DOWN!
TOO MUCH FISH OIL!
- NOW'S OUR CHANCE!
- ♪ WATCH US RISE TO THE TOP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE'RE THE FRESH FISH
ON THE SCENE ♪
♪ WE'RE THE NEW GIRLS IN TOWN ♪
♪ WE'RE STEPPING
RIGHT OVER THIS QUEEN ♪
♪ SHE'S BEEN THROWING
SOME SHADE ♪
♪ AND NOW WE DON'T
GIVE A DAMN ♪
♪ TAKE AWAY HER FISH OIL ♪
♪ AND THERE AIN'T
NOTHING LEFT THERE, MA'AM ♪
- WHOO!
- ♪ CENTER STAGE ♪
♪ ANOTHER CHAPTER
TIME TO TURN THE PAGE ♪
- ♪ AND FINALLY, I'M THE STAR ♪
- ♪ NO, I'M THE STAR ♪
- NO, GIRL.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- OH, THE SHADE,
THE SHADE OF IT ALL.
♪ LOOK AT YOURSELVES ♪
♪ SHADY LADIES ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED ♪
[LAUGHTER]
♪ OF WHAT YOU'VE BECOME ♪
♪ OH, I NEVER THOUGHT ♪
♪ THAT YOU WOULD DO THIS ♪
♪ SO LET ME REMIND YOU ♪
♪ OF JUST ONE THING ♪
♪ TAKE EACH OTHER'S HANDS ♪
♪ AND COME TOGETHER 'CAUSE ♪
♪ WE ARE EACH OTHER'S FAMILY ♪
♪ ALL 2,603,040 SISTERS ♪
♪ THIS IS OUR LAND ♪
♪ AND WE ARE THE QUEENS ♪
- ♪ TIME TO TAKE A STAND ♪
♪ AND COME TOGETHER ♪
♪ WE ARE EACH OTHER'S FAMILY ♪
- ♪ WE'RE A FAMILY ♪
- ♪ ALL 2,603,040 SISTERS ♪
♪ THIS IS OUR LAND ♪
♪ AND WE ARE THE QUEENS ♪
- SO, EVEN IF YOU'RE
A PAGEANT QUEEN,
- OR A COMEDY QUEEN,
- A FISHY QUEEN,
- A SHADY QUEEN,
- OR JUST A BIG DAMN GIRL,
- WE ARE A FAMILY
- ♪ THAT RULES ♪
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- BRAVA!
[LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHS]
- ♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
- BIANCA DEL RIO,
TRINITY K. BONET,
DARIENNE LAKE,
G--G--G--GIA,
BENDELACREME,
COURTNEY ACT,
LAGANJA ESTRANJA,
APRIL CARRION,
JOSLYN FOX,
MILK,
ADORE DELANO.
- ♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
- WELCOME, LADIES.
THIS WEEK,
YOU COMPETED IN TEAMS,
BUT TONIGHT, YOU'LL BE JUDGED
AS INDIVIDUALS.
BIANCA DEL RIO,
MILK,
LAGANJA ESTRANJA,
GIA GUNN,
JOSLYN FOX...
YOU ARE ALL SAFE.
YOU MAY LEAVE THE STAGE.
LADIES, YOU REPRESENT
THE BEST AND THE WORST
OF THE WEEK.
IT'S TIME
FOR THE JUDGES' REVIEWS,
STARTING WITH
TRINITY K. BONET.
- YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL TONIGHT.
I LIKE THE WAY THE GOWN
ACCENTUATES YOUR HIPLINE.
- I DID LIKE YOUR CHARACTER
IN THE MUSICAL,
BUT I'M NOT ABLE
TO UNDERSTAND YOU.
IT'S KIND OF
A MUSH-MOUTH THING.
WE HEARD BIANCA,
AND THEN WE'D LOSE
YOUR LINE.
- IT'S ALL
A LEARNING EXPERIENCE.
- YES, YES, BUT YOU ARE
IN THE OLYMPICS OF DRAG.
- BUT EVERY STAR WAS CRAP
BEFORE THEY BECAME THE SHIT.
- LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
PUT A CORK IN IT.
LITERALLY,
GET A CORK,
PUT IT IN YOUR MOUTH,
SPEAK WITH THAT CORK
IN THE MOUTH.
IT WILL DO WONDERS
FOR ENUNCIATION.
- NEXT UP,
DARIENNE LAKE.
- LOOK AT YOU ALL PRETTY
IN YOUR POND SCUM GREEN.
- [LAUGHS]
OH, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- AS FAR AS
YOUR COMEDY QUEEN GOES,
YOU GOT A LITTLE LOST.
- IT IS A LITTLE HARD
TO KIND OF CONTINUE ON
WITH A FIRE SIREN
BEING SQUASHED IN YOUR EAR.
- THAT'S GIA
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, RIGHT?
- OH, YEAH, YEAH.
- WELL, WHY DO YOU THINK
SHE'S SAFE AND YOU'RE HERE?
- 'CAUSE I THINK
I'M ONE OF THE TOP 3?
- ALL RIGHT, MOVING ON.
BENDELACREME.
- LET'S TALK ABOUT
THE WAY YOU LOOK.
I BELIEVE THAT LESS
IS ALWAYS BEST.
LOOK IN THE MIRROR,
TAKE A LITTLE BIT
OF SOMETHING AWAY.
- OH!
- THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT!
NOW, YOU ARE WORKING IT.
- I DID LIKE YOUR CHARACTER
IN THE MUSICAL,
BUT I FELT THAT
YOU COULD'VE TAKEN IT FURTHER.
- I LOVED YOUR PORTRAYAL
OF THE VILLAIN,
LOVED YOUR EVIL
BETTIE PAGE LOOK,
AND YOUR VOICE, TOO.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- UP NEXT, COURTNEY ACT.
- THE ILLUSION
IS WORKING FOR ME.
A-MA-ZING.
AND YOU CAN REALLY SING.
FABULOUS.
- YOU ARE A STAR.
- THANK YOU.
- BUT I WAS ACTUALLY
REALLY NERVOUS IN REHEARSALS,
BECAUSE YOU WERE
MISSING CUES.
- I WAS MUFFLING TWO WORDS,
BUT I NAILED IT ON THE NIGHT.
- NEXT UP, ADORE DELANO.
- TONIGHT, THE DRESS,
FOR ME, COULD BE LONGER.
IT COULD GO TO THE FLOOR.
- WHY IS YOUR WAIST
NOT CINCHED
WHEN I JUST TALKED TO YOU
ABOUT THIS?
- BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE, LIKE,
A "CINCHER" CINCHER, ONLY--
- BORROW A WAIST CINCHER
AND GIVE ME THE SILHOUETTE
I NEED FROM YOU,
ADORE DELANO.
- I'M A BETTER DRAG QUEEN
THAN I'M COMING OFF, I SWEAR.
- [LAUGHS]
- I LOVED YOUR VOICE.
I THOUGHT THAT
YOU COULD COMPETE
IN "AMERICAN IDOL."
- I DID.
- SEE THAT?
I GOT THAT IMMEDIATELY.
- PARTY.
- HA!
PARTY.
[LAUGHTER]
- NEXT UP, APRIL CARRION.
- WELL, YOUR FACE
IS ALWAYS BEAT FOR THE GODS,
BUT I THINK YOUR SHADING'S
A LITTLE DARK
TOWARDS YOUR HAIRLINE.
- IT'S LIKE YOU HAVE
A BEARD ON YOUR FOREHEAD.
- APRIL, I KNOW YOU TRIED
REALLY, REALLY HARD
ON THIS CHALLENGE,
BUT YOU WERE WAY OFF.
- BEING THE BIG GIRL,
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT SIZE.
IT'S MORE OF AN ATTITUDE,
AND YOU DIDN'T DELIVER
THE ATTITUDE.
YOU PUT SOME PADDING IN
AND THOUGHT
THAT IT WOULD TRANSLATE,
AND IT DIDN'T.
- THANK YOU, LADIES.
WHILE YOU UNTUCK
IN THE FORMDECOR LOUNGE,
THE JUDGES AND I
WILL DELIBERATE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, JUST BETWEEN US,
DREAM GIRLS.
- HMM.
- LET'S TALK OFF-BROADWAY.
LET'S START WITH
TRINITY K. BONET.
- DICTION, DICTION, I WANT
TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE SAYING!
- NOW, WHEN TRINITY'S IN DRAG,
SHE WEARS TEMPORARY TEETH.
WE CALL THEM FLIPPERS
IN THE BUSINESS.
I'M WONDERING,
COULD THAT BE THE REASON
SHE'S UNABLE
TO PRONOUNCE HER LYRICS?
- FLIPPER OR NO FLIPPER,
YOU'VE GOT TO WORK
WITH WHAT YOU'VE GOT.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- YES.
- AND BE OPEN
TO LISTENING TO SOMEBODY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET
ALL "UGH" FACE.
AIN'T NOBODY GOT TIME
FOR THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
- DARIENNE LAKE.
- SHE SEEMED TO GET
A LITTLE BIT
LOST IN THE SAUCE,
WHEREAS GIA,
FOGHORN OR NOT,
WAS GIVING IT ALL
WITH EASE.
DARIENNE DISAPPEARED
FOR ME.
- THE THUNDER FROM DOWN UNDER,
COURTNEY ACT.
- I INSTANTLY WAS TRANSPORTED
INTO A BROADWAY HOUSE.
- YES.
- AND I TOTALLY BOUGHT IT
FROM HEAD TO TOE,
BUT THERE WERE SOME CLUNKERS
THAT SHE HIT.
- I DIDN'T REALLY MIND
ANY OF THE NOTES
THAT MIGHT'VE BEEN
A LITTLE OFF.
SHE REALLY NAILED
THIS PERFORMANCE.
- I LOVED THAT
FRESH-FROM-KANSAS,
FRESH-OFF-THE-BUS
LOOK OF HERS.
SHE WAS FABULOUS.
- BENDELACREME.
- KNEW THE CHOREOGRAPHY,
KNEW ALL THE WORDS,
LOOKED GOOD DOING IT.
- I REALLY LOVE
HER BODY LANGUAGE, AS WELL.
- YOU CAN TELL
BY LOOKING AT HER,
THIS IS HER SHTICK.
- YEAH.
-BUT SHE ONLY TOOK IT
HALFWAY TO TONI BRAXTON.
- [LAUGHS]
- SHE DIDN'T TAKE IT
ALL THE WAY.
- ADORE DELANO.
- ADORE HAS A BEAUTIFUL VOICE,
BUT SHE CAN BE A LITTLE SLOPPY.
- ADORE WAS THE MVP FOR ME.
HER VOICE AND THE TONES
THAT WERE COMING OUT
OF HER MOUTH
MADE ME LOOK AT HER
IN A WHOLE OTHER LIGHT
OF BEING LIKE,
WOW, THIS IS A REAL TALENT.
- LAST BUT NOT LEAST,
APRIL CARRION.
- SHE'S BEAUTIFUL,
AND SHE TRIED REALLY HARD.
UNFORTUNATELY, SHE DID NOT
EMBODY THE BIG GIRL ROLE.
- WELL, THAT'S THE STANDOUT
ROLE OF THAT TRIO.
- YES, IT IS.
- AND IT HAS TO DELIVER.
THAT WAS THE PROBLEM.
- SILENCE,
I'VE MADE MY DECISION,
GUYS AND DOLLS.
NOW, BRING BACK MY GIRLS.
[LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHS]
WELCOME BACK, LADIES.
I'VE MADE SOME DECISIONS.
THE NOMINEES
FOR BEST ACTRESS
IN A RUSICAL ARE...
COURTNEY ACT
AS GOOD PENNY,
BENDELACREME
AS SHADY LADY,
ADORE DELANO
AS BAD PENNY.
MAY I HAVE
THE ENVELOPE, PLEASE?
THE WINNER OF THIS WEEK'S
MAIN CHALLENGE IS...
COURTNEY ACT.
- THANK YOU,
THANK YOU.
AND THANK YOU.
- YOU'VE WON
TWO VIP PACKAGES
FOR THE TONY-WINNING
BROADWAY MUSICAL
"KINKY BOOTS."
- OOH!
- LADIES, YOU MAY JOIN
THE OTHER GIRLS.
DARIENNE LAKE,
YOUR COMEDY QUEEN ROUTINE
DIDN'T REALLY SHTICK
WITH THE JUDGES.
TRINITY K. BONET,
YOUR PAGEANT QUEEN PERFORMANCE
WAS NOT YOUR CROWNING GLORY.
APRIL CARRION,
IN THE ROLE OF THE BIG GIRL,
YOU MAY HAVE BITTEN OFF
MORE THAN YOU COULD CHEW.
DARIENNE LAKE,
YOU ARE SAFE.
YOU MAY JOIN THE OTHER GIRLS.
TRINITY, APRIL,
I'M SORRY, MY DEARS,
BUT YOU ARE UP FOR ELIMINATION.
TWO QUEENS STAND BEFORE ME.
LADIES,
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO IMPRESS ME
AND SAVE YOURSELF
FROM ELIMINATION.
THE TIME HAS COME
FOR YOU TO LIP-SYNC
FOR YOUR LIFE.
GOOD LUCK,
AND DON'T FUCK IT UP.
♪ I'M EVERY WOMAN ♪
♪ IT'S ALL IN ME ♪
♪ ANYTHING YOU WANT DONE, BABY ♪
♪ I'LL DO IT NATURALLY ♪
♪ WHOA, WHOA, WHOA ♪
♪ I CAN SENSE YOUR NEEDS ♪
♪ LIKE RAIN ONTO THE SEEDS ♪
♪ I CAN MAKE A RHYME
OF CONFUSION IN YOUR MIND ♪
♪ AND WHEN IT COMES DOWN ♪
- I AM SERVING,
I AM OWNING THAT SONG.
OH, GOSPEL,
OH, CHURCH.
I'M A BRING JESUS,
I'M A BRING ALL THE SAINTS.
- ♪ I'M EVERY WOMAN ♪
♪ IT'S ALL IN ME ♪
♪ I CAN READ
YOUR THOUGHTS RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ EVERY ONE FROM "A" TO "Z" ♪
- I'M GIVING YOU
A PIECE OF TRINITY.
I'M CHANNELING
MY INNER CHAKA.
I'M GIVING IT ALL I GOT.
- ♪ I AIN'T BRAGGING ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M THE ONE ♪
- TRINITY IS LIP-SYNCHING
THE HOUSE DOWN WITH BOOTS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS,
BUT SHE'S DOING IT.
- APRIL IS HUNGRY FOR THIS.
- ♪ I'M EVERY WOMAN ♪
♪ ANYTHING YOU WANT DONE ♪
♪ I'M EVERY WOMAN ♪
♪ WHOA ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- NOW, THAT IS WHAT I CALL
A LIP-SYNC.
NOW, I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
TRINITY K. BONET,
SHANTE, YOU STAY.
YOU MAY JOIN THE OTHER GIRLS.
APRIL, MY FIERCE,
BEAUTIFUL QUEEN,
KEEP CALM AND CARRY ON.
NOW, SASHAY AWAY.
- LOVE YOU.
I GAVE MY ALL.
I KNOW RU SAW MY EFFORT
AND JUST MY PASSION.
I WISH I COULD'VE GONE FURTHER
AND JUST BROUGHT THAT CROWN
TO PUERTO RICO,
BUT THIS CAN ONLY
MAKE ME STRONGER.
- MY TOP 10 QUEENS,
HERE'S TO THE LADIES WHO TALK.
IF YOU CAN'T LOVE YOURSELF,
HOW IN THE HELL ARE YOU GONNA
LOVE SOMEBODY ELSE?
CAN I GET A "AMEN" IN HERE?
- AMEN!
- I'LL DRINK TO THAT.
♪ I WANNA DANCE, DANCE
I WANNA DANCE, DANCE ♪
DANCE WITH YOU ♪