- ONE YEAR AGO,
IN AN ABANDONED STUDIO,
14 QUEENS WERE TERRORIZED...
- [CRIES]
- [SCREAMS]
- [BABBLES]
- BROKEN DOWN...
- NO!
- AND CA-TORTURED.
SINCE THEN,
EVIL HAS LAIN DORMANT,
UNTIL NOW.
[CACKLING]
[COUGHS]
OH, WHOA.
WHERE'D THAT COME FROM?
THIS SEASON, "RUPAUL'S DRAG
RACE" IS ON THE EDGE OF GORY.
PIG'S BLOOD.
[ALL SCREAM]
- AS 14 UNSPOOKABLE QUEENS...
- BASIC BITCHES NOT WANTED.
- PUT THE FEAR IN FIERCE.
- GAH-AHH-GGING.
- DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS FASHION,
SCARY GOOD CELEBRITIES...
- PUT A CORK IN IT.
- AND SOME CRAZY, PSYCHO...
- OH, NO, GIRL.
- BITCHES.
[CRASHES]
- WHAT'S--WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I WILL SHOW YOU VERSATILITY
WHEN SANTINO WINS
A SEWING COMPETITION
AND VISAGE WEARS
A FUCKING TURTLENECK!
- BUT DON'T BE SCARED.
THERE'S TEARS AS WELL AS FEARS.
- I'VE GIVEN UP EVERYTHING
IN MY LIFE TO BE A DRAG QUEEN.
- YOU HAVE OVERCOME THAT,
AND I'M SO PROUD TO SEE IT.
I'M SO PROUD TO SEE IT.
SO GET READY
TO GET SCARED SILLY.
- BITCHING.
- "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
IS BACK.
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN...
[SCREAMS]
- ♪ RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ GENTLEMEN,
START YOUR ENGINES ♪
♪ RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
♪ RU-RU-RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ GENTLEMEN,
START YOUR ENGINES ♪
♪ RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ MAY THE BEST WOMAN
BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
- ♪ DA-DA, DEE
DA-DA, DEE, DA-DA, DA ♪
♪ SEXY, SEXY DRAG QUEEN ♪
♪ DA-DA, DEE DA-DA, DA ♪
♪ SEXY DRAG QUEEN ♪
[LAUGHING]
- I'M HOME!
FUCK, YEAH.
I'M THE FIRST ONE.
MY NAME IS ADORE DELANO.
I'M 23 YEARS OLD,
AND I'M A FUCKING LIBRA.
I'M SO EXCITED, I CAN PEE.
I DON'T FIT IN WITH SOCIETY.
I DON'T FIT IN
WITH THE DRAG QUEENS.
OH.
FOR ALL THE QUEENS TELLING ME
THAT I'M NOT POLISHED ENOUGH,
I JUST WANT THEM TO KNOW
THAT I'M POLISH REMOVER, BITCH.
I'M NOT WEARING ANY UNDERWEAR.
- HI, EVERYBODY.
IT'S ME, BENDELACREME.
[GIGGLES]
OH, THERE'S ONE.
MY NAME IS BENDELACREME,
AND I'M 31 YEARS OLD.
- BENDELACREME?
- YES, DELA FOR SHORT,
DUH FOR SHORTER,
MISS CREME, IF YOU'RE NASTY.
- PARTY.
- BENDELACREME IS
EFFERVESCENT AND OPTIMISTIC.
WOW, THIS IS BEAUTIFUL!
I REFER TO HER
AS "TERMINALLY DELIGHTFUL."
OH!
SO POSITIVE THAT SHE
COULD CAUSE DEATH AT ANY MOMENT.
WELL, I'M GONNA PARK
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU.
WE'RE ALREADY
THE BEST OF FRIENDS.
- WHAT'S YOUR SIGN?
- OH, I NEVER GOT ONE OF THOSE.
[WHISPERING]
WHO IS THAT?
- MY NAME IS GIA GUNN.
I'M 23 YEARS OLD.
GIA'S A FISHY GIRL.
SHE'S C.C.C.,
CRAZY CUCKOO CUNT.
JUST GOT OFF THE BOAT.
YOU KNOW, LITTLE TRIP FROM ASIA.
JUST LANDED LIKE FRESH TILAPIA.
- [LAUGHS]
GIA CAME OUT WITH A HULA-HOOP
WITH A POCKET ON IT.
I MEAN, SHE WAS REALLY
LIVING FOR HERSELF, GIRL.
- I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
GONNA KIND OF BE, LIKE,
MAYBE THE MOTHERLY FIGURE.
- THE MOTHER--CALLED ME OLD.
ALL RIGHT.
- OH, Y'ALL WANTED A TWIST, EH?
COME ON, SEASON 6.
LET'S GET SIX-Y.
YEAH.
- YES, BITCH.
WORK.
- MY NAME IS LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
I'M 24 YEARS OLD.
HI, GIRLS.
- HI!
- LAGANJA IS KNOWN FOR HER WILD
AND AMAZING DANCE ABILITY.
OH, WHOO!
- OH, DAMN!
- SHE'S GHETTO, BUT SHE'S ALSO
CLASSY AND GLAMOROUS.
- BITCH. BITCH.
- OH, SO Y'ALL KNOW EACH OTHER.
- WE STARTED TOGETHER
AT THE SAME CLUB.
LAGANJA AND I ARE
THE BEST OF FRIENDS,
BUT WHEN WE DO COMPETE,
THAT CAN GET UGLY.
SHE'S VERY COMPETITIVE.
- GIRL, IT'S ABOUT TIME THEY GOT
SOME FRESH FISH UP IN HERE.
- YES, MA'AM.
- SUSHI ROLL, SUSHI ROLL!
- BARF.
- [GASPS]
- REPORTING FOR DUTY.
APRIL CARRION IS IN THE HOUSE.
- YEAH!
- I'M APRIL CARRION.
I'M 24 YEARS OLD,
DIRECTLY FROM GUAYNABO,
PUERTO RICO.
- AND HERE I THOUGHT GAYS
WEREN'T ALLOWED IN THE SCOUTS.
- APRIL IS A CROSS
BETWEEN BJORK AND COCO ROCHA.
WHAT'S UP, GIRLS?
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING WEIRD,
BUT SOMETHING GLAMOROUS.
- YOU JUST PARACHUTED IN, GIRL?
- I'M NOT TOO SURE
ABOUT APRIL'S LOOK,
BECAUSE IT'S GIVING ME
A LITTLE BIT OF BUTCH,
BUT, UH, SHE'S CUTE.
NO.
- [LAUGHS]
- HEY, BITCHES.
Y'ALL READY TO ROCK AND ROLL?
WHOO!
OH, SHIT.
I NEED TO PUT THESE BACK ON.
- OH!
- NO, I'M JUST KIDDING.
- I'M JUST KIDDING.
I'M KELLY MANTLE.
I'M 37 YEARS OLD.
MWAH. WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- LOVELY TO MEET YOU.
LAGANJA.
- GORGEOUS.
I AM AN ACTOR.
I'VE BEEN ON A BUNCH
OF TELEVISION SHOWS,
BUT I PROMISE I'M NOT
GONNA WALK AROUND RECITING
MY IMDB PAGE LIKE SOME PEOPLE
WE KNOW FROM PAST SEASONS.
- NICE TO MEET YOU, SWEETIE.
- GIA GUNN, NICE TO MEET YOU.
- ABSOLUTELY.
KELLY LOOKED A MESS.
THE LOOK WAS NOTHING
TO GAG OVER.
GLOWING HEARTS ON A SIMPLE DRESS
IS NOT GIVING ME DRAG.
- THIS IS AWESOME.
OH!
- GIRL, WHAT?
AN ALIEN?
- YES.
YES, MAMA.
COME ON.
- PULL IT DOWN, BABY.
- LET US SEE.
- IT WAS ALL DRAMATIC,
AND THEN IT WAS JUST...
- YEAH!
- I'M VIVACIOUS.
I'M 40 YEARS OLD.
MOTHER HAS ARRIVED.
- YES.
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- VIVACIOUS IS THE LAST ORIGINAL
CLUB KID IN NEW YORK CITY.
- I'M LIVING FOR THIS HEAD.
- YES.
- GIVE ME SOME HEAD
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
- MY LOOK IS
LEIGH BOWERY ABSTRACT ENTITY.
VIVACIOUS IS LIVING ART.
I CANNOT WAIT TO SEE
WHO THE NEXT GIRL IS, HONEY.
- I WONDER
IF SHE'S GONNA BE AS FIERCE
AS ALL OF US OR MORE MANLY.
- [LAUGHS]
[SIREN WAILING]
[ALL HOOTING]
- YOU GOT SHE MAIL.
- SHE MAIL.
- ALREADY?
- WAIT A MINUTE.
THERE'S ONLY 7 OF US.
- THERE HAS TO BE
MORE GIRLS COMING.
- WHOO!
- DOES THAT MEAN
THIS IS ALL OF US?
WHO CAN COUNT THIS HIGH?
IS THIS ENOUGH?
- NO, HONEY.
THERE HAS TO BE MORE.
- WE INTERRUPT THIS KIKI
TO BRING YOU A SPECIAL BULLETIN.
THIS SEASON,
THE DRAG REVOLUTION
WILL BE TELEVISED,
SO DON'T ADJUST YOUR SETS,
BECAUSE THIS EXTRAVAGANZA
IS BEING BROADCAST IN H.D.S.
THAT'S HIGH-DEFINITION SHADE.
MM-HMM.
WE NOW RETURN TO OUR REGULARLY
SCHEDULED COMPETITION
ALREADY IN PROGRESS.
[ALL WHOOPING]
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO!
- [CHEERS]
- HI!
- WELCOME TO
"RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
NOW, LET'S SEE.
IS THERE ANYONE MISSING?
UM, LET'S SEE.
UM, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
7, THAT'S IT!
- 7 OF US.
I MEAN, IS THERE
NO BUDGET THIS TIME AROUND?
- BECAUSE, FOR THE FIRST TIME,
WE'RE NOT HAVING
JUST ONE PREMIERE.
WE'RE HAVING TWO.
YOU ARE THE FIRST 7
QUEENS TO ARRIVE.
THIS WEEK, YOU'LL BE
COMPETING AGAINST EACH OTHER,
AND ONE OF YOU
WILL BE GOING HOME.
NEXT WEEK, IT'S PART TWO,
AS 7 NEW QUEENS ARRIVE.
BECAUSE THE ONLY THING BETTER
THAN ONE BIG OPENING
IS TWO BIG OPENINGS.
- YES, MAMA.
- THIS WAY, NO ONE CAN GET
LOST IN THE CROWD.
- THERE'S 7 OF US,
AND THERE'S A FUCKING CLOSER EYE
BEING WATCHED ON US.
I'M FUCKING SCARED.
- BUT IF YOU PLAY BIG,
YOU CAN WIN BIG.
THE WINNER OF
"RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
WILL RECEIVE A SICKENING SUPPLY
OF COLOREVOLUTION COSMETICS.
- [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- OOH, YES, MAMA.
- AND I'LL BE CUTTING
A BIG, FAT CHECK...
FOR $100,000.
- [CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
- NO MORE STREET CORNERS.
- OKAY.
- THIS WEEK, WE'RE
GOING TO CELEBRATE EVERYTHING
WE LOVE ABOUT THE BOOB TUBE.
HASHTAG "ALLTVALLSHADE."
- OH.
- OKAY.
- STARTING
WITH YOUR FIRST PHOTO SHOOT.
- [CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
- IT'S TIME TO TAKE
A FLYING LEAP INTO SEASON 6.
- OH, SHIT.
[LAUGHS]
- IT'S SEASON 6, HONEY,
AND SHIT'S GETTING GAGGY.
- COMING UP...
- [SHOUTING]
- ARE YOU OKAY?
[LAUGHING]
- ADORE, MY DARLING.
- HI, RU.
- SAY HELLO TO CELEBRITY
PHOTOGRAPHER MIKE RUIZ.
- HI.
- AND LET ME INTRODUCE
THE NEW AND IMPROVED PIT CREW.
THEY'RE BUFF, THEY'RE TOUGH,
AND BROUGHT TO YOU BY THE GAY
SOCIAL NETWORK SCRUFF.
- PARTY.
- NOW, TO PROVE
YOU'RE NOT THE BIGGEST LOSER,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS TAKE A QUANTUM LEAP
AND STRIKE A SICKENING POSE
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THIS GIANT TV SCREEN.
- OH, SHIT.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
- WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR
FROM THE GIRLS IN THIS CHALLENGE
IS AMAZING FACE, DANCER-LY BODY
MOVES, AND CONFIDENCE.
- I'M REALLY SCARED THAT I MIGHT
FLY OFF THIS FUCKING THING,
AND HEELS ARE
GONNA GO FLYING HERE,
AND EYELASHES
ARE GONNA BE ON MY CHIN.
- ALL RIGHT, KIDDO.
DON'T BE NERVOUS.
I'M GONNA TALK YOU
OFF THE LEDGE.
- THIS SHIT
IS NOT LIKE THE BUSINESS.
- WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
- OKAY, READY?
- YOU'RE GONNA
COUNT IT OFF, RIGHT?
- OKAY, READY?
1, 2, 3.
- [LAUGHING]
- MY EYELASH.
- YEAH, THAT
WAS A LITTLE AWKWARD.
- OKAY.
- DO PRETTY LEGS.
LIKE, DO, YOU KNOW,
LIKE, A DANCER-LY THING.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
- [YELPS]
- YOU DID IT AGAIN
WITH THE LEGS.
- OH, I'M SORRY.
I'M A GIRAFFE!
- ADORE LOOKED LIKE
HER LIMBS WERE ALL BROKEN,
BUT SHE GAVE
REALLY AMAZING FACE.
- THIS IS LIKE AN EPISODE
OF QUEER FACTOR.
BENDELACREME,
YOU'RE ON AIR IN 3, 2, 1...
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[LAUGHS]
- YOUR BODY WAS GOOD,
BUT YOUR FACE
WAS A LITTLE EXTREME.
LET'S JUST DO A PRETTY ONE NOW.
- OOH, YES.
- OH, YEAH.
- HERE'S TO THE LADIES
WHO LAUNCH.
GIA GUNN.
- CHECK OUT
THE SIZE OF THAT SACK.
- [LAUGHS]
NOW, ON TODAY'S SHORT FLIGHT,
WE'LL BE SERVING FISH.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[LAUGHS]
QUEEN DOWN.
- WAS THAT GOOD?
- WELL, NO, BUT YOU
CAN TRY IT AGAIN.
- OKAY.
I HAVE NO FUCKING IDEA
WHAT I'M DOING.
I KNOW WE'RE TRYING
TO GIVE BODY AND MUG,
BUT I'M JUST SO SCARED
OF SNAPPING MY NECK.
- G-G-G-GIA.
[LAUGHING]
- WAS THAT BETTER?
- I REALLY THOUGHT YOU'D
BE BETTER AT GOING DOWN.
- [CHUCKLES]
- GIA MAY BE FISH,
BUT SHE AIN'T FLYING FISH.
- LAGANJA!
- YES.
- COME ON DOWN.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
- YES!
- [LAUGHS]
YOU LOOK JUST
LIKE GOLDIE HAWN IN OVERBOARD.
- OH, I GET THAT A LOT.
- IF YOU CAN GO
A LITTLE BIT HIGHER
AND A LITTLE BIT FURTHER OUT.
- OKAY.
- QUEEN OVERBOARD.
- YES, GORGEOUS.
- SHE'S GIVING YOU
A YOUNG JULIANNE "HOWE."
- OH, YEAH, JULIANNE...
[COUGHING THROATILY] HOUGH.
- KELLY MANTLE.
- 1, 2...
3.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
- OH.
- IT'S VERY DOROTHY
IN THE WIZARD OF OZ,
LIKE, WHEN SHE WAS
IN THE TORNADO.
- [LAUGHING]
- YOU GOT ONE MORE CHANCE.
- YOU GOT ONE MORE TRY.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
- THERE'S NO PLACE LIKE FOAM.
APRIL CARRION.
- TRES, DOS, UNO.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
- [LAUGHS]
I AM LOVING
THIS NEW FALL SEASON.
- AH! I CAN'T GET OUT.
- IT'S THE BOOGIE
WOOGIE BUGLE QUEEN.
- WE TOTALLY GOT THE SHOT.
- VIVACIOUS.
THERE ARE TWO THINGS
I LOVE ABOUT YOU:
YOUR FACE.
- [LAUGHS]
- LET'S GO.
DO YOU HAVE A NAME FOR THE HEAD
ON TOP OF YOUR HEAD?
- ORNACIA.
- ORNACIA, OKAY.
I BELIEVE YOU CAN FLY.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
OH, NO, YOU CAN'T.
- [LAUGHS]
- [GROANS]
- ORNACIA WAS GIVING ME FACE,
BUT YOU, NOT SO MUCH.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- OH, BOY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- UH-HUH.
- WE GOT A GOOD SHOT.
I KNOW IT'S A LOT
TO WRAP YOUR HEAD AROUND.
[LAUGHTER]
- OH, MY GOODNESS. MISTAKE.
- YOU DID NOT JUMP
WITH THAT HEAD ON.
- YES, I DID, HONEY.
- NO!
- YOU GIRLS LOOK
DIFFERENT AS MEN, HONEY.
- YES.
- DELA DEFINITELY DOES NOT LOOK
THE SAME OUT OF DRAG.
I COULD NOT CLOCK THE SPOOK.
- WELL, I'M TRYING TO GIVE A
LOOK, STROLLING ACROSS THE ROOM.
- BUT GIA IS STILL
A LADY BOY IN OR OUT OF GEISH.
- I FEEL SO FREE,
LIKE FREE WILLY.
- LOOKING AROUND THE ROOM,
THERE'S A LOT OF YOUNG QUEENS.
VIVACIOUS AND I
ARE PROBABLY THE OLDER ONES.
I'M SURE SHE'S OLDER,
BUT, YOU KNOW...
- THIS IS, LIKE,
MY 21st YEAR DOING DRAG.
- 22 YEARS?
- 21.
- I HAVE BEEN IN DRAG
FOR 17 YEARS.
- OOH, YOU BETTER DO IT.
- YOU CAN NEVER
STOP LEARNING, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU NEVER STOP
STUDYING YOUR CRAFT.
- KELLY'S DRAG CALIBER
IS JUST NOT
TO WHERE I WOULD EXPECT IT
TO BE FOR AN EXPERIENCED QUEEN.
IF IT'S JUST NOT GIVING IT,
MAYBE IT'S JUST NOT FOR YOU.
- THAT IS SO CUTE.
- OH, THANK YOU.
HOW IS SHE, THOUGH?
- GIRL, WHAT?
- HOW IS SHE, THOUGH?
- FUCK ALL THE WAY OFF.
ALL THESE GIRLS HAVE
THESE CRAZY RHINESTONE DRESSES,
AND I BROUGHT,
LIKE, FOUR GOWNS WITH ME,
SO THAT IS MAKING ME VERY
INSECURE AT THIS MOMENT IN TIME.
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO.
- HELLO!
- HI!
- I JUST FINISHED BINGE-VIEWING
YOUR ON-AIR PHOTOS.
- OH, HONEY.
- AND A COUPLE OF YOU FIZZLED,
BUT ONE OF YOU
IS A TRUE FALLING STAR.
THE WINNER IS...
LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
[APPLAUSE AND LAUGHTER]
- OOH! HONEY, THESE LEGS
ARE EVERYTHING.
- CONDRAGULATIONS, LAGANJA.
- THANK YOU, RU.
- OH, MY GOD.
I TOTALLY FORGOT
I AM DOUBLE-PARKED.
GIRLS, FOLLOW ME.
[TRUCK BEEPING]
[HORN BLARES]
- RUPAUL'S STORAGE WHORES?
- OH.
- WHOO!
- HEY!
WALK IT OUT,
WALK IT OUT, WALK IT OUT!
- DON'T BE JEALOUS OF MY RUHAUL.
- OH, GIRL!
- SO, DO YOU WANT TO MEET
THE OTHER 7 QUEENS?
- [SQUEALS]
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- OH, MY GOD.
- OOH, SHIT
GODDAMN MOTHERFUCK.
- [LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING]
DO YOU WANT TO MEET
THE OTHER 7 QUEENS?
- [SQUEALS]
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- WELL, FIRST,
YOU'LL HAVE TO SURVIVE
THIS WEEK'S MAIN CHALLENGE.
- OH.
- THESE BOXES CONTAIN ITEMS
INSPIRED BY
SOME OF TV'S GREATEST HITS.
- YES.
- OKAY.
- NOW, USING THE JUNK
FROM ONE OF THESE TRUNKS,
YOU NEED TO CREATE YOUR BEST
HIGH-FASHION DRAG LOOK.
- OOH.
- LAGANJA, YOU
WON THE MINI CHALLENGE,
SO YOU GET TO ASSIGN
ONE BOX TO EACH QUEEN.
- I'M GOING TO CHOOSE
"DANCING WITH THE STARS."
- GOOD CHOICE.
- OKAY, MISS APRIL,
I'M THINKING,
BECAUSE OF YOUR ENTRANCE LOOK,
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO TAKE
"DUCK DYNASTY" AND MAKE IT WORK.
- [LAUGHS]
- OH, REALLY?
- "DUCK DYNASTY."
IS THAT FOR REAL?
[SIGHS]
- GIA, DARLING.
I'M GONNA GO WITH "KEEPING UP
WITH THE KARDASHIANS."
- THANK YOU.
- WHAT ABOUT VIVACIOUS?
- "THE GAME OF THRONES."
- OOH!
- WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR ADORE?
- I'M WHISPERING "GOLDEN GIRLS."
LIKE...[WHISPERING]
"GOLDEN GIRLS."
- FOR MY SISTER,
I THINK I WOULD LIKE TO GO WITH
"HERE COMES HONEY BOO BOO."
- OH, YOU FUCKING BITCH!
- REALLY?
- ANSWER "GOLDEN GIRLS."
- OH, SHIT.
I'M SORRY, MAMA.
- OH, NO!
IT'S FUCKED UP, MAN.
IT'S FUCKED UP.
- WHAT DO YOU HAVE
FOR KELLY MANTLE?
- I THINK I'M GOING
TO GO WITH THE "DOWNTON ABBEY."
- WELL, THAT MEANS
THAT BENDELACREME GETS...
"GOLDEN GIRLS."
- THANK YOU FOR BEING A FRIEND.
- YES!
- GENTLEMEN, START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN.
- YES.
[APPLAUSE]
- OH, MY GOSH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK WE GOT?
- [GROANS]
- OOH, SHE GOT
SOME FEATHERS, GIRL.
- LAGANJA, YOU HOOKED ME UP.
- THANKS, MAMA, FOR BEING
SO FISHY TO THE FISH.
- IT'S ALL REDNECK STUFF.
IT'S CRAP.
I GOT A BOX FULL OF CRAP.
WHAT IS THIS?
CRAP.
LIKE, LITERALLY CRAP.
- HOW ARE YOU, APRIL?
DO YOU HATE ME YET?
- WHY WOULD LAGANJA THINK
I CAN RELATE TO THIS?
TOTAL CRAP.
[SIGHS]
- SHE'S FUCKED.
- SKETTI.
I'M NOT HAPPY THAT LAGANJA
GAVE ME "HONEY BOO BOO."
I'M SORRY.
THIS SMELLS SO GROSS.
I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S HER STRATEGY.
I'M GONNA HEAVE.
AND IF SHE DID
THAT ON PURPOSE, THEN...
KARMA.
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO.
- HELLO!
- HI!
- HERE COMES HONEY RU RU.
- [LAUGHING] YEAH.
- ADORE.
- HI.
- DARLING.
YOU WATCH "HONEY BOO BOO"?
- I DO, BUT I WASN'T HAPPY
THAT I GOT THIS.
- YOU WERE ALSO A CONTESTANT
ON "AMERICAN IDOL."
- YEAH.
- HOW DOES THIS EXPERIENCE
COMPARE SO FAR?
- IT'S SO CRAZY.
- WAIT, WHICH IS CRAZY?
- THIS IS CRAZY.
- [LAUGHS]
- WHEN I WAS 17,
I APPEARED ON "AMERICAN IDOL."
I MADE IT TO THE TOP 13.
I'M PROUD OF IT, BUT I LOOK LIKE
A LESBIAN JONAS BROTHER.
- NOW, DO YOU SEW?
- NO.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
YOU YOUNG QUEENS
WHO DON'T KNOW HOW TO SEW.
I DON'T GET THAT.
- I KNOW.
I'LL GLUE IT OR SOMETHING.
- YEAH.
- I'M VERY, LIKE,
PASSIONATE ABOUT THIS.
- BABY, I THINK YOU'D BETTER
CHUG-A-LUG SOME GO-GO
JUICE REAL QUICK
AND MAKE IT HAPPEN.
- [CRIES]
- VIVACIOUS.
- HI, RU, HOW ARE YOU?
- HI, DARLING.
NOW, "GAME OF THRONES."
YOU EVER WATCH THAT SHOW?
- YES, I THINK
IT WAS THE QUEEN'S DAUGHTER
WENT TO ONE
OF THE OTHER KINGDOMS,
AND SHE TURNED AROUND
AND HAD HER DRAGON TORCH
THE WHOLE KINGDOM.
SO, I'M JUST GONNA
TRY TO GET THIS AS FEMININE
AS I POSSIBLY CAN WITH A COWL
NECK AND A BABY DRAGON.
- A BABY DRAGON.
YEAH, OKAY.
WELL, WE WANT TO SEE
"GAME OF THRONES" TRANSLATED
THROUGH YOUR EYES.
GIRL, IT'S GOT TO SCREAM
"VIVACIOUS."
KELLY MANTLE.
- HEY, RU.
- YOU REMIND ME...
- UH-HUH.
- OF A YOUNG CAROL BURNETT.
- [SIGHS]
SHE WAS MY CHILDHOOD IDOL.
SHE'S THE WHOLE REASON
I EVEN STARTED PERFORMING.
- REALLY?
- OH, YEAH.
- SO YOU GOT "DOWNTON ABBEY."
I SEE SOME SORT OF ANTIQUE LACE.
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO FOR THE TOP?
- THIS WAS IN THE BOX,
AND I STARTED THINKING,
"THIS WOULD MAKE
SUCH AN AMAZING CORSET."
VERY KATE MOSS-Y.
- YEAH.
LISTEN, YOU USE
THE EXPERIENCE THAT YOU HAVE...
- OKAY.
- AND BRING IT
TO THIS CHALLENGE.
- I WILL.
- APRIL. HOW ARE YOU?
- HI, RU.
- YOU GOT "DUCK DYNASTY."
- YEAH.
I FOUND THESE PANTS.
- OH, YEAH, THEY'RE SORT OF
CAMOUFLAGE PANTS.
- I THINK I'M
GONNA REALLY TAILOR THESE
INTO A HIGH-WAISTED PANT
JUST TO MAKE IT HIGH-FASHION,
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE A PANT CAN BE
HARD TO TRANSLATE
INTO HIGH FASHION.
- YEAH, IT CAN BE.
- YEAH.
- ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE A MAN.
- WELL, I THINK
YOU NEED TO TAKE A RISK.
- HMM, OKAY.
- I'M SCARED SHITLESS.
I'M NOT GONNA LIE, YOU KNOW?
I CAN'T BE
THE FIRST QUEEN TO GO HOME.
- G-G-G-GIA.
- HI, RU.
- YOU GOT THE KARDASHIANS.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- NOW, YOU SEEM
A LITTLE BIT BEHIND.
- I NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT I
HAVE THE IDEA TOGETHER FIRST.
- RIGHT.
- SO I'M THINKING, UM,
SOME TYPE OF COLLAR
AND MAYBE SOMETHING,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, COMING UP HERE.
MAYBE SOMETHING FLOW-Y,
BUT I'M THINKING
I'M GONNA GO MAYBE,
LIKE, VERY GOWN-ISH.
MAYBE, LIKE, A DRESS?
- I DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT YOU...[LAUGHING]
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO.
AND I'M WORRIED
THAT YOU DON'T EITHER.
- OOF, RU JUST CLOCKED ME.
- ALL RIGHT, LISTEN.
I'M GONNA LET
YOU GET BACK TO WORK.
- OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, LADIES.
GATHER ROUND.
LATER, YOU'LL BE
MAKING YOUR MAIN STAGE DEBUT,
AND WE'LL BE JOINED
BY OUR EXTRA SPECIAL
GUEST JUDGE,
MY AMERICAN IDOL, ADAM LAMBERT.
- [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- SO DON'T FUCK IT UP.
- THE STAKES ARE HIGH.
- I CAN'T EVEN THINK PROPERLY.
- GIRL. THE FIRST QUEEN
GOES HOME TODAY,
AND NO ONE WANTS TO BE
THAT GIRL.
- HOW DO YOU TAKE THIS OFF?
SO, I MAY HAVE OR MAY HAVE NOT
GLUED MY GARMENT
TO MY MANNEQUIN.
THIS IS SO HORRIBLE.
AAH!
I'M FUCKING RIPPING
MY WHOLE DRESS.
- YOU GOOD, BABY?
- GO AHEAD, BABE.
I'LL COME ONCE I GET IT.
- I MAKE ONE ATTEMPT TO HELP
THE BITCH GET THE ENSEMBLE OFF
OF THE MANNEQUIN.
IT WAS IMPOSSIBLE!
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE FUCK I'M GONNA DO.
THESE BITCHES ARE
BASICALLY READY AT THIS POINT.
I'M FREAKING THE FUCK OUT.
FUCK!
- [LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING]
- ♪ COVER GIRL ♪
♪ PUT THE BASS IN YOUR WALK ♪
♪ HEAD TO TOE ♪
♪ LET YOUR WHOLE BODY TALK ♪
♪ AND WHAT? ♪
[APPLAUSE]
- WELCOME TO THE MAIN STAGE OF
AMERICA'S GOT CHARISMA,
UNIQUENESS, NERVE, AND TALENT.
[LAUGHTER]
HELLO TO THE STAR
OF TWO AND A HALF BOOBS,
MICHELLE VISAGE.
[LAUGHTER]
- SEASON 6,
BRING OUT YOUR BITCHES.
- [LAUGHS]
SHAKE THE DICE
AND STEAL THE RICE,
IT'S SANTINO.
WELCOME BACK, BABY.
- SOMETHING'S SMELLING FISHY,
AND THEY SAY IT'S RU.
- [LAUGHS]
AND MIKE RUIZ.
DID YOU FALL
FOR ANY OF MY GIRLS YESTERDAY?
- I DID. I FELL HARD.
- [LAUGHS]
AND PRESIDENT
OF THE GLAMBERT NATION,
ADAM LAMBERT IS HERE.
YOU LOOK REALLY GOOD TONIGHT.
- OH, THANK YOU! SO DO YOU.
- OH, THANK YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AFTER THE SHOW?
- ANYTHING YOU WANT.
[LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHS]
FOR THIS WEEK'S BIG OPENING,
WE CHALLENGED OUR FIRST 7 QUEENS
TO TAKE LEFTOVERS
FROM TV'S GREATEST HITS
AND CREATE
THEIR VERY OWN RUNWAY COUTURE.
GENTLEMEN, START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN.
♪ NOW, SISSY THAT WALK ♪
G-G-G-GIA.
"KEEPING UP
WITH THE KARDASHIANS."
KEEPING UP
WITH THE KAR-DAY-SHIANS.
- [LAUGHS]
- SO I'M THE FIRST ONE OUT
ON THE RUNWAY.
I'M READY TO SET
THAT TONE FOR THOSE BITCHES
THAT HAVE TO FOLLOW ME.
MY LEGS ARE BRONZED
AND TANNED FOR THE GODS,
SERVING UP KIM K. REALNESS.
- IS THAT THE LONG-LOST SISTER
MEI LING KARDASHIAN?
- YES.
- KIMORA LEE KAR-DAY-SHIAN.
- OH.
- APRIL CARRION,
SERVING "TUCK DYNASTY."
- [LAUGHS]
- [QUACKS]
- IS THAT A DECOY IN HER POCKET,
OR IS SHE JUST HAPPY TO SEE ME?
[LAUGHTER]
- I'M WALKING ON THE RUNWAY
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER,
AND I'M ROCKING IT.
I CAN SEE ADAM LAMBERT
WATCHING ME STYLE.
HE WANTS SOME CHICKEN LEGS.
I KNOW IT.
- TAKING HER DUCK OUT
FOR A DRAG.
[LAUGHTER]
- LAGANJA ESTRANJA,
SERVING
"DANCING WITH THE STARS."
NOMI MALONE, SHOWGIRLS.
VERY QUEEN OF THE NIGHT.
WHITNEY, WHERE'S YOUR BODYGUARD?
OH, SHE'S GOING THAT WAY.
[LAUGHTER]
- THEY CAN'T HANDLE ME.
IT'S LEG FOR DAYS,
TRAIN FOR MONTHS,
AND FACE FOR YEARS.
- WHOA!
- HEY, SOLID GOLD.
KELLY MANTLE.
NOW, SHE'S DOING
"DOWNTON ABBEY."
- CHRISTINE BARANSKI'S
IN THE HOUSE.
[LAUGHTER]
- I'VE GOT MY HAIR.
I'VE GOT MY MAKEUP DID.
I'VE GOT MY 28-INCH WAIST.
OKAY? I AM WORKING IT
LIKE A NINETIES RUNWAY MODEL.
- THERE'S SOME
KRISTEN WIIG-Y IN THERE.
- SHE GETTING WIIG-Y WITH IT?
- UH-OH, HEY.
- [LAUGHING]
- ADORE DELANO,
HONEY BOO BOO CHILD.
- HONEY CHILD.
- I'D BET $100,000
WOULD MAKE HER HOLLER.
- [LAUGHS]
- I'M SCARED.
I LOOK LIKE A FUCKING MESS,
BUT I DO NOT WANT TO GO HOME,
SO I NEED TO SELL THIS GARMENT
LIKE IT'S
A 2004 HEATHERETTE SHOW.
- SHH, IT'S A WIG.
[LAUGHTER]
REPRESENTING
"THE GAME OF THRONES,"
VIVACIOUS.
- OOH.
- HEY.
- MARY J. IN THE HOUSE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
"GAME OF THRONES" IN THE 411.
[LAUGHTER]
- I AM WALKING DOWN THAT RUNWAY,
AND I AM SERVING IT DOWN,
MISS THING.
I AM GIVING YOU OLD-SCHOOL STYLE
NEW YORK WALK, WALK, WALK, POSE.
- WHAT TIME IS IT ON YOUR CROW?
- WELCOME TO HER QUEENDOM.
AIN'T NO RED WEDDING HERE.
- UH-UH.
BENDELACREME,
SERVING "GOLDEN GIRLS."
MICHELLE VISAGE.
- BITCH STOLE YOUR LOOK!
- [LAUGHING]
- BENDELACREME VISAGE.
- IT'S MY FIRSTBORN.
- I'M GIVING BENDELACREME
IN HER FULL GLORY.
I'M GIVING THEM THE SEX APPEAL,
BUT I'M ALSO GIVING THEM
THE CAMP AND THE FUN
AND THE GOOFINESS.
- CHEESECAKE.
- MMM, EAT IT.
- ♪ NOW, SISSY THAT WALK ♪
COMING UP...
- I FELT LIKE IT WAS BOY.
- YOU'RE TRIPPING.
- THAT SKIRT IS HORRIBLE.
- HIDEOUS.
- [LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING]
WELCOME, LADIES.
IT'S TIME
FOR THE JUDGES' CRITIQUES.
FIRST UP, G-G-GIA GUNN.
- I THINK YOUR LOOK IS
WELL-ASSEMBLED.
YOUR HAIR IS FLAWLESS.
- I COULD TELL
THAT YOU'RE THE FEISTY ONE.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- ONE THING I WANT YOU
TO BE CONSCIOUS OF: A BOOTY
WITH AN OPEN LEG CUTS YOUR LEG.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- I LIKE THE BOOTY.
- THANK YOU, GIA.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- APRIL CARRION, I'M
VERY EXCITED THAT YOU CHANGED
YOUR MIND
ABOUT THAT PAIR OF PANTS.
- THE PANTS WEREN'T FITTING,
AND I LOOKED
LIKE A CRAZY MAN, REALLY.
- [LAUGHS]
- YOU DID A REALLY
AMAZING JOB AT TAKING
HYPER-MASCULINE ELEMENTS
AND MAKING A FEMININE LOOK.
- YOU ARE GORGEOUS.
- WELL, YOU'RE GORGEOUS AS WELL.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- GET A ROOM.
[LAUGHTER]
- UP NEXT, LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- HEY, GIRL.
- LAGANJA, YOU'RE
TRIPPING ON THE SKIRT.
- OKAY.
- ALSO LOST YOUR NECKLINE
COMPLETELY.
- RIGHT.
- I'M KIND OF LOVING HOW
YOUR HAIR BLENDS INTO THE TOP.
I THINK IT'S INTERESTING.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- BUT I NEED MORE FISH
FROM YOU ONSTAGE.
I FELT LIKE IT WAS BOY.
- [OBNOXIOUSLY] OKAY.
- YOU ARE FILLED
WITH ENERGY, ARE YOU?
- YES, GO ON.
- THANK YOU, LAGANJA.
ALL RIGHT, KELLY MANTLE.
- IS THAT BACON ON YOUR CHEST?
- [LAUGHS]
- WHAT IS IT?
- THEY'RE FLOWER PETALS.
- I'M STILL GETTING BACON.
- I THINK I WAS FOCUSING MORE
ON THE HIGH-FASHION PART OF IT.
- BECAUSE NOTHING SAYS HIGH
FASHION LIKE WHITE POLYESTER.
THAT SKIRT IS HORRIBLE.
- HORRIBLE?
- HORRIBLE.
- SAY WHAT YOU WILL
ABOUT THE MATERIALS,
BUT I THINK IT'S VERY FEMININE,
AND I LIKE THAT.
- ADORE DELANO,
TELL ME ABOUT THIS OUTFIT.
- WELL, UM...
I HAD A VISION.
LIKE, IF I WAS
AN EIGHTIES MERMAID
WHO GOT HER PROM DONE BY,
LIKE, HEATHERETTE
WHEN HE FIRST STARTED,
DIDN'T HAVE A SEWING MACHINE.
- [LAUGHING]
- JUST LEARNING HOW TO MAKE
SOMETHING OUT OF SOMETHING.
[LAUGHTER]
- I THINK YOU
ARE SO FREAKING CUTE.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- BUT IT'S PRETTY MUCH FABRIC
WRAPPED AROUND YOUR BODY
WITH A BELT.
- I'M NOT LOVING THIS OUTFIT.
THE EXECUTION OF THE WHOLE THING
IS NOT THERE.
- YOU KNOW, YOU WANT TO TAKE
THAT ONE LAST LOOK IN THE MIRROR
BEFORE YOU HIT THE RUNWAY.
- ALL RIGHT, NEXT UP, VIVACIOUS.
- I CAN ALWAYS TELL WHEN
A NEW YORKER WALKS THE RUNWAY,
BECAUSE WE HAVE
THAT KIND OF BALL WALK,
THAT PEPPER LABEIJA KIND OF...
- OKAY.
- YES, HONEY.
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S LIKE THIS WEIRD
COMBINATION OF CAROL CHANNING
MEETS EDGAR ALLAN POE.
[LAUGHTER]
- OH, OKAY.
- YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T WANT
TO COMBINE THOSE TWO.
YOU JUST DON'T.
- THE WORST PART
OF YOUR LOOK IS THE HEMLINE.
IT'S JUST LIKE
YOU RAN OUT OF FABRIC.
- NEXT UP, BENDELACREME.
- DID YOU SEW THIS?
- I DIDN'T.
THIS IS ALL JUST
HOT GLUE AND DESPERATION
FROM HEAD TO TOE.
I WANTED THE CRAFTSMANSHIP TO GO
WITH THE GOLDEN GIRLS THEME
AND LOOK LIKE IT WAS MADE
BY OLD ARTHRITIC HANDS.
[LAUGHTER]
- IT'S COUTURE.
IT'S A CONCEPT.
IT'S STUNNING.
- ALL RIGHT, DELA,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NOW, WHILE YOU UNTUCK
IN THE FORM DECOR LOUNGE,
THE JUDGES AND I
WILL DELIBERATE.
JUST BETWEEN US--
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS--
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
LET'S START WITH GIA GUNN.
- I WASN'T THOROUGHLY IMPRESSED
BY THE ENSEMBLE
SHE PUT TOGETHER.
- I'M NOT TRYING TO BE SHADY,
BUT I DIDN'T REALLY LIKE HER
WHEN SHE WAS TALKING.
- YOU KNOW, HER ANSWER
TO EVERYTHING WAS,
"OH, ABSOLUTELY," YOU KNOW,
BEFORE WE EVEN FINISHED
THE COMMENT.
- BUT SHE WAS ABLE
TO WORK THE GARMENT.
- LET'S TALK
ABOUT APRIL CARRION.
- I THINK SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
THE FACE, THE BODY,
AND ALSO THE OUTFIT
I THOUGHT WAS REALLY
HIGH-FASHION.
- SHE HAMMERED THIS CHALLENGE.
- FOR ME, I'VE NEVER BEEN
A FAN WHEN DRAG QUEENS
USE THEIR OWN HAIR, AND,
IF THEY DO USE THEIR OWN HAIR,
IT CAN'T HAVE
A MAN'S BUZZ CUT BACK THERE.
- I KIND OF THOUGHT
IT WAS KIND OF HOT.
- BECAUSE YOU WANT TO FUCK HER.
- [LAUGHING]
- NEXT UP, LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- THE THING AROUND HER HEAD
AND THEN THIS ELIZABETHAN COLLAR
AND THEN THAT SCHMATTA...
ON THE BOTTOM, IT WAS JUST...
[IMITATES DEJECTED TONE]
- I LIKED THAT IT WAS ODD.
THERE WERE CERTAIN PROPORTIONS
SHE WAS MAKING WITH HER HAIR
GOING INTO THAT COLLAR.
- BUT I THINK SHE'S JUST
TRYING TOO HARD.
WITH HER PERSONALITY,
"UH-HUH, MAMA,"
YOU KNOW, AND, LIKE,
ALL OF THAT, IT'S JUST ANNOYING.
- RIGHT. YOU KNOW,
WHEN I SEE OLD FOOTAGE OF ME
FROM AROUND THAT AGE,
I'M TRYING SO HARD.
I WISH I COULD SIT MYSELF DOWN
AND GO, "JUST BE YOURSELF."
ALL RIGHT, LET'S MOVE ON
TO KELLY MANTLE.
- ORDINARILY EVERYTHING
IS BETTER WRAPPED IN BACON,
BUT NOT KELLY.
[LAUGHTER]
- FROM TOP TO BOTTOM,
IT WAS OFF.
THAT WAS A SHAKE-AND-GO WIG.
THE MAKEUP WAS TERRIBLE.
- SHE WAS VERY LACKLUSTER,
BUT, DESPITE THAT FACT,
I DO FEEL LIKE
THERE'S SOMETHING UNDERNEATH.
- I AGREE.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S INTELLIGENT,
SHE'S FUNNY,
AND SHE'S A SEASONED QUEEN.
NEXT UP, ADORE DELANO.
NOW, HER OUTFIT WAS HIDEOUS.
- I THINK SHE'S GOT
THAT "IT" THING
THAT NOT ALL THESE GIRLS HAVE.
- SHE IS CHARMING,
AND SHE UNDERSTANDS
HOW TO DELIVER A JOKE.
- BUT IT WAS JUST A MESS.
- ALL RIGHT, NEXT UP, VIVACIOUS.
- GIRL, I THINK THE HAIRLINE
STARTED DOWN HERE.
[LAUGHTER]
- WELL, SHE REPRESENTS
THAT REALLY UNDERGROUND
CLUB STORYLINE.
WAS SHE ABLE TO TRANSLATE THAT
INTO HER CHALLENGE?
- NO, I DON'T GET THAT AT ALL,
BUT THAT WALK WAS EVERYTHING.
- I WAS FASCINATED
BY HER CHARACTER,
AND I WANT TO SEE
WHAT SHE HAS IN STORE.
- ALL RIGHT, NEXT UP,
BENDELACREME.
- I WAS SO IMPRESSED
WITH WHAT SHE GLUED TOGETHER.
- I MEAN, THAT WAS
SNATCHED ON HER BODY.
IT WAS SO FITTED
ON HER HIPS AND HER WAIST.
- IT WAS LIKE A COUTURE GOWN.
- IT REALLY WAS.
YOU KNOW, SHE HAS
THIS CHARACTER THAT SHE DOES.
- SHE KIND OF HAS
A FIFTIES "I LOVE LUCY"
COMEDIC KIND OF VIBE.
- THAT PERSONALITY
CAN GET OLD REAL QUICK.
- SILENCE.
I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
BRING BACK MY SQUIRRELS.
- [CLICKS TONGUE]
- [LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING]
WELCOME BACK, LADIES.
I'VE MADE SOME DECISIONS.
FIRST,
I WILL NOT BE GRANTING
IMMUNITY THIS SEASON.
PERIOD.
MAKE EVERY MOMENT COUNT.
GIA GUNN...
YOU'RE SAFE.
- [MOUTHS] THANK YOU.
- LAGANJA ESTRANJA...
YOU'RE SAFE.
- THANK YOU.
- APRIL CARRION...
YOU'RE SAFE.
BENDELACREME...
YOU WERE SERVING CHEESECAKE
AND LEFT US GAGGING FOR MORE.
CONDRAGULATIONS,
YOU'RE THE WINNER
OF THIS WEEK'S CHALLENGE.
- YES.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- YOU'LL RECEIVE
A CUSTOM JEWEL PACKAGE
FROM FIERCE DRAG JEWELS.
- [CHEERING]
- KELLY MANTLE...
YOUR RUNWAY LOOK...
WAS A LITTLE DOWNTON SHABBY.
I'M SORRY, BUT YOU'RE UP
FOR ELIMINATION.
ADORE DELANO, YOUR COUTURE
WAS A HONEY OF A BOO BOO.
VIVACIOUS,
YOUR RUNWAY STRUT
WAS PURE VOGUE,
BUT YOUR OUTFIT WAS VAGUE.
VIVACIOUS...
I'M SORRY, MY DEAR,
BUT YOU ARE UP FOR ELIMINATION.
ADORE, YOU'RE SAFE.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU MAY JOIN THE OTHER GIRLS.
TWO QUEENS STAND BEFORE ME.
LADIES, THIS IS
YOUR LAST CHANCE TO IMPRESS ME
AND SAVE YOURSELF
FROM ELIMINATION.
THE TIME HAS COME
FOR YOU TO LIP-SYNC
FOR YOUR LIFE.
- I AM NOT GOING HOME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KELLY HAS,
BUT I KNOW ONE THING:
I KNOW HOW TO EAT A STAGE.
- GOOD LUCK,
AND DON'T FUCK IT UP.
- ♪ COME ON, GIRLS ♪
♪ DO YOU BELIEVE IN LOVE? ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I GOT SOMETHING
TO SAY ABOUT IT ♪
♪ AND IT GOES
SOMETHING LIKE THIS ♪
♪ DON'T GO
FOR SECOND BEST, BABY ♪
♪ PUT YOUR LOVE TO THE TEST ♪
♪ YOU KNOW, YOU KNOW,
YOU'VE GOT TO ♪
♪ MAKE HIM EXPRESS
HOW HE FEELS ♪
♪ AND MAYBE THEN YOU'LL KNOW
YOUR LOVE IS REAL ♪
♪ YOU DON'T NEED... ♪
- KELLY IS SERVING FACE,
SERVING LIP-SYNCHING,
BUT THEN VIVACIOUS,
SHE'S, LIKE, STRUTTING LIKE--
AND I'M FEELING THAT.
I'M BELIEVING. I'M BELIEVING.
- ♪ THEY NEVER LAST, NO, NO ♪
♪ YOU GOT TO MAKE HIM
EXPRESS HIMSELF ♪
- VIVACIOUS IS SOCKING IT.
I WOULD'VE THOUGHT EXPRESS
YOURSELF IS UP KELLY'S AVENUE
OR MORE TO HER AGE GROUP.
- ♪ EXPRESS WHAT HE'S GOT ♪
♪ OH, BABY, READY OR NOT ♪
♪ EXPRESS YOURSELF ♪
- [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- LADIES, I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
VIVACIOUS, SHANTE, YOU STAY.
- THANK YOU, RU.
- YOU MAY JOIN THE OTHER GIRLS.
KELLY MANTLE,
I AM SO GLAD
WE HAD THIS TIME TOGETHER.
NOW, SASHAY AWAY.
- [LAUGHS]
- UNFORTUNATELY, I DIDN'T GET
TO STICK AROUND TO SING OR ACT,
BUT I'M NOT A SEWER.
I HAVE LITTLE SWEATSHOPS IN VAN
NUYS THAT DOES THAT FOR ME.
DON'T WEAR BACON,
DON'T WEAR BACON.
- LADIES, CONDRAGULATIONS
FOR MAKING IT THROUGH
MY FIRST BIG OPENING.
NEXT WEEK, 7 NEW QUEENS
ARRIVE TO COMPETE
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME,
AND THE WEEK AFTER THAT,
YOUR TWO GROUPS WILL MERGE.
AND THEN, CHILD,
IT'S GONNA GET
SEVERE UP IN HERE.
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- NOW, REMEMBER,
IF YOU CAN'T LOVE YOURSELF,
HOW IN THE HELL YOU
GONNA LOVE SOMEBODY ELSE?
CAN I GET AN AMEN UP IN HERE?
- AMEN!
- ALL RIGHT,
NOW LET THE MUSIC PLAY.
- YEAH!
- ♪ I WANNA DANCE, DANCE ♪
♪ I WANNA DANCE, DANCE ♪
♪ DANCE WITH YOU ♪
- BYE!