- PREVIOUSLY
ON "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE"--
IN THE MOST AMBITIOUS CHALLENGE
IN "DRAG RACE" HISTORY,
YOU'LL BE PERFORMING LIVE
IN "SHADE, THE RUSICAL."
- [APPLAUSE]
- I'M A DRAG QUEEN.
I LIP-SYNC,
I DON'T SING LIVE.
- ♪ WATCH ME BE YOUR STAR ♪
- ♪ NO "T," NO SHADE ♪
- THE WINNER OF THIS WEEK'S
MAIN CHALLENGE IS COURTNEY ACT.
WELL, WHY DO YOU THINK
GIA'S SAFE AND YOU'RE HERE?
- BECAUSE I THINK
I'M ONE OF THE TOP 3.
- TRINITY K. BONET,
SHANTE, YOU STAY.
APRIL, SASHAY AWAY.
- OOH,
THAT WAS A DOOZY, GIRL.
- A DOOZY.
- THAT WAS A LIP SYNC, Y'ALL.
- TRINITY, YOU TURNED IT, BITCH.
CLAP FOR THAT HOOKER.
- WHOO.
- NO MORE AP-R-IL.
IT'S BEEN A REALLY BUMPY ROAD.
BUT I FEEL ACCOMPLISHED,
I'M STILL HERE.
- I'LL NEVER FORGET APRIL.
MY BABY'S DUE IN APRIL.
- OH, GOD.
- REALLY?
- WHEN IT COMES
TO MILK AND HER, UM, FASHION,
I DON'T GET IT.
LIKE, WE'RE PLAYING
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL,
AND SHE'S PLAYING CHECKERS.
WE'RE NOT
IN THE SAME GAME, HERE.
- DARIENNE, YOU WOULD UP
IN THE BOTTOM 3,
YOU WEREN'T EXPECTING THAT,
WERE YOU?
- I WAS MAD
AS MOTHERFUCKING HELL--
I WAS MAD.
- WHO DO YOU FEEL
SHOULD HAVE BEEN THERE?
- MILK, SAFE?
SERIOUSLY?
I WAS GIVING YOU ADELE
GOING TO THE TONYS.
I WAS NOT GIVING YOU
PHYLLIS DILLER
GOING TO THE DELIVERY ROOM.
- GANJ-GANJ,
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- WELL, UM, MY PARENTS
ACTUALLY CAME UP
ON THE UNTUCKED SCREEN TODAY.
IT WAS JUST KIND
OF A HARD MOMENT,
BECAUSE LIKE,
THE GIRLS JUST, LIKE, KIND OF
JUMPED IN IMMEDIATELY
AND STARTED TALKING OVER ME.
I'M VERY, VERY THANKFUL.
I REALLY DO LOVE THEM,
AND I KNOW
THAT THEY SUPPORT ME 100%.
- I THINK YOUR PARENTS
ARE ABSOLUTELY LOVELY.
THE ONLY THING
I DISAGREE WITH
IS THAT THEY
THINK YOU'RE GOING TO WIN.
- I FEEL HURT THAT YOU GUYS
WOULD TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THIS MOMENT FOR YOURSELVES,
BECAUSE THIS WAS ABOUT ME.
IT WAS HARD FOR ME,
BECAUSE I NEEDED TO TAKE
THAT MOMENT TO JUST BREATHE,
AND REALLY TAKE IT IN BEFORE
I COULD SPEAK, AND I JUST--
I FELT LIKE I DIDN'T
REALLY GET THAT.
BIANCA'S LIKE,
"WELL I AGREE WITH EVERYTHING,
BUT YOU'RE NOT THE WINNER."
- BITCH, IT WAS A FUCKING JOKE.
TAKE ALL THAT WEEPY BULLSHIT,
TAKE ALL THAT ATTENTION
THAT YOU NEED,
AND APPLY IT TO THE COMPETITION.
OR GET THE FUCK OUT.
NEED HELP PACKING?
BEAT IT, QUEEN.
- ♪ RUPAUL DRAG RACE ♪
- THE WINNER
OF "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
RECEIVES A SICKENING SUPPLY
OF COLOREVOLUTION COSMETICS
AND A CASH PRIZE OF $100,000,
WITH EXTRA-SPECIAL GUEST JUDGES
HEATHER MCDONALD
AND GILLIAN JACOBS.
- ♪ RUPAUL DRAG RACE ♪
♪ MAY THE BEST WOMAN
BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
- NOW, SISSY THAT WALK.
- [HUMMING TO RUPAUL'S
"SISSY THAT WALK"]
- SO, IT'S A NEW DAY
IN THE WORKROOM,
AND WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT TO EXPECT NEXT.
- GIRL, I'VE GOT TO STRETCH.
LET ME GET UP IN HERE.
- ERYKAH BA-DON'T.
[LAUGHTER]
OF COURSE, MISS ATTENTION WHORE,
WEEPING WILLOW,
IS WEARING A MACRAME POTHOLDER
ON HER GODDAMN HEAD,
BECAUSE CLEARLY
SHE NEEDS MORE ATTENTION.
- WELL GIRL,
I'M YOUNG AND HUNG,
AND CLEARLY MARCH
TO THE SOUND OF MY OWN DRUM,
SO, PROPS TO YOU, MAMA.
- WAIT, WHERE DID
THAT COME FROM?
- DID YOU JUST GET OUT
OF THE SHOWER?
- I GUESS THE QUESTION IS,
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE PLANT
THAT WAS IN IT, HANGING IN
YOUR HOTEL ROOM EARLIER.
- OH GIRL, I SMOKED THAT PLANT,
TRUST AND BELIEVE, MAMA!
- THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
THE FASHION CHOICE.
- WELL, AT LEAST I'VE GOT
SOME FASHION GOING ON.
- OH, SURE GIRL.
- MISS BIANCA,
OLD AND WISE,
AND YET, SO FULL OF SHIT.
[SIREN WAILS]
- OHH!
- NICE SHE-MAIL FOR THE HE-MALE.
- WHAT NOW?
- OOH, GIRL,
YOU GOT SHE-MAIL.
CALLING ALL THE BASIC RACERS.
THERE IS A NEW ANNOUNCEMENT.
YOU'RE BASIC.
- [LAUGHS]
- AND AIN'T NOBODY
GOT TIME FOR THAT.
- OH BOY.
- OHH.
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO!
- HI!
- LOOK AT YOU.
NOW, LADIES,
THIS WEEK'S MAIN CHALLENGE
IS GOING TO BE PACKED
WITH MORE STARS
THAN THERE ARE IN HEAVEN.
WHO'S COMING?
WELL, YOU'LL HAVE TO TELL ME,
BECAUSE IT'S TIME TO PLAY...
SNATCH GAME!
- OH, MY GOSH.
- I AM SO FUCKING EXCITED.
THIS IS THE REASON
I CAME INTO THIS COMPETITION,
IS TO SNATCH
SNATCH GAME,
SNATCH THE TITLE.
- NOW, YOU'LL NEED TO BUST OUT
YOUR BEST CELEBRITY
IMPERSONATION.
GENTLEMEN, START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN.
- SNATCH GAME IS A REALLY
IMPORTANT CHALLENGE.
IT'S ONE THAT EVERYBODY
KNOWS IS COMING,
AND EVERYBODY'S KIND OF WAITING
ALL SEASON
TO SEE WHAT YOU PULL OUT.
BUT I DON'T DO IMPERSONATIONS--
THAT'S NOT EVER PART OF MY DEAL.
- THIS CHALLENGE IS THE ONE
THAT'S GOING TO SEPARATE
THE TALENTED
FROM THE OTHER ONES.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE, HON?
- TERESA GIUDICE, FROM JERSEY.
- WHO ARE YOU DOING, BABY?
- I'M GOING TO BE RACHEL ZOE.
- I COULD SEE THAT.
- YOU KNOW, WHEN TAY-TAY
WAS HER ASSISTANT,
BEFORE SHE TURNED BITCH.
I THINK THE KEY
TO A GOOD IMPERSONATION
IS NOT ONLY LOOKING
LIKE THE CHARACTER,
BUT SPEAKING IN THEIR VOICE.
[IMITATING RACHEL ZOE]
IT'S MAJ.
I'M NOT WORRIED.
- AND WHO ARE YOU DOING,
MISS BIANCA DEL RIO?
- CAN YOU TELL
FROM THIS HAIRDO?
- LET'S GUESS.
- SHE'S MY FAVORITE PERSON
IN THE WORLD.
- I'M JUST GOING TO GO
WITH JUDGE JUDY.
- JUDGE JUDY,
DING, DING, DING!
I LOVE HER.
I WANT TO BE HER.
THE REASON WHY
I'M CHOOSING JUDGE JUDY
IS BECAUSE SHE'S SMART,
SHE'S SENSIBLE,
AND SHE'S A FUCKING BITCH.
I LOVE HER.
I--I WATCH HER ALL THE TIME
BECAUSE SHE MAKES ME LAUGH.
- AND RUPAUL LOVES HER SO MUCH.
- OH SHE DOES?
- YEAH.
- SO, I HAVE NO IDEA
THAT "JUDGE JUDY"
IS RUPAUL'S FAVORITE TV SHOW.
HEH--PRESSURE?
SO, IT EITHER COULD BE
REALLY GOOD OR A HOT MESS.
- YEAH, YOU COULD FALL FLAT
ON YOUR FACE AND GO HOME.
- [CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY]
- BIANCA IS
A LITTLE BIT STRESSED.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER
AT ALL SWEAT IN THE COMPETITION,
AND IT'S INTERESTING
SEEING HER KIND OF
WRIGGLE A LITTLE.
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO!
- HI!
- HELLO!
- NO MORE FUN AND GAMES
OF THE MIND.
ADORE DELANO, DARLING.
- HI, RU.
- OKAY, THAT IS A BLONDE WIG.
- YEAH,
I'M DOING ANNA NICOLE SMITH.
- ANNA NICOLE SMITH!
- I LOVE HER.
LIKE, KIDS HAD SPICE GIRLS
ON THEIR FOLDERS,
AND I LITERALLY WOULD HAVE,
LIKE, THE "PLAYBOY" CUTOUT,
BECAUSE I WOULD STEAL IT--
NO, REALLY.
I THINK I IDENTIFIED
WITH THE FACT
THAT SHE WAS JUST VERY CRAZY,
AND SHE INSPIRES ADORE
A LOT, TOO.
- CAN YOU DO A SOUTHERN ACCENT
LIKE HER?
- I CAN!
- LET ME HEAR IT.
[IMITATING ANNA NICOLE SMITH]
- I WAS HONORED TO BE IN
OUR NEXT PERFORMER'S NEW VIDEO,
AND IF I EVER RECORD AN ALBUM,
I'D WANT THIS GUY
TO PRODUCE MINE,
BECAUSE HE'S FREAKING GENIUS.
I WOULD REALLY BE LETTING
DANNIELYNN DOWN
IF I DID NOT WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
- DELA.
- HI, RU.
- IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
DOING SOMEONE OLDER.
- IT IS.
I WILL BE DOING
MAGGIE SMITH.
- "DOWNTON ABBEY" MAGGIE SMITH.
- YES, YES.
- HOW WILL YOU MAKE
MAGGIE SMITH FUNNY?
- WELL, I THINK MAGGIE SMITH
IS ALREADY SUCH A CHARACTER.
- HMM.
- AND JUST, SORT OF, SHE'S BEEN
IN THE BUSINESS SO LONG.
- YEAH.
NOW, YOU DO AN ENGLISH ACCENT?
- UM, YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO DO ONE, IF I'M HONEST.
- WHAT OTHER CHOICES
WERE YOU MULLING OVER
BEFORE YOU SETTLED
ON MAGGIE SMITH?
- UM, WELL,
I WAS INITIALLY THINKING
ABOUT ONE OF MY FAVORITE QUEENS
FROM LAST SEASON,
MISS ALYSSA EDWARDS.
- CAN I SEE A LITTLE BIT
OF YOUR ALYSSA EDWARDS?
G--
[GAGGING]
- WOW. ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU'VE GOT
A LOT OF COMPETITION.
THERE ARE VERY
TALENTED GIRLS HERE.
- RU DOES NOT SEEM INTO MY IDEA.
I'M SHAKEN--MY CONFIDENCE
IS DEFINITELY SHAKEN, BUT, I--
- COMING UP--
- I'D RATHER YOU HAVE
LOW EXPECTATIONS
SO I CAN BLOW YOU AWAY.
- WELL, YOU'VE SUCCEEDED.
- AAH!
- [LAUGHS]
- TODAY'S CHALLENGE
IS THE SNATCH GAME,
WHERE YOU IMPERSONATE ONE
OF YOUR FAVORITE CELEBRITIES.
- LAGANJA GIRL.
- HEY, MAMA RU.
- AND WHAT'S WITH THIS HEADPIECE
YOU HAVE ON?
- OH, THIS OLD THING?
- [LAUGHS]
SO, WHO ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
- I'M GOING TO BE PLAYING
RACHEL ZOE.
[IMITATING RACHEL ZOE]
SHE'S BANANAS!
- [LAUGHS]
I KNOW SHE'S GOT
SOME KEY PHRASING--
"LIT-ER-AL-LY."
- AND "I DIE,"
AND "MAJ!"
- NOW, ARE YOU QUICK
ON YOUR TOES?
- I'M VERY QUICK ON MY TOES,
AND I MUST SAY, YOUR OUTFIT
IS JUST TO DIE FOR.
- LITERALLY?
- LITERALLY.
- [LAUGHS]
ALL RIGHT, GET BACK TO WORK.
- THANKS, RU.
- WELL, HELLO, MILK.
- HI!
- WHO ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
- THE CHEF THAT BROUGHT
FRENCH COOKING
TO THE AMERICAN KITCHEN,
JULIA CHILD.
- OH, WOW.
SO, HOW ARE YOU GOING
TO MAKE HER FUNNY?
- UM, SHE'S ALREADY
OVER THE TOP
BECAUSE OF HER SIZE,
BUT I'M GOING TO BRING
THAT OVER-THE-TOP
SORT OF PERSONALITY,
THAT IF SHE WROTE
A 730-PAGE BOOK
ABOUT FRENCH COOKING, AND--
I MEAN, SO--
I MEAN, SHE'S A SMART GIRL.
- HAVE YOU SEEN SNATCH GAME
ON OUR SHOW?
- WHAT SHOW?
I'D RATHER YOU HAVE
LOW EXPECTATIONS
SO I CAN BLOW YOU AWAY.
- WELL, YOU'VE SUCCEEDED.
- WELL, WELL, WELL,
BIANCA DEL RIO.
- HELLO, MR. RUPAUL.
- OH MY GOODNESS, I JUST SAW
THE JUDGE'S ROBE RIGHT THERE.
- YEAH.
- OH MY GOD.
JUDGE JUDY.
- JUDGE JUDY!
- ONLY JUDY CAN JUDGE ME.
- EXACTLY.
[LAUGHTER]
AND I'M SURE SHE WOULD!
- YOU KNOW HOW I LOVE--
- I--I JUST FOUND OUT
THAT YOU ACTUALLY LOVE HER.
- I GOT TO TELL YOU,
I WATCH "JUDGE JUDY"
EVERY SINGLE DAY--
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- I'VE SEEN EVERY EPISODE.
SO, YOU KNOW, THE HEAT IS ON YOU
TO PULL THIS OFF.
YOU'D BETTER
DO MY JUDGE JUDY PROUD.
- FUCK!
- G-G-G-GIA!
- HI, RU.
- NOW, YOU KNOW SNATCH GAME?
- YES.
- HOW ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
- WELL, NOT ONLY BE SNATCHED--
- UH-HUH.
BUT I'M GOING TO DO SELENA.
- SELENA?
- YES.
- NOT SELENA GOMEZ?
- NO, QUINTANILLA.
- SO--
- A LITTLE BEE-DEE, BEE-DEE.
- IS SHE FUNNY, THOUGH?
I MEAN, HOW ARE YOU GOING
TO MAKE HER FUNNY?
- SO, YOU KNOW, SHE CRACKED,
LIKE, A FEW JOKES
HERE AND THERE.
BUT ALSO, YOU KNOW,
REFERRING TO OTHER THINGS.
I JUST--YOU KNOW,
I'M VERY FLAPPY AT THE JAW,
I'M VERY USED TO,
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
COMING BACK WITH READS, AND--
- I'M NOT BUYING THIS, GIA.
I'M NOT BUYING IT.
GIVE ME A LITTLE SELENA.
CAN YOU GIVE ME A LITTLE SELENA?
- UH-HUH.
"HOLA, TIENEN PREGUNTAS?"
- OKAY.
- GIRL, SELENA--WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO WITH THAT?
I LOVE PIZZA,
I GOT SHOT BY YOLANDA--
LIKE, WHAT'S FUNNY?
LIKE, IT'S THE TRUTH, GIRL!
- ALL RIGHT, LADIES,
GATHER AROUND.
NOW, TOMORROW,
ON THE MAIN STAGE,
THERE'S JUST ONE MORE CELEBRITY
YOU'LL NEED TO CHANNEL.
ME!
CATEGORY IS
"NIGHT OF A THOUSAND RUS."
- [APPLAUSE]
[LAUGHTER]
GOOD LUCK,
AND YOU BETTER WORK.
- [APPLAUSE]
- SUPERMODEL!
- ARE YOU STILL DOING SELENA?
- I'M NOT SURE.
I HAD THE SELENA COSTUME
READY ON MY MANNEQUIN,
BUT I'M NOW PROCESSING
RU'S COMMENTS,
AND KIND OF NOW THINKING
MAYBE THIS ISN'T
THE BEST CHOICE.
- WHO ELSE ARE YOU
THINKING ABOUT?
- BUT YOU'RE PLANNING
ON CHANGING IT?
- I MEAN, I'M THINKING ABOUT IT.
- CAN YOU CHANGE IT?
- YEAH.
- SO, GIA'S PUTTING ON MAKEUP,
AND DON'T KNOW WHO THE FUCK
SHE'S GONNA BE.
HOW THAT WORK?
- WELCOME TO A SUPER-SIZE
EDITION OF SNATCH GAME.
LET'S MEET OUR CONTESTANTS.
COMEDIENNE, AUTHOR,
AND CHARDONNAY DRINKER,
FROM "CHELSEA LATELY,"
HEATHER MCDONALD IS HERE!
[APPLAUSE]
AND STAR OF NBC'S "COMMUNITY,"
GILLIAN JACOBS IS HERE.
- HI!
- YOU'RE A BIG FAN
OF THIS SHOW, I KNOW.
- I'VE SEEN
JUST ABOUT EVERY EPISODE,
AND "DRAG U."
- NOW, ARE YOU READY
TO MEET OUR STARS?
- YES.
- GOOD.
ORDER IN THE COURTROOM, HUNTY,
IT'S JUDGE JUDY.
HEY, YOUR HONOR.
- DID YOU FORGET YOU WERE COMING
TO COURT TODAY
DRESSED LIKE THAT?
YOU LOOK LIKE
A DAMN ROLL OF SCOTCH TAPE.
- WELL, I THOUGHT IT WAS--
- DON'T PISS ON MY LEG
AND TELL ME IT'S RAINING.
[LAUGHTER]
- UP NEXT, "PLAYBOY" PLAYMATE
AND REALITY TV PIONEER,
ANNA NICOLE SMITH IS HERE.
- LIKE MY BODY?
- YEAH.
- WANT SOME MONEY?
WANT A VIPER?
- I'VE GOT TO SAY,
DEATH REALLY BECOMES HER.
[LAUGHTER]
UP NEXT, IT'S THE FRENCH CHEF,
JULIA CHILD.
- OH, HELLO, RU,
HOW ARE YOU?
- I HOPE YOU'VE GOT
SOMETHING COOKING.
DID YOU BRING YOUR LOVIN' OVEN?
- I SURE DID.
IT'S RIGHT UNDER THIS DESK!
- ALL RIGHT.
MOVING ON DOWN
TO THE FIRST LADY OF QUEENS,
FRAN DRESCHER IS HERE.
- ARE YOU SINGLE MR. RUPAUL?
- I AM SINGLE, YES.
- BECAUSE YOU KNOW,
MY GIRLFRIEND, VAL,
EVER SINCE OBAMA GOT INTO POWER,
SHE'S BEEN LOCO FOR THE COCOA.
[LAUGHTER]
- STYLIST TO THE STARS,
RACHEL ZOE IS HERE!
- MIGHT I SAY I LITERALLY
DIE FOR YOUR OUTFIT.
- IS THAT REAL FUR
YOU'RE WEARING?
- IT'S MY NEW FUR FAUX LINE.
- ALL RIGHT, UP NEXT,
THE QUEEN OF SOUTHERN CUISINE,
MISS PAULA DEEN IS HERE!
- MY, YOU GORGEOUS
BALD-HEADED MAN.
- OH, YOU SWEET THING.
- WELL, JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE LOSING YOUR FUZZ
DON'T MEAN YOU AIN'T
A PEACH, HONEY.
[LAUGHS]
WHAT DID SHE JUST CALL ME?
MEDIA SENSATION
KIM KARDASHIAN IS HERE.
HOW'S THE BABY?
- OH, YOU KNOW,
I'M STILL, LIKE,
HAVING SOME MORNING-AFTER--
IS THAT--
YES, YOU KNOW, LIKE,
THROWING UP AND STUFF
AFTER THE PREGNANCY,
BUT EVERYTHING SHOULD BE OKAY.
- KIM, YOU LOOK GORGEOUS.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- AND LOOK WHO'S HERE.
IT'S TERESA FROM "THE REAL
HOUSEWIVES OF NEW JERSEY."
HEY, GIRL.
- DO YOU KNOW HOW
TO PRONOUNCE MY LAST NAME?
- I DON'T,
I HAD A HARD TIME WITH IT.
- WELL, IT WAS JOO-DICE--
- UH-HUH.
- AND THEN, I REALIZED
IT WAS JOO-DEE-CHAY.
- UH-HUH.
- BUT WE WENT
ALL THE WAY BACK
TO THE OLD COUNTRY,
AND IT'S ACTUALLY PRONOUNCED--
LET ME SEE IF I CAN GET IT.
JOHNSON.
[LAUGHTER]
- TERESA JOHNSON, EVERYBODY.
OKAY, WE HAVE TWO-TIME
ACADEMY AWARD-WINNING ACTRESS,
DAME MAGGIE SMITH IS WITH US.
HOW ARE YOU, MY DEAR?
- WELL, PAST A CERTAIN AGE,
ONE JUST FEELS FORTUNATE
TO SEE THE SUN RISE ANOTHER DAY.
- YES, YES, MAGGIE SMITH.
- FOR NOW, LET'S JUST KEEP IT
MR. CHARLES AND DAME SMITH,
SHALL WE?
- YES, MA'AM.
- THANK YOU.
- NOW, EVERYONE'S FAVORITE
PINK LADY,
NICKI MINAJ IS HERE.
- O-M-G. HI, RU.
- HAVE YOU HEARD
FROM MARIAH AT ALL?
[LAUGHTER]
- NO.
- ALL RIGHT,
ARE YOU READY
TO PLAY THE SNATCH GAME?
- OH, SHIT,
IT'S THE SNATCH GAME.
AAH!
- COMING UP--
- I'M SWEATING LIKE TWO RATS
HUMPING IN A WOOL SOCK,
RIGHT NOW.
[LAUGHTER]
- NOT A MATCH, YOUR HONOR.
- BALONEY!
- THAT'S REALLY RUDE.
- I'M TALKING!
- [LAUGHS]
WELCOME BACK TO SNATCH GAME.
NOW, HERE'S HOW
THE GAME WORKS, LADIES.
I ASK A QUESTION,
OUR CELEBRITY CONTESTANTS
FILL IN THE BLANKS,
AND YOU GIVE AN ANSWER
THAT YOU THINK WILL MATCH.
FIRST UP, HEATHER MCDONALD.
CHER IS COMPLETELY ADDICTED
TO SOCIAL MEDIA.
EVEN HER "BLANK"
HAS A TWITTER ACCOUNT.
- I SAID, "EVEN HER WIG
HAS A TWITTER ACCOUNT."
- LET'S GO TO THE STARS
AND FIND OUT
WHAT THEY WROTE DOWN.
JUDGE JUDY.
- HER OLD NOSE.
- NOT A MATCH,
UNFORTUNATELY, BUT--
- SHE--IT HAS BEEN
LIKE 3 OR 4.
- YEAH, SHE'S BEEN TOUCHED
BY AN ANGEL.
- YEAH.
- AND SHE LOOKS GREAT.
- I AGREE, AND YOU KNOW,
I AGREE,
AND SO DOES OFFICER BYRD.
[IMITATING BYRD]
THAT IS CORRECT, JUDGE JUDY.
- NOT A MATCH, YOUR HONOR.
- BALONEY.
[LAUGHTER]
BALONEY, SIR.
- I'M READY FOR A FRIED BOLOGNA
SANDWICH, MYSELF.
- LET'S MOVE ON DOWN
TO ANNA NICOLE SMITH.
- I SEE THAT HER HAIR
CHANGES ALL THE TIME.
- YES, IT DOES.
- AND IT HAS, LIKE,
A MIND OF ITS OWN.
- YES, IT DOES.
- SO, I PUT "HAIR,"
AND I THINK I WON SOMETHING.
- YES. YES, YOU DID.
[LAUGHTER]
- THAT'S A MATCH.
- YES.
- WHAT DO I WIN?
- WELL, WE'LL TELL YOU
IN A MINUTE, ANNA NICOLE.
- OKAY.
- LET'S MOVE ON DOWN
TO RACHEL ZOE.
- I WROTE "SHOES,"
BECAUSE SHOES
ARE THE MOST IMPORTANT ACCESSORY
TO A WOMEN'S OUTFIT.
AND YOU CAN ACTUALLY SEE ME,
RACHEL ZOE,
TO GET YOUR SHOES STYLED.
- UH, RU?
- YES?
- IS THIS GIRL
OVER THERE A ROBOT?
WHY DOES SHE SOUND LIKE THAT?
IS SOMEBODY PUSHING A BUTTON?
CAN YOU TALK NORMAL?
- I'M ACTUALLY OVERWORKED--
- I'M TALKING, I'M TALKING!
AND, UM, I THINK
THAT'S REALLY RUDE.
- IS THAT REALLY
HOW RACHEL ZOE TALKS?
NO? OH...
THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
- ALL RIGHT, DAME MAGGIE SMITH,
CHER, COMPLETELY ADDICTED
TO SOCIAL MEDIA,
EVEN HER "BLANK"
HAS A TWITTER ACCOUNT.
- WELL, RUPLE--RUPLE, IS IT?
- YES, ABSOLUTELY.
- I UNDERSTOOD VIRTUALLY
NONE OF THE WORDS
THAT LEFT YOUR LIPS
MOMENTS AGO,
BUT I DID HEAR
THE TERM "TWITTER,"
AND I ASSUME THAT IT'S
SOME SORT OF SONGBIRD?
- VERY CLOSE, NOT A MATCH.
- AM I TO UNDERSTAND
THAT ONE YANKS ONE'S TELEPHONE
RIGHT OUT OF THE WALLS
AND CARRIES IT WITH HIM?
[LAUGHTER]
- YES.
- RU, COULD YOU GET PEOPLE
THAT SPEAK NORMAL ENGLISH
NEXT TIME FOR THE SHOW?
- EXCUSE ME,
WE ORIGINATED THE LANGUAGE!
[LAUGHTER]
- OH, OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT, UP NEXT,
GILLIAN JACOBS.
THE CITY OF SAN FRANCISCO
IS SO GAY,
INSTEAD OF HORSES,
THEIR MOUNTED POLICE
RIDE "BLANK."
- I SAID, "BEARS."
- WHY NOT RIDE A BEAR?
- I KNOW YOU LIKE A BEAR.
- I LOVE A BEAR.
- I'M SWEATING
LIKE TWO RATS
HUMPING IN A WOOL SOCK,
RIGHT NOW.
- OH, DEAR.
- OH MY.
- LET'S SEE
IF YOU GOT ANY MATCHES
WITH OUR STARS.
JULIA CHILD.
- I HAD ALWAYS HEARD
THAT SAN FRANCISCO WAS--
THERE WAS A SAUSAGE FEST
ALL YEAR ROUND.
- YEAR-ROUND.
- AND SO, THEY MUST HAVE
ALL THESE TRUCKS
TO DELIVER THESE SAUSAGES.
- I'M SURE THEY MUST, YES.
- AND SO, I SAY,
"SAUSAGE TRUCKS."
- MILK AIN'T NO MERYL STREEP.
- ALL RIGHT, KIM KARDASHIAN,
SAN FRANCISCO IS SO GAY,
INSTEAD OF HORSES,
THE MOUNTED POLICE RIDE--
- WELL, LIKE I ALWAYS SAY,
YOU NEVER PUT A TATTOO
ON A BENTLEY,
AND I HOPE THAT I--
- A BENTLEY.
- SPELLED IT RIGHT.
- YOU PROBABLY DIDN'T.
- BEAUTY FADES,
DUMB IS FOREVER.
- UP NEXT,
WE'VE GOT TERESA
FROM "THE REAL HOUSEWIVES
OF NEW JERSEY."
WHAT DO THEY RIDE?
- PROSTITUTION WHORSES.
UNFORTUNATELY, NOT A MATCH.
- CAN I HAVE A PINOT GRIGIO?
- PINOT GRIGIO, COMING RIGHT UP.
ALL RIGHT, NICKI MINAJ,
OH MY GOODNESS,
YOU'VE GOT A HAIRSTYLE CHANGE.
- YES.
- LOVE IT, THAT'S GORGEOUS.
- I DIDN'T GET A CHANCE
TO WRITE ANYTHING DOWN
BECAUSE I WAS TRYING
TO CHANGE MY WIG.
- OH, OKAY.
- WIG CHANGES.
- HOW ORIGINAL.
CHAD MICHAELS,
HOW MANY YEARS AGO?
- YOU DIDN'T
WRITE DOWN ANYTHING?
- NO.
- PERHAPS SHE NEEDS ANOTHER POT
OF INK TO REPLENISH HER QUILL.
[LAUGHTER]
- ALL RIGHT, HEATHER.
THAT CHELSEA HANDLER
IS SO WRONG.
SHE'S LAUNCHING A NEW VODKA.
IT'S FLAVORED WITH "BLANK."
- XANAX.
- XANAX. WHAT A GREAT IDEA!
OKAY, LET'S GO ON OVER
TO ANNA NICOLE SMITH
TO SEE IF SHE MATCHED YOU.
- WELL, I'M NOT REALLY
A DRINKER.
- RIGHT.
- BUT I'VE TASTED VODKA
A COUPLE OF TIMES
IN MY LIFE,
AND I LIKE IT BY ITSELF.
- [LAUGHS]
- SO, I JUST PUT "VODKA."
- UNFORTUNATELY,
IT'S NOT MATCH,
BUT THAT'S A GOOD ANSWER,
ANNA NICOLE.
- KIMMY!
[LAUGHTER]
- FRAN DRESCHER.
CHELSEA HANDLER'S LAUNCHING
A NEW VODKA FLAVORED WITH...
- I SAID "ALCOHOL."
[LAUGHS]
- I KNOW I CAN DO A BETTER
FRAN DRESCHER THAN COURTNEY.
OH, MR. SHEFFIELD.
HA HA HA HA.
- LET'S MOVE
ON TO KIM KARDASHIAN.
- NEW VODKA,
FLAVORED WITH "BLANK."
- I'D HAVE TO GO
WITH "BIG BLACK"--
- KARDASHIAN,
YOU WANT TO DATE HIM?
- YES, DEAR?
OH!
- SHE'S A REAL KEEPER,
AS IN "KEEP 'ER IN A CAGE."
- ALL RIGHT, TERESA,
IT'S FLAVORED WITH "BLANK."
- CUMM-IN.
- OH, YOU MEAN CUMIN.
- YEAH, IT'S PRONOUNCED
"CUE-MIN."
- CUMM-IN.
- OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MOVE ON DOWN
TO DAME MAGGIE SMITH.
- WELL, I'M UNFAMILIAR
WITH THE WORK OF LADY HANDLER,
HOWEVER, I DID THINK THAT
IT WOULD BE RATHER AMUSING
IF THERE WERE LIBATIONS
FLAVORED WITH CITRUS.
[LAUGHTER]
CAN YOU IMAGINE SUCH A THING?
- THAT IS REALLY NEWFANGLED.
I CAN'T IMAGINE SUCH A THING.
- YES.
[LAUGHTER]
- OH, I'M SORRY,
TIME IS UP,
WHICH MEANS,
OUR WINNER IS...
WHO CARES?
THIS IS RUPAUL REMINDING YOU
TO SPAY AND NEUTER
YOUR FRIENDS AND NEIGHBORS.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
SAY "GOOD-BYE," STARS.
- BYE!
- Y'ALL COME BACK, NOW,
YOU HEAR?
- COMING UP--
SHE WAS REALLY CHANNELING HER.
- IT WAS A PERFECT CHOICE
FOR HER.
- IT'S THE TIGHTEST
SNATCH GAME IN HISTORY.
[LAUGHTER]
- [LAUGHS]
- MEOW.
- TONIGHT'S RUNWAY THEME
IS "NIGHT OF A THOUSAND RUS."
WE HAVE TO DRESS UP AS RUPAUL,
WHICH IS EXCITING,
BUT RUPAUL
IS GOING TO BE IN THE ROOM, SO--
- AM I THE ONLY ONE
THAT'S, LIKE,
HAVING A PROBLEM
WITH, LIKE, MY BODY?
MY FRIENDS AND I KID AROUND
ABOUT, LIKE--
WE CALL IT "HOG BODY."
JUST, LIKE, WE'RE REALLY THICK
IN THE MIDSECTION.
- DO YOU FEEL OVERWEIGHT?
- I JUST FEEL LIKE I HAVE
A WEIRD-PROPORTIONED BODY.
- WELL MAYBE YOU DO.
AND SO WHAT?
- YEAH.
I HAVE LOTS TO SAY ABOUT WEIGHT.
I WAS VERY HEAVY
ALL THROUGH MIDDLE SCHOOL.
AND I WAS TEASED MERCILESSLY
ABOUT IT,
FOR BEING GAY AND BEING FAT.
IT AFFECTED MY SELF-CONFIDENCE
SO PROFOUNDLY.
I JUST FELT COMPLETELY UNLOVABLE
FOR SO MANY YEARS
BECAUSE OF THAT.
MY MOM, SHE'D BEEN
SORT OF THE BIG PROPONENT
OF ME BEING MYSELF,
AND THAT I WAS BEAUTIFUL.
AND THEN, WHEN I WAS 13,
MY MOM DIED.
I JUST--
THAT REALLY THREW ME
INTO A TAILSPIN.
I DIDN'T HAVE THAT VOICE SAYING
THAT WHO I WAS WAS OKAY ANYMORE.
I JUST HAD A LOT OF VOICES
AT SCHOOL
SAYING THAT EVERYTHING
ABOUT ME WAS WRONG.
TOO FAT, TOO GAY, TOO WEIRD.
SOMETHING THAT I NEVER EXPECTED
TO HAPPEN
WAS THAT I LEARNED A LOT
FROM MY DRAG CHARACTER
THAT I COULD BRING
TO MY BOY SELF.
- RIGHT.
- I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
ANYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED TO ME
IN THOSE YEARS,
BUT I HAVE LEARNED
TO USE THE HARDSHIP
TO GET STRONGER.
- ADORE.
- YES, BABY?
- IF YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
YELLED AT BY MICHELLE,
BECAUSE DIDN'T
SHE SAY LAST TIME
THAT YOU NEEDED TO BE CINCHED?
- YEAH.
- I, AND DON'T TELL ANYBODY
THAT I'M BEING KIND,
BUT I HAVE ANOTHER CINCHER
IF YOU WANT ME
TO LACE YOU IN IT.
- I'M DOWN.
- OKAY, WE'LL DO IT.
- I'M REALLY GRATEFUL
FOR BIANCA'S
MOTHERLY KIND OF INSTINCT.
SHE'S KIND OF
MY STEPMOM, RIGHT NOW.
[LAUGHING]
I'M A FOSTER CHILD.
- ♪ COVER GIRL
PUT THE BASS IN YOUR WALK ♪
♪ HEAD TO TOE
LET YOUR WHOLE BODY TALK ♪
♪ AND WHAT ♪
[APPLAUSE]
- WELCOME TO THE MAIN STAGE
OF "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
MICHELLE VISAGE, YOU'VE NEVER
LOOKED SO BEAUTIFUL.
- [LAUGHS]
- SANTINO RICE,
IF YOU LOOKED ANY BETTER,
I'D HAVE TO "BLANK" YOU.
[LAUGHTER]
FUNNY LADY, HEATHER MCDONALD,
DID MY QUEEN
SNATCH YOUR ATTENTION?
- YES, AND YOU LOOK STUNNING.
- THANK YOU.
AND SUPERFAN GILLIAN JACOBS.
- I'M GAGGING ON YOUR ELEGANZA.
[LAUGHTER]
- THIS WEEK,
MY QUEENS WERE CHALLENGED
TO SERVE UP THEIR FIERCEST
CELEBRITY IMPERSONATIONS,
AND TONIGHT,
THE CATEGORY IS ME.
GENTLEMEN, START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN.
♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
FIRST UP, JOSLYN FOX.
YES, MAMA.
- SERVING SLIT.
- GIRL, WHY IT GOTTA BE BLACK?
- I'M SERVING EVENING,
GLAM RUPAUL.
I'M FEELING FABULOUS,
FISHY, AND FIERCE.
- I LIKE THE LITTLE SWIVEL
SHE DOES WITH HER ARMS.
- I THINK, HEATHER,
SHE JUST PASSED GAS.
[LAUGHTER]
NEXT UP, GIA GUNN.
- BITCH STOLE YOUR LOOK.
- THAT'S MY DRESS.
[LAUGHTER]
- I'M SERVING MY RUPAUL GOWN
THAT IS VERY ICONIC,
AND I'M EATING IT UP.
- AND THIS IS THE BACK.
- I LOVE A NUDE ILLUSION.
- DIP INTO THE WATERS
OF DARIENNE LAKE.
- OHH.
- RAWR.
- THE MASQUERADE BALL.
- YES, ALL-STAR.
- I'M GIVING RUPAUL,
MY VERSION OF HER RUNWAY WALK
AS "GIRTHA" KITT.
GRR.
- EYES WIDE SHUT,
LEGS WIDE OPEN.
[LAUGHTER]
- LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- UH-OH.
- WHOO.
WELCOME TO MY STRATOSPHERE.
- FEMBOTS HAVE FEELINGS, TOO.
[LAUGHTER]
- I AM SERVING SEASON 4
START YOUR ENGINES MAMA RU,
AND I'M FEELING IT, GIRL.
I'M PLUMMETING THE RUNWAY
AND DROPPING IT LIKE IT'S HOT.
- SUCH A GOOD BODY.
I WISH HER HAIR WAS FULLER,
THAT'S THE ONLY THING.
[LAUGHTER]
- BIANCA DEL RIO, COVER GIRL.
LOOKING GOOD,
FEELING GORGEOUS.
- I AM SERVING
AGE-APPROPRIATE RU.
I'M GIVING RU REALNESS NOW,
AND I'M FEELING GOOD!
- SHE SPARKLES
JUST LIKE A CABLEACE AWARD.
[LAUGHTER]
ADORE DELANO.
GLAMAZON!
SUPERSTAR.
- WHAT I'M DOING
IS ADORE DELANO,
INSPIRED BY RUPAUL.
AND I'M SHOWING
MY BRAND NEW CINCHED WAIST.
I LOOK FUCKING COOL!
- SHE'S CINCHED FOR THE GODS.
WORK THAT BODY, WORK THAT BODY.
TRINITY K. BONET.
FOXY LADY, OUT OF SIGHT.
GET YOUR REBEL ON, GIRL.
- I AM SERVING UP
ILLUSION OF RUPAUL,
AND I LOOK ABSOLUTELY AMAZING.
- BIRDS OF A FEATHER.
- I DIDN'T KNOW THAT BIRDS
CAME IN THAT COLOR.
- [LAUGHS]
- WORK IT, MAMA, WORK.
UP NEXT, BENDELACREME.
WAIT A MINUTE, THAT IS MY DRESS!
[LAUGHTER]
- I'M GIVING
SOME CONTEMPORARY RUPAUL.
I'M WORKING THAT RUNWAY,
I FEEL GREAT IN MY DRESS.
- THIS IS LIKE IDENTITY THEFT.
FIRST SHE STEALS
MICHELLE'S IDENTITY,
NOW, SHE STEALS MINE.
YOU'LL BE HEARING
FROM MY LAWYER!
[LAUGHTER]
THUNDER FROM DOWN UNDER,
COURTNEY ACT.
OH MY GOODNESS.
- I MEAN, THE LEGS
ARE THE BEST LEGS
I'VE EVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
- OH, WAIT, HOLD UP, NOW,
WAIT A MINUTE.
- BESIDES YOU, BESIDES YOU.
- I AM POSSESSED
BY THE SPIRIT OF RUPAUL,
AND I CAN HEAR RU'S VOICE
IN MY HEAD SAYING,
"SUPERMODEL OF THE WORLD."
- I WORE THIS OUTFIT
TO THE VH1 FASHION AWARDS.
- YES, YOU DID.
- BOB MACKIE.
MILK.
- OH!
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO,
IT'S WORKROOM RU.
NO ONE HAS EVER SEEN THIS
ON THE RUNWAY.
I AM WORKING MY ASCOT OFF.
- IS THAT
A KLEIN EPSTEIN PARKER SUIT?
LADY LOOKS LIKE A DUDE.
- ♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
- COMING UP--
A LOT COULD BE FORGIVEN
IF YOU WERE FUNNY,
BUT YOU WERE NOT FUNNY.
- I AM EXTREMELY OFFENDED
THAT YOU WOULD COME OUT
ON THE RUNWAY IN PANTS.
- [LAUGHS]
WELCOME, LADIES.
I'VE MADE SOME DECISIONS.
COURTNEY ACT.
DARIENNE LAKE.
JOSLYN FOX.
TRINITY K. BONET.
YOU'RE SAFE.
YOU MAY LEAVE THE STAGE.
LADIES, IT'S TIME
FOR THE JUDGES' CRITIQUES.
LET'S START WITH GIA GUNN.
- HI.
- LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE SNATCH GAME.
THIS IS SEASON 6.
YOU DON'T PICK A CELEBRITY
WITH NOT A BIG PERSONALITY.
IT WAS FLAT.
- WHEN I SPOKE WITH YOU
IN THE WORKROOM,
YOU WERE GONNA DO SELENA.
WHY'D YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND?
- BECAUSE SHE IS NOT
A COMEDY CHARACTER.
- BUT THAT JUST DAWNED ON YOU
IN THE WORKROOM?
LISTEN, A LOT COULD BE FORGIVEN
IF YOU WERE FUNNY,
BUT YOU WERE NOT FUNNY.
NEXT UP, LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- HI, MAMA RU.
- RACHEL ZOE.
YOU WERE PLAYING, LIKE,
THE CHICKEN LADY
FROM "KIDS IN THE HALL."
THERE WAS A LOT
OF THIS KIND OF--
- I AGREE.
- IT DIDN'T WORK.
- RACHEL ZOE IS KNOWN
FOR SO MANY CATCHPHRASES
THAT I MIGHT WRITE
A CHEAT SHEET.
- I DID.
- YOU DID?
- I DEFINITELY GOT
IN MY HEAD IN THIS ONE.
I SAW MY SISTERS
REALLY SUCCEEDING.
INSTEAD OF PUSHING
MORE FORWARD, I SUNK BACK.
- YOU'RE TALENTED,
SO IT HURTS TO SEE IT.
- IT HURTS ME, TOO.
- UP NEXT, BIANCA DEL RIO.
LOVE THAT DRESS.
- YOU CAN BORROW IT.
- [LAUGHS]
- I HAVE BEEN WAITING
FOR A QUEEN TO DO JUDGE JUDY.
IT WAS BRILLIANT.
- WELL IT DOES HELP THAT
I'M A JUDGMENTAL BITCH, TOO.
[LAUGHTER]
THAT DOES KIND OF HELP.
- YOU WERE ABLE TO INTERACT
WITH THE OTHER QUEENS.
IT WAS FABULOUS.
- NEXT UP, ADORE DELANO.
- THERE IS NOTHING RUPAUL
ABOUT THAT WIG,
NOR THE LOOK, QUITE HONESTLY.
- I WAS DOING ADORE
INSPIRED BY RUPAUL.
- YEAH, YOU WERE DOING ADORE.
AND I THINK THIS LENGTH IS GOING
TO BE A RUNNING THEME FOR YOU.
BUT I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH
FOR CINCHING YOUR WAIST.
IT CHANGES YOUR BODY COMPLETELY.
YOU NEED TO START DOING THIS
ALL THE TIME.
- I CAN FEEL MY HEART
IN MY THROAT,
AND IT TASTES AMAZING!
[LAUGHTER]
- YOUR ANNA NICOLE SMITH,
GUESS AD, '94 REALNESS
WAS PERFORMANCE ART.
- UP NEXT, DELA.
- I LOVE THIS YELLOW LOOK.
IT'S REALLY WELL-DONE.
- I DON'T EVEN WATCH
"DOWNTON ABBEY,"
AND I WAS DYING
OVER MAGGIE SMITH.
- YEAH, LIKE, WHEN YOU SAID,
"WE ORIGINATED THE LANGUAGE,"
THAT WAS, LIKE,
ONE OF THE FUNNIEST THINGS
I HEARD ALL DAY YESTERDAY,
AND I THINK I SAID IT
ABOUT 6 TIMES AFTER I LEFT.
- LAST BUT NOT LEAST, MILK.
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO.
- [LAUGHS]
- PART OF ME, MILK,
IS EXTREMELY OFFENDED
THAT YOU WOULD COME OUT
ON THE RUNWAY IN PANTS.
PART OF ME THINKS IT'S GENIUS
BECAUSE IT IS RUPAUL.
- WELL, THAT'S SORT OF
WHAT I LOVE--
I LOVE GOING FOR THE UNEXPECTED.
- BUT THIS
DOESN'T SHOCK ME, REALLY.
WHAT WOULD SHOCK ME
IS IF YOU HAD COME OUT HERE
AND DONE SOMETHING
SO AMAZINGLY GLAM,
BECAUSE WE REALLY HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU LIKE THAT.
- I COULD GO MORE GLAM,
BUT IT WOULDN'T BE
STAYING TRUE TO MY AESTHETIC.
- BUT I WOULD LOVE
TO SEE YOU AS GLAMAZON.
- HONESTLY, SOMETIMES,
I DO FEEL THAT,
IF I WERE TO PUT ON
A BEAUTIFUL DRESS
LIKE THESE GIRLS
AND BEAUTIFUL HAIR LIKE THEM,
I WOULD STAND OUT
FOR THE WRONG REASONS,
AND PEOPLE WOULD
JUST LAUGH OF ME,
AND I WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO LAUGH AT MYSELF.
- BUT IT'S HARD TO FALL
IN LOVE WITH SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T SHOW
THAT VULNERABILITY
THAT YOU'RE AFRAID OF.
LADIES, THANK YOU.
WHILE YOU UNWIND
IN THE UNTUCKED LOUNGE,
THE JUDGES AND I
WILL DELIBERATE.
ALL RIGHT, JUST BETWEEN US
RUPAUL IMPERSONATORS,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S THE TIGHTEST SNATCH GAME
IN HISTORY.
- I AGREE, AND I SHOULD KNOW
ABOUT TIGHT SNATCH GAMES.
- I DON'T THINK SO, MICHELLE.
[LAUGHTER]
- LET'S START
WITH BIANCA DEL RIO.
- HER JUDGE JUDY,
IT WAS WELL-RESEARCHED,
SHE STAYED IN CHARACTER.
IT WAS A PERFECT CHOICE
FOR HER.
- BUT I DIDN'T THINK
THAT SHE WAS
THE BEST RU LOOK.
YOU DIDN'T LOOK AT IT
AND GO "OH, MY GOD,
THAT JUST REMINDS ME
SO MUCH OF RUPAUL."
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S MOVE ON TO
LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- WHAT SHE WAS GIVING
IS YOUR THIN BOD, YOU KNOW,
INTERGALACTIC LOOK.
YEAH, IT WASN'T ALL GOLD,
IT WAS PURPLE AND BLACK,
BUT I DIDN'T MIND HER LOOK,
TONIGHT, ON THE RUNWAY.
- FOR ME, HER RACHEL ZOE
WAS MORE WILLIAM SHATNER
THAN RACHEL ZOE.
- OOH, THAT'S HOT.
- RIGHT?
- I REALLY THINK THE NERVES
GOT THE BEST OF HER.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S MOVE ON DOWN
TO ADORE DELANO.
THAT ANNA NICOLE SMITH--
I WAS HYPNOTIZED.
I KNEW ANNA NICOLE SMITH,
AND SHE WAS REALLY
CHANNELING HER.
- BUT WHEN SHE CAME OUT,
SUPPOSEDLY BEING YOU,
I THOUGHT SHE WAS
KIND OF STILL DOING
A LITTLE BIT OF
ANNA NICOLE, LIKE--
- [LAUGHS]
- I THINK SHE REALLY
HAS BEEN ACTING
LIKE ANNA NICOLE HER WHOLE LIFE,
AND THEN I DIDN'T THINK
THE IMPRESSION WAS AS AMAZING
AS I THOUGHT IT WAS
THE OTHER DAY.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S MOVE ON
TO BENDELACREME.
- I THINK SHE WAS SUPERIOR
IN THE LOOK OF RU,
AND ALSO IN THE CHARACTER
OF MAGGIE SMITH.
- I WOULD AGREE.
HER COMEBACKS WERE SO FUNNY.
- BUT THE CON FOR ME WAS,
IT WAS ANOTHER OLD LADY.
- AH, THAT'S RIGHT,
THAT'S HER FORTE.
- NOT THAT IT WASN'T BRILLIANT,
BUT I FELT WE SAW IT ALREADY.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S MOVE ON DOWN
TO GIA GUNN.
- YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT
A HALLOWEEN COSTUME IN A BAG--
THAT WIG, AND THE
WONKY EYE WITH THE EYELASH.
- CRACK HO.
[LAUGHTER]
- AND COULDN'T HAVE PICKED
A WORSE CHARACTER
TO DO ON SNATCH GAME.
- YOU COULD DO KIM KARDASHIAN.
- IF YOU PLAYED IT UP.
- I CONCUR.
WHERE WERE THE BOOBIES,
WHERE WAS THE ASS?
SHE COULD HAVE STARTED
EVERY LETTER WITH A "K."
- THAT'S A BRILLIANT IDEA,
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN FUNNY.
- SHE JUST DIDN'T
REALLY GO FOR IT.
- ALL RIGHT.
NEXT UP, MILK!
- WELL, I COULD SEE THE WHEELS
TURNING EVERY MOMENT
OF THE JULIA CHILD.
- I THINK SHE MADE A REALLY
POOR CHOICE BEING BOY RU,
BECAUSE WE'RE HERE TO SEE
ALL DIFFERENT SIDES OF A QUEEN.
- BUT I SEE THIS CONFLICT
IN MILK
BETWEEN WANTING TO STAY TRUE
TO THIS GENDER-BENDING,
WHICH I RESPECT,
BUT I FEEL LIKE EVERY TIME
I'VE HEARD A DRAG QUEEN
ON THIS SHOW SAY,
"I NEED TO STAY TRUE
TO MY DRAG,"
THEY GO HOME
VERY SHORTLY THEREAFTER.
[LAUGHTER]
- SILENCE.
I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
BRING BACK MY GIRLS.
- [LAUGHS]
- WELCOME BACK, LADIES.
I'VE MADE SOME DECISIONS.
- TONIGHT,
IT'S THE PRIME
OF MISS BENDELACREME.
CONDRAGULATIONS, YOU ARE
THE WINNER OF THIS CHALLENGE.
- THANK YOU SO, SO MUCH.
- YOU'VE WON TWO COUTURE OUTFITS
FROM SYREN LATEX,
A LEADER IN LATEX FASHION.
- I'M THE FIRST ONE
TO WIN TWO CHALLENGES,
AND THIS IS THE CHALLENGE
THAT I WAS MOST TERRIFIED ABOUT,
AND I WON IT!
- BIANCA DEL RIO, YOU'RE SAFE.
ADORE, YOU'RE SAFE.
MILK,
YOUR JULIA CHILD IMPERSONATION
WAS HALF-BAKED.
GIA GUNN, AS KIM KARDASHIAN,
YOU FELL FLAT ON YOUR ASS.
LAGANJA ESTRANJA,
YOUR RACHEL ZOE
WAS SO FASHION WEAK,
LITERALLY.
MILK, YOU ARE SAFE.
- THIS IS SOME BULLSHIT.
MILK BELONGS IN THE BOTTOM.
- BUT JUST BY THE SEAT
OF MY PANTS.
GIA AND LAGANJA,
I'M SORRY, MY DEARS,
BUT YOU ARE UP FOR ELIMINATION.
TWO QUEENS STAND BEFORE ME.
LADIES, THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO IMPRESS ME,
AND SAVE YOURSELF
FROM ELIMINATION.
THE TIME HAS COME
FOR YOU TO LIP-SYNC
FOR YOUR LIFE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M IN THE BOTTOM TWO,
AND I'M UP AGAINST
ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS
IN THIS COMPETITION,
AND THAT REALLY SUCKS.
- GOOD LUCK,
AND DON'T FUCK IT UP.
- ♪ HEAD TO TOE ♪
♪ I KNOW ♪
♪ TODAY STARTED
WITH A CRAZY KISS ♪
♪ ON OUR WAY HOME ♪
- GIRL, I'M GIVING IT
EVERYTHING I'VE GOT.
TOE-TOUCHING, THE SPLITS,
DEATH DROPS RIGHT OFF THE BAT--
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME.
- I'M SHOWING THE JUDGES
THAT I LOVE TO PERFORM,
THAT I LOVE TO VOGUE,
AND I'M GIVING FACE,
AND THAT'S USUALLY WHAT COUNTS.
- ♪ 14 KARAT LOVE
YOU ARE MY JEWEL OF THE NILE ♪
♪ WHEN WE MAKE LOVE
DIAMONDS ARE FOREVER ♪
♪ TOP TO BOTTOM
I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ I WILL LEAVE YOU NEVER ♪
♪ I GOT TO, GOT TO TELL YOU ♪
- RULE NUMBER ONE--
YOU'RE GOING TO DO
A REVEAL,
GET OUT OF THE DRESS.
WE ALL KNOW "REVEAL"
IN FRENCH
MEANS TAKE THE SHIT OFF.
- ♪ BUT MY ANGEL ♪
♪ YOU FORGET
YOUR WINGS TONIGHT ♪
♪ HEAVEN UP ABOVE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU GOT THE LIGHT ♪
- THE JUMP SPLIT
IS PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
I CAN SEE THE DIFFERENCE
IN THEIR STYLES.
GIA IS A LOT MORE CONTROLLED.
LAGANJA IS GIVING EVERYTHING.
[APPLAUSE]
- LADIES,
I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
LAGANJA ESTRANJA,
SHANTE, YOU STAY.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- YOU MAY JOIN THE OTHER GIRLS.
- G-G-G-GIA,
MY PET, MAKE NO MISTAKE,
I LOVE YOU FROM HEAD TO TOE.
NOW, SASHAY AWAY.
[APPLAUSE]
- YOU GUYS ARE ALL STILL DUDES.
I'M UPSET THAT THERE'S OTHER
CROSSDRESSERS STILL IN THERE
THAT FUCKING CAME TO A DRAG SHOW
DRESSED AS BOYS.
I MEAN, IF YOU LOOK UP "DRAG,"
DRAG MEANS DRESSING UP AS GIRLS,
NOT RE-ENHANCING
WHAT YOU ALREADY ARE,
WHICH IS A FUCKING BIG MAN.
- MY 9 LADIES PRANCING.
REMEMBER,
IF YOU CAN'T LOVE YOURSELF,
HOW THE HELL
YOU GONNA LOVE SOMEBODY ELSE?
CAN I GET A "AMEN" IN HERE?
- AMEN.
- NOW, LET THE MUSIC PLAY.
♪ I WANNA DANCE, DANCE
I WANNA DANCE, DANCE ♪
♪ I WANNA DANCE, DANCE ♪
♪ DANCE WITH YOU ♪