- WE'RE COMING AT YOU
FROM THE THEATER AT ACE HOTEL
IN GORGEOUS DOWNTOWN
LOS ANGELES.
IT'S THE BIGGEST NIGHT
OF THE YEAR,
IT'S "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED."
- LET'S GET "SIX-ENING," OKAY?
- OH, SCRUFF PIT CREW!
- HIEEEE.
- WHO WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE
WIN SEASON 6?
- BIANCA, BECAUSE
THE BITCH IS BADASS.
- ADORE, BECAUSE SHE'S
MY HOMETOWN CHOLA.
- AZUSA REPRESENTING.
- COURTNEY ACT, FISH, FEM,
DRAG CALIBER AESTHETIC,
LIVE, LOVE.
- THAT'S THE "T"
FROM THE RED CARPET.
IT'S TIME TO GO
INSIDE THE THEATER
FOR "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED."
- ♪ TAKE ME UP ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH ♪
- WE'RE READY FOR YOU
ONSTAGE, RUPAUL.
- I'LL BE RIGHT THERE, DARLING.
[ENGINE STARTS]
- ♪ RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ GENTLEMEN
START YOUR ENGINES ♪
♪ RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
♪ RU-RU-RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ GENTLEMEN
START YOUR ENGINES ♪
♪ RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ MAY THE BEST WOMAN
BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- LADIES, GENTLEMEN,
ALL HAIL THE QUEENS OF SEASON 6.
- ♪ PICK MYSELF UP
TURN THE WORLD ON ITS HEAD ♪
♪ DON'T FORGET WHAT
DON'T FORGET WHAT MY MAMA SAID ♪
♪ PEOPLE TALKING
SINCE THE BEGINNING OF TIME ♪
♪ UNLESS THEY'RE
PAYING YOUR BILLS ♪
♪ PAY THEM BITCHES NO MIND ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ AT LEAST I CAN SAY
I GAVE IT ALL ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ I'M ON MY WAY ♪
♪ FLY, FLY, FLY, FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH, UH-OH ♪
♪ UH-OH
NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- THE CAROL BURNETT OF DRAG,
KELLY MANTLE.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ AT LEAST I CAN SAY
I GAVE IT ALL ♪
- SERVING TRASH WITH PANACHE,
MAGNOLIA CRAWFORD.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ FLY, FLY, FLY, FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH, UH-OH ♪
- MOTHER HAS ARRIVED.
VIVACIOUS.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ FLY, FLY, FLY, FLY
UH-OH, UH-OH ♪
♪ FLY, FLY, FLY, FLY ♪
- REPORTING FOR BEAUTY DUTY,
APRIL CARRION.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- G-G-G-GIA GUNN.
- ♪ AND IF I FLY OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ AT LEAST I CAN SAY
I GAVE IT ALL ♪
- WHO WANTS
A TALL GLASS OF MILK?
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ I'M ON MY WAY ♪
♪ FLY, FLY, FLY, FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH, UH-OH ♪
- COME ON, SEASON 6.
IT'S LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ FLY, FLY, FLY, FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH
NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
- FROM THE A.T.L., IT'S T.K.B.,
MISS TRINITY K. BONET.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- SHE KEEPS IT FOXY.
JOSLYN FOX.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ AT LEAST I CAN SAY
I GAVE IT ALL ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY OR IF I FALL... ♪
- RISING TO THE TOP,
IT'S BENDELACREME.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ UH-OH, UH-OH ♪
♪ FLY, FLY, FLY, FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH, UH-OH ♪
- DIP INTO THE COOL WATERS
OF DARIENNE LAKE.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- AND NOW, OUR TOP 3 QUEENS.
- COMING STRAIGHT OUT OF AZUSA,
ADORE DELANO.
- ♪ AND IF I FLY OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ AT LEAST I CAN SAY
I GAVE IT ALL ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY OR IF I FALL... ♪
- BLAME IT ON BIANCA DEL RIO.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ UH-OH, UH-OH ♪
♪ FLY, FLY, FLY, FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH, UH-OH ♪
- AND THE WONDER
FROM DOWN UNDER,
COURTNEY ACT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ UH-OH
NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ AT LEAST I CAN SAY
I GAVE IT ALL ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ I'M ON MY WAY ♪
♪ UH-OH
NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
[DRUM ROLL]
- LADIES, GENTLEMEN,
AND ALL 54 FACEBOOK GENDER
OPTIONS IN BETWEEN,
PLEASE WELCOME
THE ONE, THE ONLY,
RUPAUL!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ DON'T GIVE ME YOUR LOVE
I DON'T WANT IT ♪
♪ DON'T GIVE ME YOUR LOVE
I WANT YOUR ♪
I DON'T WANT IT ♪
♪ DON'T GIVE ME YOUR LOVE
I WANT YOUR ♪
I DON'T WANT IT ♪
♪ DON'T GIVE ME YOUR LOVE
I WANT YOUR ♪
♪ MONEY, MONEY
MONEY, MONEY, MONEY... ♪
♪ ALL UP IN THE CLUB
I'M MAKING ♪
♪ MONEY, MONEY, MONEY, MONEY ♪
♪ WALKING DOWN THE STREET
I'M MAKING ♪
♪ MONEY, MONEY, MONEY
MONEY, MONEY... ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
WELCOME TO "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED."
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
NOW, THAT WAS
THE MOST EXPENSIVE OPENING
IN DRAG RACE "HERSTORY."
[LAUGHTER]
LITERALLY.
- WHOO!
- TO MAKE IT RAIN LIKE THAT,
WE HAD TO DIP INTO
THE PRIZE MONEY, OKAY? SO...
[LAUGHS]
BUT LADIES, WE DON'T JUST DO IT
FOR THE MONEY, DO WE?
WE DO IT BECAUSE WE LOVE IT.
SO, STARTING IN THIS BIG,
BEAUTIFUL THEATER,
LET'S SEND THE MESSAGE OF LOVE
TO EVERYBODY WATCHING
AROUND THE WORLD.
EVERYBODY SAY, "LOVE."
- LOVE!
- EVERYBODY SAY, "LOVE."
- NOW TWEET THAT HASHTAG
AROUND THE UNIVERSE.
GET YOUR ASS OUT OF HERE.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
[LAUGHS]
ADORE, BIANCA, AND COURTNEY.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
YES.
THANKS TO YOU
AND ALL THE GIRLS,
YOU'VE MADE THIS
THE MOST TWEETED,
MOST TUMBLR-ED...
[LAUGHTER]
AND TALKED-ABOUT SEASON EVER.
IT'S TRUE, IT IS.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
AND TO ALL THE DRAG RACE ROYALTY
IN THE AUDIENCE
AND AROUND THE COUNTRY,
I SALUTE YOU.
HEY, PORK CHOP!
HEY, GIRL!
NOW, ARE YOU ALL READY
FOR THIS REUNION TO SET ON FIRE?
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
GOOD,
BECAUSE I HAVE ONE THING TO SAY.
GENTLEMEN, START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN...
WAIT. WAIT, WAIT A MINUTE,
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS THE OSCARS OF DRAG,
SO BEFORE WE START,
I WANT TO TAKE A SELFIE.
OKAY? ALL RIGHT?
SO, GIRLS,
GATHER AROUND, GIRLS.
COME ON, GATHER AROUND.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
ALL RIGHT, SO...
WHO HAS THE LONGEST ARMS?
MILK? MILK...
OKAY, SO LET'S DO THIS THING.
YOU HAVE THE CAMERA?
GIVE US A "1, 2, 3,"
GIVE US A "1, 2, 3."
READY?
1, 2, 3.
GREAT.
[LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
NOW, MILK, BEFORE YOU POST THIS
TO MY TWITTER ACCOUNT, @RUPAUL,
MAKE SURE YOU PUT ON
THAT SEASON ONE FILTER.
YOU KNOW THE ONE?
[LAUGHTER]
YOU KNOW, WHERE I'M ALL
BLURRY AND SHIT?
YES, YES.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL TOGETHER NOW.
GENTLEMEN...
- START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN!
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ LET THAT BE THE REASON ♪
- COMING UP, OUR QUEENS
READ THIS SEASON FOR FILTH,
AND THE TOP 3
GET CROSS-EXAMINED, OOH,
AS WE PREPARE TO CROWN
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
DON'T GO AWAY,
"RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE REUNITED"
IS ABOUT TO POP OFF.
- ♪ NO, I'M NOT NO COMMON HO ♪
♪ SLIP SLIDING DOWN
A RABBIT HOLE, WHAT? ♪
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
WELCOME BACK TO
"RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE REUNITED."
YOU KNOW, I'VE JUST
BEEN INFORMED
THAT OUR SELFIE HAS BEEN
RETWEETED SO MANY TIMES,
IT DIDN'T JUST BREAK TWITTER,
IT TURNED IT GAY.
[LAUGHTER]
SORRY ABOUT IT.
[LAUGHS]
TONIGHT, ALL THE QUEENS ARE BACK
TO HELP ME CROWN
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
FIRST UP,
TWO DRAG DAUGHTERS
THAT POPPED OUT
OF MY TWO BIG OPENINGS.
[LAUGHTER]
A FUNNY QUEEN WHO COULD
BRING HOME THE BACON
BUT COULDN'T QUITE
FRY IT UP IN A PAN,
AND A QUIRKY QUEEN
WITH A NOSE FOR TROUBLE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
- YOU ALL READY
TO ROCK AND ROLL?
WHOO!
I AM AN ACTOR.
I'VE BEEN ON A BUNCH
OF TELEVISION SHOWS.
I HAVE BEEN IN DRAG
FOR 17 YEARS.
- IS THAT BACON ON YOUR CHEST?
- [LAUGHS]
- THEY'RE FLOWER PETALS.
- I'M STILL GETTING BACON.
- SASHAY AWAY.
- DON'T WEAR BACON.
DON'T WEAR BACON.
- MAGNOLIA CRAWFORD.
- I VIEW MYSELF AS THE WORLD'S
MOST GLAMOROUS TRASH QUEEN.
THAT'S UGLY.
AWFUL.
I GOT A BUNCH OF SHIT.
- MY EYES HONED RIGHT IN
ON THAT NOSE CONTOUR.
IT IS SO DARK, GIRL.
- I'M NOT CHANGING THIS NOSE
FOR NO MOTHERFUCKING
MICHELLE "V-I-SAGE."
[LAUGHTER]
- KELLY MANTLE
AND MAGNOLIA CRAWFORD!
SO, KELLY, FANS PREDICTED THAT
YOU WOULD BE A FRONT-RUNNER,
BUT YOU ENDED UP
BEING THE FIRST TO LEAVE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
- WELL, I CAN'T SEW,
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
[LAUGHS]
- WELL, THAT'S A BIG ONE.
I MEAN, BUT YOU KNEW THAT IT WAS
GOING BE A SEWING COMPETITION.
- I KNOW, AND I KNOW
THAT I TOLD YOU
I TOOK COSTUME CONSTRUCTION
IN COLLEGE,
BUT I FAILED TO MENTION
I MADE AN "F."
[LAUGHS]
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- SO WHAT SURPRISED YOU
THE MOST?
- YOU KNOW,
WHAT SURPRISED ME THE MOST
WAS THAT THE JUDGES
WEREN'T HUNGRY FOR MY BACON.
[LAUGHTER]
- I MEAN, WHAT, IS EVERYONE
A VEGAN NOWADAYS IN L.A.?
JEEZ.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- NOW, MAGNOLIA CRAWFORD.
NOW, A LOT OF PEOPLE
THREW YOU SHADE
ABOUT YOUR NOSE CONTOURING.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE
TO SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT.
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
I WAS A LITTLE TAKEN ABACK
THAT MY NOSE
WAS SO CONTROVERSIAL.
I GUESS, AT THE END OF THE DAY,
I NOW CAN CALL MYSELF
"MAG-NOSE-LIA."
[LAUGHTER]
SO, THERE YOU GO.
- SO, MAGNOLIA,
WHICH OF THE CHALLENGES
WOULD YOU HAVE KILLED?
- WELL, I ACTUALLY...
I DID NOT WATCH THIS SEASON.
- EX-SQUEEZE-ME?
[LAUGHTER]
- NOW, HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
IN MY DEFENSE, IN MY MIND,
I HAD A VERY GOOD EXPERIENCE,
AND DESPITE THE WAY
ANYTHING CAME ACROSS,
I HAD A FANTASTIC TIME,
AND I JUST WANTED TO REMEMBER IT
AS MY EXPERIENCE.
- HUH.
- YOU KNOW, IT WAS VERY SPECIAL
TO ME, AND I WANTED
TO REMEMBER THAT.
- THAT...I AM NOT BUYING THAT.
YOU DIDN'T WATCH...
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- YOU CAN READ ME LIKE A BOOK.
[LAUGHS]
- I'M JUST NOT--
KELLY, I MEAN, COME ON,
TALK TO HER,
BECAUSE I AM OVER IT,
OFFICIALLY, OKAY?
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
- OFFICIALLY.
HONEY, LISTEN,
I HAVE ALL THE EPISODES
ON MY DVR, OKAY?
SO YOU COME OVER
SOME MORNING...
- WELL, AREN'T THEY ONLINE?
- WE'LL BRING PORK CHOP,
I'LL BRING THE BACON.
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- THANK YOU, LADIES.
NEXT UP, THE MOTHER
OF ALL CLUB KIDS,
AND A STUNNING QUEEN
WHO MADE IT RAIN ON THE RUNWAY.
- MOTHER HAS ARRIVED.
MY LOOK IS LEIGH BOWERY
ABSTRACT ENTITY.
VIVACIOUS IS LIVING ART.
- DO YOU HAVE A NAME FOR
THE HEAD ON TOP OF YOUR HEAD?
- ORNACIA.
- ORNACIA, OKAY.
- I CAN ALWAYS TELL WHEN
A NEW YORKER WALKS THE RUNWAY.
- OKAY?
- YES, HONEY.
- REPORTING FOR DUTY.
APRIL CARRION IS IN THE HOUSE.
- YEAH!
- APRIL IS A CROSS BETWEEN
BJORK AND COCO ROCHA.
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING WEIRD,
BUT SOMETHING GLAMOROUS.
- I THINK SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
THE FACE, THE BODY.
- I CAN SEE ADAM LAMBERT
WATCHING THESE THIGHS.
HE WANTS SOME CHICKEN LEG.
- YOU ARE GORGEOUS!
- YOU'RE GORGEOUS AS WELL.
- AW, THANK YOU.
- GET A ROOM.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- VIVACIOUS, FIRST OF ALL,
HOW IS ORNACIA?
- YOU KNOW, ORNACIA, SHE SWEARS
SHE'S HER OWN PERSON NOW,
AND MISS THING
HAD THE NERVE THE OTHER DAY
TO SEND ME A WRIT
OF EMANCIPATION.
[LAUGHTER]
- NOW, YOU WERE HERE
REPRESENTING THE CLUB CULTURE,
AND YOUR WALK WAS EVERYTHING.
- YES, MAMA.
- YES.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- YOU KNOW, OLD SCHOOL WAY
IS THE OLD SCHOOL WAY, HONEY.
WE'RE GOING TO WALK AND GIVE YOU
HIPS FOR YOUR NERVE.
WE'RE GOING TO SISSY IT,
AND "SHASSAY" AND SHANTAY HER
RIGHT DOWN THE RUNWAY, HONEY.
- ALL RIGHT, APRIL CARRION.
NOW, YOU'VE BEEN TWEETING
OUTFITS YOU WOULD HAVE WORN
HAD YOU STAYED ON THE SHOW.
- YES.
- AND THEY LOOK AMAZING.
- WELL, THIS IS
MY SNATCH GAME.
I WAS GOING TO DO
KIM KARDASHIAN IN THE MET GALA.
SHE WAS PREGNANT.
[LAUGHTER]
- OH, NICE, NICE.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- THIS IS
MY BLACK AND WHITE LOOK.
IT'S INSPIRED BY "BEETLEJUICE."
I BET MICHELLE WILL CLOCK ME
WITH MY HAIR, BUT WHATEVER.
- OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
- RIGHT?
BECAUSE IT'S CUTE, RIGHT?
IT'S FUN, IT'S FUN.
- YEAH. OH!
UH-OH, UH-OH, UH-OH,
WAIT A MINUTE.
HOLD UP, NOW,
BITCH STOLE MY LOOK.
[LAUGHTER]
- YES.
THIS IS MY RU LOOK,
AND I LOVE IT.
IT'S LIKE A CLASSIC RU LOOK.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK OF YOU.
- I LOVE IT.
SO, OVERALL, IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU WOULD HAVE DONE DIFFERENTLY
IN THE COMPETITION?
- NO, LIKE, FOR REAL,
I'M REALLY HAPPY
WITH THE OUTCOME,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW WHAT? I WASN'T
MEANT TO WIN THIS SEASON.
I'M MEANT TO WIN ALL STARS 2.
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ONE LAST THING,
AS WE GO TO BREAK.
VIVACIOUS, WILL YOU TEACH THESE
CHILDREN HOW TO WALK THAT WALK?
- YES, HONEY,
IT WOULD BE A PLEASURE.
- ALL RIGHT, GO ON,
LET'S SEE IT.
[DANCE MUSIC]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- BACKSTAGE,
IN THE OVERSTOCK.COM RED ROOM,
OUR TOP 3 NERVOUSLY WAIT
TO FIND OUT
WHO WILL BE CROWNED
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
- ♪ GIVE ME ONE SHOT
ONE SHOT ♪
♪ OF ADRENALINE ♪
- COMING UP,
GIA GUNN FIRES OFF,
MILK SPILLS THE "T,"
AND MUCH MORE, AS "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED" CONTINUES.
[CHEERING]
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED."
WE ARE JUST MOMENTS AWAY
FROM FINDING OUT
WHO WILL BE CROWNED AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
BUT FIRST, IT'S TIME
TO RECONNECT WITH TWO QUEENS
WHO LEFT US GAGGING
WHEN THEY SASHAYED AWAY.
TAKE A LOOK.
- MY NAME IS GIA GUNN.
GIA IS A FISHY GIRL.
SHE IS C.C.C.,
CRAZY CUCKOO CUNT.
I'M FEELING MY OATS,
LET ME FEEL MY OATS.
- I COULD TELL
THAT YOU'RE THE FEISTY ONE.
- ABSOLUTELY.
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ FEELING LIKE PUSSY
FEELING LIKE CUNT ♪
- I'M MILK.
I'M 25 YEARS OLD.
MILK IS A VERY CONCEPTUAL
PERFORMER.
I KNOW I'M NOT GOING TO FIT IN
WITH THOSE GLAMOROUS QUEENS,
AND SO WHY NOT STAND OUT?
- BITCH, ANYBODY
THAT COMES DOWN THE RUNWAY
LOOKING LIKE THAT,
I WANT TO GET INTO YOUR BRAIN.
SO, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- G-G-G-GIA.
ARE YOU HAPPY TO BE HERE?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- [LAUGHS]
NOW, GIA, I LOVE
YOUR SENSE OF HUMOR,
BUT SOME PEOPLE
TOOK YOU VERY SERIOUSLY.
- YOU KNOW WHAT, I DO UNDERSTAND
THAT MAYBE SOME THINGS
COULD HAVE BEEN TAKEN
A LITTLE BIT THE WRONG WAY.
I JUST FELT LIKE I WAS TELLING
THE TRUTH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
[LAUGHTER]
SINCE THEN, YOU HAVE ALLOWED ME
TO EXPAND MY HORIZON
AND BE ABLE TO VALIDATE QUEENS
LIKE MILK, JUST LIKE MYSELF.
[APPLAUSE]
- I LOVE IT.
NOW, WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE
PEOPLE TO KNOW ABOUT GIA GUNN
THAT THEY DON'T?
- YOU KNOW WHAT, HONESTLY?
THAT I'M REALLY JUST A HUMBLE,
REALLY NICE ASIAN GIRL
THAT JUST...
[LAUGHTER]
IS HERE JUST
TO TURN THE PARTY, SO...
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- SO, MILK,
HOW HAS YOUR LIFE CHANGED?
- WHEN I WAS KICKED OFF
THE SHOW, I...
THANKS A LOT.
- [LAUGHS]
YOU WEREN'T KICKED OFF THE SHOW!
[LAUGHTER]
- YOU BOOTED ME IN THE BUTT.
- BUT YOU ENJOYED IT,
DIDN'T YOU?
- I SURE DID.
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- I'VE QUIT MY BOY JOB,
AND AT THE END OF MAY
I AM GOING TO LIFE BALL,
A HUGE AIDS BENEFIT,
AND I'M SO EXCITED.
IT'S JUST A PARTY.
- THAT'S LOVELY.
AND YOU GOT A LOT OF ATTENTION
AS A BOY ON THE SHOW.
- HMM?
- WERE YOU SURPRISED BY THAT?
- REALLY? WHAT? REALLY?
- WHOO! WHOO!
- WELL, I GUESS I NEVER REALIZED
HOW HORNY "DRAG RACE" FANS ARE.
[LAUGHTER]
WELL, LIKE, BOTH MEN AND WOMEN
ALIKE TELL ME HOW HOT I AM
AND HOW MUCH THEY WANT
TO SLEEP WITH ME.
- RIGHT, RIGHT.
OH, SO IS THAT
HOW YOU QUIT YOUR JOB,
BECAUSE YOU'RE MAKING
ALL THESE COINS...
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
NEXT UP,
A QUEEN THAT CAME UNCORKED,
AND ANOTHER WHO HAD
A SECRET STASH OF DRAMA, MAMA.
- COME ON, SEASON 6,
LET'S GET SICKENING!
LAGANJA IS KNOWN FOR HER WILD
AND AMAZING DANCE ABILITIES.
COME ON, NATCH!
- YOU DO THIS "OKAY, OKAY."
- I DO TALK LIKE THAT,
AND I'M SORRY YOU--
- NO, NO, YOU TALK LIKE THIS!
THIS IS HOW YOU TALK!
- I AM TRINITY K. BONET.
- GORGEOUS.
- I'M ABOUT AS CLOSE AS
YOU'RE GOING TO GET TO BEYONCE.
NOW, IF I FUCK UP, IT'S BECAUSE
THIS IS NOT MY FORTE.
- I KNOW THAT THERE'S A BLOCK
THERE FOR YOU TO UNLOCK.
- STOP RUNNING
AROUND MY HOUSE LIKE THAT,
YOU'RE GOING TO RUN
MY LIGHT BILL UP.
[LAUGHTER]
- YOU HAVE OVERCOME
YOUR SABOTEUR,
AND I'M SO PROUD TO SEE IT.
I'M SO PROUD TO SEE IT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- LAGANJA ESTRANJA,
HOW ARE YOU, MAMA?
- WELL, MAMA,
I'M DOING VERY GOOD.
- OKAY.
- WELL, YOU WERE CALLED OUT
BY THE JUDGES
AND THE OTHER GIRLS
FOR BEING FAKE.
DO YOU AGREE WITH THAT?
- WELL, NO, GIRL,
I HONESTLY JUST THINK
YOU ALL WERE BORING, AND I WAS
TRYING TO TURN THE PARTY.
YES, GONE!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- NOW, DID YOU FEEL ANY PRESSURE
TO LIVE UP TO YOUR DRAG MOTHER,
ALYSSA EDWARDS?
- WELL, YES.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
OF COURSE I FELT PRESSURE.
BUT I'M SO THANKFUL THAT I HAVE
SUCH A BEAUTIFUL PERSON
AND SOMEONE SO LOVING
TO MENTOR ME,
AND I REALLY LOVE YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
- SO, WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING
SINCE THE SHOW?
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
I HIT THE GROUND RUNNING
THE MINUTE I GOT ELIMINATED.
I GOT A SONG OUT, A MUSIC VIDEO,
A JEWELRY LINE, A MAKEUP LINE,
AND I'M ABOUT TO GO TO BRAZIL
FOR THE WORLD CUP, BABY.
- BUT, LAGANJA,
YOU'RE LEAVING SOMETHING OUT.
MY GUESS IS THAT YOU STOPPED BY
THAT WEED DEALER FIRST.
- OH, HONEY, YOU WONDER
WHY I'M CALM TONIGHT?
SHE'S MEDICATED.
AAH...
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- LEGALLY, YES.
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THANK YOU, LAGANJA.
- THANK YOU, MAMA RU.
- NOW, TRINITY K. BONET.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
YES.
YOUR TRANSFORMATION MADE ME CRY,
WHICH IS REALLY HARD TO DO,
GIVEN THE AMOUNT OF BOTOX
I HAVE IN MY FACE.
[LAUGHTER]
EARLY IN THE COMPETITION,
YOU WERE SHUT DOWN.
WHAT CHANGED FOR YOU?
- IN PARTICULAR, BIANCA.
WHEN WE DID THE COMMERCIAL,
IT WAS SOMETHING
ABOUT HER ENERGY
SITTING AT THAT TABLE, WRITING.
I NEVER GOT THAT CLOSE TO HER
IN THE COMPETITION,
AND THEN IT WAS LIKE,
"PIECE OF CAKE, LET'S DO THIS."
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- NOW, WHAT PART OF THE SHOW
WERE YOU THE MOST PROUD OF?
- BEING BRAVE,
AND TELLING MY STORY,
AND BEING ABLE TO BE
A VOICE FOR PEOPLE
WHO DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE THEY HAD A VOICE.
I CAN BE WHO THE HELL
I WANT TO BE,
AND NOBODY CAN QUESTION ME
FOR IT, BECAUSE THIS IS MY LIFE.
- RIGHT, RIGHT, I LOVE IT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- NOW, I KNOW YOUR DREAM
IS TO BECOME A BEYONCE
IMPERSONATOR, TRINITY,
BUT I THINK YOU SHOULD
JUST KEEP ON BEING YOU,
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU, TRINITY.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
NOW, FROM BEARDED LADIES
TO MERMAIDS,
FROM CLUB KIDS
TO PAGEANT QUEENS,
THIS SEASON,
THE DIFFERENT STYLES OF DRAG
RAISED A LOT OF QUESTIONS.
SO WE PUT TOGETHER A LITTLE
"HERSTORY" LESSON.
LEARN IT AND LEARN IT WELL.
WHAT IS DRAG?
DRAG IS UNDERGROUND
AND OVER-THE-TOP.
DRAG IS POLITICAL
AND POLITICALLY INCORRECT.
DRAG IS CAMP
AND COUTURE.
DRAG IS PUNK
AND MAINSTREAM.
DRAG IS A LAUGH RIOT,
AND IT COULD START A REVOLUTION.
DRAG IS NEVER HAVING TO SAY
YOU'RE SORRY,
BECAUSE DRAG IS ALL ABOUT BEING
WHOEVER THE HELL YOU WANT TO BE.
- ♪ WE CAN FLY TONIGHT ♪
♪ WE FLY TONIGHT
WE FLY TONIGHT ♪
- AND DRAG BRINGS
PEOPLE TOGETHER.
NOW, REACH OUT
AND TOUCH A DRAG QUEEN'S HAND.
MAKE THIS WORLD
A BETTER PLACE IF YOU CAN.
- ♪ TIME TO TAKE A STAND
AND COME TOGETHER ♪
♪ LET'S COME TOGETHER ♪
♪ BECAUSE WE ARE
EACH OTHER'S FAMILY ♪
♪ ALL 2,603,040 SISTERS ♪
♪ THIS IS OUR LAND
THIS IS OUR LAND ♪
♪ AND WE ARE THE QUEENS ♪
- AND THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING OF ALL,
DRAG NEVER, EVER
TAKES ITSELF TOO SERIOUSLY.
- ♪ BACK ROLLS! ♪
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- [LAUGHS]
- BACKSTAGE,
IN THE OVERSTOCK.COM RED ROOM,
OUR TOP 3 QUEENS
ARE FEELING THE DRAG UNITY.
- AW.
- COMING UP, WE'LL KEEP IT FOXY.
BENDELACREME AND DARIENNE LAKE
BREAK IT DOWN,
AND OUR QUEENS
ANSWER FAN QUESTIONS,
AS "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE REUNITED"
KEEPS ON KEEPING ON.
- ♪ I WANT TO DANCE, DANCE
DANCE WITH YOU ♪
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- WELCOME BACK
TO THE THEATER AT ACE HOTEL
AND "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE
REUNITED."
NOW, THESE NEXT 3 QUEENS
MAY NOT HAVE TAKEN HOME
THE CROWN,
BUT THEY SURE SNATCHED
PLENTY OF ATTENTION.
THE FIRST ARRIVED WITH OPTIMISM,
A WINNING SPIRIT,
AND ONE HOT BODY-ODY-ODY.
- WHOO!
- JOSLYN FOX IS ALL ABOUT
THE LOOK AND SHOWING BODY.
JOSLYN FOX IS ONE FOXY LADY.
WA-WA.
- BAM!
- WHAT?
- THAT ASS IS SO PERFECT.
- WELL, HONEY, JUST BECAUSE
NOBODY IS INTERESTED
IN YOUR STYLE,
BECAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE IT CAME
FROM THE FUCKING
QUINCEANERA STORE.
- LIKE, I KNOW
I'VE OVER-ACCESSORIZED.
THEY CAN LOVE IT OR SHOVE IT.
- HEY, MY LOVE,
IT'S YOUR FIANCE.
- OH, MY GOD!
- YOU'RE MY ROCK,
AND I SUPPORT YOU 100%.
YOU KNOW I LOVE YOUR GUTS.
- AW.
- I PLAN ON BEING THE BLACK
HORSE IN THIS COMPETITION.
- [SPEAKING ENGLISH]
- OH, IT IS DARK HORSE,
ISN'T IT?
- HELLO, JOSLYN FOX.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- HI, RU, HOW ARE YOU?
[LAUGHS]
- SO, I WANT TO KNOW
HOW YOUR FAMILY REACTED
TO YOU SHOWING ALL THAT ASS.
- OOH, I THINK
THEY'RE USED TO IT.
[LAUGHTER]
- THEY'VE SEEN IT BEFORE,
IT WAS NOTHING NEW.
[LAUGHS]
- HAS THE JUDGES' CRITIQUES
CHANGED YOUR DRAG?
- VERY MUCH SO.
I WEAR MORE ACCESSORIES.
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
SO, WHAT ADVICE
DO YOU HAVE FOR QUEENS
WHO HAVE AUDITIONED
YEAR AFTER YEAR, LIKE YOU DID?
- YOU KNOW, THIS WAS
MY FOURTH TIME AUDITIONING,
AND I THINK THE FIRST FEW TIMES
I WAS MAKING A STRONG EFFORT
TO GIVE YOU
WHAT I THOUGHT YOU WANTED,
AND IT WASN'T UNTIL THIS
AUDITION THAT I JUST SAID,
"YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST GOING TO BE ME."
SO MY ADVICE IS TO ALWAYS
STAY TRUE TO WHO YOU ARE,
BECAUSE THAT'S WHEN YOUR SHINING
PERSONALITY WILL COME THROUGH.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
AND WHEN ALL ELSE FAILS,
KEEP IT FOXY.
WA-WA.
[LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- WELL, WA-WA.
THANK YOU, JOSLYN.
[LAUGHS]
- THANK YOU, RU-ZIE-Q.
- UP NEXT, A BURLESQUE BABE
AND A GORGEOUS GAL
WITH PLUS-SIZED TALENTS.
LET'S WATCH.
- BENDELACREME IS EFFERVESCENT
AND OPTIMISTIC.
I REFER TO HER
AS "TERMINALLY DELIGHTFUL."
OOH!
- BENDELACREME VISAGE.
- BITCH STOLE YOUR LOOK!
- [LAUGHS]
I FEEL LIKE EVERY TIME, WE'RE
HIDING BEHIND ANOTHER COSTUME.
- I UNDERSTOOD VIRTUALLY
NONE OF THE WORDS
THAT LEFT YOUR LIPS MOMENTS AGO.
- [LAUGHS]
- I REALLY FEEL
SOME PSYCHIC ENERGY
BETWEEN DELA AND DARIENNE.
- YOU REMIND ME
OF A RUSSIAN DOLL.
FULL OF YOURSELF.
[LAUGHTER]
- SO, DARIENNE,
HOW DO YOU CHOOSE YOUR GROUP?
- IT'S NONE
OF YOUR FUCKING BUSINESS.
[ALL GASP]
- DIP INTO THE WATERS
OF DARIENNE LAKE.
- I WAS PICKED FAN FAVORITE
ON THE ONLINE FACEBOOK CONTEST.
- SHE'S A FIERCE LIP-SYNCER,
ALL ABOUT SELLING FACE.
- YOUR MOTHER
DARNS SOCKS IN HELL! HA HA!
- YOU WERE THROWN OUT OF
THE HOUSE AS A KID, WEREN'T YOU?
- IT WAS MORE LIKE
AN INVITATION TO LEAVE.
THERE WAS A LOT OF YEARS
OF NOT LOVING MYSELF.
- HMM.
- AND I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT,
"WELL, IF YOU CAN'T
LOVE YOURSELF,
FEEL FREE TO HATE
AS MANY PEOPLE AS YOU WANT TO."
- [LAUGHS]
- YOU KNOW?
[CHUCKLES]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- WELCOME, DELA.
NOW, DELA,
WHEN YOU SASHAYED AWAY,
PEOPLE FREAKED THE FUCK OUT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- I THOUGHT IT WAS KIND OF
WEIRD, TOO, NO OFFENSE, AND...
[LAUGHTER]
NOW, HOW HAVE FANS REACTED
TO DELA'S PERPETUALLY
PERKY ATTITUDE?
- IT'S BEEN AMAZING.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN PUTTING
THIS KIND OF POSITIVITY
INTO THE WORLD,
THAT'S, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE A LITTLE
OVER-THE-TOP AT TIMES.
AND WHAT'S HAPPENED
IS THAT I'VE HAD
SO MANY AMAZING CONVERSATIONS
WITH PEOPLE WHO HAVE FED
THAT ENERGY BACK TO ME,
AND SAID THAT IT SOMEHOW
HELPS TO LIFT THEM UP,
AND IT'S MADE BEN
A HAPPIER PERSON AS WELL.
- OH, I LOVE THAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
SO, WHAT SURPRISED YOU THE MOST
ABOUT DOING THE SHOW?
- IT IS AN ACTUAL RACE.
I DON'T THINK AT HOME
YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW FAST WE'RE ACTUALLY
DOING THINGS,
BUT YOU'RE, LIKE,
STUMBLING OUT TO THE RUNWAY
AND STRAPPING YOUR SHOE
AND GLUING ON YOUR EYELASH,
AND THEN THEY'RE LIKE, "TELL US
ABOUT WHEN YOUR MOM DIED,"
AND IT'S ROUGH.
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- IT'S TRUE. IT'S TRUE.
YEAH.
SO, DARIENNE,
LET'S GET STRAIGHT TO IT.
WHAT WERE
YOUR DIFFERENCES WITH DELA?
- YOU KNOW,
IT WAS JUST ONE OF THOSE THINGS.
IT'S LIKE, YOU KNOW,
SHE SNAPPED, I SNAPPED.
WE KIND OF HAD A MOMENT,
AND THEN, YOU KNOW...
[LAUGHTER]
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT ABOUT
ALWAYS HAVING GREAT TIMES,
IT'S ABOUT HAVING THOSE TIMES
THAT YOU NEED
TO STRUGGLE THROUGH,
SO I FEEL SO MUCH CLOSER TO HER.
- YEAH.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S ALL WATER
UNDER A DUCK'S BACK,
OR WHATEVER THE PHRASE IS.
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
DARIENNE, I DID
ACTUALLY WANT TO BRING
A LITTLE PEACE OFFERING.
YOU ONCE SAID THAT I WAS
LIKE A RUSSIAN DOLL,
AND SO HERE'S YOUR VERY OWN
DELA RUSSIAN DOLL.
- OH, MY GOD,
THERE'S MORE GOODNESS INSIDE!
- YES.
- IS THERE CANDY IN THERE?
[LAUGHTER]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU, TOO.
AN APOLOGY,
I'LL GIVE IT TO YOU.
THANK YOU FOR BEING
SUCH A GOOD FRIEND, YOU KNOW?
AND GIVING ME MY REALITY CHECK.
AND I APOLOGIZE
FOR ANY STRESS I CAUSED YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
- AW.
I LOVE THAT, I LOVE THAT.
NOW, DARIENNE,
YOU CONFIDED IN ME
THAT YOU'D HAD A BAD
FALLING-OUT WITH YOUR PARENTS,
AND, AS I'VE SAID,
WE GET TO CHOOSE OUR FAMILIES,
BUT SOMETIMES,
IF YOU'RE REALLY LUCKY,
"DRAG RACE" CAN BRING
FAMILIES TOGETHER.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
- HI, DARIENNE, IT'S MOM.
WE WISH WE COULD BE THERE
WITH YOU TODAY,
BUT WE WANT YOU TO KNOW WE DID
WATCH A FEW OF THE EPISODES,
AND I'M PROUD OF YOU.
WE KNOW HOW TOUGH
IT WAS FOR YOU TO COME OUT,
AND TELL US WHO YOU ARE,
AND HOW YOU FEEL,
AND I JUST WANT YOU
TO KNOW THAT WE LOVE YOU,
AND THAT WE SUPPORT YOU,
AND WE NOW ARE COMING OUT
AS DARIENNE'S PARENTS.
I'M HOPING THAT
WE CAN MAKE THIS MAYBE BE
THE FIRST DAY
OF THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
- HEY, DARIENNE, YOUR MOM
REALLY LIKED THE EARRINGS
YOU HAD ON THE OTHER NIGHT,
SO, GUESS WHAT?
I WENT OUT
AND BOUGHT HER A PAIR.
[LAUGHTER]
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE'RE PROUD OF YOU, SON.
- WE LOVE YOU, DARIENNE.
- AW!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- SO, DARIENNE, HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- I NEVER,
IN A MILLION YEARS,
THOUGHT THAT WOULD EVER HAPPEN,
AND WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT,
AND I LOVE YOU, GUYS, YOU KNOW?
SO...BRAVO.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- IN THE OVERSTOCK.COM RED ROOM,
OUR TOP 3 QUEENS ARE DOING
A LITTLE SISTERLY BONDING
BEFORE THEY TAKE THE STAGE.
COMING UP, WE REVEAL
THIS YEAR'S MISS CONGENIALITY,
AND AN EXTRA SPECIAL SURPRISE,
ALL WHEN "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED" RETURNS.
- ♪ WE'RE ALL BORN NAKED
AND THE REST IS DRAG ♪
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ SO LET THE MUSIC PLAY ♪
- ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WERE 3 LITTLE QUEENS
WHO WENT
TO "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE,"
EACH WITH A CHARISMA,
UNIQUENESS, NERVE,
AND TALENT OF THEIR OWN,
AND THEY LOVED TO SHOW IT OFF.
WELCOME BACK THE TOP 3!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ TOP 3 ♪
♪ TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ MY NAME IS ADORE DELANO ♪
- ♪ TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ EVERYBODY LOVES IT
WHEN I SING ♪
- ♪ TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ MY VOCAL TONE'S TO DIE FOR ♪
♪ AND I AM IN THE TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ TOP 3
TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ MY NAME IS COURTNEY ACT ♪
- ♪ TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ AND I'M AUSSIE ROYALTY ♪
- ♪ I CAN HIT
THE HIGHEST NOTES ♪
♪ AND I AM IN THE TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ HA, LIKE YOU TWO
EVER TOPPED ANYBODY BEFORE ♪
♪ I'M BIANCA, AND I COULD GIVE
A SHIT ABOUT YOUR RUNS ♪
- ♪ TOP 3 ♪
- ♪ I CAN READ YOUR ASS
TO THE BANK AND BACK FOR FUN ♪
I CAN'T FUCKING SING,
BUT I'M IN THE MOTHERFUCKING
TOP 3, MOTHERFUCKERS!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ TOP 3 ♪
♪ TOP 3 ♪
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ADORE, BIANCA, AND COURTNEY,
YOUR PUSSIES ARE ON FIRE!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
BUT IT'S TIME
FOR SOME PROBING FAN QUESTIONS.
FIRST, THE NUMBER ONE
QUESTION ONLINE IS,
WHAT'S THE STATUS OF LAGANJA
AND ADORE'S RELATIONSHIP?
- OOH.
- YOU TWO ARRIVED AS FRIENDS,
BUT YOU HAD THIS HUGE BLOW-UP,
SO WE BROUGHT YOU BACK TOGETHER
TO WATCH THAT MOMENT
BEFORE IT AIRED.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
- HI.
- AND THIS GIRL.
- [LAUGHS]
HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
- OH, GOOD.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
REALLY INTERESTING.
- A LITTLE BIT, YEAH.
- I'M SCARED.
- LET'S DO IT,
LET'S ROLL THE TAPE.
- THIS RIGHT NOW,
THAT'S THE BITCH THAT I KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW "YES, MAMA."
- WHEN I'M WITH MY BEST FRIENDS
I SAY, "YES, MAMA."
- THAT AIN'T HOW YOU TALK
WHEN I HANG OUT WITH YOU
WHEN THE CAMERAS AREN'T HERE.
- NOW I AM ANNOYING, I AM FAKE,
I'M NOT WHO I'M BEING...
- HOLD UP. HOLD UP, BITCH.
- I'M PRETENDING TO BE
SOMEBODY I'M NOT...
- NO, THAT'S WHAT I DID NOT
WANT TO MAKE IT, GANJA.
- WELL, HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FEEL IN THIS MOMENT?
- GANJA, I DIDN'T
WANT TO MAKE IT
THAT EVERYBODY
WAS ATTACKING YOU.
- YEAH, I FEEL VERY ATTACKED!
- I DIDN'T MEAN IT TO COME OFF
LIKE HOW IT CAME OFF,
BUT I WAS JUST, LIKE,
REALLY FRUSTRATED.
LIKE, YOU PUT THAT ON
TO DO SOMETHING
FOR, LIKE, A CHARACTER
OR SOMETHING.
I'VE NEVER IN MY LIFE
HEARD YOU TALK LIKE THAT,
IN MY LIFE.
- I WAS JUST TRYING TO BE FUNNY.
- BUT THEN YOU'RE SAYING
THAT THAT'S YOU.
- YOU CAN SAY
THAT ALL THIS IS FAKE,
BUT THIS IS REAL, BITCH.
- I DON'T KNOW, I'M STILL
STICKING BY TO WHAT I'M SAYING.
I DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE THAT WAS GENUINE.
LIKE, I DIDN'T WANT THIS TO TURN
INTO A BULLYING LAGANJA THING,
BECAUSE I FUCKING
FELT BAD FOR YOU,
AND I STILL HAVE YOUR BACK,
EVEN THOUGH I HEAR THINGS.
- I FEEL LIKE
THERE'S THINGS THAT...
AHH, YOU'VE HEARD
BECAUSE I'M FUCKING JEALOUS.
- LIKE...
- I DON'T WANT
TO LOSE MY FRIEND.
- I FEEL LIKE THIS NEEDS TO BE
A CONVERSATION, LIKE,
IN PRIVATE.
- SO, ADORE, DID YOU TWO END UP
HAVING A PRIVATE CONVERSATION?
- THERE IS A CUTE, LITTLE BAR
ACROSS THE STREET,
SO WE GOT A COUPLE
OF DRINKS, AND...
[LAUGHS]
WE ACTUALLY TALKED IT OUT,
AND I DID REALLY HAVE
A STRONG CONNECTION WITH LAGANJA
BEFORE COMING
INTO THIS COMPETITION,
SO WE'RE AT A GOOD PLACE
RIGHT NOW, WE REALLY ARE.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- SO, LAGANJA, DO YOU THINK
THE FRIENDSHIP IS MENDED?
- ABSOLUTELY.
RELATIONSHIPS GO THROUGH
TOUGH TIMES, AND WE'VE MOVED ON,
AND, YOU KNOW,
I LOVE ADORE WITH ALL MY HEART.
THAT'S MY SISTER,
AND I LOVE HER.
- RIGHT ON. RIGHT ON.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
THANK YOU, LADIES.
LET'S TAKE SOME FAN QUESTIONS
FROM THE AUDIENCE.
OH, OH, OKAY. HEY.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- [LAUGHS]
I LOVE IT.
OKAY, THIS IS A FAN OF FACEBOOK
QUESTION FOR ADORE
FROM MIGUEL TORRES.
"I KIND OF GET THE FEELING
THAT YOU HAVE A CRUSH
"ON BIANCA DEL RIO
WHEN SHE'S NOT IN DRAG.
DO YOU?"
- UM...
[LAUGHTER]
IF I HAD A CRUSH ON BIANCA,
I WOULD HAVE TRIED
TO COP A FEEL, BUT I DIDN'T.
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- I WOULD NEVER SLEEP WITH HER,
BECAUSE I ONLY GIVE TO CHARITY
ONCE A YEAR, ALL RIGHT?
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- ALL RIGHT,
WE HAVE ANOTHER QUESTION
FROM A YOUNG LADY IN YELLOW.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- HIEEEE.
- I HAVE A FACEBOOK QUESTION...
[LAUGHTER]
FROM TEAL FLEMMING,
FOR GIA GUNN.
- [LAUGHS]
- "WHAT WAS WITH
THAT EYELASH, GIRL?"
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- YOU KNOW,
TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST,
I DO HAVE ONE EYE
THAT IS SMALLER
AND BIGGER THAN THE OTHER,
BECAUSE I DO HAVE
VERY ASIAN-ESQUE EYES,
AND HOPEFULLY
IT'S A LOT BETTER TONIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
- ABSOLUTELY.
- HEY!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- YES!
- [LAUGHS]
- OKAY.
HERE'S ONE FOR BIANCA
FROM NINA FORLINI,
AND SHE SAYS,
"HONESTLY, I JUST WANT
BIANCA TO READ ME,
AND SINCE SHE'S NOT HERE,
WHY DON'T..."
OH, "WHY DON'T YOU
JUST READ ME?"
OH, SHIT.
[LAUGHTER]
- WAIT, NOW, YOU KNOW
GOOD AND WELL, JIGGLY,
THAT WE ARE VERY,
VERY GOOD FRIENDS.
I COULDN'T POSSIBLY DO IT,
BUT I'M GOING TO TRY, BITCH.
- [GROANS]
- YOU ARE FROM SEASON 4,
THE SEASON OF TEETH.
THAT WAS YOU, IT WAS
THAT LITTLE SNAGGLETOOTH
THAT CAME OUT AND SAID,
"HEY, I WANT TO BE
PART OF THE SHOW!"
[LAUGHTER]
OH, BITCHES, FUCK YOU,
IF WE WERE IN A BAR,
YOU WOULD BE LAUGHING
AT THIS BULLSHIT RIGHT NOW.
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
DO WE HAVE ANY MORE QUESTIONS?
- HELLO, I'M ANDRE,
FROM WORCESTER, MASSACHUSETTS,
JOSLYN'S FIANCE.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
JOSLYN, YOU KNOW,
I ASKED YOU 3 YEARS AGO
IF YOU WOULD MARRY ME, AND YOU
SAID THAT YOU WERE WAITING
TILL YOU GOT
ON "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
UNTIL WE COULD GET MARRIED,
SO, YOU FINALLY MADE IT,
AND I WAS WONDERING
IF WE COULD GET MARRIED
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- YOU ARE IN LUCK, ANDRE!
COME ON DOWN, BECAUSE MAMA RU
IS AN ORDAINED MINISTER.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
THAT'S RIGHT!
I TELL YOU WHAT,
YOU STAND HERE.
I'M ALSO A WEDDING PLANNER.
YOU STAND THERE,
AND YOU STAND HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE US
A WEDDING, YOU ALL.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
OH, SCRUFF PIT CREW!
[WAGNER'S BRIDAL CHORUS PLAYS]
- [LAUGHS]
WELL, WELL, WELL.
THE MOTHERS OF THE BRIDE
AND GROOM ARE HERE.
SUSANNE AND DEBORAH.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TONIGHT
TO CELEBRATE
A CRAZY LITTLE
THING CALLED LOVE.
JOSLYN AND ANDRE,
DO YOU PROMISE
TO CHERISH, HONOR,
AND RESPECT EACH OTHER
AS LONG AS YOU BOTH SHALL LIVE?
- I DO.
- WHAT LOVE
HAS BROUGHT TOGETHER,
LET NO MAN PUT ASUNDER.
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU MARRIED!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ANDRE, YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
WA-WA.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
[WAGNER'S BRIDAL CHORUS
CONTINUES]
- NOW, SASHAY THAT BOUQUET.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- COMING UP,
MISS CONGENIALITY IS REVEALED,
AND WHO DO YOU WANT TO BE
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR?
ARE YOU TEAM ADORE,
TEAM BIANCA, OR TEAM COURTNEY?
KEEP TWEETING, AS "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED" CONTINUES.
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED."
NOW, AS YOU KNOW,
WINNING THE TITLE
OF AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR
IS WORTH $100,000.
BUT WINNING THE HEARTS
OF FANS IS PRICELESS.
TO ANNOUNCE WHICH ONE
OF THESE BITCHES
YOU VOTED TO BE
MISS CONGENIALITY,
PLEASE WELCOME
LAST YEAR'S WINNER,
I LOVE SAYING THIS,
IVY WINTERS!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ SHE'S SO BLOODY TALL ♪
♪ SHE'S SO WILD, SO ANIMAL ♪
♪ SHE'S GOING TO WORK
THAT SEXY BODY SO SEXUAL ♪
♪ SHE'S LIKE
A FEMALE PHENOMENON ♪
♪ SHE'S A GLAMAZON ♪
♪ FEMALE PHENOMENON
A GLAMAZON ♪
- THE FANS HAVE SPOKEN.
- REALLY? WHAT HAVE THEY SAID?
- OH, MY GOD.
[LAUGHTER]
THE WINNER OF SEASON 6
MISS CONGENIALITY
AND A $2,500 GIFT CARD
FROM OVERSTOCK.COM IS...
BENDELACREME!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ EVERYBODY WANTS HER
MISS SEXY IN THE CITY ♪
♪ SHE'S ON THE PROWL
SHE RUNS THIS TOWN ♪
♪ WHO'S THAT GIRL
A FLY FEROCIOUS LADY ♪
♪ GET UP AND DANCE ♪
♪ GET, GET UP
AND SASHAY, SHANTAY... ♪
- CONDRAGULATIONS, IS THERE
ANYTHING YOU'D LIKE TO SAY?
- IT HAS MEANT
SO MUCH FOR SOMEBODY
WHO IS A SHY PERSON,
WHO DOESN'T ALWAYS FEEL
LIKE THEY WANT TO REVEAL
THEMSELVES TO EVERYBODY,
TO BUILD SOMETHING
TO HELP THEM DO THAT,
PUT IT IN THE WORLD,
AND HAVE IT RECEIVED SO WELL.
THANK YOU, GUYS, SO MUCH.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- AND THANKS TO ALL
THE FANS FOR VOTING.
NOW, WHEN IT COMES
TO THIS SEASON'S TOP 3,
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS A, B, C.
"A" IS FOR ADORE DELANO.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- MY NAME IS ADORE DELANO,
AND I'M A FUCKING LIBRA.
FOR ALL THE QUEENS TELLING ME
THAT I'M NOT POLISHED ENOUGH,
I JUST WANT THEM TO KNOW
THAT I'M POLISH REMOVER, BITCH.
PARTY!
- YOU'RE RELYING A LOT
ON YOUR CHARM AND PERSONALITY,
WHICH CONCERNS ME.
- I CAME HERE TO BE, LIKE,
TOP 3, AND TO FUCKING WIN IT.
- YOU HAVE TO LEARN
TO APPLY YOUR GREAT THINGS,
LIKE IN THE RAPPING
OR THE SINGING,
INTO THE OTHER CHALLENGES.
- SHE'S A PERFORMER.
ADORE IS DEFINITELY A SUPERSTAR.
HER VOICE MADE ME LOOK AT HER
IN A WHOLE ANOTHER LIGHT.
- ♪ WHEN YOU LOVE ME... ♪
- BECAUSE WHOEVER SAID BEAUTY
WAS ON THE INSIDE...
- IS UGLY.
♪ MY NAME IS ADORE ♪
♪ AIN'T NO NEED
TO TRY TO FORCE IT ♪
♪ LOOK AT MY BODY
IN THIS BRAND NEW CORSET ♪
♪ MEN TURN AROUND
PANTS COMING DOWN ♪
♪ GO HOME, HOS
WHERE'S MY DRAG RACE CROWN? ♪
- YOU MADE ME SO HAPPY TONIGHT,
I COULD KISS YOU!
- OH, MY GOD,
ARE WE GOING TO DO TONGUE?
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ALL SEASON LONG
YOU WERE FULL OF SELF-DOUBT.
THEN DURING THE GLITTER BALL
YOU HAD AN EPIPHANY.
- YES.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- IT WAS DEFINITELY
THE TALK THAT YOU GAVE ME.
IT CHANGED MY LIFE, REALLY,
AND I APPLIED THAT
TO MY DAILY LIFE
AS WELL AS MY DRAG CAREER.
IT WAS REALLY AN EYE-OPENER.
NO ONE HAS, LIKE,
EVER, LIKE, SAT ME DOWN
AND ACTUALLY PUT IT INTO WORDS
AND HAD IT MAKE SENSE,
AND I JUST, LIKE,
AM FOREVER GRATEFUL FOR THAT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
I ALREADY FEEL LIKE A WINNER.
WELL, I STILL WANT TO WIN
REALLY BAD...
[LAUGHTER]
BUT, LIKE, REALLY BAD.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE
A FULLY DEVELOPED CHARACTER
BECAUSE OF YOU
AND BECAUSE OF THE SHOW.
I FEEL MORE LOVE FOR MYSELF
THAN I'VE EVER FELT,
AND I NEVER THOUGHT THAT
THAT WOULD HAPPEN.
YOU GAVE ME THAT,
AND YOU MADE ME REALIZE THAT
WITH JUST PUTTING IT
REALLY SIMPLE.
- YEAH, YEAH, WELL,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO DIFFERENTLY
HAVING SEEN THE SHOW?
- IN THE BEGINNING,
I THINK I REMEMBER EVEN TELLING
YOU THIS IN THE WORKROOM,
I WENT IN AND I WAS LIKE,
"HMM, I'LL PROBABLY MAKE IT
THIRD EPISODE," AND THEN...
[LAUGHTER]
WELL, BECAUSE I STARTED SEEING
ALL THE GIRLS' SHIT,
AND I WAS LIKE,
"OH, FUCK," AND THEN...
[LAUGHTER]
YEAH.
YEAH, MAN, AND THEN I'VE SEEN
GIA'S STUFF, AND SHE'S LIKE,
"HOW ABOUT HER, THOUGH?
WELL, HOW IS SHE?"
AND I WAS JUST LIKE, "OH."
[LAUGHTER]
LIKE, I STARTED APPLYING MYSELF
TO THE CHALLENGES MORE.
I REALLY FELT CRAZY, I WAS
LOOKING AT MYSELF IN THE MIRROR,
AND I WAS LIKE,
"YOU GOT THIS."
LIKE, "YOU ARE GOING TO SLAY
THIS SHIT, NO MATTER WHAT."
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- SO, I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN DOING
SINCE WE STOPPED FILMING.
- I JUST FINISHED MY ALBUM.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
I'M REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT THAT, YEAH.
- GREAT.
SO, ADORE, IF YOU WON
THE CROWN AND THE $100,000,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
- I WOULD TRY MY HARDEST
TO BREAK THROUGH MAINSTREAM
AND CARRY ON YOUR LEGACY,
I THINK IT'S TIME.
I MEAN, LADY GAGA IS DOING IT.
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
HER AND I IS I HAVE A PENIS,
AND THAT'S QUESTIONABLE,
AND I JUST...
[LAUGHTER]
MY THING IS, LIKE,
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES TO BECOME
THAT CRAZY DRAG SUPERSTAR,
POP STAR, TOUR THE WORLD,
INSPIRE KIDS AROUND THE WORLD,
AND I THINK WINNING
THE CROWN WOULD HELP ME
REALLY PUT MY STAMP ON THAT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- NOW, I KNOW YOUR MOM, BONNIE,
IS YOUR BEST FRIEND.
- YES, SHE IS.
- LET'S SAY HELLO.
- HI, MOM!
- OH, HEY, BONNIE!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- WHO IS SHE HERE WITH?
- SHE'S HERE WITH JERRY,
HER BOYFRIEND,
WHO'S ALSO A FAN OF THE SHOW,
AND HE LIKES BIANCA.
HE'S PROBABLY
JUST HERE TO WATCH HER.
[LAUGHTER]
HE THINKS SHE'S SO FUCKING COOL.
LIKE, I THINK IT'S, LIKE,
THE HUMOR THAT IS LIKE...
IT'S ODD, THEY HAVE THE KIND
OF THE SAME HUMOR.
I THINK THAT'S WHY
I LOOK AT HER AS A DAD.
NO, I'M JUST KIDDING.
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- YOU GOT ME, BITCH!
YOU GOT ME, BITCH.
- SO, BONNIE, IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY TO ADORE?
- JUST KEEP DOING
WHAT YOU'RE DOING,
AND WE'RE VERY PROUD OF YOU.
I LOVE YOU VERY MUCH,
AND I MISS YOU.
- I MISS YOU, TOO.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER IN, LIKE,
IN 2 1/2 WEEKS.
- OH, REALLY?
- YEAH.
- OH, YOU'VE BEEN ON THE ROAD.
- HMM, MAKING THAT MONEY,
MONEY, MONEY, MONEY,
MONEY, MONEY, MONEY.
- HEY!
WELL, THANK YOU, MISS DELANO,
I ADORE YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- I THINK I SPEAK FOR ALL
"DRAG RACE" FANS EVERYWHERE
WHEN I SAY, "PARTY."
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
- NEXT, BIANCA AND COURTNEY
LET US HAVE IT,
AND WE'RE THIS CLOSE TO CROWNING
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
- ♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED."
"B" CAN STAND FOR MANY THINGS.
BEAUTIFUL, BALLSY, BOSSY,
OR JUST BIANCA DEL RIO.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- MY NAME IS BIANCA DEL RIO.
I AM AN INSULT COMIC,
JUST LIKE DON RICKLES,
BUT IN A DRESS.
YOU LOOK LIKE A DAMN ROLL
OF SCOTCH TAPE.
- [LAUGHS]
- YOU KNOW EXACTLY
HOW TO LAND A JOKE.
- MY MOTHER INSISTED
THAT WE STAY TRUE
TO OUR SPANISH HERITAGE,
SO MY FIRST WORDS WERE...
[KNOCKS]
"HOUSEKEEPING."
[LAUGHTER]
- I THINK THE DEL RIOS
NAILED IT.
- BALONEY!
- BIANCA IS SECRETLY ADORABLE.
- DON'T TELL ANYBODY
THAT I'M BEING KIND.
- SHE'S THE TYPE OF PERSON WHERE
YOU, LIKE, WANT TO HUG HER,
AND SHE'S JUST LIKE,
"UGH, GET AWAY."
LIKE, IT'S VERY THAT.
- I HAD A GUARD.
I HAVE BUILT UP THIS WALL,
AND THIS EXPERIENCE
HAS CHANGED ME.
I WENT THROUGH A SELF-DISCOVERY,
ACCEPTING THAT I'M NOT
SUCH A BAD BITCH.
- THANK YOU, BIANCA.
- THANKS, RU,
YOU SHADY BITCH.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- NOW, BIANCA,
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO BELIEVE
THAT YOU'RE ACTUALLY
A NICE PERSON?
- [CHUCKLES]
NO, IT'S ALL IN THE EDITING.
IT'S ALL EDITING.
- [LAUGHS]
- WHAT I DO ON STAGE,
AND WHAT I'VE DONE
FOR A LONG TIME HAS BEEN
A BITCH OR AN INSULT COMIC
OR SOMEONE TO BE AFRAID OF,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IN MY EVERYDAY LIFE, YOU KNOW,
I CAN'T GO TO RITE AID AND SAY,
"FUCK YOU, BITCH,
GIVE ME MY SHIT."
[LAUGHTER]
- NOW, AND YOU'RE
A SEASONED QUEEN.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG
TO AUDITION FOR THE SHOW?
- WELL, I REALLY DIDN'T,
YOU KNOW,
SEE ANYBODY THAT WAS LIKE ME.
I THOUGHT THERE WAS
A CERTAIN TYPE.
I THOUGHT IT WAS ALWAYS
FOR YOUNGER GIRLS
THAT KNEW BEYONCE MEDLEYS.
AND I WAS FRIENDS
WITH LADY BUNNY,
WHO GAVE ME SOME
GOOD ADVICE, AND SHE SAID,
"GIRL, TRY IT!
YOU NEVER KNOW!"
[LAUGHTER]
AND WHEN I TOLD HER
I WAS LEAVING TO DO THE SHOW,
SHE GOES, "THIS IS YOUR CHANCE
TO ELECTRIFY THE NATION.
SEE YOU IN A WEEK
WHEN YOU'RE ELIMINATED."
SO...
[LAUGHTER]
- SO, HOW HAS "DRAG RACE"
CHANGED YOUR LIFE?
- FOR SOMEBODY LIKE ME,
WHO HAS WORKED IN THIS BUSINESS
FOR 18 YEARS,
IS GIVEN THIS OPPORTUNITY,
THIS PLATFORM,
HAS BEEN PHENOMENAL.
TO TRAVEL THE COUNTRY AND GET
TO MEET ALL THESE PEOPLE,
AND THE FACT THAT I'M NOW A PART
OF IT IS PRETTY FUCKING CRAZY.
- IT IS, IT IS.
- IT'S INSANE.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- YOU ARE A QUEEN
WHO SPEAKS HER MIND.
WAS IT HARD FOR YOU TO WATCH?
- YEAH, SOMETIMES.
I HAD THOSE MOMENTS
WHEN I WOULD CRINGE,
AND YOU'RE JUST LIKE,
"OH, SHIT."
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
"I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID THAT,"
BUT I THINK THAT
IN THAT SITUATION, YOU KNOW,
IT BRINGS OUT THE GOOD
AND BAD IN EVERYBODY.
- SO, WHAT WOULD IT MEAN TO YOU
TO BECOME AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR?
- WELL, IT WOULD MEAN
THAT I BEAT THESE OTHER BITCHES.
NO.
[LAUGHTER]
I THINK IT'D BE AMAZING,
I MEAN, I'M IN GREAT COMPANY.
AND I'VE REALIZED THAT I DON'T
HAVE TO BE A LIP-SYNC ARTIST,
I DON'T HAVE TO BE A DANCER,
I DON'T HAVE TO BE A SINGER,
I CAN BE ME, WHICH IS A FOOL,
AND DO IT ON THAT LEVEL.
[APPLAUSE]
- SO, WHO'S HERE
SUPPORTING YOU TONIGHT?
- MY GOOD LITTLE FRIEND LOLA
IS HERE TONIGHT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- SO, LOLA, IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY TO ROY LADY?
- LASHES AND LIPSTICKS
AND HIPS THAT KILL,
RUPAUL, YOU SURE HAVE
SOME BIG HEELS TO FILL.
BUT I KNOW BIANCA,
I'M HER NUMBER ONE FAN.
IF YOU CROWN HER OUR QUEEN,
I WON'T TELL SHE'S A MAN.
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- BIANCA, WE KNEW YOU WERE
A HARD AND HILARIOUS BITCH,
BUT IT'S REWARDING TO FIND OUT
THAT YOU'RE A NICE ONE, TOO.
I PROMISE I WON'T TELL ANYONE.
YES.
- THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- NOW, IT'S TIME TO FINISH
OUR LESSON IN THE ABCs OF DRAG,
AND I THINK WE ALL KNOW
WHAT THE C-WORD IS.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- COURTNEY ACT, A PROVEN STAR
ACCUSED OF RESTING ON PRETTY,
AS IN PRETTY FUCKING AMAZING.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
- IS THIS AMERICA'S
NEXT TOP MODEL?
MY NAME IS COURTNEY ACT.
I GUESS MY REPUTATION COULD
INTIMIDATE THE OTHER QUEENS.
I'M A SINGER.
- OH.
- ♪ I'M GOING TO BE
THE GREATEST STAR ♪
- YOU ARE A STAR.
- I HONESTLY WANT
TO JUST SKIN YOU ALIVE
AND WEAR YOUR BODY.
- [LAUGHS]
- YOUR BODY IS PHENOMENAL.
- COURTNEY KNOWS HOW TO DO SEXY.
SHE'S A NATURAL.
- IS THAT ALL YOU'VE GOT?
- [GRUNTS]
- I'M GETTING, DARE I SAY,
BORED WITH THIS PRETTY THING.
- SHE DOES RELY ON THAT,
BUT THAT'S WHO SHE IS.
SHE IS BEAUTIFUL.
- COURTNEY ACT
IS AN IMMENSE TALENT
WHO HAS CONSISTENTLY BROUGHT
AMAZING LOOKS TO THE RUNWAY.
- I AM ONE DEGREE OF SEPARATION
FROM CHER!
- I AM SECURE ENOUGH
IN MY HETEROSEXUALITY
TO SAY "WOW."
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE]
- HAS BEING IN THIS COMPETITION
ADDED PRESSURE?
BECAUSE YOU WERE ALREADY
A STAR DOWN UNDER.
- COMING INTO THIS COMPETITION,
THERE WAS SUCH HIGH EXPECTATION,
AND IT DID ADD
A LOT OF PRESSURE.
I LEARNT SO MUCH ABOUT MYSELF
GOING THROUGH THIS COMPETITION.
- LIKE WHAT?
- AUSTRALIANS DO HAVE
A VERY BLUNT,
KIND OF HONEST SENSE OF HUMOR,
AND THERE WAS A LOT OF TIMES
WHERE I THOUGHT
THAT I WAS BEING HELPFUL,
AND I WATCH IT BACK,
AND I'M LIKE,
"OOH, DID SHE JUST SAY THAT?"
- [LAUGHS]
- SO I'M DEFINITELY
LEARNING TO CHIP AWAY
THAT SORT OF COLD
AUSTRALIAN EXTERIOR.
- SO, WHAT WOULD IT MEAN TO YOU
TO BECOME AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR?
- I MOVED FROM AUSTRALIA
3 YEARS AGO.
I MOVED FROM A FANTASTIC LIFE
INTO, LIKE,
A SHOEBOX APARTMENT
IN WEST HOLLYWOOD,
EARNING LESS MONEY
I DID WHEN I WAS 18,
AND IT WAS A STRUGGLE, BUT EVERY
MOMENT OF IT I WAS SO EXCITED,
BECAUSE I GOT TO BE HERE
LIVING MY DREAM.
AND IN JUST 3 YEARS
I'M SITTING ON THIS STAGE
AS ONE OF THE TOP 3
IN "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
JUST HAVING THAT DREAM
VALIDATED, IT IS OTHERWORLDLY.
SO I THANK YOU,
AND I THANK YOU,
AND I THANK YOU ALL
FOR THIS OPPORTUNITY.
- YES. YES.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
WELL, I KNOW THAT YOU ARE
A LONG WAY FROM AUSTRALIA,
BUT DO YOU HAVE ANY
FRIENDS AND FAMILY HERE
TO SUPPORT YOU TONIGHT?
- I HAVE GOT A FRIEND HERE
WHO I ACTUALLY MET ON THE SHOW.
MR. CHAZ BONO.
- OH, REALLY?
- YEAH!
- OH, MY GOODNESS!
[LAUGHS]
- HE WAS DOING
A MUSICAL PRODUCTION,
AND HE ASKED
IF I WOULD BE IN IT.
WE GOT TO BECOME FRIENDS.
IT'S JUST KIND OF,
LIKE, BLOSSOMED.
CHAZ CAME TO AUSTRALIA
WITH ME TO--
- REALLY?
- YEAH, TO DO MY SHOW
AT THE SYDNEY
GAY AND LESBIAN MARDI GRAS.
I GOT TO SING "I GOT YOU, BABE"
WITH CHAZ BONO.
- WOW.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
AMAZING, AND...
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE JUST FRIENDS?
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE I AM
AN ORDAINED MINISTER.
[LAUGHTER]
- AND I'VE STILL GOT TIME,
I COULD MARRY YOU, GUYS.
- NO, WE'RE GOOD.
- OKAY.
- WE'RE GOOD, WE'RE OKAY.
I MEAN, SHE IS LOOKING
PARTICULARLY LOVELY TONIGHT.
- [LAUGHS]
- BUT WE'RE GOOD, I THINK.
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE IF SHE WINS...
I MEAN, I COULD USE
HALF OF $100,000, BUT...
[LAUGHTER]
- I'M GETTING A PRENUP.
- I LOVE IT.
[LAUGHTER]
SO, LET'S GIVE A BIG ROUND
OF APPLAUSE TO OUR FINAL 3,
BECAUSE THE CHILDREN,
THEY DO LIVE FOR THE APPLAUSE,
OKAY?
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
[LAUGHS]
WHEN WE COME BACK,
I'M GOING TO CROWN
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
OR AM I? HMM...
- ♪ IF YOU LIKE DANCING
TURN IT UP ♪
- WE ARE SECONDS AWAY
FROM FINDING OUT
WHO WILL BE CROWNED
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
WILL IT BE ADORE DELANO,
BIANCA DEL RIO, OR COURTNEY ACT?
ALL WILL BE REVEALED WHEN
"RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE REUNITED"
CONTINUES FROM THE THEATER
AT ACE HOTEL IN DOWNTOWN L.A.
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S
DRAG RACE REUNITED."
ADORE DELANO.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
BIANCA DEL RIO.
COURTNEY ACT.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
ONE OF YOU IS JUST MOMENTS AWAY
FROM BEING CROWNED AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
BUT FIRST, JOINING US
FOR HER LAST LAP
AS AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR,
PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER
FOR JINKX MONSOON!
[MUSIC]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- [LAUGHS]
HEY, JINKX, HOW'S TRICKS?
- TRICKS ARE FOR KIDS.
I'M AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
- [LAUGHS]
- FOR ABOUT 60 MORE SECONDS.
- YES.
WELL, WELL.
WHAT'S LIFE BEEN LIKE
SINCE YOU SNATCHED THAT CROWN?
- WELL, MOTHER DARLING,
I GOT TO DO MY ORIGINAL SHOW,
"THE VAUDEVILLIANS,"
ALL ACROSS THE WORLD THIS YEAR.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
MY FULL-FEATURE DOCUMENTARY
"DRAG BECOMES HIM"
WILL COME OUT THIS SUMMER,
AND I JUST RELEASED
"THE INEVITABLE ALBUM"
BY JINKX MONSOON.
[CHUCKLES]
AVAILABLE ON iTUNES!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- [LAUGHS]
SO, JINKXY, DO YOU HAVE
ANY WORDS OF ADVICE
FOR AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR?
- WELL, I HIGHLY SUGGEST
YOU REVEL
IN EVERY SINGLE SECOND OF IT,
MIND YOUR Ps AND Qs,
AND WHEN THE BITCHES
COME FOR YOU,
LET THAT BULLSHIT BE WATER OFF
A MOTHERFUCKING DUCK'S BACK.
- [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
WELL, JINKX, YOUR REIGN
MAY BE ENDING TONIGHT,
BUT IT WILL ALWAYS BE
FOREVER MONSOON SEASON.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
WELL, THE WAIT IS OVER, KITTENS.
IN ADDITION TO THE TITLE OF
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR,
TONIGHT'S WINNER
WILL ALSO WALK AWAY
WITH A CROWN AND SCEPTER
PROVIDED BY FIERCE DRAG JEWELS,
A SICKENING SUPPLY
OF COLOREVOLUTION COSMETICS,
AND A CASH PRIZE OF $100,000.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
ALL RIGHT.
THE TIME HAS COME
TO CROWN OUR QUEEN.
AS ALWAYS, I HAVE CONSULTED
WITH THE JUDGES AND THE FANS,
BUT THE FINAL DECISION
IS MINE TO MAKE.
ADORE DELANO.
BIANCA DEL RIO.
COURTNEY ACT.
THE WINNER
OF "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE,"
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR,
IS...
BIANCA DEL RIO!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ IF I DREAM EVERYTHING
I WANT TO BE ♪
♪ IF I DREAM
ALL THE POSSIBILITIES ♪
♪ IF YOU JUST BELIEVE
IN YOUR WILDEST DREAMS ♪
♪ THEY WILL COME TRUE ♪
♪ IF I DREAM EVERYTHING
I WANT TO BE... ♪
- FUCK YOU, BITCH, I LOVE YOU.
- THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ IF YOU JUST BELIEVE
IN YOUR WILDEST DREAMS ♪
♪ THEY WILL COME TRUE ♪
- NOW, IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY?
- [CHUCKLES]
THAT IN THE SHOW
I DIDN'T CRY ONCE,
AND THE WEIRD THING NOW,
I'M NOT CRYING,
IT'S MY FUCKING EYELASH,
GIA JINXED ME, BUT...
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
ON A SERIOUS NOTE,
AS A 30-YEAR-OLD MAN IN A WIG,
NEVER GIVE UP, SOME SHIT
CAN REALLY HAPPEN LATER IN LIFE,
AND I AM THE MOST GRATEFUL GUY
ON THE PLANET,
SO THANK YOU, THANK YOU ALL.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- MY QUEEN, I BOW TO THEE.
NOW, PRANCE, I SAID.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
- ♪ NIGHT AFTER NIGHT
I CLOSE MY EYES ♪
♪ AND I WONDER
WHEN THE SUN WILL RISE ♪
♪ A MOMENT OF HOPE
IS ALL I NEED ♪
♪ TO KEEP ME MOVING ON ♪
♪ THROUGH THE DARK
TILL I SEE ♪
♪ WHAT'S LEFT
TO BE REVEALED TO ME ♪
♪ IF I DREAM EVERYTHING
I WANT TO BE... ♪
- NOW, REMEMBER,
IF YOU CAN'T LOVE YOURSELF,
HOW IN THE HELL ARE YOU
GOING TO LOVE SOMEBODY ELSE?
AND I KNOW I CAN GET
AN AMEN UP IN HERE.
- AMEN!
- ALL RIGHT.
NOW, GO ON HOME,
DO DRAG, EVERYBODY.
- ♪ IF I DREAM EVERYTHING
I WANT TO BE ♪
♪ IF I DREAM
ALL THE POSSIBILITIES ♪
♪ IF YOU JUST BELIEVE
IN YOUR WILDEST DREAMS ♪
♪ THEY WILL COME TRUE ♪
- I THOUGHT BIANCA WAS A HOOT,
BUT, RU, YOU'RE STILL
MY FAVORITE.
- BALONEY!