- IT'S "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE:
COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN."
WITH JUST ONE WEEK
UNTIL WE ANNOUNCE
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR,
GET READY
FOR THE JUICIEST, GAGGIEST,
AND SHADIEST SHENANIGANS
OF THE SEASON.
- I HOPE YOU BITCHES ARE READY.
- OF COURSE!
- ♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
AS WE COUNT DOWN
THE TOP TURNT-UP RUNWAY LOOKS,
THE TOP JUDGE MENTAL
MOMENTS ...
THEY CREATED A CHARACTER...
- PAUSE.
- THE TOP SMACKDOWNS.
- DARIENNE, WHY DIDN'T
YOU CHOOSE ME?
- IT'S NONE
OF YOUR FUCKING BUSINESS.
- OOH!
- THE TOP MOMENTS
THAT MADE US GO,
"WHAT THE FUCK?"
THAT'S RIGHT,
ALL TOPS, NO BOTTOMS,
JUST LIKE THE PIT CREW.
- EXCUSE ME.
- [GIGGLES]
PLUS EXTRA SPECIAL FOOTAGE
NEVER BEFORE SEEN ON TV.
I'M NOT MAD AT YOU,
I'M MAD AT THE DIRT.
AND THE WORLD VIDEO PREMIERE
OF "SISSY THAT WALK."
♪ UH-OH
UH-OH ♪
- NOW SISSY THAT WALK.
- TO DIAGNOSE
THE MOST SICKENING SEASON
IN "DRAG RACE" HERSTORY,
WE'LL BE JOINED
BY LEGENDARY QUEENS,
EACH WITH A PhD IN FIERCE.
- PUT ON YOUR BIFOCALS,
AND LET'S READ THESE BITCHES.
- HOW YOU DOIN'?
- LET THE COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN
BEGIN IN 7, 6, 5...
AH, JUST START THE MUSIC.
THE WINNER
OF "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
RECEIVES A SICKENING SUPPLY
OF COLOREVOLUTION COSMETICS,
AND A CASH PRIZE OF $100,000.
♪ RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE ♪
♪ MAY THE BEST WOMAN ♪
♪ BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
WELCOME TO "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE
COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN."
WITH JUST ONE WEEK
UNTIL I CROWN
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR,
I HAVE A CONFESSION TO MAKE.
I STILL HAVEN'T MADE UP MY MIND.
[GIGGLES]
SO TELL ME,
WHO DO YOU THINK SHOULD WIN?
ARE YOU TEAM ADORE DELANO?
TEAM BIANCA DEL RIO?
OR TEAM COURTNEY ACT?
- OH WE'RE PLAYING THAT
THIS YEAR, BITCH?
- UNDECIDED? THEN STAY TUNED
FOR UP CLOSE
AND PERSONAL MOMENTS
WITH THE FINAL 3.
IT JUST MIGHT CHANGE YOUR MIND.
- YES, GOD.
- FIRST UP,
THE TOP 6 CATCHIEST PHRASES.
- THERE WERE SO MANY
MEMORABLE PHRASES THIS SEASON.
- YES, GOD.
- OKAY.
- OH, YES, MAMA.
- PROPS TO YOU, MAMA.
- NUMBER 6.
- MOTHER HAS ARRIVED.
JUST LET ME OPEN
MY TEAR-AWAY THING.
MOTHER'S GOING
TO ARRIVE IN JUST A SECOND.
- MOTHER HAS ARRIVED.
- MOTHER ARRIVED,
BUT THEN SHE DIDN'T
STAY FOR TOO LONG.
- THOSE LITTLE SHADY APES.
- NUMBER 5.
- HEY, RUSIE Q.
- EVERYTHING JOSLYN
SAID WAS PRICELESS.
- I PLAN ON BEING
THE BLACK HORSE
IN THIS COMPETITION.
- STAND-UP COMEDY
IS NOT MY CUP OF SOUP.
GASP!
- GASP!
- EVERYTHING THAT JOSLYN SAID
WAS CUTE, BUT "KEEP IT FOXY,"
THAT WAS HOT.
- WHEN ALL ELSE FAILS,
KEEP IT FOXY. WAH WAH.
- IT'S SORT OF LIKE
A LITTLE CAROL BURNETT,
LIKE TUGGING-ON-THE-EAR
THING MAYBE,
INSTEAD YOU'RE JUST
TAPPING THE TIT.
- YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP IT FOXY?
WAH WAH.
- WAH WAH.
- IS THAT HOW SHE
PUNCTUATES HER SENTENCES?
I JUST FOUND OUT
I HAVE CHLAMYDIA.
WAH WAH.
YOU KNOW, LIKE?
- NUMBER 4.
- I CAN TELL THAT YOU'RE
THE FEISTY ONE.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- A BOOTY CUTS YOUR LEG.
[LAUGHS]
- ABSOLUTELY.
- IT'S ONE OF THOSE VOICES
THAT JUST STICKS WITH YOU.
- [SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
- NO, YOU HAVE
TO ASK ME A QUESTION,
LIKE WHAT'S THE WEATHER
LIKE TODAY?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- DO YOU LOOK
LIKE A FUCKING DUMPSTER?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- I'M NOT TRYING TO BE SHADY,
BUT I DIDN'T REALLY
LIKE HER.
- I HAVEN'T HEARD A VOICE
MORE ANNOYING THAN GIA GUNNS
SINCE, WELL, LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- ABSO-FUCKING-LUTELY.
- NUMBER 3.
- BIANCA IS A WALKING
CATCHPHRASE. I MEAN...
- I'M THINKING ABOUT
WEARING FACIAL HAIR.
- HOPE YOU'RE PACKED.
- YOU NEED HELP PACKING?
- NEED HELP PACKING?
BEAT IT, QUEEN.
- YOU NEED HELP PACKING?
YOU NEED HELP PACKING?
- BIANCA'S ROLODEX OF HATE
IS ACTUALLY MORE LIKE
AN ENTIRE WIKIPEDIA PAGE.
- TRINITY REMINDS ME
OF A DEAR FRIEND OF MINE
FROM NEW ORLEANS.
SHE'S DEAD.
- IF I WAS GOING
TO COME FOR YOU,
I'D COME INTO YOUR ROOM AT NIGHT
AND CUT UP YOUR FUCKING WIGS.
- LOOK AT THAT NOSE.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS
A FUCKING SWORDFISH.
SHE COULD FLIP PAGES IN A BOOK.
- NUMBER 2.
OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T.
- HASHTAG
"OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T."
[TRILLS]
- I THINK I HEARD IT AT LEAST
26,000 TIMES ON THE RUNWAY.
- VERY C.E...OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T.
RAINBOW, SHE BETTER DON'T.
DOMINO, SHE BETTER DO.
- I LOVE THAT ACTRESS
ON "GREY'S ANATOMY,"
SANDRA OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T.
- OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T,
BITCH.
- NUMBER 1.
- THERE WAS ONE WORD
THAT ADORE SAID A LOT.
- FUCK.
- ADORE, THAT'S YOUR CUE.
- OH, FUCK, YES.
UH-OH-OH, FUCK.
- ADORE DELANO'S FAVORITE
CATCHPHRASE IS...BEEP.
I CAN'T SAY IT,
BECAUSE I KEEP IT CLEAN.
- I HAVE A WHORE MOUTH, I DO.
- NO, NOT THAT WORD.
- PARTY.
PARTY.
- BLAST OFF TO PARTY CENTRAL.
- PARTY.
- GALAPAGOS ISLAND, PARTY.
- PARTY. PARTY.
- [GASPS]
PARTY.
- THIS SEASON WAS
ALL ABOUT #TEAMTALENT,
WITH ONE BREAKOUT PERFORMANCE
AFTER ANOTHER.
LET'S COUNT DOWN THE TOP 4
TEAM TALENT MVPs.
NUMBER 4.
- MY MOTHER IS FROM CUBA,
AND MY DAD IS FROM HONDURAS,
WHICH BASICALLY MEANS
I HAVE A LARGE DICK, NO CREDIT,
AND A TENDENCY TO TAKE THINGS
THAT DON'T BELONG TO ME.
[LAUGHTER]
- I WOULD NEVER WANT
TO SIT FRONT ROW
AT A BIANCA DEL RIO COMEDY SHOW,
BECAUSE SHE'S COMING FOR YOU
AND YOUR WEAVE.
- DO NOT FALL ASLEEP
WHILE BIANCA'S ON STAGE.
- CAN YOU WAKE THAT BITCH UP?
THE ONE
WITH THE HORIZONTAL STRIPES.
NOT A GOOD LOOK IN YOUR
THIRD TRIMESTER, SIR, ALL RIGHT?
[LAUGHTER]
- I REALLY DON'T WANT BIANCA
TO READ ME, EVER,
OR EVEN LOOK AT ME.
- NOT TODAY, SATAN, NOT TODAY.
- NUMERO TRES.
- ♪ MY NAME SAYS IT ALL ♪
♪ AIN'T NO NEED
TO TRY TO FORCE IT ♪
♪ LOOK AT MY BODY ♪
♪ IN THIS BRAND-NEW CORSET ♪
- ADORE SLAYED.
BITCH SLAYED. GO ON AHEAD.
- ADORE'S RAP, FLAWLESS,
AND I KNOW RAP.
STOP RELYING
ON THAT BODYGUARD SOUNDTRACK.
- ♪ MEN TURN AROUND ♪
♪ PANTS COMING DOWN ♪
- THAT HAIR LOOKED LIKE
IT WAS GROWING OUT OF HER HEAD.
WAS THAT HER HAIR?
I'M GOING TO BE MAD
IF THAT WAS HER HAIR.
- OKAY, SHE BETTER SHOULD.
- NUMBER 2.
- ♪ AND YOU, AND YOU ♪
♪ AND ALL OF YOU ♪
♪ I'LL MAKE YOU LOVE ME ♪
- COURTNEY BROUGHT
THE HOUSE DOWN, THE HOUSE DOWN.
- I FELT LIKE, OH,
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I HAD TURNED ON
A TONY'S PERFORMANCE.
- WHAT'S A TONY?
- SHE WAS SO FREAKING TALENTED,
AND SO FREAKING ADORABLE,
AND BEAUTIFUL, AND SPOT-ON.
SHE'S MY VIP TONIGHT.
- I LOVE BROADWAY MUSICALS.
AND COURTNEY ACT
WAS A PERFECT ADELE DAZEEM.
- NUMBER 1.
- WELL, RUPLE...RUPLE, IS IT?
- IT'S SO FUNNY
ABOUT THESE SEATTLE GIRLS
NOT REALLY BEING TAKEN SERIOUSLY
UNTIL SNATCH GAME.
- RU, COULD YOU GET PEOPLE
THAT SPEAK NORMAL ENGLISH
NEXT TIME FOR THE SHOW?
- EXCUSE ME,
WE ORIGINATED THE LANGUAGE.
[LAUGHTER]
- CITRUS, COULD YOU IMAGINE
SUCH A THING?
- NOW, YOU DO AN ENGLISH ACCENT?
- YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO DO ONE, IF I'M HONEST.
- I DON'T BELIEVE FOR A SECOND
THAT BENDELACREME
DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO DO
A BRITISH ACCENT.
LIES! LIZA MINELLI'S
SISTER, LORNA LUFT.
- QUITE GAY, I FOUND, YES.
- NOW, I KNOW BENDELACREME
MAY HAVE WON THE CHALLENGE,
BUT ADORE
BLEW IT OUT OF THE WATER.
- KIMMY!
- PEOPLE THINK IT'S EASY
TO PLAY A BUSTY DRUNK.
TRUST ME, IT ISN'T.
I'VE BEEN DOING IT FOR 30 YEARS.
- THE TOP 3
WTF CHALLENGE MOMENTS.
NUMBER 3.
- ♪ WHERE MY GIRLS AT?
MAKE YOUR HEELS CLAP ♪
- I LOVE THAT MINI-CHALLENGE
WHERE ONE QUEEN
IS ON THE BOTTOM
WITH THEIR LEGS SPREAD,
AND THE OTHER ONE IS ON TOP,
MOVING HER MOUTH.
IT WAS LIKE
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH SHARON.
- [GASP]
- I'M THE BOTTOM.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HALF THESE CHALLENGES
HAVE TO DO WITH ANYTHING,
BUT I AM SO ENTERTAINED.
- I MIGHT FART ON YOUR STOMACH.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- I WAS VERY NERVOUS
WHEN I SAW VIVACIOUS
LAYING IN THE SAND,
BECAUSE I THOUGHT FOR SURE
GREENPEACE WAS GOING TO COME
AND HARPOON HER.
- NUMBER 2.
OH, SCRUFF PIT CREW.
- OH, OH.
- OH, OH!
- YOU'RE GOING TO COMPETE
IN A GAME OF HUNGMAN.
A, S, ANOTHER S.
- ASS ASS ASS ASS ASS ASS.
DO I LOVE ASS.
- I HAVEN'T SEEN THAT MUCH JUNK
SINCE TOURING
WITH MILLI VANILLI.
- NUMBER 1.
QUEEN OVERBOARD!
- YES.
- IN THE FIRST EPISODE, THEY HAD
TO JUMP OFF A HIGH PLATFORM
AND STRIKE A GLAMOROUS POSE.
- OH, AND THEN THE OTHER GIRLS
GOT TO HAVE A FUN PILLOW FIGHT
WITH A BUNCH OF NAKED MEN.
LEAPING TO MY DEATH
OR BEING IN A BED
WITH LOTS OF MEN.
I DON'T KNOW.
- [SCREAMS]
- THE ONLY THING
THEY HAVEN'T DONE YET
IS SET FIRE TO THE QUEENS.
SEASON 7,
BURN ALL THEM BITCHES.
- COMING UP, STAY TUCKED
AS WE COUNT DOWN
THIS SEASON'S TOP 10
TURNT-UP FASHIONS.
- HOW IS SHE, THOUGH?
- WHAT?
- THE TOP 5 SMACKDOWNS.
- AND YOU ARE BEYONCE.
- OH, I AM.
- A SALUTE TO THE TOP 3.
PLUS THE WORLD VIDEO PREMIERE
OF "SISSY THAT WALK,"
WHEN "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE:
COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN"
CONTINUES.
[LAUGHS]
WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S DRAG
RACE: COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN."
THIS SEASON'S QUEENS
CAME DRESSED TO THRILL
FROM THE BOTTOM
OF THEIR CHA-CHA HEELS
TO THE TOP
OF THEIR SECOND HEADS.
- OH!
- THE TOP 4 DRAG-CESSORIES.
NUMBER 4.
- GIA GUNN'S GIANT PURSE
IS LIKE A PETITE CLUTCH
FOR A DRAG QUEEN,
BECAUSE IT DO
TAKE A LOT TO LOOK LIKE THIS.
- I GOT A LITTLE BRUSH.
- IS THIS YOUR BABY?
- I GOT A LITTLE TILAPIA
IN HERE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT
WOULD'VE MADE IT BETTER?
IS IF THE PURSE ROLLED IN
AND THEN STOPPED,
AND THEN SHE GOT OUT OF IT,
AND THEN PICKED IT UP
AND WALKED OUT,
BECAUSE IT WAS BIG ENOUGH.
- COME ON NOW.
IT IS A KNOWN FACT
THAT A WOMAN DO CARRY
AN EVENING BAG
AT A DINNER PARTY.
NUMBER 3.
- OH, THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
WITH THE YELLOW IN THE UMBRELLA
AND THE BLUE,
THAT WAS GORGEOUS.
SHE LOOKED STUNNING.
- IF YOU CAN JUST WALK AROUND
WITH YOUR OWN SPECIAL EFFECTS,
AND JUST HAVE RAIN FALLING
ON YOU, LIKE, IT'S GREAT.
- THIS RUNWAY LOOK
WAS A LITTLE MISLEADING, THOUGH,
BECAUSE I THOUGHT HER NAME
SHOULD HAVE BEEN APRIL SHOWERS.
- MAKE IT RAIN, GIRL.
MAKE IT RAIN.
NUMBER 2.
- COURTNEY'S CHARACTER
IN THE RUSICAL
GOT ADDICTED TO FISH OIL.
I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS SO ADDICTIVE.
I WOULD HAVE NEVER STARTED.
- ♪ ALL YOUR WISHES WILL GROW ♪
♪ IF YOU TAKE A SWIG
OF THIS FISH OIL ♪
♪ DRINK FOR ME ♪
- DON'T DO IT. DON'T DO IT!
DON'T DO IT!
- NUMBER 1.
- I THINK IT'S VERY IMPORTANT
FOR A QUEEN
TO HAVE GOOD HEAD
ON HER SHOULDERS.
- DO YOU HAVE A NAME
FOR THE HEAD
ON TOP OF YOUR HEAD?
- ORNACIA.
- ORNACIA, OKAY.
- I REALLY EXPECTED
A LOT FROM ORNACIA.
I'M SHOCKED SHE DIDN'T MAKE IT
INTO THE FINAL 3.
- OH, BOY!
- ORNACIA MEAN MUGS THE CAMERA.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- UH-HUH.
- BACK IN NEW YORK CITY, I USED
TO GO CLUBBING WITH ORNACIA
ALL THE TIME.
WE'RE ON THE LIST,
ORNACIA PLUS ONE.
I LOVE THIS SONG,
ORNACIA, DON'T YOU?
OH, MY GOD, THIS DJ
IS REALLY GREAT.
- YOU KNOW, SOME PARTS
OF THE SHOW REALLY MADE ME WET.
IN THE EYE.
GET YOUR MIND OUT OF THE GUTTER.
PERVERT.
THE TOP 5 MOMENTS
THAT MADE US FEEL THINGS.
NUMBER 5.
- THANK YOU.
- MILK GOT REALLY CHOKED UP
WHEN SHE LEFT.
- I JUST WANT
TO THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR ALLOWING ME
TO BE WHO I AM
WITHOUT FEAR OF BEING RIDICULED.
- MILK GETS ELIMINATED,
AND IT'S SUCH A SHAME,
THE ONE TIME
SHE LOOKS LIKE A WOMAN,
AND SHE GETS SENT HOME,
WHAT THE HELL?
- IF YOU LOVE YOURSELF
AND ARE HAPPY
WITH WHAT YOU'RE CONTRIBUTING
TO THE WORLD,
THEN NO ONE
CAN FAULT YOU FOR THAT.
- I HAD TO CUT MILK
OUT OF MY DIET
AND I WASN'T READY.
I'M NOT READY FOR SOY.
IT DOESN'T TASTE THE SAME!
- CAN I GET MY PHONE BACK?
- NUMBER 4.
- EVERY TIME WE GO
ON "UNTUCKED,"
ONE MINUTE THEY READING HOES,
THE NEXT ONE, THEY BOO-HOOING
INTO THEIR GLASSES.
I CAN'T TAKE IT!
- YOU GOT EVERYTHING FROM MAMA.
WE'RE CUT FROM THE SAME CLOTH.
YOU GOT THE BOOBIES.
WELL, MAMA AIN'T GOT A BUTT,
BUT YOU DO.
- [LAUGHTER]
- AND GET GHETTO IF YOU HAVE TO
WITH THESE GIRLS, OKAY?
SEE YOU WHEN YOU GET HOME
WITH THAT MONEY.
- MY MOM'S A CHOLA,
SHE LIKES BIG COCKS, OKAY!
- [LAUGHS]
NUMBER 3.
- I FEEL VERY ATTACKED.
- RELAX, RELAX.
- AFTER THE STAND-UP,
LAGANJA BROKE DOWN...AGAIN.
- I'VE GIVEN UP EVERYTHING
IN MY LIFE
TO BE A DRAG QUEEN,
WHEN I'M...
- BREATHE, BREATHE.
- IF YOU ARE GOING TO CRY
THAT FUCKING MUCH,
GET A BETTER DAMN LASH ADHESIVE
AND WATERPROOF
FUCKING MASCARA.
- THE 5 Gs: GOOD GOD,
GANJA, GET A GRIP.
- THIS IS JUST TOO FUCKING MUCH.
YOU BROKE ME DOWN,
I FEEL LIKE SHIT,
I LOOK STUPID.
GOD, THIS FUCKING SUCKS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT TOOK
ALL THE TIME TO EPISODE 8
FOR PEOPLE TO TELL LAGANJA
THAT HER VOICE WAS ANNOYING.
COME ON! OKAY?
- THAT'S NOT FAIR, I'M SORRY,
WE ALL HAVE DIFFERENT VOICES,
YOU KNOW?
I'VE BEEN TOLD MY WHOLE LIFE
MY VOICE WAS ANNOYING,
AND, YOU KNOW, NOW,
IT'S HOW I MAKE MY MONEYS.
- WORK, BITCH.
- NUMBER 2.
- I AM HIV POSITIVE.
I WANTED TO COME ON THIS SHOW,
AND I WANTED TO BE
THAT VOICE FOR PEOPLE
WHO ARE SCARED
TO SPEAK OUT ABOUT THAT.
- TRINITY ADMITTED
THAT SHE HAS HIV,
WHICH I THINK
IS EXTREMELY BRAVE.
- I MISS YOU AND I LOVE YOU.
YOU TOLD ME
WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE,
"I'M GOING TO BE A STAR,
I'M GOING TO BE ON TV."
SO HERE WE ARE.
- THE FACT
THAT TRINITY K. BONET'S MOTHER
SENT THAT BEAUTIFUL MESSAGE
AND THE FACT
THAT SHE JUST SEEMED,
LIKE, SO TEAM TRINITY,
I LOVE THAT.
I THINK ALL MOTHERS
SHOULD BE THAT OPEN
AND LOVING TO THEIR KIDS.
IT WAS SO GREAT TO SEE.
- NUMBER 1.
HERE COMES THE BRIDE.
- [FAKE CRYING]
- [LAUGHTER]
- AND SOME PEOPLE
SHED REAL TEARS.
- I BELIEVE
EVERY LIVING CREATURE
IN THE UNIVERSE
DESERVES THE RIGHT TO LOVE
AND TO BE HAPPY.
AND I'M FINALLY GOING HOME
TO PLAN MY OWN WEDDING, FINALLY.
[SIGHS]
- THAT'S CUTE. LITTLE
MISS JOSLYN'S ALL EMOTIONAL,
BECAUSE SHE HAS TO MAKE OVER
THESE WEDDING COUPLES,
AND SHE'S ENGAGED.
THAT'S SPECIAL.
I KNOW I BETTER
HAVE AN INVITATION.
- GUESS WHO CAUGHT THE BOUQUET.
THANKS, BRANDONNA.
[LAUGHS]
SMELLS ROTTEN.
A MOMENT YOU DIDN'T SEE
THIS SEASON
CAME
DURING THE TALK SHOW CHALLENGE.
WE SURPRISED EACH OF THE QUEENS
WITH A MYSTERY GUEST
AND THINGS GOT A LITTLE WILD.
- IT'S FINALLY THAT TIME
TO REVEAL
OUR SPECIAL MYSTERY GUEST.
- FROM THE NATIONAL
WILDLIFE FEDERATION--
I WENT TO CONTINUATION SCHOOL,
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT WORD MEANS. N-N--
- NATURALIST DAVID MISS-A-JEWS.
MISAJEWS-AH.
- MIS-AJUSKY.
- MISAJUSKY.
- MR. JEW SKY.
- HELLO, DAVID.
- HI, THERE.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
- I HAVE AN ANIMAL OUT HERE
THAT YOU'VE PROBABLY
NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
IT'S CALLED A BINTURONG
OR BEARCAT.
- OKAY.
- HAVE YOU EVER SEEN ONE
THIS BIG BEFORE?
- I HAVE, ACTUALLY.
- OH, AWESOME. YOU SEE THAT
OTHER THING STICKING OUT THERE?
- I DO, BUT I DIDN'T WANT
TO MENTION IT.
I JUST THOUGHT
SHE WAS EXCITED TO SEE ME.
SO IS THAT HER TAIL THAT'S--
- THAT IS HER TAIL, YUP.
- OKAY, THAT'S A LOOK.
- IS SHE A MARSUPIAL?
- SHE'S NOT A MARSUPIAL.
THAT'S A GREAT QUESTION.
YOU KNOW,
REFLECTING YOUR HOMELAND THERE.
- GOOD GIRL, RAJI.
YOU LOOK LIKE SOMEBODY
I KNOW CALLED RAJA.
- COMING UP, WE COUNT DOWN
THE TOP 10 TURNT-UP LOOKS
ON THE RUNWAY.
- ELOQUENT, IT'S A WORD.
- THE TOP 5 JUDGE MENTAL
MOMENTS.
- PUT A CORK IN IT.
- AND THE TOP 3 QUEENS
LET US HAVE IT.
PLUS THE WORLD VIDEO PREMIERE
OF "SISSY THAT WALK"
AS "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE:
COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN"
KEEPS ON KEEPING ON.
[LAUGHS]
WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S DRAG
RACE: COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN."
THIS SEASON, THE RUNWAY,
LIKE MY PUSSY, WAS ON FIRE.
WANT TO TAKE A LOOK?
THE TOP 10
TURNT-UP RUNWAY LOOKS.
NUMBER 10, DARIENNE LAKE.
- SHE GOT THE GIRLS
FRONT AND CENTER,
AND SHE LOOKS GORGEOUS.
LOVE IT.
- NUMBER 9, LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- LAGANJA, LADY GAGA CALLED.
SHE WANTS HER HAT BACK.
- NUMBER 8, TRINITY K. BONET.
- I ALWAYS TRAVEL
WITH A SATELLITE DISH,
BECAUSE YOU GET MORE CHANNELS.
- NUMBER 7, BENDELACREME.
- NOW, I'M NOT BIASED,
BUT BENDELACREME
IS THE MOST GORGEOUS GIRL
TO EVER POUNCE THAT RUNWAY.
IT'S LIKE LOOKING IN A MIRROR.
A FUNHOUSE MIRROR.
YOU KNOW,
ONE THAT MAKES ME LOOK THIN.
- NUMBER 6, BIANCA DEL RIO.
- WHO PUTS A STREAK
IN THEIR WIG?
I MEAN, WHO DOES THAT?
THAT'S SO 3 SEASON AGO.
- NUMBER 5, VI-VI-VIVACIOUS.
- VIVACIOUS' SPIKE OUTFIT
LOOKED LIKE A MICROSCOPIC IMAGE
OF A SYPHILIS SPORE.
- NUMBER 4, JOSLYN FOX.
- I THINK JOSLYN'S ASS
IS HER BEST OUTFIT.
OH, MY GOD, THAT'S SO SHADY.
- NUMBER 3, ADORE IN DIAMONDS.
- IT LOOKS LIKE TONYA HARDING
IS GOING TO CHASE AFTER HER
WITH A CROWBAR ANY MINUTE.
- NUMBER 2, MILK.
- MILK CAME OUT ON THE RUNWAY
DRESSED AS MOTHERFUCKING
PINOCCHIO, BITCH.
NOW, THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
- NUMBER 1, COURTNEY ACT.
- COURTNEY ACT AS A BIRD.
YES, BITCH.
- I THOUGHT THAT COURTNEY
WAS ACTUALLY GOING
TO TAKE FLIGHT
OFF THE STAGE
AND TAKE MICHELLE VISAGE'S
LACE FRONT WITH HER.
- THAT'S IT? THAT'S EVERYTHING?
YOU'VE LOOKED
AT THE EDITING FLOOR
AND THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE FOR ME?
- WE CAN'T FORGET RU'S
TOP 12 TURNT-OUT LOOKS, HUNTIES.
- [LAUGHS]
♪ COVERGIRL ♪
- MISS RU WORE EVERY LOOK
POSSIBLE THIS SEASON,
AND THEY WERE ALL TURNT-OUT.
- RU'S OUTFITS ARE ANNOYING,
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL
FUCKING BEAUTIFUL,
AND I HATE HER.
- YOU'RE SWEET. I LOVE YOU.
THE TOP 5 JUDGE MENTAL MOMENTS.
- THE JUDGES GOT INTO IT
THIS SEASON, HONEY.
THEY WERE TELLING IT LIKE IT IS.
- NUMBER 5.
- I CAN SEE ADAM LAMBERT
WATCHING THESE THIGHS.
HE WANTS SOME CHICKEN LEG.
I KNOW IT.
- ADAM AND APRIL CARRION
SITTING IN A TREE,
DOING SOMETHING WE CAN'T SEE.
- YOU ARE GORGEOUS.
- YOU'RE GORGEOUS AS WELL.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- GET A ROOM.
- BUT YOU CAN HEAR IT, AND IT
PROBABLY SOUNDS LIKE THIS.
[SUCKING NOISE]
AHH...
- NUMBER 4, THE OG DREAM GIRL,
SHERYL LEE RALPH.
- LOVE THE ORIGINAL DREAM GIRL.
COME ON, IT DOESN'T
GET BETTER THAN THAT,
AND SHE DON'T MIND TELLING IT
LIKE IT IS, EITHER.
- IT'S LIKE YOU HAVE A BEARD
ON YOUR FOREHEAD.
AIN'T NOBODY GOT TIME FOR THAT.
PUT A CORK IN IT.
- PUT A CORK IN IT. I WAS LIKE--
- LITERALLY, SPEAK
WITH THAT CORK IN THE MOUTH.
IT WILL DO WONDERS
FOR ENUNCIATION.
- IT HELPS YOU ENUNCIATE
YOUR WORDS,
AND PEOPLE
CAN UNDERSTAND YOU BETTER.
- NUMBER 3, LEAH REMINI IS HERE.
- SO THE LIPSTICK
SHOULD STAY ON.
- SHE SAID IT LASTS
THROUGH ALL THAT.
- I LOVE LEAH REMINI AS A JUDGE,
SHE AND MICHELLE ARE JUST
LIKE THOSE TWO MUPPETS
WHO JUST
READ THE SHOW FOR FILTH.
- WHEN LEAH REMINI
AND MICHELLE VISAGE
WERE GETTING INTO IT, HONEY,
I WAS LIKE, "CAN THIS BE
THE 'UNTUCKED' EPISODE, PLEASE?"
- DID IT STAY ON
THROUGH THE TRICK OR NOT?
- YES.
- WELL, I DIDN'T GET THAT.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
- YEAH, YOU WERE
ON THE KING OF QUEENS?
I'M THE QUEEN OF QUEENS.
- I THOUGHT THEY WERE TRYING
TO BE TOO FUNNY,
THEY WERE TRYING
TO OUTDO EACH OTHER,
AND THAT'S NOT A TEAM PLAYER.
- I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
YEAH, I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
- HALLELUJAH.
- SO THEY CREATED A CHARACTER--
- PAUSE. ONE SECOND, RU.
- OKAY.
- MICHELLE JUST
SAID I WAS RIGHT,
SO IF WE COULD
JUST TAKE A MOMENT.
- I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
- [LAUGHTER]
- SPEAKING OF SISTERHOODS,
YOU HAVE MICHELLE VISAGE
AND SANTINO RICE GOING AT IT
LIKE THEY'RE HAVING
THEIR OWN FREAKING QUARRELS.
I--DO THEY JUST NOT
AGREE ON ANYTHING?
- NUMBER 2.
- HE WANTS TO SAY
WHATEVER I SAY, THE OPPOSITE.
- NO, I DON'T.
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU SAY.
- I THINK
THAT MICHELLE AND SANTINO
ARE DEFINITELY FIGHTING
A LITTLE BIT MORE THIS YEAR,
BECAUSE I'VE SEEN
A 33% INCREASE IN SIDE EYE.
- IT WAS GREAT TO SEE BIANCA
DEL NERO IN THAT LIGHT.
- OR DEL RIO.
- I ACTUALLY THOUGHT IT WAS LIKE
WATCHING BIANCA DEL NERO'S PAST.
- DEL RIO?
- WHAT'D I SAY?
- DEL NERO.
- NO, DEL RIO.
- THIS IS THE SECOND TIME
YOU'VE SAID--
DEL NERO.
- I WOULD NEVER SAY "DEL NERO."
- YOU SAID IT TWO TIMES.
GO TO THE TAPE.
- WE HEARD YOU SAY IT TWICE.
- SHUT THE FUCK--NO.
- YOU'RE FUCKING CRAZY
IF YOU THINK YOU DIDN'T SAY IT.
- I ACTUALLY THOUGHT
WE WERE WATCHING
A TAPE FROM BIANCA DEL NERO.
[LAUGHS]
NOW YOU'RE NODDING,
YOU JUST SAID.
- THIRD TIME.
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
- WHAT'S A DEL NERO?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT SOUNDS DELICIOUS.
NUMBER 1. "DRAG RACE"
SUPER FAN KHLOE KARDASHIAN.
- KHLOE KARDASHIAN
IS SORT OF LIKE
THE HONEY BADGER OF DRAG.
SHE DOESN'T CARE.
- BASIC BITCHES NOT WANTED.
I HAVE A VERY BIG CAMEL TOE.
MY PUSS IS VERY LARGE
AND IN CHARGE.
I'M A BIG GIRL.
- I LOVE ANYBODY'S WHO'S GOT
A LARGE AND IN-CHARGE PUSS.
- HASHTAG NO FILTER.
- NOW, DURING KHLOE KARDASHIAN'S
SECOND APPEARANCE THIS SEASON,
SHE PERFORMED ON THE MAIN STAGE
WITH RAVEN AND MANILA.
THE SEQUENCE WAS SUPPOSED TO AIR
ON "KEEPING UP
WITH THE KARDASHIANS,"
SO THIS FOOTAGE IS SO EXCLUSIVE,
IT GOT CUT FROM NOT JUST ONE,
BUT TWO SHOWS.
LOOK AT THAT BODY,
MY GOD, IT'S GORGEOUS.
- WHICH ONE? ME? OH.
- YOUR PADS ARE AMAZING.
- [LAUGHS]
- YES.
- I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D BE LIP-SYNCHING
ON THE STAGE
OF "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE" AGAIN.
- ♪ SASHAY SHANTE
PANTHER ON THE RUNWAY ♪
♪ DO IT, DO IT, OH
ALL THE GIRLS SAY ♪
♪ WELCOME TO THE JUNGLE ♪
KHLOE KARDASHIAN,
SHANTE YOU STAY.
- WHOO! THANK YOU, BOO.
- RAVEN AND I LOST
TO KHLOE KARDASHIAN.
DAMN.
- UP NEXT,
THE TOP 5 SMACKDOWNS.
- YES, GOD, NESSA.
- ONE FINAL LOOK
AT OUR TOP 3 QUEENS.
AND WHY ARE THESE QUEENS
BLINDFOLDED?
- BITCH, GET INTO IT.
- FIND OUT
AS "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE:
COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN"
CONTINUES.
[LAUGHS]
WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S DRAG
RACE: COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN."
NOW, HERE
AT THE "DRAG RACE,"
WE'RE ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY.
AND LIKE EVERY FAMILY,
WELL, SOMETIMES
SHIT DO GET REAL.
THE TOP 5 SMACKDOWNS.
NUMBER 5.
- BITCH, ANYBODY THAT COMES
DOWN THE RUNWAY
LOOKING LIKE THAT,
THINKING THAT THE TONY AWARDS,
I WANT TO GET INTO YOUR BRAIN,
SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
- GIA IS VERY ONE-SIDED
WITH HER IDEA OF DRAG.
I COULD GO OFF
ON THE NUMBER OF THINGS
THAT SHE NEEDS TO FIX,
BUT I'D RATHER NOT.
- GIA'S DRAG IS ALL
ABOUT BEING FISHY,
GIVING THE ILLUSION OF A WOMAN,
AND MILK'S DRAG
IS KIND OF OPPOSITE THAT.
- I LOVE MILK'S DRAG.
I THINK THERE'S
AN AUTHENTICITY TO IT.
IT'S JUST HIS OWN PARTICULAR
THING, AND I LIVE.
I COMPLETELY LIVE FOR MILK.
- JUST GOT OFF THE BOAT,
YOU KNOW,
A LITTLE TRIP FROM ASIA.
JUST LANDED LIKE FRESH TILAPIA.
- WHY'S SHE SO PROUD OF TILAPIA?
IT'S LIKE THE CHEAPEST FISH.
- SASHAY AWAY.
- YOU GUYS ARE ALL STILL DUDES.
- NUMBER 4.
- NICE TO MEET YOU, COURTNEY.
I'M A BIG FAN OF YOURS.
MY NAME'S JOSLYN FOX.
- WHEN WE NEED A LOW-RENT
VERSION OF COURTNEY ACT,
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
[LAUGHTER]
- SOMETIMES IT'S GREAT
TO MEET YOUR IDOL,
AND SOMETIMES IT'S NOT.
- YOUR DRAG ISN'T AS POLISHED
AS OTHER DRAG
IN THE COMPETITION RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT BEING MEAN.
I'M JUST BEING FACTUAL,
BUT I DIDN'T MEAN IT
IN ANY WAY TO HURT HER FEELINGS.
- IT WAS VERY BIG SISTER,
LITTLE SISTER, YOU KNOW?
THE LITTLE SISTER
IDOLIZING THE BIG SISTER,
AND THEN SHE WAKES UP
AND REALIZES THAT IT'S A MAN.
[LAUGHS]
- I'VE GOT MY LACE FRONT
GLUED DOWN.
I DO GLANCE OVER
AND NOTICE JOSLYN
GIVING A LITTLE SIDEBURN ACTION.
WE'LL HAVE TO GET HER
INTO A NICE LACE FRONT WIG.
- NUMBER 3.
- YOU WON A CHALLENGE.
- I WON THE FIRST CHALLENGE TOO.
- OH YOU DID? OH.
- I DID.
- I WASN'T THERE.
YEAH, IT DOESN'T COUNT.
- HONEY,
I DIDN'T HAVE MY GLASSES ON,
SO I DIDN'T SEE THE ULTIMATE
SHADE SHOWDOWN COMING.
- WHY DID DARIENNE HATE
BEN SO MUCH?
- DARIENNE,
WHY DIDN'T YOU CHOOSE ME?
- IT'S NONE
OF YOUR FUCKING BUSINESS.
- OOH!
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT INTIMIDATES A GIRL MORE,
THE GIRLS WHO ARE GOOD
AT THE THINGS
THEY'RE NOT GOOD AT,
OR THE GIRLS WHO ARE GOOD
AT THE THINGS THEY'RE GOOD AT.
- I'M TOO YOUNG AND PRETTY
TO BE A COUGAR.
- [LAUGHS]
- AND A LOT OF, YOU KNOW,
COUGARS ARE DELUSIONAL.
- DARIENNE DOES NOT LIKE DELA,
AND YOU KNOW WHY?
IT'S NONE
OF YOUR FUCKING BUSINESS.
- I'M NOT A MONSTER.
- NUMBER 2.
- I DO FEEL A LITTLE BIT SHAFTED
BY YOU TODAY.
- WHEN?
- I DON'T REMEMBER
THE EXACT COMMENT YOU SAID.
- WHAT DID SHE SAY, LAGANJA?
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT SHE SAID.
- I TRIED
TO FIGURE IT OUT, LIKE,
WHAT IT IS I THOUGHT YOU SAID,
AND I THINK IT WAS JUST, LIKE,
THE FACT THAT, YOU KNOW,
I WAS JUST REALLY EMOTIONAL
AND DISTRAUGHT AND ALREADY DOWN.
- BUT I FELT LIKE AT ONE POINT,
MAYBE EARLIER,
OR MAYBE YESTERDAY,
THAT POSSIBLY THERE WAS
SOMETHING GOING ON
BETWEEN ADORE AND LAGANJA,
BUT I CAN'T REMEMBER,
BUT I'M SORRY.
- NUMBER 1.
- FUCK THESE BITCHES.
ARE YOU IN A WHITESNAKE VIDEO?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OVER THERE?
- SHE MOUTHED OFF
TO EVERY SINGLE PERSON.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHO YOU ARE.
- I WILL SHOW YOU VERSATILITY
WHEN SANTINO
WINS A SEWING COMPETITION
AND VISAGE
WEARS A FUCKING TURTLENECK.
- AND THEN I LOVE THE FACT
THAT SHE THROWS THE TRUTH
BACK IN THEIR FACE.
- I'M MORE OF A BEYONCE MYSELF.
- AT LEAST BEYONCE'S DRESSES
HIT THE FLOOR.
- NOW, LET'S GET
ONE THING STRAIGHT.
BIANCA'S NOT A BITCH,
SHE'S RIGHT.
- WE'RE DRAG QUEENS
IN A FUCKING COMPETITION.
THE ONLY THING WORSE
IS FUCKING PRISON.
- NOW, LIKE TRUE SISTERS,
MY GIRLS ARE ALWAYS THERE
TO LIFT EACH OTHER UP.
LET'S COUNT DOWN THIS SEASON'S
TOP 3 SUPPORT HO'S.
NUMBER 3.
- WHEN EVERYBODY WAS BAGGING
ON MILK FOR HER LOOK,
JOSLYN WAS THE ONLY ONE
TO STICK UP FOR HER.
- YOU'RE IGNORANT.
I'M SORRY, IT'S IGNORANCE.
- OH, IGNORANT NOW.
- YES.
- OKAY, WELL, IGNORANT
WOULD BE ME NOT WANTING
TO BETTER EDUCATE MYSELF.
- WELL, EDUCATE YOURSELF.
- AND THAT'S WHY I'M ASKING HER
WHAT SHE THINKS.
- NO, YOU'RE READING HER.
- OF COURSE,
WHEN A PERSON'S IGNORANT,
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT THAT WORD MEANS.
[LAUGHS]
SO SHE GOT ALL BENT
OUT OF SHAPE,
AND IT WAS THE TRUTH.
- I'M NOT EDUCATED?
YOU LOOK
LIKE A FUCKING RECYCLING BIN.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- NUMBER 2.
YOU ARE BENDELACREME,
AND THAT'S THE CHARACTER
THAT YOU HAVE BUILT,
AND DON'T YOU CHANGE IT
FOR NOBODY.
- WHEN HER SISTERS
WERE FEELING DOWN
AFTER A ROUGH DAY AT THE OFFICE,
IT WAS NICE TO SEE
THAT TRINITY WAS ABLE
TO GO AROUND AND GIVE THEM
A LITTLE PEP TALK, YOU KNOW?
- DO NOT BEAT YOURSELF UP
OR FEEL BAD
BECAUSE COURTNEY,
YOUR COMPETITOR,
TOLD YOU
THAT YOUR LOOK IS NOT POLISHED.
- SHE WAS GIVING THEM A PEP TALK
LIKE SHE WAS A COACH
IN THE SUPER BOWL OR SOMETHING.
- EXACTLY.
- DID BEYONCE PERFORM
AT THE SUPER BOWL?
SHE WASN'T THE COACH, RIGHT?
[LAUGHS]
- NUMBER 1.
- REMEMBER, TRINITY,
YOU KNOW YOU CAN DO THIS.
YOU GOT THIS, BITCH.
- BIANCA HAS A SOFT SIDE,
AND SHE HELPS THE GIRLS.
- I THINK THAT BIANCA IS
ACTUALLY A REALLY NICE PERSON.
I THINK SHE'S PROBABLY
A VERY SENSITIVE PERSON,
I'M IMAGINING.
- I, AND DON'T TELL ANYBODY
THAT I'M BEING KIND,
BUT I HAVE ANOTHER CINCHER
IF YOU WANT ME
TO LACE YOU IN IT.
- I'M DOWN.
- OKAY, WE'LL DO IT.
- SECRETLY, SHE ALLOWED ADORE
TO BORROW ONE OF HER CORSETS
IN FRONT OF 9 CAMERAS.
WAY TO PLAY THE GAME, BITCH.
- COMING UP, LEGENDARY QUEENS
GIVE NEW INSIGHT INTO THE TOP 3.
- FOR SUCH A VICIOUS BITCH,
SHE SHO IS PURTY.
- CALM DOWN, BEYONCE.
- AND THE PIT CREW
SISSY THAT WALK.
- AY, DIOS MIO.
- AS "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE:
COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN"
CONTINUES.
- OKAY?
- [LAUGHS]
WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S DRAG
RACE: COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN."
WITH JUST ONE WEEK
UNTIL WE CROWN
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR,
IT'S ANYBODY'S GAME.
- PREGNANT PAUSE,
PREGNANT PAUSE.
- THE TIME HAS COME
TO SCHOOL THE CHILDREN
ON THE ABCs.
LEARN IT, AND LEARN IT WELL.
- FUCK YEAH, I'M THE FIRST ONE!
- A YOUNG QUEEN BURSTING
WITH RAW TALENT,
AND THE ABILITY TO CHARM
HER WAY OUT OF...ANYTHING?
- BUT I HAD TO WEAR IT,
BECAUSE IT WAS SEE-THROUGH,
AND I WANTED TO SHOW MY BODY.
- [LAUGHTER]
- ADORE HAS BABY JESUS EYES.
SHE JUST...
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT LOVE HER.
- I LOVE ADORE DELANO,
BECAUSE SHE'S LIKE,
"MY DRESS DOESN'T HIT THE FLOOR,
AND I LOOK FUCKING COOL."
- YOU KNOW,
I LOVE THAT SHE'S GOT
A LITTLE BIT
OF MESSINESS TO HER.
I THINK A LITTLE BIT OF DIRT
UNDER THE ACRYLIC FINGERNAILS
IS KIND OF HOT SOMETIMES.
- I'M FUCKING HOOD.
I'M FROM AZUSA.
I'LL STAB A BITCH.
[LAUGHS]
- SHE TAKES THE CRITIQUES,
SHE TRIES TO GROW FROM THEM,
BUT SHE'S STILL LOVING IT.
- SHE HAD A BREAKTHROUGH WITH RU
IN THE WALKTHROUGH.
- I CAME HERE TO BE TOP 3,
AND TO FUCKING WIN IT.
- YOU CAN TASTE
THAT SHE REALLY WANTED IT.
- OOH, GIRL, BITCH BROUGHT IT
FOR THE VIDEO SHOOT.
- HER SISSY
WAS SISSYING MY WALK.
SHE WAS GIVING ME SISSY SPACEK.
- SHE'S EAGER, SHE'S READY,
AND SHE SINGS.
- OH, AND IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE.
- OH, SHIT, SHE'S GOING
TO TAKE MY GIGS. I HATE HER.
- PARTY.
- ADORE MAY HAVE STARTED
WITH A WHIMPER,
BUT SHE ENDED WITH A BIG BANG.
WILL THIS FALLEN IDOL CONTINUE
HER RISE TO THE TIPPITY TOP?
- NOT TODAY, SATAN. NOT TODAY.
- BIANCA DEL RIO WAS
THIS SEASON'S MOUTH THAT ROARED.
- THESE PEOPLE
ARE A BUNCH OF ASSHOLES.
- SHE'S A KILLER COMEDIAN,
A SEASONED QUEEN,
AND A DAMN SEAMSTRESS.
LOVE THAT DRESS.
- YOU CAN BORROW IT.
- THAT DRESS IS GORGEOUS.
- YOU CAN BORROW THIS ONE TOO.
I'LL LEND IT TO YOU, GIRL.
- NOT ONLY CAN SHE CUT
A DRESS PATTERN,
BUT SHE CAN CUT YOU TO FILTH.
- OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M NOT YOUR MAMA.
MY NAME IS BIANCA.
- NOTHING GETS PAST BIANCA,
AND I LOVE THAT.
- AND I GOT TO THINKING
THAT IT WAS A CROCK OF SHIT.
- SHE'S THE BITCH
THAT I AGREE WITH.
- SHE KEEPS IT SO REAL,
AND EVERYTHING
THAT COMES OUT OF HER MOUTH
IS JUST ALL BRILLIANCE
ALL THE TIME.
- SHE'S A MAN WITH ONE EYE.
- AT THE BEAT OF HER EYELASH,
SHE COULD DROP
A FREAKING ONE-LINER.
- WHO'S HELPING YOU OUT?
- WELL,
THEY'RE ALL HELPING ME OUT
BY BEING HORRIBLE
AND MAKING ME LOOK BETTER.
- [LAUGHS]
- I WAS PRETTY FLABBERGASTED
HOW SWEET BIANCA HAS TURNED OUT.
SHE'S ACTUALLY HELPED PEOPLE
DO THEIR MAKE-UP,
CINCHED THEIR BODY,
AND REACHED OUT
IN A TIME OF NEED.
- IF YOU EVER NEED ANYTHING,
CALL A HATEFUL BITCH LIKE ME.
- BUT IS SHE REALLY HELPING?
YOU NEVER KNOW.
THIS IS A COMPETITION, GIRLS.
- COME ON, SHAKE IT OFF.
SHAKE IT OFF, SHAKE IT OFF.
PRETEND IT'S GAS.
JUST LEAVE IT IN THE HALLWAY.
- BIANCA DEL RIO
IS A TAKE-NO-PRISONERS
PROFESSIONAL BITCH
WITH A HEART OF GOLD.
- YOU ALWAYS END
WITH A NASTY COMMENT.
- I ALWAYS BEGIN WITH ONE TOO!
- SHE'S A CUTTHROAT CONTENDER
FOR THE CROWN,
BUT SHE'S NOT ALONE.
- IS THIS "AMERICA'S
NEXT TOP MODEL"?
- ENTER COURTNEY ACT.
- I HONESTLY WANT TO JUST SKIN
YOU ALIVE AND WEAR YOUR BODY.
- A PROVEN SINGER AND SUPERSTAR
FROM THE LAND DOWN UNDER,
COURTNEY ACT CAUGHT
OUR ATTENTION FROM DAY ONE.
- [SQUAWKS]
- [LAUGHS]
- OH, IF PRETTY HURTS,
COURTNEY IS MURDERING US.
- EVERY TIME SHE WALKS DOWN
THE RUNWAY, I'M LIKE,
"WHO LET THAT GIRL IN HERE?
CAN SOMEONE CALL SECURITY?
"THERE'S A YOUNG WOMAN
WALKING AROUND
THE MAIN STAGE."
- SUCH A SHAME ABOUT THAT BODY.
I KNOW SHE WISHES SHE HAD
MY CURVES AND SWERVES, BABY.
- THE ONLY THING WRONG
I WOULD SAY IS, YOU'RE PERFECT.
- WELL, EVERYONE ELSE
IS RELYING ON UGLY.
WHY CAN'T I RELY ON PRETTY?
- [LAUGHTER]
- SHE IS BEAUTIFUL AND TALENTED.
- ♪ I DON'T DRINK
OR EAT OR CUSS ♪
- I HATE THAT.
- JUST WHEN YOU'RE READY
TO HATE COURTNEY,
SHE DOES SOMETHING NICE.
YOU SHADY LITTLE BITCH.
- YOU CAN FIND YOURSELF
A NICE MAN
LOOKING JUST LIKE THAT.
- YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU'RE RIGHT.
- I JUST FEEL LIKE I HAVE
A WEIRDLY PROPORTIONED BODY.
- WELL, MAYBE YOU DO,
AND SO WHAT?
- COURTNEY HAS STAR QUALITY
WRITTEN ALL OVER HER.
- WOULDN'T IT BE SO EXCITING
TO HAVE AN AUSTRALIAN
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR?
- WILL THIS AUSSIE IMPORT
PULL AHEAD
AND LEAVE THESE DOMESTIC MODELS
IN HER DUST?
- COURTNEY DEFINITELY
HAS WHAT IT TAKES
TO BE AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG
SUPERSTAR, BUT I--
- BIANCA SHOULD WIN.
- I LIKE ADORE DELANO,
BECAUSE SHE'S 22, AND SHE'S--
- SILENCE.
I HAVE NOT MADE MY DECISION.
SO WHOSE TEAM
ARE YOU PLAYING FOR?
TEAM ADORE DELANO,
TEAM BIANCA DEL RIO,
OR TEAM COURTNEY ACT?
HASHTAG IT AND TELL THE WORLD
WHO YOU THINK SHOULD BE CROWNED
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
- COULD WE JUST
CROWN THIS BITCH ALREADY?
- UP NEXT,
MY GIRLS GO BLINDLY
WHERE NO QUEENS
HAVE GONE BEFORE.
- OKAY.
- PLUS, THE WORLD VIDEO PREMIERE
OF "SISSY THAT WALK"
WHEN "RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE:
COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN"
CONTINUES.
[LAUGHS]
WELCOME BACK TO "RUPAUL'S DRAG
RACE: COUNTDOWN TO THE CROWN."
ADORE DELANO, BIANCA DEL RIO,
COURTNEY ACT,
WHO DO YOU THINK
HAS THE BIGGEST CHARISMA,
UNIQUENESS, NERVE, AND TALENT?
STARTING NOW,
YOU'VE GOT ONE WEEK
TO LET ME AND THE WORLD KNOW.
RIGHT, GIRLS?
- YES, GOD.
- ABSOLUTELY.
- DON'T WEAR BACON.
- THIS SEASON,
I'VE BEEN CRITICIZED
FOR PROMOTING
TOO MANY OF MY PRODUCTS,
SO, TONIGHT
I WILL NOT BE PLUGGING
MY NUMBER ONE ALBUM
"BORN NAKED."
I WILL MAKE NO MENTION
OF MY SIGNATURE FRAGRANCE
RUPAUL'S GLAMAZON.
AND MY FINAL VOW, YOU WILL NOT
HEAR A PEEP OUT OF ME
ABOUT THE NEW RUPAUL CANDY BAR.
NOT A PEEP. I WON'T MENTION IT,
EVEN THOUGH IT IS MADE
WITH DELICIOUS MILK CHOCOLATE,
SEA SALT, AND...
♪ PEANUT, PEANUT, PEANUT ♪
♪ PEANUT, PEANUT,
P-P-P-P-PEANUT ♪
♪ PEANUT PEANUT-- ♪
♪ LET ME FEED Y'ALL! ♪
♪ PEANUT, PEANUT
PEANUT, PEANUT ♪
- OH!
- ALL RIGHT.
- OH, MY GOD.
- [LAUGHS]
THAT SHIT IS GOOD.
AND NOW, THE WORLD PREMIERE
OF THE OFFICIAL VIDEO
FOR "SISSY THAT WALK."
AND NEXT WEEK,
JOIN ME AND ALL MY GIRLS
FOR
"RUPAUL'S DRAG RACE REUNITED."
- OKAY.
- NOW, REMEMBER,
IF YOU CAN'T LOVE YOURSELF,
HOW IN THE HELL
YOU GON' LOVE SOMEBODY ELSE?
CAN I GET A CHOCOLATE BAR
UP IN HERE?
- AMEN.
- HALLELOO.
- LET THE MUSIC VIDEO PLAY.
♪ PICK MYSELF UP ♪
♪ TURN THE WORLD ON ITS HEAD ♪
♪ DON'T FORGET WHAT ♪
♪ DON'T FORGET
WHAT MY MAMA SAID ♪
♪ PEOPLE TALKING ♪
♪ SINCE THE BEGINNING OF TIME ♪
♪ UNLESS
THEY PAYING YOUR BILLS ♪
♪ PAY THEM BITCHES NO MIND ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY
OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ LEAST I CAN SAY
I GAVE IT ALL ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY
OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ I'M ON MY WAY
I'M ON MY WAY ♪
♪ FLY FLY FLY FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH OH UH-OH ♪
♪ FLY FLY FLY FLY
UH-OH ♪
♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
♪ BETTER BEWARE
AIN'T NO T ♪
♪ AIN'T NO SHADE
BUT AT THE SAME TIME ♪
♪ BITCHES BETTER
GET OUT THE WAY ♪
♪ I'M A FEMME QUEEN ♪
♪ MOTHER OF THE HOUSE
OF NO SHAME ♪
♪ MY...IS ON FIRE ♪
♪ NOW KISS THE FLAME ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY
OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ LEAST I CAN SAY ♪
♪ I GAVE IT ALL ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY
OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ I'M ON MY WAY
I'M ON MY WAY ♪
♪ FLY FLY FLY FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH OH UH-OH ♪
♪ FLY FLY FLY FLY
UH-OH ♪
♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY
OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ AT LEAST I CAN SAY
I GAVE IT ALL ♪
♪ AND IF I FLY
OR IF I FALL ♪
♪ I'M ON MY WAY
I'M ON MY WAY ♪
♪ FLY FLY FLY FLY ♪
♪ UH-OH OH UH-OH ♪
♪ FLY FLY FLY FLY
UH-OH ♪
♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
- COME ON, NATCH.