- PREVIOUSLY ON
"RU PAUL'S DRAG RACE..."
- BITCH!
- LAGANJA AND I ARE
THE BEST OF FRIENDS,
BUT WHEN WE DO COMPETE,
THAT CAN GET UGLY.
- IT'S TIME TO PLAY
"SNATCH GAME."
- I DON'T DO
IMPERSONATIONS.
- KIMMY.
- HA HA HA!
- WE ORIGINATED THE LANGUAGE.
- BALONEY!
- HOW'S THE BABY?
- OH, YOU KNOW, I'M STILL, LIKE,
HAVING SOME MORNING AFTER...
IS THAT...YES, YOU KNOW,
LIKE THROWING UP AND STUFF
AFTER THE PREGNANCY.
- BEN DE LA CREME, YOU'RE
THE WINNER OF THIS CHALLENGE.
LAGANJA ESTRANJA,
SHANTE YOU STAY.
G-G-G-GIA,
SASHAY AWAY.
- WHOO!
- CONGRATULATIONS,
LAGANJA.
- I AM SO GRATEFUL THAT I AM
STILL IN THIS COMPETITION.
- YES, GIRL, YOU MADE IT.
- YOU LIVE ANOTHER DAY.
- BUT IN THE OUTSIDE WORLD,
I'M USED TO WINNING.
SO IN THIS COMPETITION,
IT'S REALLY HARD TO SEE ALL
MY FRIENDS GET A LOT OF PRAISE,
ESPECIALLY ADORE,
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK HER LOOK
IS AS STRONG AS MINE,
AND IT'S REALLY STARTING
TO GET TO ME.
- LAGANJA IS AN EXTREMELY
EMOTIONAL PERSON,
AND THAT'S GOING TO PLAY A TOLL
ON HER IN THE COMPETITION.
I THINK SHE'S JUST GOING TO
HAVE TO GET OUT OF HER FEELINGS
JUST AS MUCH
AS I DO, TOO.
- UM...WELL, MOST OF THE GIRLS--
I HAD ALREADY SHARED THIS
IN "UNTUCKED."
BUT I WANT TO TAKE
THE TIME OUT TO TELL EVERYBODY
AUGUST OF 2012, I WAS
DIAGNOSED WITH H.I.V.
I WANTED TO SHARE THAT
WITH EVERYBODY IN HERE
BECAUSE I WANTED TO BE
AN ADVOCATE FOR PEOPLE
IN THIS PARTICULAR COMMUNITY
WHO ARE SUFFERING WITH THIS
AND THEY'RE SCARED
TO SAY SOMETHING.
AND I NEED PEOPLE TO KNOW
THAT IT'S OK.
- I THINK ALL OF US THINK
THAT IS SO NOBLE AND COURAGEOUS.
[CLAPPING]
WE'RE PROUD OF YOU, GIRL.
- I THINK IT'S A HUGE STEP
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION
FOR TRINITY
TO SPEAK HER MIND.
I WAS REALLY, REALLY
IMPRESSED WITH THAT.
I THINK THAT'S
REALLY COMMENDABLE.
I THINK IT'S AMAZING.
GOOD JOB.
- ON A LIGHTER NOTE,
CONGRATULATIONS, MISS DE LA!
- THANK YOU.
- DID ANY OF THE ORIGINAL SIX
WIN TWO CHALLENGES?
- I WON A CHALLENGE.
YOU WON A CHALLENGE.
- I WON THE FIRST
CHALLENGE, TOO.
- OH, YOU DID? OH.
- I DID.
- I WASN'T THERE.
YEAH, IT DOESN'T COUNT.
I THINK IT'S BETTER
NOT TO STRUT AROUND
AND BE LIKE A PEACOCK
WHEN YOU WIN.
YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU'RE NOT
TOO IN LOVE WITH YOURSELF.
BEN DE LA CREME.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT'S ABOUT.
- I'VE GOT
TO SEND HER HOME.
- THE WINNER OF
"RU PAUL'S DRAG RACE"
RECEIVES A SICKENING SUPPLY
OF COLOREVOLUTION COSMETICS
AND A CASH PRIZE
OF $100,000,
WITH EXTRA-SPECIAL
GUEST JUDGES--
THE DIAMOND PRINCESS TRINA
AND THE E-V-E, EVE.
- ♪ "RU PAUL'S DRAG RACE" ♪
♪ MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
♪ BEST WOMAN WIN ♪
- GOOD MORNING.
- MORNING.
- SO IT'S A NEW DAY,
AND WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S TO COME.
I'M FEELING GREAT
IN THE COMPETITION SO FAR.
SO I KNOW SOMETHING AROUND
THE CORNER IS GONNA FUCK ME UP.
- SO, WHAT ARE
PEOPLE THINKING?
- MAYBE IT WILL BE
AN INDIVIDUAL CHALLENGE.
- I THINK WE'RE ALL COOL WITH
INDIVIDUAL CHALLENGE, RIGHT?
- I COMPLETELY AM.
I'M NOT A GROUP PERSON.
I'M MORE OF A BEYONCE MYSELF.
- AT LEAST BEYONCE'S DRESSES
HIT THE FLOOR.
- WHOO!
- SO DO YOUR TITS!
- OOH!
- GIRL, YOU GOT SHE-MAIL.
YO, FLY GIRLS, AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR
NEEDS TO GET
HER FREAK ON,
SHAKE WHAT HER MAMA
GAVE HER,
AND THEN DROP IT
LIKE IT'S HOT.
YOU DOWN WITH O.P.P.?
- YOU KNOW ME!
- HEY, LATIFA,
PAGE ME, GIRL.
- YAY! I'M READY.
- HELLO, HELLO, HELLO.
- HELLO.
- ALL RIGHT.
- LADIES, TODAY'S MINI CHALLENGE
IS SPONSORED BY...
THE LETTER "T,"
AS IN ALL "T,"
ALL SHADE, HUNTIES.
IN THE GREAT TRADITION
OF "PARIS IS BURNING..."
THE LIBRARY IS OPEN!
[CHEERING]
- BECAUSE READING IS WHAT?
- FUNDAMENTAL.
- THERE YOU HAVE IT,
DARLING.
FIRST UP,
BIANCA DEL RIO.
THE LIBRARY
IS NOW OPEN.
- HA HA HA!
- MISS BEN DE LA CREME,
AFTER SEEING YOU IN DRAG,
I REALIZE NOW WHY SEATTLE HAS
A HIGH SUICIDE RATE.
- HA HA HA!
- OH, MY GOD.
- JOSLYN FOX, SHE'S SO GAY,
EVEN HER ASSHOLE HAS A LISP.
THEN WE HAVE ADORE.
I KNOW WHAT YOU GOT
ON YOUR S.A.T.'s.
KETCHUP.
[LAUGHTER]
- TRINITY, I BELIEVE YOUR SMILE
BELONGS ON SEASON 4.
EVERY DAY IS SHARK WEEK
WITH YOUR GRILL.
MISS LAGANJA ESTRANJA,
NEXT TIME YOU DEATH DROP,
REVERSE THAT AND DROP DEAD.
[LAUGHTER]
- DARIENNE LAKE,
I WEIGH, LIKE, 110,
AND I'M REALLY
SCARED OF YOU,
SO I'M JUST GONNA
KEEP IT AT THAT.
- YOU BETTER.
- AND I'M SURE YOU ALL
WILL REMIND ME
THAT MY HAIR IS SO FRIED
AND DAMAGED
THAT I'M FORCED TO WEAR
THIS CLIP-ON PONYTAIL.
IF YOU CAN'T READ YOURSELF,
HOW THE HELL CAN YOU
READ SOMEBODY ELSE? THANK YOU.
- JOSLYN FOX, YOU MAY NOT
BE ALL THAT SMART,
AND YOU MAY NOT BE
ALL THAT PRETTY...
- HA HA HA!
- I GUESS THAT'S IT.
- MISS DARIENNE LAKE,
YOU SHOULD BE ARRESTED
FOR ANIMAL CRUELTY.
THE WAY YOU ABUSE THOSE
KITTEN HEELS ON THE RUNWAY
IS ABSOLUTELY CRIMINAL!
- BEN DE LA CREME,
THE CREAM ALWAYS
RISES TO THE TOP,
BUT THEN AGAIN,
SO DOES THE SCUM.
[LAUGHTER AND JEERING]
MISS JOSLYN FOX,
WHEN WE NEED
A LOW-RENT VERSION OF COURTNEY
ACT, WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
[LAUGHTER]
- ADORE, YOU KNOW YOU'RE
FROM THE WEST COAST
BECAUSE IT'S A 3-HOUR DELAY
BEFORE YOU FINALLY GET A JOKE.
- HA HA HA!
- DARIENNE LAKE--
THIS IS THE GIRL
WHO PROBABLY SITS
REVERSE COWGIRL
ON THE TOILET
JUST SO SHE HAS A FLAT
SURFACE TO EAT OFF OF.
- OOH!
- JOSLYN, YOU HAVE
SOME REALLY COMFORTING
OLD-FASHIONED QUALITIES,
LIKE HOW YOU PAINT
IN SEPIA TONES
AND YOUR VOICE SOUNDS
LIKE A DIAL-UP MODEM.
[DIAL-UP MODEM SOUNDS]
MISS DARIENNE LAKE,
YOU HAVE A LOT OF JOKES,
BUT TO ME THEY'RE
MORE LIKE UFO's--
I MEAN, THEY ARE
WAY OUT THERE,
AND I'VE NEVER
SEEN ONE LAND.
- HA HA HA!
- A-BORE DE-LAME-O, IS THAT
A HOG ON YOUR BODY,
OR ARE YOU
EXCITED TO SEE ME?
- HA HA HA.
- BIANCA DEL TACO TRIO,
YOUR STYLE IS AS OLD
AND BITTER AS YOU.
YOU'VE EVEN GOT THE CRYPT-KEEPER
CRYING, "WHOO-HOO-HOO."
- THANK YOU, DR. SEUSS.
- MILK, YOUR BEAUTY
AND FASHION
IS LISTED RIGHT ON THE SIDE
OF YOUR CARTON,
UNDER "MISSING."
[LAUGHTER]
BEN DE LA CREME,
YOU REMIND ME
OF A RUSSIAN DOLL--
FULL OF YOURSELF.
[LAUGHTER]
- ADORE DELANO,
I'M GOING TO SAY THIS
VERY SLOWLY
SO YOU CAN UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE DUMB.
[LOUD LAUGHTER]
- ALL RIGHT, THE LIBRARY
IS REALLY CLOSED OFFICIALLY.
[NO AUDIO]
THE WINNER IS...
DARIENNE LAKE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SHADY BITCH.
OK, LADIES.
IT'S TIME TO PROVE YOU'RE SOME
HARDCORE O.G.'s.
YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING?
ORIGINAL GLAMAZONS.
FOR THIS WEEK'S
MAIN CHALLENGE,
YOU'RE GONNA FACE OFF
IN A NINETIES-STYLE
RAP BATTLE ROYALE.
Y'ALL NEED TO WRITE
AND PERFORM YOUR OWN RAP
TO A TRACK PRODUCED
BY DJ SHYBOY
CALLED "OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T!"
DARIENNE LAKE, SINCE YOU WON
THE MINI CHALLENGE,
YOU CHOOSE THE 4 M.C. QUEENS
YOU WANT ON YOUR CREW.
- LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
WHO'S GOT A FAST MOUTH?
BIANCA DEL RIO.
- HA HA HA!
- AND I MEAN, I WOULD BE STUPID
NOT TO PICK TWO OF MY IDOLS--
ADORE DELANO
AND COURTNEY ACT.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT DARIENNE
ISN'T CHOOSING ME.
IT'S A LITTLE BIT
OF A SLAP IN THE FACE
TO NOT BE CHOSEN WITH THE REST
OF THOSE GIRLS.
- AND THAT MEANS
THE OTHER CREW
IS MILK, BEN DE LA CREME, JOSLYN
FOX, AND TRINITY K. BONET.
GENTLEMEN,
START YOUR ENGINES,
AND DON'T GET CAUGHT SLEEPING
ON YOUR CHARISMA,
UNIQUENESS, NERVE, AND TALENT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
- ♪ LEFT, RIGHT, BOOM, BOOM,
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM ♪
THIS IS THE CHALLENGE
THAT I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
AND THEN WE DO THIS
TO SWITCH LINES... ♪ BOOM BOOM ♪
I LOVE TO RAP,
AND I'M A PROFESSIONAL
CHOREOGRAPHER.
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T,
LEFT, RIGHT ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
- WHY ARE WE ALL
DOING THIS SHIT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE FUCK THAT MEANS.
NINETIES RAP IS REALLY
ABOUT THE FEEL.
♪ YEAH, MOTHERFUCKER, YEAH ♪
IT'S VERY THAT.
IT'S NOT LIKE...
[HUMMING] FUCKIN'...
- ♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
- I HATE THIS.
I DON'T REALLY WANT TO LOOK
LIKE 'N SYNC, BITCH.
I WANT TO LOOK LIKE
SALT-N-PEPA.
- COMING UP...
- SO, DARIENNE,
WHY DIDN'T YOU CHOOSE ME?
- OOH!
- I'M A WHITE LADY
FROM THE SUBURBS.
SO WHEN IT COMES
TO STREET CRED...
♪ BIG GIRL WALKING
DOWN THIS DIRTY STREET ♪
♪ WALKING DOWN IN...
OH, THE DIRTY FEET ♪
JEEZ. FUCK!
- OK.
[RU PAUL LAUGHING]
- ♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
- ♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
- OUR MAIN CHALLENGE
IS A RAP BATTLE,
LIKE WE'RE FLY GIRLS
IN THE NINETIES.
WE'VE GOT TO COME UP
WITH COSTUMING,
LYRICS, AND CHOREOGRAPH
A WHOLE HIP-HOP DANCE.
LET'S JUST SEE
WHERE WE'RE ALL AT,
AND THEN WE CAN SEE WHERE
WE NEED TO GO FROM THAT.
- DO YOU WANT TO START?
- ♪ JUST TAKE--AH.
♪ JUST TAKE A SECOND,
LET ME SHOW YOU HOW I FLOW ♪
♪ RHINESTONES AND BIG HAIR
AND GOWNS TO THE FLOOR ♪
- I DO THINK THAT THIS IS
A PRIME OPPORTUNITY
FOR YOU TO PRACTICE
YOUR ENUNCIATION.
- FUCK THAT. YOU DON'T
TELL ME ABOUT ENUNCIATING.
YOU UNENUNCIATE. SHIT.
THIS IS HOW I TALK.
- JUST REALLY MAKE SURE YOU,
LIKE, REALLY, LIKE,
WRAP YOUR MOUTH AROUND
ALL THOSE VOWELS
AND ALL THE CONSONANTS
INDIVIDUALLY.
- THIS IS RAP.
YOU AIN'T SUPPOSED TO USE
NO SYLLABLES, NO VOWELS.
IT'S JUST ALL
STREET SLANG.
- I'M SO EXCITED
ABOUT THAT.
THIS IS ACTUALLY A REALLY FUN
CHALLENGE FOR ME,
BECAUSE I SPIT ILL SHIT
ON A FUCKING DAILY.
♪ MEN TURN AROUND,
PANTS COMING DOWN ♪
♪ GO HOME, HOS,
WHERE MY GODDAMN CROWN? ♪
- THAT'S GOOD.
- I'M FUCKING HOOD.
I'M FROM AZUSA.
I'LL STAB A BITCH.
HA HA HA!
- UM...I NEED HELP.
- I'M A WHITE LADY
FROM THE SUBURBS.
SO WHEN IT COMES
TO STREET CRED...
- YOU JUST NEED
ANOTHER WORD IN THERE.
- THAT'S WHY I PICKED YOU GUYS
TO BE ON MY TEAM,
BECAUSE YOU'RE RAP PEOPLE.
- JUST BECAUSE DARIENNE
HAS PICKED
THE STRONGEST GIRLS
FOR HER TEAM
DOESN'T MEAN THAT SHE'S
GOING TO BE SAFE.
- LET'S WORK ON
THE GROUP CHOREOGRAPHY.
- I'M A DANCER, SO NOW I'M GONNA
HAVE TO SHOW THESE HOS
WHAT IT IS THAT I DO.
SO, YOUR MOTION
WOULD BE...
UP, SLIDE, PULL.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LOOK SO...
LIKE YOU'RE THROWING IT.
YOU JUST WANT IT TO BE
KIND OF LIKE...
- OK. YOU HAVE TO
BREAK THIS DOWN
SO BABY-STEPS FOR ME.
YOU HEAR THE PHRASE, YOU KNOW,
THAT THEY HAVE TWO LEFT FEET.
♪ PULL, BOOM, BOOM ♪
THERE YOU GO.
BUT SOME OF MY GIRLS
AIN'T GOT NO FEET.
[CLANGING]
- OOH!
- HA HA!
- YO, YO, YO!
- HI!
- HOW ARE MY HIP-HOP
DRAG QUEENS DOING?
- MAKIN' DAT MONEY.
- WORD.
- NOW HERE'S THE 411.
TO HELP YOU WITH YOUR FLOW,
IN A MOMENT,
YOU'LL MEET WITH TWO OF THE
HOTTEST RAPPERS IN THE GAME--
THE BADDEST BITCH TRINA...
[GASPING]
- OH, MY GOD!
- AND THE PIT BULL
IN A SKIRT,
THE E-V-E, EVE IS HERE.
[CHEERING]
SO GOOD LUCK,
AND DON'T...
WICKY-WICKY-WICKY-WICKY...
FUCK IT UP. OK?
- THANK YOU, MAMA RU.
- SO DARIENNE, HOW DID YOU
CHOOSE YOUR GROUP?
- HOW DID I CHOOSE MY GROUP?
- YEAH.
- THAT SOUNDED REALLY SHADY.
- RIGHT?
- WHAT WAS IT, DARIENNE? WHY
DON'T YOU ENLIGHTEN THIS BITCH?
- I REALLY WAS...I MEAN--
- NO, YOU WEREN'T.
I CAUGHT IT.
- I'LL BE DIRECT
ABOUT IT.
DARIENNE, WHY
DIDN'T YOU CHOOSE ME?
- AND I'LL BE
COMPLETELY HONEST.
IT'S NONE OF YOUR
FUCKING BUSINESS.
- OOH!
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO DEAL
WITH THIS RIGHT NOW.
WHEN I THINK
NINETIES RAP GIRL,
MY FIRST THOUGHT ISN'T
TO GO TO DE LA.
- I WAS NOT ACTUALLY
TRYING TO BE SHADY,
AND I CAME OFF THAT WAY MAYBE
BECAUSE MY FEELINGS WERE HURT.
- SUCK IT UP, BUTTERCUP.
- ♪ THIS, THIS IS A JAM ♪
- COME ON, PANTY HOS.
- OK.
- WE WALK IN, AND I SEE
THE SCRUFF PIT CREW,
EVE, AND TRINA.
IT'S LIKE WALKING IN TO PLAY
CHESS WITH BOBBY FISCHER.
YEAH, YOU'RE GONNA SHIT
YOUR PANTS A LITTLE BIT.
- WELCOME, PANTY HOS.
- YES.
- HI.
- IT'S TIME
FOR THE SOLOS.
BIANCA DEL RIO.
- ROLL TRACK.
♪ MY NAME IS BIANCA,
I'M FROM THE DEEP SOUTH ♪
♪ OH, THEM BITCHES CAN'T HANDLE
MY SASSY-ASS MOUTH ♪
YOU LIKE THAT?
I MADE THAT SHIT UP TODAY.
- HA HA HA!
NOW IT'S TIME
FOR YOUR WIDE.
SO GIVE IT TO US
WIDE AND SASSY.
- WIDE AND SASSY.
THAT WAS MY NAME IN PRISON.
[LAUGHTER]
- BIANCA IS DOING
AMAZING.
SHE'S FUCKING HILARIOUS.
SHE'S EVERYTHING I WANT TO BE
WHEN I'M 57.
HA HA HA!
SHE'S GONNA KILL ME.
- WHO'S UP NEXT?
- HI. I'M ADORE.
- HI!
- HI, ADORE.
- UH-OH. HA HA HA!
- SHE'S NOT FULLY TUCKED.
SHH! PARTY.
♪ MY NAME'S D-D-DOLL ♪
♪ AIN'T NO NEED
TO TRY TO FORCE IT ♪
DID I DO IT WRONG?
OK. SORRY.
- NO. ALL GOOD. ONE MORE TIME.
- I THINK YOU WERE TOO EARLY.
- ♪ MY NAME'S D-D-DOLL ♪
♪ AIN'T NO NEED
TO TRY TO FORCE IT ♪
[STAMMERING]
♪ ...BAD CORSET ♪
- CUT.
- OOH. FUCK.
- I LIKE THAT YOU
KEPT GOING.
YOU GET ONE MORE CHANCE, AND
THEN THAT'S THE ONE THAT'S IT.
♪ MEN TURN AROUND,
PANTS COMING DOWN ♪
♪ GO HOME, HOS,
WHERE MY "DRAG RACE" CROWN? ♪
- ♪ UH-OH, UH-OH,
AH, AH, AH, AH ♪
GOOD. WHO'S NEXT?
- ♪ LAGANJA'S ON THE TRACK ♪
♪ AND I'M BUSTIN'
THROUGH THE DOOR ♪
♪ I ALREADY FUCKED IT UP,
BUT I COME FOR SOME MORE ♪
I FUCKED IT UP.
- YOU GOT TO GET
THE LYRICS RIGHT.
- SORRY. ONE SECOND.
- OH! GIRL!
[MUTTERING LYRICS]
SHIT!
I CAN'T REMEMBER IT.
♪ LAGANJA'S ON THE TRACK,
AND I'M... ♪
FUCK! FUCK, FUCK, FUCK.
- IF YOU FORGOT THE LYRICS,
JUST CALM YOURSELF.
IT'LL COME BACK TO YOU.
- YEAH.
- I GOT IT.
- BAM.
- THANK YOU, JESUS.
- ALL RIGHT. CUE THE TRACK.
- ♪ PANTY HOS
AND CONTROL-TOP D ♪
♪ SERVIN' YOU BODY,
I KNOW YOU'RE LIVING FOR ME ♪
- FOR LAGANJA TO BE
A RAPSTRESS,
SHE KIND OF FELT
LIKE A LITTLE WHITE GIRL.
- OH, PLEASE.
- NEXT, M.C. CONTROL TOP.
[CRASH]
- OOH!
- UH-OH.
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ARE YOU OK?
- YEAH, I'M GOOD.
I FEEL SO TENSE
IN THIS SITUATION,
BECAUSE IT'S SO OUT
OF MY COMFORT ZONE.
- CUE TRACK.
- ♪ BIG GIRL WALKING
DOWN THIS DIRTY STREET ♪
♪ WALKING DOWN IN...
ALL THESE DIRTY FEET ♪
[MUTTERING LYRICS]
FUCK! I'M SORRY.
- CUT. CUT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- WELL, FUCK
BEGINNER'S LUCK.
- I THINK YOU'RE
THINKING TOO HARD
ABOUT THE PERFORMANCE
OF THE SONG.
JUST GIVE IT
ANOTHER SHOT.
- ♪ KEEP YOUR SHOES ON, HONEY,
AND MAKE THAT MONEY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE A...'CAUSE A...
FEET AND AIN'T FUNNY ♪
- CUT. CUT.
- FUCK ME.
- DARIENNE'S IN TROUBLE,
AND I'M WORRIED.
THAT COULD FUCK UP
OUR WHOLE TEAM.
SHE'S OVERTHINKING,
AND SHE'S...
SHE'S THINKING
ABOUT A SANDWICH.
- COMING UP...
- IT'S TIME FOR THE RU-TANG
CLAN TO TAKE THE STAGE.
CREMINEM IS IN THE HIZZY
FO' SHIZ, BOY!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- OH, SORRY.
THAT WAS MY CUE.
- YEAH, THAT WAS YOUR CUE.
[RU PAUL LAUGHING]
- WHAT UP, DAWGS?
- WHAT UP?
- HI.
- IT'S TIME FOR THE RU-TANG CLAN
TO TAKE THE STAGE
FOR OUR RAP BATTLE,
AND WE ARE PUMPED,
WE ARE LOOKING FLY,
AND WE ARE GOING TO GIVE IT.
- CREMINEM, GIVE IT TO US.
CUE THE TRACK.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- OH, SORRY. THAT WAS MY CUE.
WAS THAT MY CUE?
- YEAH, THAT WAS YOUR CUE.
- IT'S THAT LITTLE EFFECT?
I'M SORRY.
♪ WELL, IT'S DE LA TO THE CREME,
I'M THE FATAL FEMME ♪
♪ BUT I GOT...
SO THEY CALL ME CREMINEM ♪
♪ I BACK UP 4 OR 5 LADIES
WHO ARE GONNA COME YOUR-- ♪
BBBBLLLL!
THIS NEXT ONE
IS GONNA BE AMAZING.
- WHAT LANGUAGE
WAS THAT?
- I MIGHT NOT BE THE BEST
RAPPER IN THE WORLD,
BUT CREMINEM IS IN THE HIZZY
FO' SHIZ, BOY!
- OK, MILK, IT IS
YOUR TURN UP NEXT.
- ♪ NEVER BEEN AN IN GIRL
SINCE SHE CAME OUT ♪
♪ MILK SHUDDERS IN HER UDDERS
AT YOUR PLAYED-OUT ROUTE ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A DUDE
OR IN PREGGERS IN A MOOD-- ♪
- CUT.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING
AT THAT PART?
- IF YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR A DUDE
OR YOU'RE IN
THE PREGGERS MOOD.
- OK. LET'S DO
YOUR WIDE SHOT.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHING]
- I DON'T CARE IF THIS
IS NINETIES HIP-HOP.
IT'S PROBABLY NOT,
BUT I AM JUST GETTING
DOWN AND DIRTY.
- OK.
- I JUST HOPE THAT EVE AND TRINA
ARE LAUGHING WITH HER
AND NOT AT HER.
- OK. CUT. CUT.
WE GOT IT.
WE GOT ENOUGH.
WE'RE GONNA MOVE ON NOW.
MCTKB.
- NOW, IF I FUCK UP,
IT'S BECAUSE THIS IS NOT
MY, YOU KNOW, MY FORTE.
AND I MAY GET MY INTRO
WRONG THE FIRST TIME.
LET ME LISTEN.
- A DISCLAIMER, GIRL?
AH...
- JUST GIVE IT TO US.
- OK. ROLL TRACK.
- ♪ CHECK IT, JUST TAKE A SECOND
TO SEE HOW THIS GOES ♪
♪ RHINESTONES-- ♪ UCK!
- UH-OH.
♪ CHECK IT, JUST TAKE A SECOND
TO SEE HOW THIS GOES ♪
♪ RHINESTONES,
NICE GOWNS...FLOW ♪
- MM-HMM.
♪ RHINESTONES, NICE GOWNS
INTO THE FLOOR ♪
FUCK!
I CANNOT FUCK THIS UP,
BUT I'M FUCKING IT UP, SO...
- TAKE A BREATH.
THINK ABOUT IT.
- EXHALE.
- YEAH.
- ♪ CHECK IT,
TAKE A SECOND-- ♪
- GO AHEAD.
- I JUST THINK TRINITY
NEEDS TO JUST BE
A LOT MORE CONFIDENT.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- SHE KIND OF PSYCHED HERSELF
OUT BEFORE SHE STARTED.
- IT'S OK.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
- I'M FEELING FOR TRINITY
BECAUSE SHE REALLY WANTS
TO DO REALLY WELL, BUT...
- ♪ LET'S TAKE A SECOND
TO SEE HOW THIS GOES ♪
[DING]
- I HONESTLY HAD NO IDEA
WHAT SHE WAS TALKING ABOUT.
- FUCK!
- YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
WHAT'S UP?
- HI!
- COME ON, LADY RAPPERS.
- TODAY'S RUNWAY LOOK
IS CRAZY SEXY FOOL.
- LET'S DO THIS, MAMAS.
- WHEN ALL ELSE FAILS,
YOU JUST HAVE TO KEEP IT FOXY.
WAH WAH!
- SO, MILK, YOU'RE GONNA
GIVE US GLAMOUR?
- UM...GLAMOUR. YEAH.
- SPOOK-HOUSE GLAMOUR
OR REAL GLAMOUR?
- UM...
- "UM" IS NOT AN ANSWER, SIR!
- LOVE IT.
- I THINK MILK
COULD PULL IT OFF,
BUT AS YOU CAN TELL BY THE WAY
MY VOICE IS GOING REALLY HIGH,
I COULD BE LYING.
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING,
MISS TRINITY?
- I'M GREAT.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- YOU KNOW THAT I DON'T GET
VERY SERIOUS OR VERY NICE
ABOUT MANY THINGS.
I JUST WANTED
TO SAY TO YOU
THAT I'M VERY PROUD OF YOU FOR
PUTTING YOUR STORY OUT THERE.
- AS SOON AS TRINITY
DISCUSSED HER STATUS,
IT ALL MADE SENSE TO ME
AS TO WHY SHE WAS BEING
SUCH AN INTROVERT
AND ANTISOCIAL, BECAUSE
I'D BEEN THROUGH IT
WITH SOMEONE ELSE
BEFORE.
I HAD A FRIEND OF MINE.
FOR A WHILE,
WHEN I MOVED TO NEW YORK,
I DIDN'T GET TO SPEAK TO HIM,
DIDN'T HEAR FROM HIM,
AND I HAD NO IDEA
WHAT REALLY WAS HAPPENING.
AND I HAD FOUND OUT
THROUGH EVERYONE ELSE
THAT HE WAS HIV-POSITIVE,
AND HE DIDN'T FEEL THE NEED
TO DISCUSS IT WITH ANYONE
BECAUSE HE WAS
SO FULL OF SHAME.
SO THE STIGMA WITH THIS ISSUE
AND THIS SICKNESS...
AND IT WAS JUST FAR TOO MUCH
FOR HIM TO HANDLE.
I HAD FOUND OUT
THAT HE HAD PASSED AWAY.
- WHEN I FOUND OUT, LIKE,
IT WASN'T A SENSE
OF "OH, MY GOD,
MY LIFE IS OVER."
LIKE, THE FIRST THING WAS,
"HOW DO WE FIX IT?"
I JUST KNEW THAT THERE WAS
SO MUCH IN LIFE
THAT I WANTED TO ACHIEVE
AND THAT I WASN'T GONNA ALLOW
H.I.V. TO GET
IN THE WAY.
- I REALLY DO ADMIRE TRINITY
FOR BEING OPEN AND HONEST
AND TAKING CARE OF HERSELF
THE WAY SHE DOES,
BECAUSE IF MY FRIEND
HAD DONE THE SAME,
I THINK THINGS WOULD HAVE
TURNED OUT DIFFERENTLY.
I THINK WHAT YOU'VE DONE
IS AN AMAZING THING,
AND IF YOU EVER NEED ANYTHING,
CALL A HATEFUL BITCH LIKE ME,
EVEN IF IT'S FOR A LAUGH.
- BIANCA'S SECRETLY ADORABLE
IN A CERTAIN WAY,
LIKE SHE'S THE TYPE
OF PERSON
WHERE YOU, LIKE,
WANT TO HUG HER,
AND SHE'S JUST LIKE,
"UH, GET AWAY."
LIKE, IT'S VERY THAT,
BUT SHE LOVES YOU.
- ♪ COVER GIRL,
PUT THE BASS IN YOUR WALK ♪
♪ HEAD TO TOE,
LET YOUR WHOLE BODY TALK ♪
AND WHAT?
WHOO! WELCOME
TO THE MAIN STAGE
OF "RU PAUL'S DRAG RACE."
MY HOMEGIRL, MICHELLE
"MISDEMEANOR" VISAGE.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- LET ME BLOW
YOUR MIND, BOO.
AND DA BRAT, SANTINO RICE.
WHAT UP, G?
- LET THE RHYTHM
HIT 'EM, RU.
- HA HA HA!
- AND TRINA. ARE MY GIRLS
THE BADDEST BITCHES?
- YES, THEY SURE ARE.
- WELL, YOU WOULD KNOW.
- AND EVE. HEY, GIRL, HOW WAS IT
WORKING WITH MY QUEENS?
- AMAZING. AND YOU
LOOK AMAZING.
- OH, I BET YOU SAY THAT
TO ALL THE DRAG QUEENS.
THIS WEEK,
WE CHALLENGED OUR QUEENS
TO BECOME NINETIES RAPPERS,
AND NOW THEY'RE
READY TO SHOW OFF
THEIR FAVORITE BODY PARTS
IN OUTFITS
THAT ARE CRAZY SEXY COOL.
GENTLEMEN,
START YOUR ENGINES,
AND MAY THE BEST
WOMAN WIN.
COMING UP...
- THE CLOTHES WERE
WAY OFF FOR ME.
- THE RAP
WASN'T ON BEAT.
- YOU FREAKED YOURSELF OUT.
- SECURITY.
[RU PAUL LAUGHING]
- NOW SISSY THAT WALK.
FIRST UP, THE FOXY
JOSLYN FOX.
FOX ON THE RUNWAY.
SOMEBODY'S ROCKIN'-KNOCKIN'
THE BOOTS, TOO.
- MY RUNWAY LOOK
IS TYPICAL JOSLYN.
I KNOW MY ASS
IS LOOKING GREAT,
AND I'M FEELING
SUPER-CONFIDENT.
- HONEY, SHE IS STRAPPED.
IT AIN'T NOTHING
BUT A G-STRING.
BEN DE LA CREME.
- PURR-FECT.
- YES. CREMINEM DEVILLE.
- I'M SERVING UP
SOME ELIZABETH TAYLOR.
I JUST SKINNED
A SNOW LEOPARD.
I'M A CURVY GIRL,
AND I FEEL GORGEOUS.
- LUX LADY.
- NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
HAS ANYBODY SEEN MY DOG?
- HA HA HA!
- TRINITY K. BONET.
IT'S BLACK CHER.
- HA HA HA!
WHY IT GOT TO BE BLACK?
- I AM SERVING YOU
HIPPIE CHIC FLOWER-POWER FISH.
I LOOK ABSOLUTELY FABULOUS,
AS USUAL.
- PEACE, QUEEN.
- YES. HALF-BREED--
HALF MAN, HALF WOMAN.
- HA HA HA!
- MILK...
SERVING FISH TAIL.
- MILK IS SERVING UP
SOME THRIFT-SHOP GLAMOUR.
I AM FEELING GORGEOUS!
- I WOULD DRINK THIS
TALL GLASS OF MILK.
- OOH, SHE'S A DAIRY QUEEN.
LAGANJA ESTRANJA.
- WHOO! STRUT.
THE FREAKS
COME OUT AT NIGHT.
- LOOK OUT, HONEY.
HERE COMES MAMA.
I'M SERVING BULLETPROOF.
Y'ALL CAN'T TAKE IT.
- NOW, HOW DID SHE GET THROUGH
THE METAL DETECTORS
IS WHAT I WANT TO KNOW.
SECURITY.
- HA HA HA!
- IT'S TIME TO TAKE A DIP
INTO THE MARVELOUS WATERS
OF DARIENNE LAKE.
OH, YES, THE STARS
HAVE COME OUT TONIGHT.
- I DEFINITELY AM FEELING
CRAZY SEXY COOL.
LIKE, YOU MAY THINK I'M CRAZY
TO LOOK THIS SEXY,
AND I'M COOL
WITH THAT.
- LOVE, LOVE, LOVE
THAT DRESS.
- PEEKAROO. I SEE
YOUR PANTY LINE,
AND I LIKE IT.
BLAME IT
ON BIANCA DEL RIO.
- WOW!
- FLY GIRL.
- GOLDEN LADY.
- SHE LOVES ONLY GOLD.
- I'M GIVING GOOD SIXTIES
"VALLEY OF THE DOLLS"
KAFTAN REALNESS.
I AM FEELING THE FANTASY.
- YES, HUNTY. YES.
GLITTER TITS.
HA HA HA!
- ♪ SISSY THAT WALK ♪
- ADORE DELANO.
- SHE'S A MOTHER-TUCKER MONSTER.
- WHENEVER I PUT
FAKE LEATHER ON MY BODY,
I COMPLETELY
TURN INTO CAT WOMAN.
I HAVE ABOUT 5 LIVES LEFT,
SO WHY NOT JUST LIVE IT UP?
IT'S A PARTY.
- NO GLOVE, NO LOVE.
- UH-UH.
- HA HA!
- BAD KITTY.
[LAUGHTER]
- BLACK PANTHER ON THE RUNWAY.
- HA HA!
- COURTNEY ACT.
- SHH. SHE'S SLEEPING.
- WHO ARE YOU WEARING?
AND WHAT'S THE THREAD COUNT?
- OH!
- GOOD MORNING.
- JUST LIKE
LINDA EVANGELISTA,
I DON'T ROLL OUT OF BED
FOR ANYTHING LESS THAN $10,000.
I'M SERVING BODY-ODY-ODY.
I THINK THIS COULD BE
THE TIGHTEST TUCK OF MY CAREER.
- SHE GIVES GREAT BED-HEAD.
- LOVE THE ASS.
- WHAT'S YOUR SLEEP NUMBER?
- ♪ NOW SISSY THAT WALK ♪
- WELCOME, LADIES.
LET'S FLASH BACK
TO THE NINETIES
AND WATCH YOUR PERFORMANCES
IN "OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T,"
STARRING RU-TANG CLAN
AND THE PANTY HOS.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
- ♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
- IT'S THE RU-TANG CLAN.
- ♪ HERE'S YOUR GIRL JOSLYN,
AND I'M THE FOX ♪
♪ HEADS TURN, NECKS BREAK,
WHEN THIS BITCH WALKS ♪
♪ ALWAYS KEEP MY NOSE CLEAN,
BUT FOR ME THE BOYS FIEND ♪
♪ TRY ME, BITCH, I'M
A MOTHER-FISHIN' DRAG QUEEN ♪
- ♪ THIS IS DE LA TO THE CREME,
I'M THE FATAL FEMME ♪
♪ BUT I GOT THE CANDY COATING,
SO THEY CALL ME CREMINEM ♪
♪ THAT'S CREAM AU FRANCES,
VOULEZ WANT TO COUCHE? ♪
♪ I BACK 4 FLY LADIES
WHO WILL BE COMING YOUR WAY ♪
- ♪ CHECK IT, JUST TAKE A SECOND
TO SEE HOW THIS GOES ♪
♪ RHINESTONES, BIG HAIR,
GOWNS TO THE FLOOR ♪
♪ TONIGHT I'M GONNA
MAKE HISTORY ♪
♪ DON'T EVEN TRY
TO COME FOR ME ♪
♪ MY FLOW IS SUCH A MYSTERY,
I AM YOUR GIRL T.K.B. ♪
- ♪ NEVER BEEN AN IN-GIRL
SINCE SHE CAME OUT ♪
♪ MILK SHUDDERS IN HER UDDERS,
WE'RE THE EASY WAY OUT ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A DUDE
OR IN THE PREGGERS MOOD ♪
♪ MILK IS IN THE HOUSE
AND THEM OTHER BITCHES, RU ♪
- ♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
- THE PANTY HOS!
♪ LAGANJA'S ON THE TRACK,
AND Y'ALL CAN'T HANDLE ME ♪
♪ I'M BUSTIN' THROUGH THE DOOR
AND SMOKING ON THAT TREE ♪
♪ PANTY HOS
AND CONTROL-TOP D ♪
♪ GIVIN' YOU BODY,
YOU'RE ALL LIVIN' FOR ME ♪
- ♪ BIG GIRL, WHY YOU ALL
IN BARE FEET ♪
♪ WALKING DOWN
THE DIRTY CITY STREET? ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR SHOES ON, HONEY,
TO MAKE THAT MONEY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR TOENAIL DRAGGING,
AND THAT SURE AIN'T FUNNY ♪
- ♪ MY NAME IS BIANCA,
I'M FROM THE DEEP SOUTH ♪
♪ ALL THEM BITCHES CAN'T HANDLE
MY SASSY-ASS MOUTH ♪
♪ I LIKE TO SAY IT FAST,
I LIKE TO SAY IT QUICK ♪
♪ I'M GONNA CALL
YOUR ASS CHIMNEY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU LOOK
LIKE A BRICK ♪
- ♪ MY NAME SAYS IT ALL ♪
♪ AIN'T NO NEED
TO TRY TO FORCE IT ♪
♪ LOOK AT MY BODY
IN THIS BRAND-NEW CORSET ♪
♪ MEN TURNING AROUND,
PANTS COMING DOWN ♪
♪ GO HOME, HOS,
WHERE MY "DRAG RACE" CROWN? ♪
- ♪ LOOK LIKE GLENDA
AND WALK LIKE NAOMI ♪
♪ GET MESSED UP LIKE KATE,
AND YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ME ♪
♪ LOOKING LIKE THIS
IS A GODDAMN STUNT ♪
♪ ALL YOU OTHER BITCHES
BETTER LICK MY... ♪
♪ FOOT ♪
- ♪ SHE FEELING
SOME TYPE OF WAY ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
[LAUGHTER]
- YEAH.
WOW!
GORGEOUS!
THE SINGLE "OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T,"
PRODUCED BY DJ SHYBOY,
IS AVAILABLE ON iTUNES,
AND A PORTION
OF THE PROCEEDS
WILL GO TO THE L.A. GAY
AND LESBIAN CENTERS'
HOMELESS YOUTH SERVICES.
AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR THE JUDGES' CRITIQUES.
COMING UP...
- THE HIP-HOP WAS
SOMETHING THAT THREW YOU.
- YOU WERE NOT
ON RHYTHM, GIRL.
- DON'T BE A CLICHE, MY DEAR.
[RU PAUL LAUGHING]
- LADIES, THIS WEEK
YOU WORKED IN GROUPS,
BUT TONIGHT, YOU'LL BE
JUDGED INDIVIDUALLY.
COURTNEY ACT.
IT'S A CLICHE, BUT YOU'RE
RESTING ON PRETTY.
DON'T BE A CLICHE, MY DEAR.
COURTNEY ACT.
BEN DE LA CREME
AND LAGANJA ESTRANJA...
YOU ARE...SAFE.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU MAY LEAVE
THE STAGE.
NOW IT'S TIME
FOR THE JUDGES' CRITIQUES.
LET'S START WITH
JOSLYN FOX.
- YOUR RUNWAY LOOK
IS A BIT BUSY.
- ALL THE LAYERS
ON TOP OF LAYERS,
IT JUST STARTS TO GET
A LITTLE MESSY FOR ME.
- I DO FEEL LIKE I TEND
TO OVERACCESSORIZE.
- I ALWAYS
LOVE IT MYSELF.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IF YOU WANT TO
PLEASE THESE BITCHES UP HERE,
YOU KNOW,
YOU'VE GOT TO...
- I THINK YOUR RAP WAS GREAT.
I LOVE "MOTHER-FISHER."
[LAUGHTER]
- YOU REALLY STEPPED UP,
AND I'M VERY PROUD OF YOU.
- HA HA. THANK YOU.
- ALL RIGHT. NEXT UP,
TRINITY K. BONET-NET.
HEY, GIRL.
- YOU GIVE ME
NAOMI CAMPBELL DOWN.
- NOW LET'S MOVE
TO THE RAP.
THE LOOK WAS
REALLY SPOT-ON.
IT WAS SALT-N-PEPA
MEETS ANITA BAKER.
BUT YOU WERE NOT
ON RHYTHM, GIRL.
- YOU FREAKED YOURSELF OUT.
- YOU KNOW, I'VE NEVER BEEN
THE QUEEN TO MAKE EXCUSES,
BUT THIS IS NOT SOMETHING
THAT I'M ACCUSTOMED TO.
I LIP-SYNC FOR A LIVING.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
- ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, TRINITY.
NEXT UP, MILK.
- THE RAP WASN'T
ON BEAT,
BUT IT WAS YOUR OWN
PERSONALIZED UNIQUENESS.
YOU JUST WENT INTO
THIS LITTLE FUNNY...
YEAH, I LOVE THAT.
THAT WAS JUST SO YOU.
- THE CLOTHES WERE
WAY OFF FOR ME.
YOU HAD, LIKE, JOEY BUTTAFUOCO
ZUBAZ PANTS ON.
NOTHING TO DO
WITH HIP-HOP.
LOTS TO DO WITH THE BOYS I USED
TO HAVE SEX WITH AT THE GYM.
TONIGHT ON THE RUNWAY,
IT'S GREAT TO SEE YOU
WITH PRETTY MAKEUP ON.
BUT I WOULDN'T EVER TURN AROUND
IN THAT SKIRT AGAIN.
- IT LOOKS LIKE BED SHEETS
WRAPPED AROUND YOU,
PINNED IN THE BACK.
THE ATTENTION TO DETAIL
NEEDS TO BE JUST AS ON POINT
AS WHEN YOU COME OUT HERE
WITH A PINOCCHIO NOSE.
- ALL RIGHT.
DARIENNE LAKE.
- WELL, DARIENNE, PRETTY DRESS.
IT'S NOTHING SPECTACULAR.
- YESTERDAY,
WITH YOUR PERFORMANCE,
YOU GAVE ME, LIKE, MISSY ELLIOTT
WITH THE TRASH BAG.
I WANTED TO SEE YOU,
LIKE, BUST OUT OF IT
AND, LIKE, JUST REALLY
GIVE IT TO US,
BUT YOU WERE
A LITTLE WITHHELD.
- I THINK THE HIP-HOP
THREW YOU A LITTLE BIT.
- NEXT UP,
BIANCA DEL RIO.
- THIS IS PROBABLY THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL I'VE SEEN YOU YET.
YOUR EYE MAKEUP--
YOU DIDN'T PUT
THAT HARSH WHITE LINE.
- I DIDN'T PUT IT,
BUT I DID SNORT IT.
- AT LEAST IT WAS USED.
- THAT'S WHY
I'M ALERT, GIRL.
- YESTERDAY,
YOU WERE HILARIOUS.
- OTHER THAN
THE PIGTAILS, THOUGH,
YOU WERE GIVING ME
KIND OF URKEL.
- I DISAGREE,
BECAUSE AS B-GIRLS,
THAT WAS THE LOOK
THAT WE ROCKED.
- AND LET ME
REMIND EVERYBODY
THAT MICHELLE VISAGE
IS ALSO A RAPPER.
SHE HAD A SONG
ON THE "BODYGUARD" SOUNDTRACK.
- TRACK 9. GO ON.
- ALL RIGHT. UP NEXT,
ADORE DELANO.
- WELL, ADORE, I'M HAPPY TO SEE
THAT YOU HAVE A WAIST.
- BUT?
- BUT WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
ABOUT THIS KIND OF
MID-SHIN LENGTH?
- BUT I HAD TO WEAR IT
BECAUSE IT WAS SEE-THROUGH,
AND I WANTED
TO SHOW MY BODY.
[LAUGHTER]
- YOU ASSASSINATED THE RAP.
YOU'RE ON RHYTHM.
YOU WERE LIKE
JUST A REAL ARTIST.
- YOUR LYRICS WERE GREAT.
YOUR ATTITUDE WAS EVERYTHING.
- YEAH, MOTHERFUCKER, YEAH.
[LAUGHTER]
- WELL, THANK YOU, LADIES.
WHILE YOU UNTUCK
IN THE FORMDECOR LOUNGE,
THE JUDGES AND I
WILL DELIBERATE.
[ENGINE REVVING]
ALL RIGHT. NOW, JUST BETWEEN
US FREAKNIKS,
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
STARTING WITH JOSLYN FOX?
- HER RUNWAY LOOK TONIGHT
WAS JUST A DISASTER.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU COULD
HAVE THAT MUCH ON AND STILL--
- BE THAT NAKED?
[LAUGHTER]
I THINK SHE NAILED
THE VIDEO.
- THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME I FELT
LIKE I REALLY HEARD HER VOICE,
AND IT BOOMED THROUGH.
- ALL RIGHT.
TRINITY K. BONET.
- IN THE VIDEO,
SHE GOT HER GHETTO PASS REVOKED
FOR THAT RAP, FOR REAL.
- AND AGAIN, I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
MUCH OF WHAT SHE WAS SAYING.
- I THINK SHE GAVE UP REALLY
BEFORE SHE STARTED.
- YEAH.
- MM-HMM.
- UP NEXT, MILK.
- I THINK MILK IS REALLY,
REALLY UNIQUE AND DIFFERENT...
AND OFF, BUT IT WORKS.
- HOWEVER, WE ASKED
TO SEE MORE FROM MILK,
AND THIS IS WHAT SHE BROUGHT
OUT HERE TONIGHT.
- DARIENNE LAKE.
- DARIENNE LOOKED LOVELY
TONIGHT ON THE RUNWAY,
BUT IN THE VIDEO, HER DELIVERY
NEEDED A LOT OF WORK.
- SHE SEEMED
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE.
SHE REALLY WASN'T
DELIVERING HER PERFORMANCE.
- BIANCA DEL RIO.
- ON THE RUNWAY,
SHE LOOKED INCREDIBLE.
- HER HIP-HOP THING
WAS HILARIOUS,
BECAUSE IT WAS
ON THE COMEDY SIDE.
- BUT IT DID GET TO BE
A LITTLE "DUDE."
- UP NEXT, ADORE DELANO.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO SAY ANYMORE, KIDS.
EVERY TIME I SAY,
"LOOK AT THE LENGTH,"
SHE COMES OUT THE NEXT WEEK
IN THE SAME LENGTH.
- YESTERDAY, SHE CAME OUT
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING
AND JUST SLAYED IT.
- TENS ALL THE WAY--
LOOK, ATTITUDE, CHARACTER,
PERSONALITY, EVERYTHING.
- THE QUESTION IS--
- SILENCE!
I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
BRING BACK MY HOMEGIRLS.
AND, UH...
♪ OH, NO, SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ OH, NO,
SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
♪ SHE BETTER DON'T ♪
[ENGINE REVVING]
[RU PAUL LAUGHING]
WELCOME BACK, LADIES.
I'VE MADE SOME DECISIONS.
BIANCA DEL RIO...
YOU ARE SAFE.
ADORE DELANO, THIS WEEK
YOU PUSHED IT REAL GOOD.
YOU ARE THE WINNER
OF THIS WEEK'S CHALLENGE.
[APPLAUSE]
AND YOU'VE WON A COLLECTION
OF CUSTOM-MADE JEWELRY
FROM THE FOUNDRY.
- JESUS KNOWS I NEED IT.
I WON FINALLY.
I'M MOTHERFUCKING LEGIT.
- JOSLYN...
YOU'RE SAFE.
TRINITY K. BONET.
MCTKB WAS NOT A TKO.
I'M SORRY, MY DEAR,
BUT YOU ARE UP
FOR ELIMINATION.
MILK, YOUR RAP AND RUNWAY LOOK
WERE NOT MC SUPREME.
DARIENNE LAKE, YOUR PERFORMANCE
AS MC CONTROL TOP
WAS NO RAPPERS DELIGHT.
DARIENNE LAKE...
YOU ARE SAFE.
[EXHALES]
YOU MAY JOIN
THE OTHER GIRLS.
MILK, I'M SORRY, MY DEAR,
BUT YOU ARE UP FOR ELIMINATION.
TWO QUEENS
STAND BEFORE ME.
LADIES, THIS IS
YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO IMPRESS ME AND SAVE
YOURSELF FROM ELIMINATION.
THE TIME HAS COME...
[THUNDER]
FOR YOU TO LIP-SYNC
FOR YOUR LIFE!
- I'M FEELING SHOCKED.
I DIDN'T EXPECT TO BE
IN THE BOTTOM TWO,
BUT I'M GONNA
WORK IT OUT.
GOOD LUCK,
AND DON'T FUCK IT UP.
- ♪ OOH, WHAT A MAN,
WHAT A MAN, WHAT A MAN ♪
♪ WHAT A MIGHTY GOOD MAN ♪
♪ I WANT TO TAKE A MINUTE OR TWO
AND GIVE MUCH RESPECT TO ♪
♪ TO THE MAN THAT'S MADE
A DIFFERENCE IN MY WORLD ♪
♪ AND ALTHOUGH MOST MEN ARE
HOS, HE GOES ON THE DOWN LOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I NEVER HEARD ABOUT HIM
WITH ANOTHER GIRL ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T SWEAT IT,
BECAUSE IT'S JUST PATHETIC
♪ TO LET IT GET ME INVOLVED IN
THAT "HE SAID, SHE SAID" CRAP ♪
♪ I KNOW THAT AIN'T
NOBODY PERFECT ♪
♪ I GIVE PROPS TO THOSE
WHO DESERVE IT ♪
♪ AND BELIEVE ME, Y'ALL,
HE'S WORTH IT ♪
♪ WHAT A MAN,
WHAT A MAN ♪
WHAT A MIGHTY GOOD MAN ♪
♪ MY MAN IS COOL LIKE BARRY,
AND HIS VOICE GOT BASS ♪
♪ A BODY LIKE ARNOLD
WITH A DENZEL FACE ♪
- MILK IS HIGH ENERGY.
SHE IS SO WEIRD AND SO WILD.
IT'S JUST TOTALLY MILK.
- ♪ HE NEVER RAN A CORNY LINE
ONCE TO ME YET ♪
♪ SO I GIVE HIM STUFF
THAT HE'LL NEVER FORGET ♪
♪ YES, MY MAN
SAYS HE LOVES ME ♪
♪ NEVER SAYS
HE LOVES ME NOT ♪
♪ NOT TRYING TO RUSH ME GOOD
AND TOUCH ME... ♪
- TRINITY IS REALLY
SERVING IT UP.
WITH HER LONG-ASS WEAVE,
SHE LOOKS FUCKING
BOMB.COM.ORG.CO.UK.
- ♪ HE'S GOT ME OPEN
LIKE 7-11 ♪
♪ AND YES, IT'S ME
THAT HE'S ALWAYS CHOOSING ♪
♪ WITH HIM I'M NEVER LOSING,
AND HE KNOWS ♪
♪ THAT MY NAME
IS NOT SUSAN ♪
♪ HE ALWAYS HAS HEAVY
CONVERSATION FOR THE MIND ♪
♪ WHICH MEANS A LOT TO ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE GOOD MEN
ARE HARD TO FIND ♪
♪ WHAT A MAN, WHAT A MAN,
WHAT A MAN ♪
♪ WHAT A MIGHTY GOOD MAN ♪
♪ I SAID WHAT A MIGHTY ♪
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
- LADIES, I'VE MADE
MY DECISION.
TRINITY K. BONET...
SHANTE, YOU STAY.
[CLAPPING]
MY DEAR MILK,
YOU'VE CONSISTENTLY SHOWN US
THAT YOU CAN THINK
OUTSIDE THE CARTON.
- I JUST WANT TO
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR ALLOWING ME
TO BE WHO I AM
WITHOUT FEAR
OF BEING RIDICULED.
THANK YOU.
- IN MY HEART,
IT WILL ALWAYS BE
MILKIN' TIME.
NOW SASHAY AWAY.
[APPLAUSE]
[CHUCKLING]
- I WANTED TO LEAVE
MY STAMP,
AND I REALLY THINK I DID.
I'M SO HAPPY WITH WHAT
I'VE SHOWN THE WORLD,
AND I'M EXCITED
TO KEEP GOING
AND FOR PEOPLE TO LOVE MY DRAG
AS MUCH AS I DO.
CAN I GET MY PHONE BACK?
HA HA HA.
- MY CRAZY 8 QUEENS...
CONDRAGULATIONS.
NOW REMEMBER,
IF YOU CAN'T LOVE YOURSELF,
HOW IN THE HELL ARE YOU
GONNA LOVE SOMEBODY ELSE?
CAN I GET
AN "AMEN" IN HERE?
- AMEN!
- ALL RIGHT.
NOW LET THE MUSIC PLAY.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- ♪ I WANT TO DANCE, DANCE ♪
♪ I WANT TO
DANCE, DANCE ♪
♪ I WANT TO DANCE, DANCE ♪
♪ DANCE, DANCE NOW ♪